Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
Ellie Calhoun: Hi 👋 I'm here!
John Pullum: Good day, everybody!
Sammy Super Star: 🕺💃🕺💃🕺💃
John Pullum: We need a new TV show called "Dancing With Markus"
Ellie Calhoun: Great dancing!
Ellie Calhoun: Markus!!!
Sarah | Small Changes: LYNN, MARKUS!!!
Ellie Calhoun: 😂
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Lynn!
MySnoopy80: Hi❤️❤️
Robert Hicks: I made it!! 🙂
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Just jumping in but glad to catch y’all live!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Wow!!! Thank you Lynn!! Those are great points to share
John Pullum: Your story and its ups and downs have helped a lot of people going through the same thing.
Blind Guy, His Wife, Their Life: Yes knowing the knowledge of the audience is helpful 💫
John Pullum: Giving a child in need of fostering and showing them what a loving family is like is a wonderful thing.
John Pullum: I'm not pregnant, but look like I am. I'm working on that.
John Pullum: I cried with you when I watched that video. You have a world of supporters and felt your pain.
Ellie Calhoun: Lynn, thank you for opening up here and with your followers. You are so genuine and real!💜
John Pullum: Most people want to only post the good parts of their life. You sharing the good, bad, happy and sad is the right way to go to really connect with people. It lets people know that aren't alone.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Thank you for being so brave and wonderful. Selfless by sharing your story and educate us!!! Some of us can be so insensitive because we are ignorant abut it
Blind Guy, His Wife, Their Life: That's great to get a glimpse of the impact and reach of their story from the feedback 😊
John Pullum: #TeamLynn
Ellie Calhoun: And often after a miscarriage, it's not common to take the time to grieve. In fact, you end up just going on with your day, week, life.
John Pullum: Before YouTube and social media people would have to look up a support group and actually go to a meeting. Now they can get support and watch others and realize they aren't along right online.
John Pullum: Thanks for keeping it real and not sugar coating anything.
John Pullum: NEVER ask a woman if she is pregnant. Trust me. NEVER do it!
John Pullum: Watching Lynn eating broccoli in a bathtub was one of my favorites.
Robert Hicks: KALE!!!!
Ellie Calhoun: Just a reminder, press that like button for this stream!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Acrhonims?
John Pullum: There is an orphanage that has children living there that need fosters or adoptions at my corner. Many times they post photos of the children, but have a smily face emoji over their faces.
John Pullum: Thanks for opening your heart and your home to these children.
Sarah | Small Changes: Q: Do you have any suggestions for how to be a good friend and support someone on a journey to fertility or fostering/adoption? I'm so worried I'll say the wrong thing 🙈
John Pullum: Teach any child you have or foster to be a minimalist and it will make Sarah happy.
John Pullum: Thank you!
John Pullum: Now dance it out.