Success with Sunita: yay!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sunita!
Paul Burke: nice thumbnail Markus!
Ellie Calhoun: Markus!!!! I won't be here long- phone battery is running low.
Ellie Calhoun: Love the dancing 💃 hands 🙌🏿!💕
Rich Vybz: Hello lovely people!
Success with Sunita: Camping!
Rich Vybz: We have all been there
Success with Sunita: Oh yes...we learn the hard way we are too old for that
Rich Vybz: Forgetting we are not 20 anymore
Success with Sunita: Hi Lala
Success with Sunita: If I don't have an audience, then I leave after a few minutes.
Rich Vybz: Did you enjoy the hike though
Rich Vybz: A good audience will carry you through…
Tech Troublemaker: Why didn't YouTube tell me you were live. Silly YouTube.
Success with Sunita: You have to try different things and you learn...
Success with Sunita: Yay!
Rich Vybz: Ooh what will you and Sunita be talking about
Rich Vybz: We all get that feeling sometimes
Success with Sunita: Rich I am not sure!
Success with Sunita: I will let Markus drive
Rich Vybz: What is ur channel about Sunita
Success with Sunita: Metaphysic, mindset and personal transformation
Rich Vybz: Ooh sounds good.. will try to tune in
Success with Sunita: Metaphysics, mindset and metamorphasis. Or even from one content creator to another chit chat. will depend on what audience wants.
Success with Sunita: Yes, 4pm EST.
BravoPup Dog Training: Hi Markus!!
Rich Vybz: Great job Markus.. will see you next time
Success with Sunita: see u next week!