BravoPup Dog Training: front row.
Sara S: I like the look of your other guest!
Sammy Super Star: Hey Markus!!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Markus
Sammy Super Star: I didn’t know you played guitar Markus lol 😂
Sandi Thompson: Love the hat Ellie!
Stephanie Gieseke: HELLOOOOOOOOOO!!!
Sandi Thompson: STEPHANIE!!!!
Stephanie Gieseke: Sandi!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Stephanie! Sandi!
Sandi Thompson: Lala!!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sammy & Roy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Love the polo shirt Markus!
Stephanie Gieseke: Hey LaLa!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi dear Ellie!
Sandi Thompson: Joe
Sara S: Fred
Mommy Guide Inc: I miss massages. Still can't do it here yet for safety reasons.
Mommy Guide Inc: I need Ellie! I have tons of chronic pain. huhuhu
signmore: Hello
Kali Co: hey 🤗❤️
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Lala!! Hey Sammy! Hey Sara!! Hey Stephanie! Hey Sandi!! Hey Kali!!
Kali Co: so glad I'm getting to catch you two live!!!
Kali Co: @Tech Troublemaker hey!!!!
Sandi Thompson: @Tech Troublemaker 👋
Kali Co: that's awesome Ellie
signmore: Ellie 🤩
Kali Co: I totally relate
Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Hello Markus & Ellie😀🎄
signmore: What Ellie is human lol
Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Hi to Everyone here😀👍
signmore: The gang all here 🎉
Sandi Thompson: if a dog gets aggressive all of a sudden - it's usually a pain issue.
Kali Co: Don't forget to hit that like button!
Sarah | Small Changes: MARKUS! ELLIE!!
signmore: Thanks Kali for the reminder 👏
Sara S: I love a good rant
Mommy Guide Inc: Ellie is this also a form of reflexology? Is that also an ok technique to handle pain?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Kali! Hi Sara!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hey Ejnar:)
Sandi Thompson: Q - oh wait- Lala just asked what i was thinking!
Sara S: Hi All!
Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Hi Mommy😀
Kali Co: @Sara S hey!
Sara S: What’s your take on Rolfing and Alexander?
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Ellie! Indeed more options. Important thing - do something = take steps to find ways to stop the pain hopefully without meds.
Kali Co: wow i love that
Kali Co: great thought process
Sara S: Getting curious is IT!! You can start to get intimate with your intricate anatomy.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I so wish I knew this before my shoulder surgery in April. Big mistake
Kali Co: truth!!!
Kali Co: @Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing ❤ ❤
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: That is so true...our inner wisdom is so powerful
Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Pain in the Knee is a very bad thing😫
Sara S: I think we live in our heads until it gets too painful
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @Kali Co 😻
signmore: I have bad shoulder, I use massage and specific exercises to specific to help.
Sandi Thompson: Dont forget to hit the LIKE button!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I have heard of it. T-Touch is based on that right?
Sara S: I experienced Rolfing as very powerful in terms of releasing long held trauma
Mommy Guide Inc: Find Ellie Calhoun here:https://www.mybodyworksnatick.comhttps://www.facebook.com/MyBodyWorks
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Thanks for posting Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Will you have online classes at least for the basic movements Ellie?
Mommy Guide Inc: Ejnar i have been experiencing very nad pain on my right knee lately.
Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: @mommy guide inc The same for me but the left. Stairs is a painful thing😖
Stephanie Gieseke: oooo...a membership sounds helpful!
John Pullum: Ellie, The guy behind you needs to eat a bit more.
Mommy Guide Inc: yes Ellie explains each movement very clearly and reasons for each step
Sara S: Do you remember the name of the camera David was tsaying he was usies w/ his wife for yoga in SA this morning? I can’t remember but I thought it might be something Ellie would want to look into
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi John!
Sara S: *saying
Sara S: *uses
Sara S: Can no longer type. Obviously.
John Pullum: Hi @Mommy Guide Inc Thanks again for the wonderful birthday video today. 🙂
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @Sara the camera that follows you.
Mommy Guide Inc: Ellie's FB: https://www.facebook.com/MyBodyWorks
Sara S: Hi John
Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Hey John👋
John Pullum: Hi @Sara S Thank you for the great video last night, too. 🙂
John Pullum: Hi Ejnar!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Razer Kiyo pro??
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi John
Sandi Thompson: Ellie- I was breathing with you this morning during your live!
John Pullum: Hi @Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing 🙂
Heather Roma: Hello Ellie and Markus! Ellie has taught me so much!
Sara S: I don’t think the Razer. It was something I’d never heard of.
Mommy Guide Inc: Thank you John! My kids basically know everyone in our group specially you. So they wanted to join me greeting you A Happy Birthday!
Heather Roma: Well we know she is not scared of skeletons
John Pullum: It's video stage fright. You know people are watching you. It's the imposter syndrome it sounds like.
Mommy Guide Inc: Don't worry much about the bad comments - you will find your tribe and what you do can help a lot of people Ellie - the breathing and the basic movements - everyone need. Whether in pain or not.
John Pullum: @Heather Roma She has one inside her.
John Pullum: I don't remember what I called it half the time either. 🙂
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Love you are both stepping up and doing it. you are both an inspiration.
Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: LSP was a life changer to me. 😀👍
John Pullum: Has she dealt with breathing techniques for those recovering from the current virus?
Stephanie Gieseke: My feet don't usually touch the floor 🙂 I have to wear shoes in the house so I can zoom around to get stuff done
Heather Roma: Can’t see your holiday socks today
Mommy Guide Inc: Ejnar i totall agree about LSP! And I continue to learn so much from them.
Mommy Guide Inc: I am flat footed so I have to wear special slippers to improve my arch on my foot.
Heather Roma: Hips don’t lie 😏
Mommy Guide Inc: I agree Markus - Ellie's voice alone can make you feel more relax.
Heather Roma: Me too Lala. Flat feet.
Mommy Guide Inc: Heather LOL!
Mommy Guide Inc: Don't forget to hit the like button everyone:)
John Pullum: I also have flat feet.
John Pullum: EEE wide flat feet
Mommy Guide Inc: Ellie I find myself doing some sort of movement while watching you and Markus now:).
Sandi Thompson: This is so interesting!
Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: @Mommy For me too👍 Watch them so much I can. It’s so inspiring and Luria and Kali are fantastic👍 Looking forward to my fourth LEDA in April. LEDA learns you new things every time😀👍👋
Sandi Thompson: I’m pigeon toed. 😭
Mommy Guide Inc: Yeah, breathing exercise:)
Heather Roma: Breaking old patterns starts with being aware of them.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Breathing into the belly and feeling feet is very relaxing and grounding.
John Pullum: I used to raise pigeons and never had any that were people toed.
Heather Roma: Markus got taller
Sandi Thompson: John- 😂🤣
John Pullum: Click the like button 2, 3, 4, 5..... Subscribe 2, 3, 4, 5 ...
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: beautiful Ellie. thank you
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: oh John you are such a card!
John Pullum: Thank you!
John Pullum: Thanks Ellie and thanks Markus for having such great shows.
Mommy Guide Inc: ooh that's great advice Ellie - a lot of people have issues trying to get to sleep.
Mommy Guide Inc: Thank you so much Ellie!
John Pullum: Sandi!!!! That will be GREAT, too.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Thank you Ellie & Markus.