BostonDonMTB: Hi Markus, and Janet
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Markus Schaub Hey @BostonDonMTB
BostonDonMTB: Hi Roy
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I love that.
Paul Burke: hey Markus!
Tech Troublemaker: I am glad you always use your power for good instead of evil.
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Paul Burke Is your show online somewhere? I wanted to watch replay.
Tzeli Triantafillou: Hi Janet🤩❤️!
BostonDonMTB: What is the most interesting animal you have worked with?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Markus and Janet!
Mommy Guide Inc: Coming in late but great I made it! Hi Don! Roy! Tzeli!
BostonDonMTB: Hi Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Yup only 1 take!
Mommy Guide Inc: Big hugs to everyone!
Tzeli Triantafillou: Hi @Mommy Guide Inc 🤩❤️
Mommy Guide Inc: It’s fine Markus. Yes interaction is one thing that live-streaming is king compared to edited videos
BostonDonMTB: She gives them treats
Mommy Guide Inc: Let’s hit that like button for this awesome stream.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh hi there Paul! Indeed Janet eventually the regular viewers become part of our community.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: This is Janet’s awesome channel - https://youtube.com/user/KatySammy
Sandi Thompson: Hi!!!!!! Just got here!
Mommy Guide Inc: And Janet’s website: https://www.animalparadise.com
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Hi Sandi!
Sandi Thompson: Hi Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed going live consistently helps so people can plan also their schedule and best is to do set remind!
Mommy Guide Inc: Create a “guest list”. What an awesome advice:)
Mommy Guide Inc: And probably repeat collaborations on a regular basis for some that really resonated with your community.:)
Sandi Thompson: Dogs. 2.
Mommy Guide Inc: Both your audios sound very nice. Really crisp! Absolutely perfect for repurposing into a podcast:)
Tzeli Triantafillou: 2 cats, 1 dog and many wildlife critters who love our yard.... like skunks, opossums, raccoons, doves, hawks, and snakes🤩
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow Tzeli! What a very interesting yard.:)
Sandi Thompson: I also have flies.
Tzeli Triantafillou: @Mommy Guide Inc 😂
Tzeli Triantafillou: Oh yeah and I forgot the occasional ducks who come for a swim in our pool😂
Mommy Guide Inc: We do have half a dozen neighborhood cats who have taken over our verandas
Mommy Guide Inc: There is communication in silence. Just being present starts or is a form of communication. Very interesting indeed.