Mommy Guide Inc: Hi everyone!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Lala. so happy so "see you"
Cheryl Wolf: Hello Markus and Tim!!
Cheryl Wolf: Hi lala
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh boy dance time!!!💃💃💃💃💃
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Janet
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey! Ja et my friend me too! Glad to see you and be here:)
Ellie Calhoun: Hey 👋 every body!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Cheryl
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Cheryl!
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Ellie
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Ellie!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hello everyone 🎉🎉🎉🎉
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ellie!
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Ana
Mommy Guide Inc: Go Markus!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: anna!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: party time
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana:)
Cheryl Wolf: Yes Dance Markus
Eaglevp: Hello all in the chat
Mommy Guide Inc: 💃 💃 💃
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Keith
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: 🕺🕺🕺🕺🕺🕺🕺🕺💃💃💃💃💃💃
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Keith!!!
Eaglevp: Hi Cheryl thanks for the workout the other day
Cheryl Wolf: 👯👯👯
Eaglevp: Evening Lala hope you are keeping well
Cheryl Wolf: Anytime Keith
Eaglevp: Hope to make your next live Cheryl
SiShong Victor: What we got going on here :0
SiShong Victor: 🙂
Eaglevp: Hi SiShong
Mommy Guide Inc: Getting there Keith:) Let’s go!
SiShong Victor: Hi Hi
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Dancing 💃 victor!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I love this open!!! sing along!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Victor! Work is done early?:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Victor!!!
Eaglevp: Howdy Ana
SiShong Victor: Nope still working SHHH hahaha
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: here we gooooo
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: start this darn show
Make and Do Crafts: Hi Marcus and Tim (it's Diane)
Mommy Guide Inc: markus should have a karaok/videoke versiok pf thos!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Make some noise 🎉🎉
Eaglevp: Hi Markus
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Can't want to meet new people too
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Diane!
Mommy Guide Inc: Dont forget to smash thr like button friends:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: it's a journey for sure...
Make and Do Crafts: Hi Lala! 🙂
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Thanks lala. i forgot
Cheryl Wolf: Hey Victor
SiShong Victor: Hello
Ellie Calhoun: This is the place to be!🎶🎶🎶
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Luna is dancing
Eaglevp: Hi Ellie
Cheryl Wolf: Yes it is Ellie
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: it's happening here for sure
Mommy Guide Inc: Awww miss Lynn
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Love this song
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Kali!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: let's go
Cheryl Wolf: Me to Ana
Make and Do Crafts: I'm here! Diane
Mommy Guide Inc: We’re all here and having an awesome workput!
Make and Do Crafts: We're all here. Full house!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Diane
Make and Do Crafts: Hi
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: So happy you showed up
Cheryl Wolf: You are amazing markus
Make and Do Crafts: I'm looking forward to this!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for the likes let’s give some more hit that LIKE button.:) thanks everyone!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Tim
Make and Do Crafts: Tim!!!
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Tim!
SiShong Victor: Oh I remember Tim
Mommy Guide Inc: Howdy Tim!
Eaglevp: Hi Tim
SiShong Victor: Best was to prepare, Don't HAHAHA
SiShong Victor: way*
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Haha Victor
Cheryl Wolf: Go Keith
Mommy Guide Inc: Archaeology interesting :) Tim is born ready.:)
Make and Do Crafts: Gift of the gab Tim
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: yay Tim is moving to Ecamm
Mommy Guide Inc: Woah! Welcome to the Ecamm Fam Tim.;)
Cheryl Wolf: Tim are you doing any shorts ?
Mommy Guide Inc: Tim is crushing it!
SiShong Victor: HAHAHA who is interviewing whom
Ellie Calhoun: Yes!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: haha... 1758
Make and Do Crafts: Atfield in Artferdshore
Mommy Guide Inc: Janet i started doung thr Math too!
Cheryl Wolf: lol
Make and Do Crafts: Looks good for a few hundred years old
Mommy Guide Inc: Next will be a dance with Tim. He can do everything.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Lol Diane.
Mommy Guide Inc: So podcasting seems to be a perfect avenue indeed For Tim.:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: So interesting 🧐
Mommy Guide Inc: Exactly Ana. Ive only read about these places and Tim has been there in the frontlines nonetheless.
Cheryl Wolf: Interesting life
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: ☹️
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yes a very "interesting" live to say the least.
Ellie Calhoun: Wow! My nephew was in Iraq in 2006 and 2008.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I meant "life" sorry about that
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes! Dangerous. My son in law is coming back from deployment next week.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: People that serves our countries are real heroes 🦸
Mommy Guide Inc: That’s great news Ana.:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Q about how many uniforms do you have?
Mommy Guide Inc: Great Q Ana.:)
Make and Do Crafts: Yes
Mommy Guide Inc: A beret! Perfect
Cheryl Wolf: yes I want to touch it
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: oh wow. beautiful and poor bear
Ellie Calhoun: Wow!
Mommy Guide Inc: That one is for parade?
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Oh wow!
Eaglevp: Cheryl you will have to come over to the UK
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Q is it heavy? Hot?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh like Rolling Thunder?
Cheryl Wolf: I want to come to UK it has been a long time since I was there.
Eaglevp: Where have you visited in the UK Cheryl
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I almost went this summer on a mission trip…I hope one day!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: oh the red one is to impress the girls?
Cheryl Wolf: I lived in Germany for five years. So went all over
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Oh wow!!!!
Cheryl Wolf: Fancy Tim
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Love it! 🤩
Mommy Guide Inc: It would be great to have a trip to the UK and have a great reunion!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: We are learning 🤓
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: @Mommy Guide Inc…that would be a dream come true!
Mommy Guide Inc: Prayers for the whole world to heal completely soon and so we can go back to travelling more often.:)
Make and Do Crafts: Wow, a lot of medals!
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow awesome! Those accolades - money can’t buy/
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: 🎖🎖🎖🎖🎖
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Lol
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I keep chocolate under my desk 🤪
Eaglevp: You should listen to Tim's story on his podcasts
Make and Do Crafts: Lol
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Beautiful legacy!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Q what is the name of the podcast?
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for the reminder to binge watch Tim’s podcasts aoon.
Ellie Calhoun: Good point!
Make and Do Crafts: LEDA!!
Mommy Guide Inc: What a great why Tim.:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: You did great in Leda!
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yes Adrian Salisbury is a great tracher.
Mommy Guide Inc: Teacher:)
Cheryl Wolf: Cheryl's yes
Cheryl Wolf: Tim are doing shorts now?
Eaglevp: Tim always forgets the call to action at the end of his live streams
Mommy Guide Inc: Is anybody else doing shorts? Loving Janet’s shorts.:) And Victor started too.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Keith i often forget to do my own CTAs too but not my guests. My own. He he he
Eaglevp: Yep Lala agree but it's one of the most important things at the end
Eaglevp: Don't forget to buy both Markus and Tim a coffee on there next streams
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: We need to remember to do our CTA's. I often forget.
SiShong Victor: My audience is 50 plus years old and 100% male. Like really?
Mommy Guide Inc: Last time i checked i am not male Victor. He he he.
Eaglevp: My audience are all over 70 wish I could get to 20-40 age group in
SiShong Victor: My point HAHAHA they lied to me
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh i love that movie!
SiShong Victor: Oh nice
Cheryl Wolf: I have to run to a meeting. Great Show today!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yes a really great show
Make and Do Crafts: Very interesting. Thanks Markus and Tim!
Eaglevp: Bye Cheryl
Make and Do Crafts: Bye Cheryl
Mommy Guide Inc: Bye Cheryl have an awesome rest of the day:)
Eaglevp: Brilliant show Markus with a great and interesting guest.
Mommy Guide Inc: Agree Keith!
Mommy Guide Inc: Pod Match!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Thanks Tim and Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: What a time well spent with Markus and Tim! And everyone in the chat - you alll are rrock stars!
Make and Do Crafts: It's Diane here. Thanks Tim