Mommy Guide Inc: Hi everyone!!!
Intan Masuri: Hi everyone!
Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sammy!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: You want to join us in Zoom Sammy?
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hi Sammy! Glad you are here!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Markus Schaub
Mommy Guide Inc: The link is in Markus Discord server. you want me to send you the Link?
Andy H: An all-star cast!
Mommy Guide Inc: Her Roy!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Andy!
Andy H: LALA!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Guys if you want to join us in Zoom just FYI me or Markus and we'll send you the link!
Mommy Guide Inc: I meant Hey Roy! He he he
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hello Roy....when are you going to dance?
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hi Andy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana!
Andy H: Ana!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Good morning to you too Intan!
Andy H: zoom link please
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi everyone.
Intan Masuri: Good morning Lala, Ana, Andy Roy n everyone!
TonyRIversen one crazy dane: hello from Sunny California
Tech Troublemaker: It's the Hollywood Squares. Who is Paul Lynn?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Janet!
SiShong Victor: I know everything about nothing BAM
Tech Troublemaker: I will be dancing soon but it has been a busy two days on my side. 😛
Andy H: Gotta love that Ana!
Mommy Guide Inc: Excited for it Roy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hello there in sunny California Tony!
Mommy Guide Inc: And Adam too!
Mommy Guide Inc: Don't we all right Victor! Thanks for dropping by:)
Andy H: sorry ... zoom link plz
Mommy Guide Inc: Andy I sent it on your messenger:)
Andy H: thank you
Mommy Guide Inc: Janet I also sent the zoom link!
Mommy Guide Inc: if you can join us in Zoom that would be great!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Ana! Thanks Adam:).
Mommy Guide Inc: great Ejnar!
Mommy Guide Inc: yey Intan! thanks for waking up so early and joining us - its 4:13AM Malaysia time!
Intan Masuri: Thanks Lala! for letting me in...
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: It's fantastic! I love it!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Tony again!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Andy!!!!!
Tech Troublemaker: Lala is too busy to be lazy.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I totally agree!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Sir
Intan Masuri: Agreed with u Roy
Mommy Guide Inc: He he he. Great to see you here Andy!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Janet I sent you the zoom link if you can join us here that would be great!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: That is so awesome!!! Go Andy
Mommy Guide Inc: Absolutely awesome!!! A TED Talk!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Lala- thanks. I would love to join that zoom but I’m in the membership course. I’m checking in on break. Will watch replay with sound. Love you and group.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Roy!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh that's absolutely ok Janet. Thanks for being here in the chat during the break:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Your dog has so much to say and teach!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: 🎉party on!
SiShong Victor: Lazy people are great I should know I'm an Alsome lazy guy 🙂
Mommy Guide Inc: yes Ellie hello on replay:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hope to see everyone soon!
TonyRIversen one crazy dane: Yea for the lazy people here in this group. Can you imagine how much they could accomplish if they were NOT lazy. LoL
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I love that!!! constructive criticism
SiShong Victor: Imagining is hard work not my thing hahaha
Mommy Guide Inc: constructive criticism - yea I am all for it!
TonyRIversen one crazy dane: Live streaming is far from LAZY. I commend all of you who get and start or end your day Streaming to the WORLD.
Mommy Guide Inc: done with love:)
SiShong Victor: Im having a brandy bunch flash back right now.
Mommy Guide Inc: awww thanks Tony! I agree too - it took a long time - baby steps to learn how to do livestreaming:) kudos to everyone who does and wants to do so!
Ate MARGIE: done shared
Ate MARGIE: hello Mommy G
Ate MARGIE: hello everyone
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ate Margie!!!
SiShong Victor: Got to go catch ya all next time
Mommy Guide Inc: Welcome to Markus' Channel:) This is the first stream with the setting up of LLPGP -Live Livestreamer Peer Group Project - how we can as livestreamer help each other out:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Victor for dropping by!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Take Care Victor.:)
Ate MARGIE: listening here Mommy G
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ate Margie!!! Thanks for sharing this stream:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Great example!
Mommy Guide Inc: The polite and correct way - ask permission first before we give a creative criticism:)
Sarah | Small Changes: Hi Everyone!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sarah!
Mommy Guide Inc: Sarah do you want to join us in Zoom?
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I love that we are already learning something and setting work grounds!
Sarah | Small Changes: I wish I could ❤️ I'm just in the middle of getting kids ready for school. But i'm listening 👂🏻
Mommy Guide Inc: oh yes you are in the future Sarah. Thanks for dropping by and listening with us in the chat!
Sarah | Small Changes: Pixelmator Pro for thumbnails is a game changer ❤️
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for the suggestion Sarah!
Sarah | Small Changes: So fun to see all my friends on screen at once
Ate MARGIE: 🎧
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hi Sarah!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: definitely we will be able to streamline the rules everything in the future.
Dr. ELO - Live Streaming: hELO ELO everyone
Dr. ELO - Live Streaming: Wow - Full House 🏠
TonyRIversen one crazy dane: Hello @ Dr. ELO
Dr. ELO - Live Streaming: Hey Tony
Mommy Guide Inc: Hello Dr. Elo!
Mommy Guide Inc: Care to join us next time on Zoom Dr. Elo?
Sarah | Small Changes: I'll catch you guys in the discord ❤️
Dr. ELO - Live Streaming: Hola Lala, sure
Mommy Guide Inc: You want to jump in now just quick?
Mommy Guide Inc: Sent you the Zoom Link Dr Elo:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Only if you can:) Thanks for the support and joining us:)
Dr. ELO - Live Streaming: Gracias
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Thank you so much! Markus this is great!
U Do It: I'll catch the replay! Good seeing you!
Mommy Guide Inc: thank you so much Markus and everyone for the time and the suggestions. Learning with peers!