Mommy Guide Inc: Hi everyone! Hi Janet!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi LALA!!! good morning.
Mommy Guide Inc: Good afternoon to you! he he he
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: You are so funny
Andy H: And good afternoon from here to there!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh boy! dance time
Mommy Guide Inc: and Hello Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Andy!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Andy
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hello!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yay Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: and then we have Ana!
Ellie Calhoun: hi everyone!
Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hi Andy and Lala! we meet again!!!
Andy H: Hi and Hello, always hello, never good-bye!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Ana
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: SAMMY!!!
Samantha JustInspire: Hey everyone
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Samantha
Andy H: Lala Lala Lala Lala!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hello friends!!! So happy to see so many of you here!!
Ellie Calhoun: looking forward to this experiment!
Andy H: Ana Aan Ana Ana Ana
Andy H: Funky music hurts my head, and so it goes ...
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Ellie. hey there
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed Ellie!
Andy H: Ellie EllieEllie Ellie!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I can't want to hear about the experiment too.
Ellie Calhoun: hi Janet and Lala and Andy, Andy, Andy and Samantha and... everyone!
Samantha JustInspire: Mommy LaLa I miss you 😊
Mommy Guide Inc: Lovin' Andy's song for all of us:)
Samantha JustInspire: Hi Ellie
Andy H: Music makes the world go 'round!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I love this song. everyone sing along!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: and then it's time for our fav countdown timer song!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Samantha! how are you?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: This IS the place to me
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I mean be
Samantha JustInspire: I’m doing good!
Mommy Guide Inc: that's great Samantha!
Samantha JustInspire: This song is so inviting! Love it 😍
Andy H: All the cool kids ...
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: @Samantha JustInspire I love that song too!
Mommy Guide Inc: HI Sammy!
SiShong Victor: Cool Kids room? Did I go to the wrong room again
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes! Pier group sounds great.
Samantha JustInspire: Loving the pink light in your Background! Of course it’s my favorite color 🤩🤩🤩
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Victor!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: @SiShong Victor you belong here too
SiShong Victor: 🙂
Andy H: Victor makes is cooler, for sure, peer to peer!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Victor!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I love this idea
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: lol see me no English very well is peer not pier LOL
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Be positive... it WILL fly in one direction or another
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Thanks Andy
Andy H: Birds gotta fly, so do good ideas ...
Tech Troublemaker: @Markus Schaub is LIVE!!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: take the first step and let it evolve. cool
Mommy Guide Inc: Howdy Roy!
Paul Burke: it's a fun idea!
SiShong Victor: Peer: a person who is an equal (noun); to look attentively (verb). Pier: a structure extending out over water.
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Lala @Mommy Guide Inc
Ellie Calhoun: I like it, an interesting idea
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Paul-eeee
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I think is a great idea!!!
Tech Troublemaker: I think it is a fun idea.
Paul Burke: More accurate hair.....but still enormous eyes 🤣
Paul Burke: hey @Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing 🙂
Andy H: Peer pressure sucks, but this seems like peer pleasure
Samantha JustInspire: It’s a great idea! When do we start? And what will be doing?
Tech Troublemaker: the logistics will be interesting.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I think having real and interactive time is great! maybe a zoom and each week have someone come up with a theme about streaming?
Ellie Calhoun: We should do it during your lives when you don't have a guest...
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: How often do you plan to do it?
Mommy Guide Inc: will it be like a Round Table Discussion live?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: See... it is evolving already... ZOOM is good so we can see each other.
SiShong Victor: HAHAHA LaLa Do we have a round table?
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: oh!!! no, that is great!!! like a panel discussion live!! i think that would help us and all the people that is starting
Ellie Calhoun: you can stream a zoom live, right? I think doing it all live would make it interesting to see how people learn to collaborate and grow as a peer group...
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: every other week is good. How will we communicate with each other? your discord?
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: yes! we are not pros but venturers
SiShong Victor: I was thinking something similar but was thinking of streaming it into the FB group if we streamed it
Tech Troublemaker: What about Google Meet with virtual cameras to live stream it maybe?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: and when you figure out how to do that... zoom... let us know too.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Ah... really like this idea.
Mommy Guide Inc: yes I've brought in zoom via ecamm several times it can be done indeed and Markus for sure can do that if there are more than 5 of us:)
Markus Schaub: https://discord.gg/QDXWX8B889
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: my vote is also for every other week
Mommy Guide Inc: oh Yes indeed. I haven't tried going live from Discord.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I'm in!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh you have a new discord. ha
Mommy Guide Inc: If you are not yet members of Markus Discord server pls do join.
Andy H: The answer to How is YES!
Billy Robbins: I'm intrigued by the idea
Coffee Talk & Tech: if you do a BBQ over the summer ☀️ I'm in!
SiShong Victor: Zoom is easy and if it was to be streamed thats easy too
Tech Troublemaker: If it's easy anyone can do it. I prefer hard and difficult. I must I keep doing everything that way.
Ellie Calhoun: I'm in!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Billy and John@Coffee Talk & Tech!
Coffee Talk & Tech: hi Lala and Markus.
SiShong Victor: Ok ill refrash that, easy for me HAHAHA
SiShong Victor: rephrase*
Billy Robbins: Hello, hello!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: lol go Janet!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: To join Markus Discord Server just go to this link: https://discord.gg/QDXWX8B889
Design On Brand: Hey Markus. Just joining. Will Replay
BostonDonMTB: Hey Markus, joining late. Sorry.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Heather and Don!
Mommy Guide Inc: I think everyone is IN Markus:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi John
SiShong Victor: Im working now, from home, so this is not a good time for me
Coffee Talk & Tech: shhh yes I'm usually driving cut out an hour early.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Heather!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Please dont forget to like this stream!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Im in too
BostonDonMTB: Hi Lala
Ellie Calhoun: So maybe the first week we talk logistics and how to start, brainstorm ideas etc.
Mommy Guide Inc: So we can start readying our Qs, comments and suggestions about livestreaming:)
Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Hi Markus😀👋
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Q Would you give us a theme to talk about or would it be like an organic conversation?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: You are funny and always on top of things LALA
Samantha JustInspire: I’m in!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Ana! you have the first "Q" ;-)
Tech Troublemaker: hit the like button!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh cool. We can do that in the discord and then bring to life in the live
Mommy Guide Inc: I am sure it's doable via Discord too Janet. Markus can have a Feedback Channel on the Server. And then we can go live in there too!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh wow LALA. I forgot we can go live in discord. wow.
Andy H: You're magnetic, Markus!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I love it! I can also see some accountability
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed M is for Markus with the magnetic awesome supporting friend to all:)
Andy H: Got that one Lala!
Coffee Talk & Tech: good people deserve good things!
Ellie Calhoun: yes Ana, accountability... there can be a thread - if someone has a goal and asks for assistance then they can show the result in the next stream...
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Thanks you Markus and everyone.
Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: I am in also😀
Mommy Guide Inc: Accountability - great big word and super helpful for sure Ana. We all do need one:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ejnar:)
Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: 👋
Mommy Guide Inc: Dont forget to hit the like button on your way out today.:)
Andy H: Happy Easter / Happy Passover ya'll!
Ellie Calhoun: 👋👋👋
Mommy Guide Inc: See you again next week! But dont forget to join us in Markus Discord Server too! https://discord.gg/QDXWX8B889