Mommy Guide Inc: Hi everyone! Hi @Markus! Hi Suzan!
Lynn Clementi: Hi Markus and Suzan!
Sandi Thompson: Hallo!
SuzanCz: Hi everyone! Excited to get this started!
Steve Worthy: Lets @Markus Schaub, catching you Live Buddy! Hey @SuzanCz
Steve Worthy: @SuzanCz You have some Moves Girls!
Tech Troublemaker: Introverts rule.
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Markus
Steve Worthy: What's going @Tech Troublemaker, good to see you here dude!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Steve
Sandi Thompson: Hieveryone!
SuzanCz: Great to see you all here!
Lynn Clementi: Can't wait to be a guest on your show. We'll talk soon about our schedules!
Sarah | Small Changes: SUZAN!!! MARKUS!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Don’t forget to hit the like button everyone.:)
SuzanCz: SARAH!
Sarah | Small Changes: Introvert 💯
Sandi Thompson: I'm an extrovert trapped in an introverts body.
Mommy Guide Inc: I love Suzan’s logo - have super hero feels:)
Mark Thomas: Speaking on the phone in a public place is my hell
Sandi Thompson: okay. I'm 95% introvert.
Sandi Thompson: YEP! you got me.
Jayne Mattson: Even though I am a strong extrovert, I really like my quiet time and being alone.
Mommy Guide Inc: I think I am an ambivert. I also need my “me” time.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Jayne Mat
SuzanCz: @Jayne Mattson! ❤
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Jayne Mattson. I can totally relate:)
Mark Thomas: Introverts are great dancers. I prefer to dance alone in a nightclub
Mark Thomas: My extrovert friends freak out when I say that
Mark Thomas: It’s better to be an introvert, I think 🤔
Ana Zugheri: hello friends! Im late but so glad Im able to catch some of the live
Mark Thomas: I love to research and explore things in detail
Lynn Clementi: ooooh, do me next
Paul Burke: MARKUS! SUZAN!
Paul Burke: LYNN!
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: Is listening easier for certain personality types like for introverts?
Stephanie Gieseke: Ahhhhhhhh!!! I am late - so sorry!!!! I have been SO excited for this stream!!
Lynn Clementi: PAUL!
Ellie Calhoun: Hello!!! Catching you live!
Cheryl French: Hey Markus and Suzan! I was just talking to my daughter in the car about how she identifies herself as an introvert.
Paul Burke: STEPHANIE!
Stephanie Gieseke: PAUL!!!
Ana Zugheri: oh! that is so good! skill strenght!
Paul Burke: introverts make great editors too....also cause they're so observant on timing, and subtle communication cues
Sandi Thompson: Don't forget to hit the like button!
Stephanie Gieseke: I spent the past 13 years thinking my daughter was an extrovert and come to find out this summer she is an introvert. It has been a HUGE game changer with how I interact with her after school now.
Lynn Clementi: I think I'm an extrovert
Ellie Calhoun: I'm an introvert
Paul Burke: I think I'm an introvert
Stephanie Gieseke: Extra-extrovert
Ana Zugheri: Im an extrovert and my family is introvert it has been a game changer for me to understand them. Improved our communication!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Lala @Mommy Guide Inc (wow 4am?)
Tech Troublemaker: I am an introvert but my alter ego is an extravert so I guess I am an ambivert.
Stephanie Gieseke: I have found that the people I have met online (through LEDA and SA) understand me SO much better than my family and friends do.
Sandi Thompson: @Stephanie Gieseke - me too!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Roy! Since you guys changed time - its actually past 5am.:) and i love waking up early to be here.:)
Paul Burke: movies alone are a delight
Cheryl French: Can Suzan tell us more about the different types of introverts? I was telling my daughter about Suzan’s business today, but I couldn’t
Cheryl French: Remember the different types of introverts
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: so being shy doesn’t always equate to bring an “introvert”?
Stephanie Gieseke: My dad always used to say 'God gave you two ears and only one mouth so you should listen more than you talk'. a nice way to tell me to shhhhhhhhhh 🙂
Paul Burke: I think I'm an introvert....maybe an ambivert...i don't know.
Ellie Calhoun: I used to take it personally when my husband wouldn't talk to me after he got home from work. And then I learned that he was an extreme introvert. Once I understood, life was so much better!
Lynn Clementi: Stephanie, my mom used to tall me the same thing. haha
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Suzan
Cheryl French: I do worry, however, that some of our young people are identifying themselves as introverts because they find being online (gaming and social media and watching YouTube videos, etc) to be less …
Ana Zugheri: I hear you Ellie! understanding the same from my husband has helped us to communicate better
Stephanie Gieseke: @Ellie Calhoun that is exactly what I found out with my daughter! I realized I need to stop ask her questions right away and let her go hibernate in her room for a little while first
Cheryl French: …or rather more rewarding than contact with people in real life
Ana Zugheri: @Cheryl French that is a genuine worry I wonder too
Stephanie Gieseke: @Cheryl French I don't know if its because we live waaaaaaay out in the suburbs, but I feel that I can find more of a variety in the people I meet online vs who lives close to me
Cheryl French: @Ana Zugheri yes because social media, gaming and pretty much all of the internet is designed to give us dopamine kicks. REal life not so much.
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: is there a one technique or marketing plan that can be effective for all personality types? Or it has to niched it to be more effective?
Stephanie Gieseke: @Mommy Guide Inc you have such good questions!
Stephanie Gieseke: I am in awe of people who can maintain FB Groups - I am an extrovert but they suck the life out of me. You need to post sooooooo much to keep the engagement going
Stephanie Gieseke: Q: do you also have resources for how extroverts can market to introverts or to create campaigns specific to introverts?
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks @Stephanie marketing and sales are the most difficult for me. I am better at operations and technical side of the biz
Lynn Clementi: Lala, I'm the same way
Cheryl French: @Stephanie Gieseke good point. I’m not saying the online world isn’t without value, but I sometimes think my daughter feels more at home there than in the real world BECAUSE it gives more kicks.
Tech Troublemaker: Ooooo PowerPoint presentation
Lynn Clementi: I like problem solving and not so much the marketing
Mommy Guide Inc: You can reach Suzan: https://suzancz.com
Stephanie Gieseke: @Cheryl French I totally get it and understand where you are coming from. Sometimes it is hard to drag our kiddos away from their devices and online worlds. Its hard to know what the perfect...
Stephanie Gieseke: ...balance is
Sarah | Small Changes: Q: I really struggle with feeling like I'm bothering people when I put marketing out there... even though I know people can't come if they don't know about it 🤣 Any tips for those feelings?
Cheryl French: @Sarah really good question! Feeling like we’re bothering people…
Ellie Calhoun: Regarding technology, I'm one of those introverts who really hates talking on the phone, so having the option to text has been great!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes I agree composing the right email to market ones business is very important. it's not something that you just send out and hope it works.
Stephanie Gieseke: YES!!! I found my people!!!
Ellie Calhoun: Hmmm I think I'm a thinking introvert combined with the previous one, observing and reading the room before jumping in
Sarah | Small Changes: I sometimes get confused what is my introvert nature and what is my anxiety 🤣
Sandi Thompson: @Sarah | Small Changes - me too.
Tech Troublemaker: Q. I am a lousy salesman. It is so hard to approach people. Any suggestions?
Ana Zugheri: that is so good
Ana Zugheri: Yes! believing
Tech Troublemaker: Great show!