Cheryl Wolf: Games , card games, board games, games we play??
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Cheryl. can't wait for games!!! I will be meditating at the same time. Is that possible? I don't think so. hahaha
Cheryl Wolf: lol
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: :chillwcat:
Cheryl Wolf: maybe it will be a dizzy game
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: oh no!!! a dizzy game for we dizzy blondes? hahahaha
Markus Schaub: Trivia
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: dance time!!! you can dance in a circle Cheryl and get dizzy!!!
Cheryl Wolf: Thanks janet for playing along
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: 💃💃💃💃💃💃💃💃💃💃💃
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: trivia? I"m bad at that. haha
Cheryl Wolf: yes dance time!!
Cheryl Wolf: jump jump jump
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: 🦄🦄🦄🦄
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: the gang is here!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: have fun!!
Ellie Calhoun: "Our Song" 🥰🥰🥰
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: ELLIE!!!!
Cheryl Wolf: Hey Ellie
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Cheryl and Janet!
Ellie Calhoun: 😘💃🏼💃💃🏾
Cheryl Wolf: Is that a new mic??
Ellie Calhoun: hey Markus!
Ellie Calhoun: I don't do much trivia, but willing to try!
Markus Schaub: jackbox.tv
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: oh we have to go there too? sorry
Ellie Calhoun: what's the code?
Markus Schaub: ensl
Cheryl Wolf: yes code
Cheryl Wolf: yes
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: this is interesting.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: ellie!!
Ellie Calhoun: oh, I look lovely lol
Cheryl Wolf: yeah scary ellie
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: 😳
Ellie Calhoun: no!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: oh I know... fabric
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: silly me
Cheryl Wolf: winner
Ellie Calhoun: how do you answer? I knew it
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: noooo
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: hahah that is a riot
Ellie Calhoun: lololol
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I went to the light
Ellie Calhoun: oh no! Janet!!
Cheryl Wolf: lol
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: 👻
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: i know i'm dead twice
Ellie Calhoun: darn
Ellie Calhoun: yes
Ellie Calhoun: first one I didn
Ellie Calhoun: t realize there was a time limit
Ellie Calhoun: darn!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: i said lion
Ellie Calhoun: oh, I'm all bones
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: welcome to the light Ellie
Ellie Calhoun: lol @Janet
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: that's not fair
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: only 4???
Cheryl Wolf: hat
Ellie Calhoun: we got it right Janet
Ellie Calhoun: even though we are dead
Ellie Calhoun: guessing...
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: me
Cheryl Wolf: lol
Ellie Calhoun: lol
Ellie Calhoun: this is funny
Cheryl Wolf: safe
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: haha 🔪
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: me
Ellie Calhoun: argh
Ellie Calhoun: oh oh, bye bye
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: $$$$$$
Ellie Calhoun: im doing terribly
Ellie Calhoun: bye!
Ellie Calhoun: I would have got that last answer!
Ellie Calhoun: fun!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: too funny
Cheryl Wolf: yeah it was fun
Ellie Calhoun: mind meld accident
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I didn't know any of these. haha
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: yes fun
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I'm in spirit now so watch out!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: something new
Ellie Calhoun: that's what it said about me, how I died...
Markus Schaub: ewid
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: oh good... humor
Ellie Calhoun: where do we put the code?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: why does everyone die?
Ellie Calhoun: you guys are slow
Ellie Calhoun: lol
Cheryl Wolf: lol
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: ha
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: i'm done
Cheryl Wolf: lol
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: how do we pick? it's not coming up
Cheryl Wolf: booooo
Cheryl Wolf: omg
Sarah | Small Changes: Did I miss it?
Ellie Calhoun: that was hard
Sarah | Small Changes: Unicorns 🤣
Ellie Calhoun: go Markus!
Ellie Calhoun: hi Sarah!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: you won!!! i was bumped
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: this is rigged!!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: hahaha
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: SARAH
Ellie Calhoun: let's do it - I got nothing to do (another lie) loil
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: let's do it for Sarah
Cheryl Wolf: yes
Cheryl Wolf: oh no markus
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: tell Sarah what to do
Markus Schaub: wajn
Sarah | Small Changes: What site do I go to?
Markus Schaub: jackbox.tv
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: oh this is creepy
Sarah | Small Changes: Error message 😭
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: what
Markus Schaub: ueob
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: whats the code again? I got bounced
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: strange
Ellie Calhoun: are we supposed to be good at drawing?lol
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: i can't draw but why not try. haha
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: oh no
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: i'm goping to die here
Ellie Calhoun: was there space for a slogan? I didn't see it
Eaglevp: Evening Markus
Eaglevp: Hi Ellie
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: the flower one is not mind
Tim Heale 9: Me too
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: not mine
Eaglevp: Love the graphics
Cheryl Wolf: hey tim and keith
Tim Heale 9: Hi all
Ellie Calhoun: Go Janet!
Eaglevp: Hi Cheryl
Ellie Calhoun: I liked the first 2 games better
Eaglevp: Hey Animal Paradise
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: hey eagle gap
Tim Heale 9: Hi Cheryl I would like you back on my Thursday live
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: on no we are going to die again
Sarah | Small Changes: They are both mine 🤣
Eaglevp: Hello Sarah
Sarah | Small Changes: Obviously I’m an artist
Cheryl Wolf: Thanks tim
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: so you have something about poo and smells Sarah? haha
Ellie Calhoun: I think they decide based on who wrote the comment?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: oh interesting
Ellie Calhoun: that's my art
Sarah | Small Changes: I have a 5 year old boy can you tell 🤣
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: so funnhy
Cheryl Wolf: congrats
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: oh we can buy these? haha
Sarah | Small Changes: Thanks so much for staying on for me ❤️
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: congradts Sarah
Ellie Calhoun: fun!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: that was fun
Sarah | Small Changes: This was so fun ❤️
Sarah | Small Changes: Siri would love to join next time
Cheryl Wolf: Thanks