Mommy Guide Inc: Oh my i love this game Markus! I played this with Austin last December.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: See you later!
Mommy Guide Inc: Let's Go!
Sammy Super Star: Markus!!
Sammy Super Star: Lala go to sleep! It’s very late
Tech Troublemaker: Can you get there from here? Where are we going today?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sammy! Hi Roy!
Mommy Guide Inc: I slept early guys!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Lala!!! Sammy!!!! (7 Year Anniversary, so awesome @Sammy Super Star )
Sammy Super Star: You have to wake up every early today lol 😆
Mommy Guide Inc: Let's do this!
Mommy Guide Inc: let's look for signs
Mommy Guide Inc: Japan
Mommy Guide Inc: the cars go back
Mommy Guide Inc: let's lookout plate nos Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus go back to the car
Cheryl Wolf: Hello !!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Cheryl
Cheryl Wolf: Hi lala
The Crafty In Me: Hi Markus, Hi mommy lala
Mommy Guide Inc: somewhere in Europe?
Cheryl Wolf: I never seen this before, interesting
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi JUdy @The Crafty In Me
Mommy Guide Inc: Chile
Julie Ulrich: Hiiiii 😊
The Crafty In Me: just dropping by before dozing off.
Cheryl Wolf: Hi julie
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Julie
Mommy Guide Inc: South America
Julie Ulrich: Hi Markus! Hi Cheryl and Lala and Sammy 😊🎉
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for dropping by Judy.
Julie Ulrich: I’m doing well! Hope you are too ❤️
Mommy Guide Inc: Please don't forget to like this awesome stream!
Mommy Guide Inc: hmm so where are we now
Cheryl Wolf: country roads
Cheryl Wolf: hahaha sing it
Mommy Guide Inc: what does the sign say again?
Mommy Guide Inc: Japan again?
Sammy Super Star: Hahahaha
Cheryl Wolf: 🤣
Julie Ulrich: 🎵🎶🎵
Sammy Super Star: Does Markus like to sing I see lol
Mommy Guide Inc: kosovo?
Cheryl Wolf: Thank you Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: the sign board markus
Sammy Super Star: My week is going great so far
Tech Troublemaker: I get to put up a kitchen light and replace a garbage disposal tomorrow. 😛
Sammy Super Star: What do you do for work? I have been always curious
Sammy Super Star: Yes
Sammy Super Star: Tonight
Mommy Guide Inc: go back
Tech Troublemaker: @Sammy Super Star when is the live stream?
Sammy Super Star: I might be singing lol 😆
Sammy Super Star: You have to find out
Mommy Guide Inc: the car plate no
Sammy Super Star: Very interesting
Sammy Super Star: That’s pretty cool
Sammy Super Star: Oh man. It’s 1am for you!
Cheryl Wolf: wow congrats sammy!!
Sammy Super Star: I feel bad now
Mommy Guide Inc: Join us as well in Sammy's 7th year anniversary stream in a few hours! - https://youtu.be/irngk_QupdY
Sammy Super Star: Oh I know this song lol from lsp
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus the name of the building
Mommy Guide Inc: Lithuania?Latvia?
Kali Co: latvia!
Kali Co: that's latvia!
Tina Wan Kenobi: Past Markus 😛
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Kali!
Tina Wan Kenobi: Psst
Kali Co: hai!!! ❤ ❤
Kali Co: ahahahahha
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Tina!!!
Tina Wan Kenobi: Lala the vampire 😆
Cheryl Wolf: Hi kali
Kali Co: Hey party peeps ❤🤗
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Tina
Kali Co: dang this is where the party is
Sammy Super Star: Kali is giving to be a guest tonight if it’s still on
Cheryl Wolf: yes party is here!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Welcome to the party guys!
Tina Wan Kenobi: Hi Cheryl, Sammy, Roy, Kali!
Mommy Guide Inc: please don't forget to smash the like button!
Kali Co: YAY!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey we got it!
Kali Co: @Sammy Super Star heck yeah
Tina Wan Kenobi: Ooh I remember this game from December!
Mommy Guide Inc: Just chillin' today - playing a game together.
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Tina we played this with Austin:)
Mommy Guide Inc: And I think Sammy was there too.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hi 👋
Sammy Super Star: If I have a wireless mic on then you will know lol 😆
Kali Co: oo nice they gave you that one!
Kali Co: east coast of cananada
Kali Co: on montreal
Kali Co: *in
Sammy Super Star: Hahaah
Kali Co: on the east side of canada
Mommy Guide Inc: HI Ana!
Kali Co: that's west it's east!
Kali Co: other side other side!
Tina Wan Kenobi: To the right
Kali Co: there is is!
Kali Co: i thought monstreal~
Kali Co: oo IW AS RIGHT
Mommy Guide Inc: awesome!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: 😆 the other right
Kali Co: HECK YEAH
Tina Wan Kenobi: You’re getting big pts!
Mommy Guide Inc: oh yeah the other right! LOL
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Ana
Kali Co: this is very flat here
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hi Cheryl 👋
Mommy Guide Inc: the building!
Kali Co: any time a place is so flat, i think it is kentucky haha but of course there are tons of other place in the world that are flat
Tina Wan Kenobi: You’re driving very fast 😆
Kali Co: @Tina Wan Kenobi yeah he is going over the speed limit for sure
Kali Co: hahahahhaa
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hi Cheryl 👋
Cheryl Wolf: Midwest is very flat
Mommy Guide Inc: plate no Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: can you take a closer peek at the plate nos?
Kali Co: That is my chest. I'd recognize that flatness anywhere
Tina Wan Kenobi: They blur the plates I think
Mommy Guide Inc: they blurred it '
Tina Wan Kenobi: Kali 😆
Kali Co: hmm i don't think it's us
Kali Co: i thought it was but now i don't think so
Kali Co: 😂😂😂
Kali Co: i know that i don't want to live there hahahaha
Tina Wan Kenobi: Shirt
Kali Co: his shirt said cash is killing i think?
Kali Co: oo that doe slook like
MySnoopy80: Hi❤️
Kali Co: hey snoopy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @MySnoopy80 !
Kali Co: this one is hard haha
Tina Wan Kenobi: The signs over fence
Kali Co: OHH king hahahahhaha
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I came in late so I don’t even know what WE are doing…I love the music!
Kali Co: i was like "wow that is a statement of a shirt damn!"
MySnoopy80: Im asking myself the same thing😅
Kali Co: what is the area code 076
Kali Co: that is not us
Kali Co: hmmmm
Kali Co: what is near uk?
Kali Co: *what if
Mommy Guide Inc: south africa
Tina Wan Kenobi: Johannesburg!
Tech Troublemaker: Pakistan is zo country code
Mommy Guide Inc: 076- netherlands
Mommy Guide Inc: no wait!!!
Tina Wan Kenobi: Oh zO?
Tina Wan Kenobi: I thought zA lol
Tech Troublemaker: the address on the sign, was it not ending in zo website?
Tina Wan Kenobi: Waitttt
Cheryl Wolf: If we are on a road trip , I would say how long before we get there lol
Tech Troublemaker: yes za is south africa
Kali Co: that makes sense
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: And I would ask where is the snack bag
Mommy Guide Inc: whew!
Kali Co: oooo dang!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: He he he.
Kali Co: that was good!!!!
Kali Co: totally
Sammy Super Star: I’m becoming a mad man
Sammy Super Star: Hahaha bad joke
Mommy Guide Inc: yes Southeast Asia looking - banana leaves!
Kali Co: @Sammy Super Star ahahahha
Kali Co: yeah looks like southeast asia!!
Kali Co: yeah this is so cool
Tina Wan Kenobi: I’m on phone, in bed sideways with one eye open, googling
Kali Co: @Tina Wan Kenobi 😂😂😂
Mommy Guide Inc: can we see the house?
Mommy Guide Inc: near my country Philippines
Kali Co: vietnam? cambodia?
Sammy Super Star: It’s very late for Tina and lala
Mommy Guide Inc: can we see the houses?
Mommy Guide Inc: yes we all have similar countryside look!
Kali Co: awwwe
Kali Co: damn
Kali Co: in our defense, they didn't give us any buildings!
Mommy Guide Inc: that's fine still south east asia
Tina Wan Kenobi: Yup it’s 4:30am hehe, but woke up to pee TMI and remembered Markus streams this hour
Mommy Guide Inc: we should have gotten more points. let's do an appeal! LOL
Kali Co: @Tina Wan Kenobi every time I pee, I am reminded of Markus too 😂
Cheryl Wolf: lol lala
Tina Wan Kenobi: Kali 😆😆😆
Mommy Guide Inc: TIna!
Kali Co: hahahahah
Kali Co: 😂😂
Mommy Guide Inc: go back to the sign Markus
Tina Wan Kenobi: Cebu!
Kali Co: they purposefully drop you in the middle of nowhere on this one
Tina Wan Kenobi: Did it say LlEX?
Mommy Guide Inc: no the other one
Mommy Guide Inc: further back
Tina Wan Kenobi: Llex
Mommy Guide Inc: forward more not that one
Tina Wan Kenobi: Don’t go in the water 😆
Mommy Guide Inc: its a blue sign
Tina Wan Kenobi: Or game over
Mommy Guide Inc: there!
Mommy Guide Inc: russia?
Tina Wan Kenobi: How do I google those foreign alphabet 😆
Sammy Super Star: Guess what song I will be singing tonight Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: Sammy I think its GOLD!
Sammy Super Star: Everyone is wrong so far lol 😆
Mommy Guide Inc: oh yeah!!!
Sammy Super Star: You have to wait lol
Mommy Guide Inc: Please dont forget to join Sammy for his 7th Anniversary stream at 7AM EST https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=irngk_QupdY
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus can we go back to the sign?
Tina Wan Kenobi: 🇧🇷
Tina Wan Kenobi: Happy anniversary Sammy!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Brazil probably:)
Tina Wan Kenobi: Yikes 😆
Mommy Guide Inc: toink! he hehe
Mommy Guide Inc: is there a song "nowhere?
Mommy Guide Inc: me and signs! I learned how to read by reading signs
Mommy Guide Inc: for real!
Mommy Guide Inc: vandalism is a crime! grrr
Mommy Guide Inc: it's fun way to learn how to read right?
Mommy Guide Inc: why is it always taking us to the countryside?
Mommy Guide Inc: waah! we're on clincher level. LOL
Tina Wan Kenobi: Markus! Late to greet… Congratulations on being newly crowned LSP team member!!
Kali Co: yes!! congratulations markus!!!! sorry i am taking care of bird so i am here but lurking
Kali Co: have to take her on quick walk
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Tina - Congratulations Markus!!!🎊
Tina Wan Kenobi: Greek?
Tina Wan Kenobi: Europe?
Mommy Guide Inc: Greece could be
Tina Wan Kenobi: Are their E’s that way
Mommy Guide Inc: yey!!!
Tina Wan Kenobi: Ibar a river
Mommy Guide Inc: yes I was going to type Serbia Markus is so fast:)
Mommy Guide Inc: to the building
Tina Wan Kenobi: Sounds foreign 😛
Mommy Guide Inc: new zealand
Mommy Guide Inc: otewa road, new zealand
Tina Wan Kenobi: Otorohanga
Mommy Guide Inc: nice try
Tina Wan Kenobi: What no pts?
Mommy Guide Inc: nice neighborhood
Mommy Guide Inc: Hamilton, Ontario canada
Tina Wan Kenobi: Ontario?
Tina Wan Kenobi: Above minesotta
Mommy Guide Inc: we're getting the countries right
Tina Wan Kenobi: Waaat?
Tina Wan Kenobi: Heemstede
Mommy Guide Inc: awesome!!!
Tina Wan Kenobi: Big pts!!
Tina Wan Kenobi: Ok both eyes open now
Tina Wan Kenobi: Phone code
Tina Wan Kenobi: Nice to drive thru a canopy of trees 😍
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus is overspending again:) LOL
Tina Wan Kenobi: La 😆
Mommy Guide Inc: oops not overspending ! LOL
Tina Wan Kenobi: Markus is paying for gas!
Mommy Guide Inc: Northeren Ireland?
Mommy Guide Inc: wow that was fast.
Tina Wan Kenobi: That’s a lot of vans
Mommy Guide Inc: looks like Greece again
Mommy Guide Inc: oh no wait lets investigate some more
Tina Wan Kenobi: One hour only?
Mommy Guide Inc: thanks Markus!
Tina Wan Kenobi: Markus thanks for driving us all around!
Mommy Guide Inc: loved this game:)
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Markus!