Samantha JustInspire: Hi Markus
Sammy Super Star: Hey Markus!
Samantha JustInspire: Hey Sammy
Samantha JustInspire: It’s the end of the year…Happy New Year!
Samantha JustInspire: I saw that but it won’t let me open your message
Sarah | Small Changes: MARKUS!!!
Sarah | Small Changes: I'll watch it on the replay!
Mary Speegle: Yay! I caught you live.
Sarah | Small Changes: https://smallchanges.tv/smallchanges22/
Sarah | Small Changes: Hi Mary 👋🏻
Sarah | Small Changes: I'm so excited!
austinator: hey Markus
John Pullum: Hi Markus! I commented on here before Markus did.
Sarah | Small Changes: Do you feel more confident now?
austinator: thanks for the heads up Sarah!!!
John Pullum: Let's see how long you can grow a beard in 2022, Markus.
austinator: I had a lot of fun playing Chess with you Markus
Sammy Super Star: How many streams have you done this yeaerr
John Pullum: @Sarah | Small Changes I've been sorting stuff and throwing out stuff this week.
austinator: Sarah I haven't decluttered at all this week
John Pullum: ALWAYS GO LIVE!
Sarah | Small Changes: @John Pullum you're ahead of the game!
Mary Speegle: I loved it when you asked Marga if she ever thought about being an accountant.
Sammy Super Star: I did 30+ interviews it was crazy next you you will do more interviews then me 😉
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Markus Schaub . Wow, YouTube didn't notify me you were live.
Sammy Super Star: once a week is nice
Sammy Super Star: you did a great job
Kali Co: just stopping by to say hey!!!! in the middle of a few things so can't hang but will pop back in and see if you're still here 🤗 also hi everyone!!!
Sarah | Small Changes: Have any of your friends or family watched your streams?
austinator: I went live 11 times this year
austinator: KALI!!!!!!!!
austinator: 💚💚💚
Sarah | Small Changes: KALI!!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey@Kali Co
John Pullum: I miss @Kali Co
austinator: I went live 11 times and posted 11 videos... wow
John Pullum: I'm so proud of you, Markus. You are getting better and better. You are also such a kind and wonderful person. Such a big supporter of so many people.
Sarah | Small Changes: Favourite guest? 😉
John Pullum: @Sarah | Small Changes I bet he says John Pullum
John Pullum: or Sarah
Sarah | Small Changes: but me the most?
austinator: you can tell when I went through LEDA because my confidence on camera really shot up
Sarah | Small Changes: Thing you learnt after going LIVE?
John Pullum: Blink at some point if I was your favorite. Don't blink the rest of the stream if it was Sarah.
Samantha JustInspire: You have been doing so well Markus
Sarah | Small Changes: @John Pullum It's a Trap!
Sara S: Hi Markus! Happy Holidays!
Tech Troublemaker: Don't forget to hit that Like button.
austinator: Sarah I read just as you'd expect I'd read it, Star Wars fans unite!!!
John Pullum: @Sarah | Small Changes He's blinking even more now. I know you noticed that.
Sarah | Small Changes: @austinator this is why i love ya ❤️
austinator: I'm your favorite Austin 😉
John Pullum: I have @Sara S 's calendar next to me. Do you? You should!
Sara S: @Sarah | Small Changes let me know about signing up for your challenge!!!
SiShong Victor: lets get this party started now
austinator: I was gonna say I was your favorite minor but Sammy is here too
Sarah | Small Changes: @Sara S https://smallchanges.tv/mylink/sarah/
Sara S: @John Pullum very expensive to ship outside of the U.S.
Sarah | Small Changes: Favourite tech purchase in 2021?
Samantha JustInspire: Yes let’s here it
Tech Troublemaker: I think you should do a 24 hour Live Stream. You don't sleep anyway. 😛
John Pullum: Yes I want to hear it
SiShong Victor: Fav tech purchase of 2021? ALL OF THEM
austinator: oh Markus don't be a tease
Samantha JustInspire: Yes….nice Markus!
Sarah | Small Changes: I love it!!
John Pullum: Nice!
Tech Troublemaker: Wow, love the song.
Samantha JustInspire: @SiShong Victor agreed
austinator: my favorite Tech Purchase of 2021 was the Samson Q2U
Sandi Thompson: Hi! Late to the party!
Sammy Super Star: I went live over 70+ times on the channel and then i did 30 videos that were not live
Sammy Super Star: I told you about the Samson Q2u
Sarah | Small Changes: @SiShong Victor Mine is Pixelmator Pro... It was a game changer for thumbnails
austinator: yes you did Sammy, but it's still my favorite purchase
Sarah | Small Changes: SANDI!!!
John Pullum: Smash the like button @Sandi Thompson
Sammy Super Star: 24 hours that might be a little crazy for your GF
austinator: there's 10 people watching and only 7 likes... come on guys hit the like button
Sandi Thompson: I have vacation Brain. I forgot. 🤓
Sammy Super Star: Favorite gear its hard to say I have like 5 ideas LOL
SiShong Victor: 24 hrs? this isn't Twitch now 😁
Tech Troublemaker: Wow, I have gone Live 75 times in 2021 and 17 recorded videos.
austinator: oh no, I forgot I need to do something for Lala's stream tonight!!! I'll be lurking
SiShong Victor: That all Tech Troublemaker? Slow year ah
Sarah | Small Changes: Favourite channels for creators?
Sammy Super Star: Live streaming pros top
Sarah | Small Changes: YES!! Channel Makers is one of my favourites
Sammy Super Star: Dee Nimmin and Daniel Batal are great
Tech Troublemaker: Go Live and then edit it to be your recorded video. So much faster. Haha.
Sammy Super Star: Its almost been 2 years since I haven't missed a LSP stream. Once I had a tooth pulled and I was still watching
John Pullum: You give a LOT back to the community. You're so great.
Sammy Super Star: Also John Pullum is good 😉
Sarah | Small Changes: YT channel you watch that no one would guess?
austinator: ok maybe I thought that was gonna last longer than it actually did 🤣
John Pullum: @Sammy Super Star Wait until you are married with kids and you won't have as much time to do anything.
John Pullum: Thanks. It's a great group. Easy to keep going with great members.
Sarah | Small Changes: I watch a channel called Fascinating Horror 🤣
Sarah | Small Changes: This was so much fun!!
John Pullum: Fascinating Horror is a channel about a minimalist that goes around killing hoarders.