Mommy Guide Inc: Good day everyone!
Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
Mommy Guide Inc: And here comes my favorite opening video!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sammy!
Sammy Super Star: Will not be able to join the stream today on zoom but I will watch on YouTube
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Sammy! How are you?
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Everyone! I will be watching. Have a great show!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy@Tech Troublemaker
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ejnar and Adam!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Markus Schaub, Ejanar, and Coach Adam!
Sammy Super Star: You used Final cut
Sammy Super Star: I haven't used iMovie in years
Sammy Super Star: I want some advice, Should I have someone take over my stream tomorrow or do a premiere on the channel
Mommy Guide Inc: THanks Sammy! My brain froze on the name thanks Sammy!
Sammy Super Star: I'm sick with covid so I'm not camera ready right now
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh my. I hope you get well soon Sammy.
Sammy Super Star: Yeah
Mommy Guide Inc: If someone can take over that would be great. But if not then a premiere would be great as well.
Tech Troublemaker: @Sammy Super Star I hope you get to feeling better quick.
Sammy Super Star: I already have a interview that I made a Couple of weeks ago
Sammy Super Star: Thanks @Tech Troublemaker
Mommy Guide Inc: oh I think that would be better I think Sammy so you don't need to worry about anything. Just rest Sammy.
Sammy Super Star: Yes
Sammy Super Star: True
Mommy Guide Inc: You've been working and crushing it for a long time Sammy. A break is ok.
Sammy Super Star: Spend money on your content
Sammy Super Star: Austin was about to do it but he has a graduation
Sammy Super Star: Yes
Sammy Super Star: Thanks so much!
SiShong Victor: hola
Mommy Guide Inc: Hola Victor!
Mommy Guide Inc: Ejnar that's amazing - despite the tech issues you still overcame them.:)
Tech Troublemaker: I am waiting for the "Ducks in a Box" podcast.
Markus Schaub: Adam on Lalas Stream: https://youtu.be/LBu1EDaV73U
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow! your content is always very useful Adam.
Mommy Guide Inc: @Tech Troublemaker LOL! Yes the follow through with Ducks in A Box.:)
SiShong Victor: Heard Tacos. Still need to get lunch hungry
Mommy Guide Inc: I love how Adam walks the talk - how he gives actual examples to better understand the concepts.
Mommy Guide Inc: Don't forget to like this stream guys! Thanks for being here and sharing this stream:)
Mommy Guide Inc: You'll turn pizza lovers into Tacos and podcasting pretty soon Coach Adam!
Sammy Super Star: I want tacos now!
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh Sammyy. Yes eat tacos and anything you want. Get better my friend:)
Mommy Guide Inc: If you want to join: https://www.wbecs.com
SiShong Victor: Easiest way to edit = out source hahaha that's just me I can't edit
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hi guys sorry I couldn’t make it but will do the replay
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: How are you?
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: That is a great leader mentality!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I did!!! For my online course
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I have to post it to get your feedback
Mommy Guide Inc: we would love to do a feedback Ana:) Congratulations for this win!
SiShong Victor: I learned how to terminate data cables they said I need to know how it is done so I understand the contractors plans for cabling. Ya I ended up running all the cables once the company knew I knew how.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: You don’t steal, you get inspired!!!!
Sammy Super Star: Thumbnails are important
SiShong Victor: A thumbnail can make or break ya
Mommy Guide Inc: @SiShong Victor LOL! you should have gotten extra credits for that right?
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: That’s what I did for my intro video, I got inspired by Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes thumbnails is the first thing that people would see visually.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes!
SiShong Victor: extra $$$would be nice. Im not a professional cabling guy.
Mommy Guide Inc: how about people in the chat? what's your 10c view about thumbnails? pls join us next week.
SiShong Victor: I do a thumbnail try to make it basic and add some graphics and if I don't get clicked I replace it
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Markus intro video is super nice!
Sammy Super Star: I’m getting better at thumbnails
SiShong Victor: I had 0 views after 24Hrs and replaced the thumbnail and bam 10 in the same day
Sammy Super Star: Hahaha 😂
Sammy Super Star: I think I will be better to my self next week
SiShong Victor: I just hit 3K views in the last 28 days I feel the thumbnails helped
SiShong Victor: Yes they clicked then leave hahaha
Mommy Guide Inc: wow Congratulations Victor!
Sammy Super Star: For 4 Years on my old YouTube channel I didn’t even use thumbnails I used auto generated thumbnails. It was soooo bad
SiShong Victor: Saturday for me
Mommy Guide Inc: See you! https://youtu.be/BooZh-osuPg
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks everyone! for coming in. Had another awesome day with you all. See you back next week! please dont forget to like this again!
SiShong Victor: Saturday morning for the USA