Mommy Guide Inc: Hi John! 2nd row seats today:).
Tech Troublemaker: Okay, I will take the 3rd row then.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy!
Mommy Guide Inc: And we are live! Hi Markus and Sandi!
Samantha JustInspire: Hi Markus
Samantha JustInspire: Hello @Tech Troublemaker and @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Samantha!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Samantha JustInspire
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Mommy Guide Inc
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Markus Schaub
Tech Troublemaker: Live is Live!
Ellie Calhoun: Hello! Excited to be here!
Mommy Guide Inc: yey! nothing can stop this interview with Sandi!
Tech Troublemaker: Isn't that called TikToxic?
Ellie Calhoun: Hey Sandi!!!! Hey Markus!!!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Ellie Calhoun
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ellie!
Tech Troublemaker: I do dance with my dogs but they get confused. I am not a good dancer.
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL @Tech Troublemaker
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Lala and Roy and everyone !
Ellie Calhoun: Sounds like some old parenting techniques 😠
LOVEFACE. XYZ - НЕRЕ GIRLS WАNТ ЕVЕRYОNЕ ЕVЕN YОU: 💌🥰👍
LOVEFACE. XYZ - НЕRЕ GIRLS WАNТ ЕVЕRYОNЕ ЕVЕN YОU: 💞💞💞💦
LOVEFACE. XYZ - НЕRЕ GIRLS WАNТ ЕVЕRYОNЕ ЕVЕN YОU: 👍💌💦
LOVEFACE. XYZ - ОNLINЕ SТRIРS WIТНОUТ СLОТНING!: 💞🥵💞🤪✅🥵
LOVEFACE. XYZ - ОNLINЕ SТRIРS WIТНОUТ СLОТНING!: 🤪💋💌✅
Sarah | Small Changes: MARKUS!! SANDI!!
Mommy Guide Inc: People are lining up and waiting for their turn to attend your classes for their dogs to be trained because of the credibility that you have built Sandi
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Sarah | Small Changes
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed the community support is super awesome:)
Sarah | Small Changes: YES!!! I feel the same ❤️
Mommy Guide Inc: wow what an amazing transformation Sandi! You are truly an inspiration:)
Ellie Calhoun: Yup I did that!
Mommy Guide Inc: oh yes I was ready to quit on day 1
Sarah | Small Changes: I burst into tears after my day 1 🤣
Tech Troublemaker: Almost comfortable on YouTube, not sure I will ever be comfortable on TikTok
Mommy Guide Inc: but I am glad that I did not and the rest is history! otherwise I wouldn't have not met all of you:)
Sarah | Small Changes: @Tech Troublemaker Roy this video was my favourite video EVER!!
Tech Troublemaker: @Sarah | Small Changes mine too now.
Ellie Calhoun: Love this video!!
Tech Troublemaker: @Markus Schaub you were so amazing. You guys made it so easy to make an incredible video.
Mommy Guide Inc: Here is the 13 days of Christmas of Tech Troublemaker: https://youtu.be/RXT_LDS1SM8
Sarah | Small Changes: Whenever I'm having a bad day I'm going to watch it!
Sammy Super Star: Hey @Markus Schaub
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sammy!
Mommy Guide Inc: I agree Sarah. Watching that video is a great way to put a smile into one's face.
Mommy Guide Inc: and then there was Tiktok and then there was Sandi and the rest is history! Congratulations Sandi!
Mommy Guide Inc: Sandi's Tiktok: https://vm.tiktok.com/ZM8cAtvyL/
Mommy Guide Inc: Gosh only 3 months?
Mommy Guide Inc: 1.2M views
Ellie Calhoun: So amazing!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Laughter is the best medicine!
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL!
Ellie Calhoun: 😂🤣😂🤣
John Pullum: I'm here. What did I miss?
Mommy Guide Inc: Awesome Sandi!
Mommy Guide Inc: HiJohn!
John Pullum: The cool thing is the link you shared for her TikTok is in your language, Markus.
Mommy Guide Inc: Sandi's Tiktok: https://www.tiktok.com/@sandi_thompson?
Mommy Guide Inc: I totally agree I tried one 16sec and in 2 days I got 1500 views. first time for me. I just tried it.
Mommy Guide Inc: I really love that video as well. and over 1.2M thinks the same thing:)
Mommy Guide Inc: and all of your videos are still over 100. very inspiring Sandi:).
Mommy Guide Inc: wow! 500 followers. awesome.
Mommy Guide Inc: there you go - having fun is very important right?
Mommy Guide Inc: Don't forget to like this stream of course:) thanks!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes - Nika's classes are super awesome. Thanks for these tips Sandi.
LOVEFACE. XYZ - ОNLINЕ SТRIРS WIТНОUТ СLОТНING!: ✅✅👍💋💞🥵
LOVEFACE. XYZ - ОNLINЕ SТRIРS WIТНОUТ СLОТНING!: 💌🤪✅
Ellie Calhoun: So would you say the biggest thing for TikTok is the editing?
Mommy Guide Inc: How about doing YT shorts Sandi?
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes because there is a YT short bonus for creators no matter how many subscribers you have
Ellie Calhoun: Oh cool. I didn't know the editing is done in the app
Mommy Guide Inc: I also don't understand YT shorts that much. he he he.
Ate MARGIE: hello
Ate MARGIE: Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: that's a short you can use:)
Tech Troublemaker: @Markus Schaub I am still fighting that battle. I have no idea what my channel is about.
Tech Troublemaker: I have yet to niche down on YouTube.
Samantha JustInspire: I have been there too, and got help from my community
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ate Margie! Thanks for dropping by:)
Ellie Calhoun: Your channel Sandi, is about you...
Tech Troublemaker: But Dogs are always funny
Mommy Guide Inc: I am sure we will all figure out our niche sooner or later:) LOL
Ellie Calhoun: Markus I like that you are connecting all these people who are in different stages of live streaming and they all have different careers/backgrounds
Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Hi Markus and Sandi😀👍
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming
Ate MARGIE: :stayhome:
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL!
Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Hi @Mommy Guide Inc
Samantha JustInspire: lol
Mommy Guide Inc: Again Sandi's tiktok: Sandi's Tiktok: https://www.tiktok.com/@sandi_thompson?
Mommy Guide Inc: and don't forget to hit that like button on our way out:)
Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Bye bye Everyone😀