Tech Troublemaker: Yah! Markus and Lala!!!! Merry Christmas!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hello Roy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Markus!
Samantha JustInspire: Hey mommy Lala and Roy
Sandi Thompson: hi!
Lynn Clementi: Nice Christmas music. 🙂
Mommy Guide Inc: Hello Samantha!
Samantha JustInspire: I can’t wait to have Ecamm set just right
Sarah | Small Changes: LALA, MARKUS
Mommy Guide Inc: Happy Birthday again Sandi!
Samantha JustInspire: Hi Sandi
Samantha JustInspire: Hey Sarah
Coffee Talk & Tech: on my way home just wanted to say hi.
Sandi Thompson: thank you!!
Paul Burke: oh good...your house is still standing!
Sandi Thompson: hi everyone!
Paul Burke: Happy Birthday Sandi!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sarah!
Mommy Guide Inc: John Hi!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hello Paul!
Samantha JustInspire: The best time of the year!
Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone!
Paul Burke: anyone else concerned this elfs are never landing these hot hair balloons? The sky is filled with elves floating around
Samantha JustInspire: Hey Sammy my super star
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sammy!
Sammy Super Star: great dancing! Dancing along with you
Stephanie Gieseke: Hey Markus and Lala!!!
Paul Burke: hey Lala!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Lynn!!!
Sandi Thompson: How are you feeling Markus?
Lynn Clementi: Hey Lala!!
Stephanie Gieseke: @Markus Schaub good to see there are no flames in your background from your tree 🙂
Mommy Guide Inc: And then we have Stephanie hello!
Stephanie Gieseke: Glad to hear you are better!
Stephanie Gieseke: What time is it for @Mommy Guide Inc
austinator: hey Markus hey Lala
Samantha JustInspire: That’s mommy Lala! She’s always ready to jump in
Sarah | Small Changes: Morning ☀️
Tech Troublemaker: Hey all my YouTube friends!!
Lynn Clementi: I always wonder when the two of you sleep! haha
Samantha JustInspire: Hey Roy!
Samantha JustInspire: Question: how to you get the animated background in Ecamm with Picture in Picture
Lynn Clementi: That's so exciting Lala!! How long have you been livestreaming?
Sandi Thompson: I just got 1K followers on TikTok (on my bday!) and now I can go live on TikTok! Look out world!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hello guys!!!
Sandi Thompson: Lala - you look beautiful!
Lynn Clementi: We started right around the same time! My first livestream was in January too.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Love your background Markus!
Lynn Clementi: @Sandi, you're crushing it!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Sandy is rocking it!
Sandi Thompson: Thanks guys! Im having fun!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Lala you look so pretty!!!
Samantha JustInspire: Yes, I got some from them as well
Samantha JustInspire: Yes mommy Lala
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: super cute!!!
Sandi Thompson: Love it!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Markus you need one!!
Tech Troublemaker: @Samantha JustInspire so create a new scene, take the background that is a mp4 file and drag it to the scene, then add two Camera overlays and put your cameras you want in.
Samantha JustInspire: @Tech Troublemaker, I did that but I can’t get the camera to stay in the cut out! It’s off and don’t fit in correctly
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I love that veda! It sounds like the word live in spanish! That is a great idea!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes!! huge commitment Mommy Lala is a super MOM!!
Tech Troublemaker: @Samantha JustInspire set the camera overlay to custom rather than any of the shapes or sizes and resize it whatever size you want.
Samantha JustInspire: Can it be a shorts as well mommy Lala
Samantha JustInspire: I started late and just added a shorts last night
Samantha JustInspire: Ok I’m going to attempt again
Sarah | Small Changes: Lala you are amazing 🙌🏻 I'm struggling to get 1 video out a week let alone a VLOG everyday 🤣
Tech Troublemaker: I am calling it YuleVlog haha
Tech Troublemaker: Lala aka @Mommy Guide Inc is a content creation machine and like Santa is everywhere.
Sammy Super Star: a lot of people are doing vlogmas and its 30 days. Why would you only do it for 20 days. If your doing it with ecamm its 30 days.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes!!! She is!
Sammy Super Star: lala needs a editor
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Christmas eve
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: That is the way we do it in Mexico! and we call it noche buena too!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: ber moths!!! lol that is great!
Sandi Thompson: i used to always travel to SE Asia every year during Christmas. It's a HUGE celebration.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: September!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I know!!! he is so good!!! I have learned a lot from him to do my streaming interviews!
Sarah | Small Changes: REAL CANDLES 😱
Tech Troublemaker: Yikes, candles on the tree sounds dangerous.
Sarah | Small Changes: I'm up at night worried for Markus 🙈
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Fake candles fan right here!
Sarah | Small Changes: I have a fear of candles in general... its probably because I live on the surface of the sun 🤣
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hi Sarah! I absolutely love your channel!!! Big fan right here.
Sarah | Small Changes: Oh Thank you so so much @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: That sounds soooo much fun!
Sarah | Small Changes: I adore real Christmas cards... but I'm terrible at craft
Sandi Thompson: me too sarah!
Samantha JustInspire: Have to jump off, have a good one Markus!
Tech Troublemaker: I send Peanuts (Snoopy) Christmas cards. I am just not crafty. Diabolical maybe but not crafty.
Sarah | Small Changes: I need those 🙋🏻‍♀️
Sarah | Small Changes: It will be beginners cards I hope
Sarah | Small Changes: Sandi should also join us
Sandi Thompson: 🤪🥰
Sarah | Small Changes: Send me a list of things I need to buy
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Take it slow with us!!!
Sandi Thompson: i need to watch that!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: yes! send us a list please
Sarah | Small Changes: @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52 can also come!! Ecamm can do 5 guests right?
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: lol count me in!!!
Tech Troublemaker: break out the paper and the glue sticks and permanent markers.
Sandi Thompson: can't wait!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: if John Ryan can do it so can we!!!
Sarah | Small Changes: I'll make the card then post it to you Lala ❤️
Sandi Thompson: can we drink and craft?
Sarah | Small Changes: I've seen Markus's drawing on Pauls stream.... we are in for a treat 🤣
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: @Sandi Thompson if I drink and craft...I would end up with a card looking like I am in kindergarten lol
Sarah | Small Changes: @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52 That might happen to me without the drink 🤣
Sandi Thompson: sounds like fun tho!! 🖌+🍸!
Sarah | Small Changes: Did you love Seinfeld?
Sarah | Small Changes: We won't take any photos for our cards 🤣
Sandi Thompson: @Sarah | Small Changes -YES WE WILL!
Tech Troublemaker: @Sandi Thompson isn't that what a "Paint and Pour" is? Paint and wine?
Sandi Thompson: @Tech Troublemaker - sounds appropriate!
Sandi Thompson: I'll bring the cheese!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes! give them courage to craft lol
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: LOL
Sandi Thompson: Guzzle and Van Gough!
Sarah | Small Changes: I do not.... 🤣
Sandi Thompson: before you guys get the wrong idea - I don't drink!
Sandi Thompson: wow - my goodness.
Tech Troublemaker: I do not drink either. Someone has to drive.
Sarah | Small Changes: I don't drink either 🤣 too small 🤪
Sandi Thompson: i just like the sound of it. I want to watch others intoxicated and crafting. Pure spectator sport for me! 🤣
Tech Troublemaker: So you have to go to Coco Mama and tell us how the ice cream is.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Ivan
Sandi Thompson: YES! Ivan
Tech Troublemaker: Ivan
Sarah | Small Changes: I gotta take kids to school! Thanks so much for the great stream ❤️
Sandi Thompson: I adore you guys!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Thank you guys!!! you are awesome!