Mommy Guide Inc: He he he Tony, just a tad early but perfectly fine. LOL. See you in about 5 hours:)
Mommy Guide Inc: And were here! Front row seats.:)
Paul Burke: love the new Markus tattoo Kali
Ellie Calhoun: front row!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey! Hi Markus! Hi Kali!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ellie!
Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Paul!
SuzanCz: hey hey!
Sammy Super Star: Just woke up from my nap
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Mommy Guide Inc Lala!
Paul Burke: hey @Mommy Guide Inc 🙂
Sammy Super Star: Kali got another hair cut!
Samantha JustInspire: Hi Markus
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Sammy Super Star
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Lala, Paul, Suzan!! oh, just hello to everyone! ha ha!
Mommy Guide Inc: And Sammy is here! Perfect timie to wake up Sammy.:)
SuzanCz: I cann't stay because I need to go drink margaritas 🍸 But great to see you all here!
Paul Burke: hey @Ellie Calhoun 🙂
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Paul Burke and @Samantha JustInspire and @SuzanCz
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Ellie Calhoun
Paul Burke: @SuzanCz ...do you have a secret room you do that in?
Tech Troublemaker: wow so many folks I know 😛
Samantha JustInspire: Hey Roy
SiShong Victor: For a sec thought that was a chest tattoo haha I need glasses
Paul Burke: hey @Tech Troublemaker !
SuzanCz: Hahaha! Yes, yes, I do, @Paul Burke
Kurt Grela: Hey party people / streamers!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Roy! samantha! And Suzan!
Ellie Calhoun: pre-storm margaritas Suzan?
Sammy Super Star: Kali is rocking a emo cut I think lol 😂
SuzanCz: hey @Tech Troublemaker and @Mommy Guide Inc
Paul Burke: @SuzanCz ....."and over here in my Hard Alcohol wing of my home is the tequila room and whiskey add-on"
SuzanCz: @Ellie Calhoun YES! ☃️
SuzanCz: @Paul Burke HAHAHAHAHA!
SuzanCz: OOOH -- I love this video so much!
Mommy Guide Inc: Too early for those kind of drinks here Paul.:)
Sammy Super Star: 🕺💃
Paul Burke: yeah...well edited Markus...you found some great moments
SuzanCz: @Mommy Guide Inc It's 5pm somewhere.
Sammy Super Star: I think my and Markus both have live musicians
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hello everyone!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey everyone!
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL true Suzan. Truly love this song
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana and Janet.:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Markus & Kali
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I love this intro. Super sweet song! that sounds even sweeter watching everyone in it
Ellie Calhoun: this video just ,makes me smile! all the guests
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I so needed this video and music right now
SuzanCz: I love that @Paul Burke is the opening and closing of that video
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hello Markus!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Lala. How is tomorow?
Paul Burke: I love that it looks like I left the interview @SuzanCz 🤣
Paul Burke: "Urgent drinking business"...I'm using that phrase this week
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes!!! can't wait!!!
SuzanCz: Haha "I'm outta hea"
SuzanCz: We have a snowstorm coming in. Drinking is required.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Love the T-shirt
SuzanCz: Yay, Kali!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: stay safe @SuzanCz
Ellie Calhoun: ❄❄❄
SuzanCz: Did he say she's a hero? Or a Euro? Either would be correct.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: We love you Kali. great intro
Sammy Super Star: Lol 😂
Mommy Guide Inc: Janet do far tomorrow is looking great:)
SuzanCz: Thank you, @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52 . I won't go anywhere during the storm!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: :washhands::washhands::washhands:
Paul Burke: Markus rules. It's fact
SuzanCz: how much does it cost to rent Kali's chest for marketing purposes...? 🧐
Mommy Guide Inc: Stay safe everyone who will be having a storm soon.
Sammy Super Star: You painted your face before with sharpie 😂😂😊
Ellie Calhoun: Markus Rules!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: The laugh...it's contagious. lol
Mommy Guide Inc: Kali you have Sammy Super Star background feels.:)
SuzanCz: Kali is one of my favorite people. Anyone else feel that way?
SiShong Victor: You are all them things and a bag of chips and a Burger and frys
Ellie Calhoun: yes Suzan!
Sammy Super Star: Next thing you need a live band like me lol 😂
Paul Burke: It looks good with the light
Kurt Grela: The light adds to the background
Mommy Guide Inc: Absolutely Suzan! Great idea Victor!
Sammy Super Star: Yes I was about to say that it looks my very expensive certain and a cheap one that is better from Amazon 😂😂😂
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: and a SHAKE
austinator: woo!!! I've been anticipating this all week
SiShong Victor: Food is one thing always on my mind
Sammy Super Star: Markus Rules
Sammy Super Star: I like the background I will do that next stream
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Kurt!
SuzanCz: I'm out. Cheers all! 🍸
Tech Troublemaker: I really need to get some people skills.
Sammy Super Star: 😂
SiShong Victor: Did ya sale her a new work phone for you?
Mommy Guide Inc: Austin! Atay safe Suzan.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: bye Suzan
SiShong Victor: to funny
austinator: hey Lala!!!
Ellie Calhoun: bye Suzan - stay out of the deep snow!
Sammy Super Star: Craigslist the best way to be sketchy 😂😂
Ellie Calhoun: you are a natural, so genuine
austinator: yes it is Sammy
Paul Burke: Hey @austinator !
Paul Burke: we all breathe
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed Kali you really do have great people skills - specially making people feel important.
Mommy Guide Inc: Empathy and kindness wins !
Paul Burke: You have a lot of empathy Kali...that's a big gift
Paul Burke: @Mommy Guide Inc ...exactly
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: love that. showing up for yourself.
Sammy Super Star: That’s is amazing
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @Paul Burke well said about empathy
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: That is a quote right there!!!
austinator: Kali is my unpaid therapist, she always knows exactly what to say to get me through tough times and is so genuine and nice, Kali is the best, I love you 💚
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: So sweet
TonyRIversen: kali you rule as an outgoing person.
SiShong Victor: Austin Kali needs a raise. whats 10% increase of 0?
TonyRIversen: tell Luria to order double doors
Mommy Guide Inc: Hey Tony.;)
austinator: @SiShong Victor... umm... a virtual hug? I'd give a real one but that's not accessible at the moment
Sammy Super Star: Kali is the unpaid therapist for me and Austin 😂😂
austinator: Hawaiian with BBQ and not tomato sauce
Sammy Super Star: Yea that’s true
Sammy Super Star: I do that too!
Paul Burke: really smart Kali...."how can I help you" approach
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yes it's about serving our communities. that is 1st.
Sammy Super Star: The tutorial was amazing Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Community Care Hero - that title in itself is so positive and very encouraging rather than saying customer support
Dash With Ash in Canada: Better late than never! How's it going everyone ?
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yes Discord - Austin and Kali really encouraged me to start w my own Discord Server.
austinator: my Discord has been around for about 2 years now and yet it's still not very active, it doesn't start immediately
Paul Burke: THOT of the night Kali? Wow....thats edgy
austinator: I'm gonna start doing weekly Karaoke nights, Markus was there for the test one
SiShong Victor: Im only on two and always forget about them
Ellie Calhoun: my kids have been on very active discord groups for 5 years!
Paul Burke: thats fun @austinator
Sammy Super Star: Q: For my conference I’m going to do discord but what are your thoughts on a Facebook group or another platform do you think discord is still good for a community
Sammy Super Star: Your so right Kali!!
Dash With Ash in Canada: I think one day in the future i'd consider a Discord but I have so much growing to do on this channel first.
Sammy Super Star: The world of mouth is important
Paul Burke: thats a great point Kali
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: All that you are saying is fantastic and also applies to a good FB group. it takes time and effort and then the community will follow.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hey Ash! Great to see you.
austinator: yes Ash, Discord is a huge commitment, and it's a lot to learn in managing a server as well
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: yes!!! inspiration vs copycats and envy. I love this community because we share and empower one another.
Mommy Guide Inc: Ditto those thoughts Ana.:)
Dash With Ash in Canada: @austinator , yeah I can't commitment to that
Sammy Super Star: To be honest before Kali came to lsp almost 2 years ago it was fine but when Kali came she made the chat so much fun and made some great inside jokes that are still going on for 2 years
Paul Burke: The classic phrase...."the gardener can take care of the grass....but if the sun is blotted out because of the nuclear winter apocalypse ...the grass won't grow"
Mommy Guide Inc: So i thank Austin to the moon and back for creating and helping me with my crafty community Discord Server
Sammy Super Star: #LEDA for life
Mommy Guide Inc: LEDA and LSP - where it all started for me to learn about great community
austinator: @Mommy Guide Inc you are so welcome, I find fun in building servers, and I love experimenting because no two servers are the same
Sammy Super Star: Yes your so right
Sammy Super Star: Ohhh 😮 I might know it 😂
austinator: it's funny, I gotta say it all started with James who most of you don't know, but he showed me Paul who opened my world to all of you wonderful people
Sammy Super Star: The other group is slowly dying and nobody is their but on Online Master Mind group it is like a new born baby. 😂
Paul Burke: I tried to keep @austinator out everyone. I'm so very sorry. 🤣
Sammy Super Star: Your so right
austinator: @Paul Burke I'm persistent, you gotta try harder 🤣🤣🤣
Paul Burke: True...you can't cling
Sammy Super Star: I’m learning so much
Mommy Guide Inc: Aww Austin pls thank James for all of us! Its a great blessing to have you in our community.:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: There is enough for everyone. no worries. you want to nurture the people that love you and the rest will just be taken care of.
Paul Burke: @austinator ...thank you....it's an important lesson...just keep trying ahrder
austinator: Kali is always right about anything and everything
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: the name is so Kali (community care hero) is so beautiful and powerful too.
SiShong Victor: Q: Kali do you have CCH as ya title on your business cards?
Samantha JustInspire: I created one too, but not sure how to grow it!
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow tickled pink to have you Kali! OMG.:)
Ellie Calhoun: I want to join too Lala!
austinator: @Mommy Guide Inc do you want me to get a link for you?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Me too Lala!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks everyone. Yes pls absolutely love for you all to join us - https://discord.gg/B5bwHUGk
austinator: nope, you got it
Mommy Guide Inc: Austin did i get the link right?:) he he he
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yes!
Ellie Calhoun: Markus, all the more reason to have a pet section
Sammy Super Star: You can always photoshop you with the best
Paul Burke: take pictures of pets on the Swiss streets Markus
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: What about a "pet rock" (do you remember them?)
austinator: @Mommy Guide Inc yep, that's right
Sammy Super Star: Discord 🔥🔥🔥🔥
Sammy Super Star: True
austinator: I live on Discord 🤣🤣🤣
Sammy Super Star: I think Facebook is only good for Leda that’s mostly it
Sammy Super Star: I’m going to talk to my Business consultant Austin about using discord
BostonDonMTB: Hi Kali and Markus!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Q what about this...youtube do you think this is a way to build community as well?
Paul Burke: Markus getting the exlusives on his show!
austinator: Discord is also a minimalist's dream, it's so organized
Sammy Super Star: Just say it 😂😂
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: So if we have a FB group what is the best way to transition to Discord or just forget about Discord? and can you live stream into Discord?
Mommy Guide Inc: Absolutely! Though it took quite a while to get used to it bec like for me i was so used to FB groups already but after doing Discord its so life changing
BostonDonMTB: They will follow you wherever you are.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Sorry forgot to put a Q
SiShong Victor: Kali if you have to think about it don't say it. I never think before I speak 99.9% of the time. Not a good thing I guess
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Don!
Sammy Super Star: The good thing is I have a discord
BostonDonMTB: Hi Lala
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Discord seems so intimidating
Sandi Thompson: Hello!
Sammy Super Star: Ohh 😮 you gave me a idea
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: That is a great point, already have discord going. I have a channel but just 3 people. Need to learn more.
Mommy Guide Inc: Discord conpliments my crafty streams - everyone submits their finished output and its so easy for me to showcase their work
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Sandi!
Ellie Calhoun: what if your audience are older people? they already struggle with computer stuff and Facebook. I would be afraid to lose connection with too many people because discord is a big learning curve
austinator: Ana it does seem intimidating from the surface but it's actually not too bad, there are also a few Discord run throughs in this community I believe
Paul Burke: yeah tehre are some great tools in discord
Sammy Super Star: Movie night!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Q can we live stream from ecamm? that kind of live streaming?
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Q can you use streamyard in discord?
SiShong Victor: I used Discord for group meets before I ever heard of Zoom,
austinator: 11 watching... 11 likes... and 111 subscribers... what is happening?
Mommy Guide Inc: Ana absolutely. I felt that way in the beginning. But when Austin did a tutorial and helped set it up - now there’s no going back.
SiShong Victor: Im working now 😛
Sammy Super Star: Kali is always working me and Austin are talking about it 😂😂
Mommy Guide Inc: That’s awesome Austin! Reminds me to pls ask everyone to like this stream
austinator: yeah, Kali is a working gal
Sammy Super Star: Q: what are your thoughts should I use discord over zoom for the conference? Do you think that I should use zoom still or should I do booth for the people that want discord and the people wants zoom?
Sandi Thompson: Hey all - late again!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: @Mommy Guide Inc I did watch that episode, Austin did a great job! but I did feel like my brain was in high work mode trying to understand...im old lol
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus Discord -https://discord.gg/HXxUcfHj
Mommy Guide Inc: Austin did i get the link right for Markus?
Sammy Super Star: Yes 😂😂
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: hello @Sandi Thompson
Mommy Guide Inc: Hey Sandi!
Sammy Super Star: Bathroom life 🚽🚽🚽
austinator: @Mommy Guide Inc yup, that's right
Sammy Super Star: You need a bathroom set
Ellie Calhoun: 🤣😂🤣😂🤣Kali you are too much!
Sandi Thompson: 👋🏻
austinator: ITS SUCH A FUNNY BIT!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: TMI !!! hahaha:oops:
Ellie Calhoun: Sandi!!!
Sammy Super Star: I tell Austin that kali is drunk while in the bathroom 😂😂😂😂
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Never grow up! I"m not!
Ellie Calhoun: never too late! I was 48 when I went back to school!
austinator: a pipe dream? a plumber?
Paul Burke: that's really cool....you'd be a great teacher
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh Kali, you would be the best. I would go back to school to take that course.
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL Kali’s streaming set up - epic. The bathroom’s other purpose - streaming space.:)
Sammy Super Star: Kali you have 20 years+ you can go back to school
SiShong Victor: Only 29, I don't remember 29
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I second @Ellie Calhoun
Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Hi Markus and Kali😀😀 Nice to see you😀👍
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I'm 40 years older. haha.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh we do things like that in my workshops....
Sammy Super Star: 😂😂
austinator: I also don't remember 29... wonder why?
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: ah! to be 30 again lol
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: @austinator 🤣🤣🤣🤣
Sammy Super Star: I use to have BBQ chicken pizza while watching lsp 😂
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Alrighty then!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @Sammy and you will never be able to eat it again without thinking about this stream
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: weak stomach girl right here 🤢
Mommy Guide Inc: BBQ chicken puzza that is making me hungry now Sammy. Wish i can have that for breakfast.:)
Sammy Super Star: Wow 😯
Sammy Super Star: Blue hair is awesome
SiShong Victor: I cut most off my hair off but that's because i'm going bald.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Loved the blue
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Thank you so much for sharing that. Being vulnerable is also a part of building trust in a community. On side note, you have great hair. You are so pretty.
Sammy Super Star: I’m thinking of dying my hair to red and yellow for ketchup
John Pullum: Is Markus the first man's name you wrote on your chest?
Sammy Super Star: Oh poor kali
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Prayers for fast healing 🥰
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey John
Ellie Calhoun: Kali, Hope everything clears up soon for you
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: We all do. You are so inspiring
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi John!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @Lala I so agree with what you said?
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: @Mommy Guide Inc I was so mad at myself...I have no idea how I missed your LIVE with John...I thought it was this coming saturday at 6 am. Seriously, I need to learn to tell world time!!!
Paul Burke: ironically...reading this answer off a template
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow that’s real commitment. And it truly does Kali have that effect - personalized and it feels awesome to the recipient.:)
Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Your mails and answers are always so nice👍👍👍
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ejnar.:)
Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: It’s so much with it😀
Mommy Guide Inc: Pls dont forget to like this stream and share it as well.:)
Sammy Super Star: Can’t wait to see the new studio!!
Ellie Calhoun: we love watching and listening to you!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes absolutely yes!!!!
Sammy Super Star: Yes!! Have her back and do if sooner
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yay! yes yes....
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: yes! April is around the corner...looking forward to LEDA this year
Paul Burke: N.....I mean.....yes (phew. Nice save Paul)
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks everyone for being here with Markus and Kali!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: lol
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh Paul.... you always crack me up
Ellie Calhoun: great stream!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: That went by really quick! thank you both
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Thanks Markus & Kail and love this group. great show