Mommy Guide Inc: Yey! See you in a bit in zoom if you can! Or feel free to join us here in YT
Markus Schaub: Follow along on miro: https://miro.com/app/board/uXjVO5TgwJc=/?share_link_id=765719056347
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi everyone. I'm here but can't get into zoom. I'll be there asap.
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey! See you in awhile Janet.:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hello!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana! Can you join us in zoom?:)
Ellie Calhoun: Watching from the vet
Ellie Calhoun: Our Rooster got sick
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi everyone!
Markus Schaub: https://us02web.zoom.us/j/82706505610?pwd=VWg3WUIrd2dpb2dlL0tkRWpsMUE5UT09
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi everyone! Thanks for joining us:)
BostonDonMTB: Hello everyone
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh my. Hope everything will be better Ellie.
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh my. Hope everything will be better Ellie for your rooster:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @Ellie love the roosters. without them the sun will not come up in the morning. I hope all goes well. thinking about you all
Ellie Calhoun: Thank you 🙏🐓🐓🐓
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I second Janet Ellie, I hope all goes well, I had to take my dog to the Vet ER on monday and that was not fun. Prayers your way.
BostonDonMTB: How about Niche rather than trying to do all the formats? Which one has given you traction? Which one of the formats actually gives you "JOY"?
Ellie Calhoun: Thanks Ana... lots of waiting! Hope your dog is well.
BostonDonMTB: I know you love to interview, so I imagine you will keep doing that because that brings you "JOY".
BostonDonMTB: Just like the word "Value"
Ellie Calhoun: W: Do you have a different standard for yourself for pre/recorded vs live streaming? Are you having an expectation that pre-recorded means perfect?
Ellie Calhoun: That was supposed to be a "Q"
Ellie Calhoun: And can you do a prerecorded but not edit? Or simple edit?
BostonDonMTB: Tony: Brilliant
Ellie Calhoun: Suggestion... Prerecord but don't edit it! Or minimally edit.
Ellie Calhoun: I like the schedule idea
BostonDonMTB: Q: Off of Tony's question - Could you take that 4 hour crafting project and break it down ahead of time so people can figure out a part they could tune in for?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Don!
BostonDonMTB: Cont: You could break into smaller pieces of that project to peel off for other content.
BostonDonMTB: @Mommy Guide Inc Hi Lala.
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for that suggestion I’ll definitely try that out
Ellie Calhoun: Great ideas Janet!
Mommy Guide Inc: I am super lovin everyone’s suggestion.
BostonDonMTB: Mommy Lala Crafting Shorts
BostonDonMTB: oops Mommy Lala Crafting Mini's
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: DOC Rock did a great little show about creating a short from a live. It was so good.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: That is great advice Tony!
BostonDonMTB: Q: Just shoot for what brings you "JOY" focus on that. Pick the aspects that you don't dread doing. Focus on that.
Ellie Calhoun: Viewers hit that LIKE button!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: thanks for the reminder Ellie
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh Don thanks. Indeed editing is something I think doesn’t bring me JOY right now. But I know it’s because of my fear of not being great at it.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @Lala editing takes year to learn if one is to do it right. most people do not but do begin with basics and get better... just like live streaming.
BostonDonMTB: Lala wants to Martha Stewart. 🙂
BostonDonMTB: oops be Martha Stewart
Tina Wan Kenobi: Morning 🙂
BostonDonMTB: Q: Do you have a mailing list? Create a questionnaire to have your viewers answer questions on what content they want from you, what it is that they like about you, and other questions. Direct feedbc
Tina Wan Kenobi: Do scheduled premieres! 😁
BostonDonMTB: They watch because of you and your amazing personality.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: but the filler words are so you LALA
TonyRIversen one crazy dane: Editing your show has the rule of thumb that could take 20 to 60 minutes for each minute of finished show.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: and when you hear it from people you trust!!! so important too.
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed Ana! Thats so true i know you all understand where Inam
Mommy Guide Inc: Where I am coming from so everyone’s suggestions is so very much welcome. Thank you so much! Love you all!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Tina my friend!!! Thanks for waking up so early:)