BostonDonMTB: Sweet thumbie!!
Sammy Super Star: Hey Markus
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Markus Schaub
Sandi Thompson: Hey everybody!
BostonDonMTB: Hey Sammy, Roy, and Sandi
MySnoopy80: Hey everybody:)
Sandi Thompson: Hi everyone and Markus!
BostonDonMTB: Hey @MySnoopy80 Your boyfriend has been kicking butt with this live streaming stuff. 😀
Sandi Thompson: my favorite part!
Sandi Thompson: so fun!
MySnoopy80: @BostonDonMTB yes he has:)))
BostonDonMTB: Ever since day 1 of April LEDA when I saw his first stream. Trying to throw rolled up paper into the wastebasket.
Adam Tinkoff: Good morning!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Markus and everyone
MySnoopy80: @BostonDonMTB yeah that were the days😂
Sammy Super Star: What’s up Markus
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh good tip about titles. thanks
Paul Burke: Hey Markus....overthinking....great topic!
Adam Tinkoff: It's super cool how the LSP community helps each other. That's something special.
Tech Troublemaker: I think you are overthinking this overthinking thing.
Samantha JustInspire: Hey Markus
Adam Tinkoff: My challenge is the opposite, I start lots of projects, but blow them up after a few weeks before they have a chance to grow.
Paul Burke: good for you man...just going live...and sometimes the best conversations are the unplanned ones
Design On Brand: Hey Marcus! 👋🏻 Overthinking? Me? Never! 😁
Billy Robbins: Hiya Marcus! Glad to catch you live.
Samantha JustInspire: Wow! Awesome 👏
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh no pressure now! to go live no matter what. ha!
Billy Robbins: Great tweet from Luria 😉
Sandi Thompson: i was live on Janets channel and my internet was going in and out. We just kept going!!
Billy Robbins: Happy 1st Anniversary!
Adam Tinkoff: Yes, please. Show us!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh wow 1 year ago tomorrow. I can remember the feeling
Sandi Thompson: yes!
MySnoopy80: For sure❤️
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: you were amazing Sandi.
Design On Brand: Yes! Show us noobie streamer Marcus!
Paul Burke: did you complete the rubik cube?
Paul Burke: still lovin those stripes
Adam Tinkoff: That's awesome. Look at how you've grown and how much you've learned! Great job. Your journey is inspiring. You are a leader now!
Billy Robbins: Cov!d cuts - we all had em
Design On Brand: Fantastic use of visual aids
MySnoopy80: @bostonDonMTB 😂😂
Adam Tinkoff: What were the rules for LEDA?
Sandi Thompson: I remember that title!
Sandi Thompson: I was in awe!
Paul Burke: lil 'ol me!??? You flatter me
Paul Burke: i have a little pad of notes....that can be helpful...couple keywords
Adam Tinkoff: I keep a little Field Notes book and a pen with me at all times.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: thanks for going live today Markus. I always look forward to our time.