BravoPup Dog Training: Here I am in the front row again!
Stephy Hogan: I'll sit with ya. 🙂
Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
Stephy Hogan: Hi Sammy 🙂
Cheryl Wolf: Hey sammy and stephy
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Sandi in the front row:).
Stephy Hogan: Hi Cheryl! Hi Lala!
Seesawforit: Hey hey! I'm here for the live! Woot!
Seesawforit: (Lisa here btw, Little F
The Venture Forward: Good afternoon, good evening or good morning wherever you may be...
Stephy Hogan: 😁
Stephy Hogan: good day to you too! I have to say that to all of my clients now, I never know where they ARE
Cheryl Wolf: lala your everywhere
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Lisa @Seesawforit
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed, Hi @The Venture Forward 🙂
austinator: Markus and Paul!!!
austinator: this is gonna be great
BravoPup Dog Training: Hi @everyone!
Cheryl Wolf: Makus and Paul 🎉
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL@Cheryl Wolf - love supporting my friends:)
austinator: I feel like it's been forever since I've seen Paul
Stephy Hogan: omg
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @austinator!
The Venture Forward: intsintsintsintsints
Seesawforit: Hey Lala!
austinator: hi @Mommy Guide Inc
Seesawforit: Yessss
austinator: go Paul go!!!
Ana Zugheri: Hello 👋
The Venture Forward: awwwwwwwww yeah!
Mommy Guide Inc: Let the Improv begin:)
The Venture Forward: I heard that this is a chance that this conversation "may go off the rails."
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Ana Zugheri
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Markus Schaub!!
Mommy Guide Inc: I definitely agree @The Venture Forward - with @Paul and Markus together - everything and anything is possible:)
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Lala!
The Venture Forward: Learned those dance moves from one lifespert Turner Stone ™️
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Markus Schaub and @Paul Burke:)
Ana Zugheri: Lala!!! 🎉
Inspirational Connection TV: Hey Markus
BravoPup Dog Training: Buckle up! Here we go!!!!!
Inspirational Connection TV: Love the music
Inspirational Connection TV: Hello mommy laly
Ana Zugheri: This is going to be fun!!
The Venture Forward: and we're live!
Inspirational Connection TV: Mommy Lala
Seesawforit: Hey hey!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Hi Roy @Tech Troublemaker
Cheryl Wolf: Yes fun !
Mommy Guide Inc: HI Samantha @Inspirational Connection TV
austinator: Paul is an amazing Improv teacher, even if he never gets to do the Online ones much anymore
Sarah | Small Changes: MARKUS!!!
Ana Zugheri: That was a workout 🏋️‍♀️ loved the dancing
The Venture Forward: (applause)
Cheryl Wolf: 🎊
Inspirational Connection TV: Hello Paul
Mommy Guide Inc: I agree @austinator, I've been in his Improv Virtual classes:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Sarah | Small Changes
Ana Zugheri: I love Paul’s voice
Mommy Guide Inc: Paul Burke on Youtube:https://www.youtube.com/user/mithough...
Cheryl Wolf: love your kitty's
austinator: Scribs!!!
The Venture Forward: Paul's voice is indeed amazing... especially in person.
Mommy Guide Inc: ooh I thought there was an earthquake. It was a cat quake:)
Ana Zugheri: Cat 🐱 quake 😂
David W. Ryan: Hi Markus and Paul!
Seesawforit: Catquake! lol @Mommy Guide Inc
Inspirational Connection TV: Cat quate. Lol
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @David W. Ryan
David W. Ryan: Hi @Mommy Guide Inc
austinator: !catfacts
Mommy Guide Inc: I was really scared the first day of Improv Class but that went away the window the minute Paul started the Improv Class
austinator: !redeem corgi
The Venture Forward: ✅ question answered.
Inspirational Connection TV: Hey @Ana Zugheri, saw you in another stream checked out your channel, you got a sub! Will be supporting you!
Mark Thomas: Is Improv is about being comfortable disclosing and dropping the barriers we put around ourselves
Cheryl Wolf: Story telling is an Art , I need work on !
Mommy Guide Inc: Please don't forget to hit the like button:)
The Venture Forward: Q: what is your favorite Whose Line game, or any improv game in general?
BravoPup Dog Training: I've done Pauls improv class 2 or 3 times. It was a blast! (signed up for next week too)
austinator: oh yeah, I was extremely nervous when I did my first Improv... but I was also the first one because I'd rather be early than late and Paul and I had a little chat, him basically calming me down
Mommy Guide Inc: Please put a "Q" in front of your question so Markus can see it fsster:)
Ana Zugheri: @inspirational connection thank you 😊
austinator: @The Venture Forward, mine is 5 things
Sara S: Wasn’t notified. Oh well.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Sara S:)
The Venture Forward: Sara!! how are ya?
Cheryl Wolf: Sara!
Sarah | Small Changes: I love a good tangent ❤️
The Venture Forward: Like. Comment. Subscribe. Ring! That! Bell!
austinator: I love Tangents and Secents and Cosines
Mommy Guide Inc: Paul Burke on Youtube:https://www.youtube.com/user/mithough...
Seesawforit: Q: I'm all about making others shine. what is the place for the "straight man" in improv. Subtle humor too small?
Sara S: @Mommy Guide Inc. fine. Eating lunch . That’s what kind of day it’s been.
The Venture Forward: I'm a big fan of "Questions Only"
austinator: I still need to teach @Paul Burke the 5 things song
Seesawforit: I love singing in small ensembles for the same reason. The connection.
austinator: Markus, not having a guest will come sooner than your prepared for, thanks to Paul with Improv and thanks to LSP with LEDA my first time alone I wasn't extremely nervous
Mark Thomas: I love the way you say your not a strong singer rather than LI can’t sing. Andy Halper must be the improv singer of NY
The Venture Forward: The straight man in a game of "Party Quirks" usually is the one that generates the "matter of fact" funny lines as they are guessing the other's quirks.
Cheryl Wolf: Old show , The odd couple was great at that
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Mark Thomas - absolutely agree about @Andy
Sara S: @The Venture Forward- up since 2:30, breakfast at 5, meditation, nap 7-8:20, going ever since. Eating lunch now😂
The Venture Forward: We are always about breaking the fourth wall... whether doing a show or doing improv... what have you.
The Venture Forward: dayum @Sara S !!
Cheryl French: Hey guys! So glad I didn’t miss the whole thing!
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow @Sara S up since 2:30am? great that you had a nap:)
Ana Zugheri: Q what do you do if when the audience participantion goes wrong? Like someone gets offended…what do you do to bring it back to funny?
Seesawforit: Moving through the thought like meditation. Deep Thoughts with Live Streaming.
The Venture Forward: You can dance if you want to, you can leave your friends behind
austinator: I don't Dance... *flashbacks to my Freshman Christmas concert*
austinator: concert? I meant Christmas Program?
Cheryl French: Yeah, but you’re a charming singer!
austinator: idk what it's called
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed @Improv class with @Paul Burke helped me with my streaming. I learned to relax. and just go with the flow:)
Sara S: Hi @Cheryl French! Where’ve you been 😉
BravoPup Dog Training: I've done Pauls improv class a few times. It was really helpful and a blast (signed up for next week too)!
Mark Thomas: We are our own worse critics
Mommy Guide Inc: @austinator what happened in Freshman Christmas concert?:)
Sara S: I do that with everything. Eeeek. Time to move. Or die. Or something.
Mommy Guide Inc: @BravoPup Dog Training - totally agree! There is another virtual class next week - will be there for sure:). another 2am class for me:)
austinator: @Mommy Guide Inc... I embarrassed myself in front of the entire school
Seesawforit: @Sara S when you played guitar and sang I was literally jumping and OMGing in my office. So good.
BravoPup Dog Training: @Mommy Guide Inc - i'll see you there! Already signed up!!
Sarah | Small Changes: Q: Do you think people don't realise how much of our lives are improv and its not just who's line is it anyway?
Seesawforit: @austinator Solidarity! I did that once too. Voice just stopped mid song. It was hard to get back on the horse the next time.
Mark Thomas: What’s that show with the Jewish American comedienne? She was great at improve and managing the heckles from the audience
Sara S: @seesawforit that was a huge kill me now moment.
Seesawforit: It was so. good.
David W. Ryan: Clowns doing the crucifixion. They really should have given that a second thought!
Ana Zugheri: Yes 👍
Sarah | Small Changes: Thats my entire parenting strategy right there 🤣
Mark Thomas: Mrs Maisel - watching her was like watching rehearsed improv 😂
Julie Ulrich: yay so good to see you guys! I'm late but i'm here 🙂
Sarah | Small Changes: JULIE!!!
ConsistentAsh: hey everyone!
Mommy Guide Inc: awww that must have been hard @austinator. but you are very confident now:)
Sarah | Small Changes: ASH!!
Sara S: I think “be curious “ is fabulous advice for life, period.
ConsistentAsh: Hey Sarah! how's it going @
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Julie Ulrich Hi Ash @ConsistentAsh
ConsistentAsh: ?*
David W. Ryan: Hey @Julie Ulrich
Sara S: Hi @Julie Ulrich!
ConsistentAsh: Hey Mommy Lala
Seesawforit: Agreed @Sara S . Being curious opens so many doors.
John Venturini: Being curious is being inquisitive and wanting to learn -- as long as we continue to learn, we stay the most optimal.
Sara S: Truth. Beginners Mind.
Lynn Clementi: Hi Friends!!
Sara S: Hey Lynn!
Sarah | Small Changes: Bahahahaha me too Paul 🦈
Julie Ulrich: @Sarah | Small Changes @Mommy Guide Inc @David W. Ryan @Sara S love you guys!
BravoPup Dog Training: @Julie Ulrich - hi!
David W. Ryan: yes and...
John Venturini: Blurry Paul ™️
David W. Ryan: Paul is now in witness protection
John Venturini: The DMV
Julie Ulrich: location: Pluto
Sarah | Small Changes: AUSTRALIA 🇦🇺
Mark Thomas: Hawaii
Seesawforit: Location: witness protection
BravoPup Dog Training: location: a bar bathroom.
Ana Zugheri: I second DMV
David W. Ryan: Behind an abandoned K-Mart
Sarah | Small Changes: Probably couldn't get into Australia right now 🤣
Ana Zugheri: Lol
BravoPup Dog Training: @David W. Ryan - LOL!!
ConsistentAsh: I love how they both have the purple going on 😍
Sara S: @Bravo pup dog training— that’s a Kali idea
Ana Zugheri: 😂
Mommy Guide Inc: Back to the Future feels:)
Julie Ulrich: this is amazing
Ana Zugheri: I love this!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes you're still good Paul. Audio is still on point:)
BravoPup Dog Training: @Sara S - a dingy and gross bathroom in a bar.
David W. Ryan: Paul went back in time and he's on a dial-up connection
Ana Zugheri: Streaming life!
Julie Ulrich: Paul goes so fast he's blurry
Seesawforit: @David W. Ryan lolol
ConsistentAsh: My dad had hair on his head as a younger man and now he doesn't haha
Mommy Guide Inc: @Ash LOL
Ana Zugheri: 😂
Mark Thomas: Love it
Julie Ulrich: omg 🤣
ConsistentAsh: You two are a bunch of fun lol
Mark Thomas: Nail bar
David W. Ryan: air traffic controller
Julie Ulrich: operating room
Sarah | Small Changes: Surgeons
Sara S: Nuclear bunker
Ana Zugheri: Markus you are good at that!!! So fast thinking
John Venturini: A circumcision.
Mommy Guide Inc: location - IT Help Desk!
ConsistentAsh: LOL John!
BravoPup Dog Training: back ally in a bad neighborhood.
ConsistentAsh: No, just pick one hahahah
ConsistentAsh: We are waiting for more fun 😛
John Venturini: ❤ 👍
Mommy Guide Inc: Improv Class is super awesome. Paul have classes and one is coming up soon.
Ana Zugheri: And people like when they hear their names…shout outs
Mommy Guide Inc: Paul Burke on Youtube:https://www.youtube.com/user/mithough...
Ana Zugheri: 😂😂😂
John Venturini: M
Cheryl Wolf: N
BravoPup Dog Training: N
Julie Ulrich: W
Seesawforit: P
Ana Zugheri: M
Ana Zugheri: 🤣🤣🤣🤣😂😂😂😂😂
Cheryl Wolf: markus laughing makes me laugh!
John Venturini: lol quasimoto
Seesawforit: lolol
Ana Zugheri: I thought it was with a k 🤣
BravoPup Dog Training: hahahahahahaha!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: aaah! Xylophones! LOL
Cheryl Wolf: zoom
Mark Thomas: My sides hurt
Ana Zugheri: 😂
Ana Zugheri: 👏👏👏
David W. Ryan: that was great
Sarah | Small Changes: Quasimoto 🤣🤣
John Venturini: 👏👏👏
Julie Ulrich: look at Markus improving!! 👏👏👏
Julie Ulrich: i meant improvising!
Ana Zugheri: That’s good 👍
BravoPup Dog Training: @Julie Ulrich - he's also improving!
Mark Thomas: I e just noticed- your both purple
Ana Zugheri: Be your unique you
Mark Thomas: People think you’re fun - ooh you could take that so any ways 😀
John Venturini: I think you'll manifest a best seller. #secret
Mark Thomas: Suspending judgement is such a wonderful way to be. I’ve learnt a lot from watching you two ❤️
BravoPup Dog Training: I'm signed up!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey - virtual IMPROV classes are back!
John Venturini: 9 ET / 6 PT
Mommy Guide Inc: yey - perfect time finally for me!!
Julie Ulrich: yay more zoom improv classes!
Ana Zugheri: What is that central time?
Seesawforit: Sleepless Markus = funny Markus?
John Venturini: 9 ET / 8 CT / 7 MT / 6 PT 🙂
Sarah | Small Changes: isn't every Markus Sleepless 🤣
Sarah | Small Changes: JV where my time at?
Inspirational Connection TV: So we’re watching 2 streams at the same time @ConsistentAsh
Ana Zugheri: Sign me up for that!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: https://www.improvwithpaul.com/what-i-do
BravoPup Dog Training: sign up you guys!! I'll be there!
Julie Ulrich: Paul is the best improv teacher. I highly recommend the zoom class 🙂
Mommy Guide Inc: https://www.improvwithpaul.com
John Venturini: Australian Central Standard Time @Sarah | Small Changes ? 🙂
Nourish Hive: I just wanted to jump in and say Hello
John Venturini: 10:30am the next morning ACST... lol (head in hands)
Mommy Guide Inc: wow time flew by so fast!
BravoPup Dog Training: Thaks!!
Nourish Hive: Ah I just caught the end.
Seesawforit: Loved this live so much!
Mommy Guide Inc: thanks so much @Markus and @Paul!
Seesawforit: Have a great one everybody!