Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Markus! Hi Heather!
Mommy Guide Inc: I beat Sandi for front row seats today:) LOL
Sandi Thompson: Damn, you beat me Lala!!
Sandi Thompson: Ho Markus, Heather and Lala!
Sandi Thompson: 'Hi' - not Ho -lol!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Sandi Thompson! Indeed only for today I am first:). LOL. Loving your videos by the way.:) Keep it up. You are an inspiration.
Stephanie Gieseke: Heeeeeeey!!!!
Sandi Thompson: @Mommy Guide Inc - thank you so much!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Stephanie! Hello!
Sandi Thompson: Hi Stephanie!!
Stephanie Gieseke: Hi Lala!! Hi Sandi!
Sarah | Small Changes: MARKUS!!!
Sandi Thompson: SARAH!
Stephanie Gieseke: Hey Sarah
Mommy Guide Inc: Love this countdown music...Howdy Sarah!
Sarah | Small Changes: STEPHANIE!! LALA!! SANDI!!!
Sarah | Small Changes: HEATHER!!!
Stephanie Gieseke: Markus!!! Heather!!
Stephanie Gieseke: Darn…I didn’t get VIP seats for today 😫
Caleb McDonald: Hellooooo!
Sandi Thompson: CALEB!!
Caleb McDonald: Hi SANDI! 😁
Mommy Guide Inc: wow Congratulations Markus for another milestone. Hi Caleb!
Dwain Woode MD: Markus!!!! I’m catching you live!!!!
Stephanie Gieseke: CALEB!!!!!!
Caleb McDonald: Hi Lala!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Heather in the house! https://linktr.ee/turningscenes
Caleb McDonald: STEPHANIE!!! 🦆 🦆 ✋🏻 👋🏻
Stephanie Gieseke: I am such a dork. I was just clapping and I realized no one could hear me 😀
Sarah | Small Changes: @Stephanie Gieseke I do that all the time!! and I dance to the countdown timer
Stephanie Gieseke: Fellow career bouncer here too!
Sandi Thompson: me too!
Caleb McDonald: Heather, I really like your box in the corner with the blue lighting coming through! Kinda looks like a droid of some sort. 🤖 💯
Stephanie Gieseke: Shhhhhh…she doesn’t want people to know what she’s hiding in that box 🤫
Mommy Guide Inc: Heather's audio is on point! love it!
Caleb McDonald: Also, your shirt! Rebels FTW
Paul Burke: SARAH! MARKUS HEATHER! STEPHANIE! CALEB! SANDI! LALA!
Sammy Super Star: Hey Everyone!]
Sandi Thompson: PAUL!
Sandi Thompson: SAMMY!
Stephanie Gieseke: PAUL!!! SAMMY!!
Paul Burke: SAMMY!
Sarah | Small Changes: @Paul Burke Did you take a deep breath before you sent that comment 🤣
Stephanie Gieseke: Sarah - you know he totally did!!
Paul Burke: hahaha....yep @Sarah | Small Changes ...I needed all my energy
Mommy Guide Inc: And now we have @Paul Burke and @Sammy Super Star in the house:) Hi to you both:)
Caleb McDonald: OMG PAUL!! SO MUCH YELLING… *insert Will Farrell meme* WE ARE LAUGHING..!
Caleb McDonald: Yes, agree Lala, audio is on point. 👌🏻
Paul Burke: Q - Heather....question....do you have a favorite client you've helped tell their story? one student you remember when they had a big breakthru
Stephanie Gieseke: Stephanie’s story: beginning - she was a weird child, middle - she was still weird and strange early in her career, now - I AM STILL WEIRD AND LOOOOOVE IT!!
Efrain Valles: Love this pair
Paul Burke: Q - Heather...did you see Lamb? What's your Roma Review?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Efrain Valles!
Caleb McDonald: Most common thing in movie trailers these days are that epic bass drop sound throughout it… *Boooom*
Efrain Valles: Hello Lala :)
Mommy Guide Inc: We super love the "weird" Stephanie yesterday today and tomorrow!
Stephanie Gieseke: I wish they made trailers that just showed the ending. I always want to know how a movie ends before I commit time to watch it
Stephanie Gieseke: THANKS LALA!!
Caleb McDonald: That’ll be the worst Stephanie!! 😆
Mommy Guide Inc: Gosh me too Stephanie. I do that with a book too! We are weird this way. LOL
Stephanie Gieseke: Yes Lala!! I do that same thing with books too!
Caleb McDonald: Imagine finding out Bruce Willis is a ghost in Six Sense! *spoiler alert* 😅
Sarah | Small Changes: @Stephanie Gieseke , @Mommy Guide Inc Me too!! If it has a sad ending I'm out!
Caleb McDonald: Who are you ending spoiler people… “how dare you!”
Stephanie Gieseke: Caleb…it’s the only way to live. Ending spoilers are awesome
Caleb McDonald: Sarah is always googling stuff about movies and shows while we watch. 🙈
Mommy Guide Inc: Don't forget to smash the like button for tonight. And to follow Heather at https://linktr.ee/turningscenes
Sarah | Small Changes: I need to know everything will be okay ❤️I also only listen to solved true crime 🤣
Stephanie Gieseke: If you don’t have your phone out while watching a show or movie to google stuff…are you even human?
Efrain Valles: Heather and Markus in one frame is absolute bliss...
David W. Ryan: Talk nerdy to me!
Caleb McDonald: 🤣
Sandi Thompson: 🤣
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @David W. Ryan!
Stephanie Gieseke: Markus is a people magnet!!!
Sarah | Small Changes: Q: Do you think now that there is so much saturation across different platforms we will see a move away from big numbers and towards finding the right people for your niche?
Mommy Guide Inc: Totally agree - community engagement in the virtual realm. @Markus Schaub is great at it:)
David W. Ryan: HI @Mommy Guide Inc
Caleb McDonald: The story force is strong with this one
Mommy Guide Inc: A subniche to separate one from the rest. Awesome:)
Caleb McDonald: Q: how do your clients feel about getting their own personal story weaved into their business/branding?
Mommy Guide Inc: whoa - awesome list of cinematic gurus!
Efrain Valles: Heather is a great Guru !!!!
Efrain Valles: so is Markus!!!
Caleb McDonald: Also, that’s a JUMBO 🥤!! Which begs the question…. What’s in it? 😏
SamanthaJustInspire: Hey Markus
SamanthaJustInspire: Hi Heather
Sarah | Small Changes: @SamanthaJustInspire 👋🏻
SamanthaJustInspire: Mommy Lala hello, and Sarah how are you?
Sarah | Small Changes: Doesn't Luria not watch movies? 🤣
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @SamanthaJustInspire!
Mommy Guide Inc: If you want to learn more about Heather's program https://linktr.ee/turningscenes
David W. Ryan: It's a really great approach.
Tech Troublemaker: Yes, I need to storyboard out my videos.
Tech Troublemaker: hard to do for a live stream though. 😛
Tech Troublemaker: @Sarah | Small Changes Luria lived in a very strict environment growing up and so she has commented that she isn't up on all pop culture because of it.
Mommy Guide Inc: HI Roy@Tech Troublemaker. I actually like how you unpack your livestreams:)
Colorful Delights: Hi Markus & Heather! Great topic.
Colorful Delights: Hi @Mommy Guide Lala! Good morning
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ms. Rams@Colorful Delights 🙂 So nice to see yo here on the chat! Welcome:)
Tech Troublemaker: @Mommy Guide Inc Hey Lala, wow good really really really too early morning.
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL @Tech Troublemaker indeed I am a super early riser every Friday mornings:).
Efrain Valles: Amazing layout by heather!
Colorful Delights: Yeah thanks! Still awake at 4:30am 😊 I would rather listenb
Efrain Valles: Q: How does consistency fall into storytelling, does the story evolve as the work happens?
SamanthaJustInspire: Hey Roy, and color delights, how are you?
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Stephanie Gieseke
Tech Troublemaker: @SamanthaJustInspire I am great so far. How about you?
Mommy Guide Inc: Brand recognition via great story telling. that's awesome:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Let's go hit that like button:)
SamanthaJustInspire: I’m trying to understand Instagram too and niche too
SamanthaJustInspire: I am well thanks for asking
Caleb McDonald: Q: if you could only ever watch/have one sci-fi/geeky movie/show, what would it be? (I.e if you’re on an island with no wifi and can only have one…) 🤔
Tech Troublemaker: I still do not know my niche. I want to help others through what I do.
Colorful Delights: Hi @Samantha! No sleep yet. Listening to this talk for my channel apart from crafting with Mommy Lala.
Paul Burke: really interesting conversation 🙂
Sandi Thompson: @Caleb McDonald : The Good The Bad and the Ugly.
Efrain Valles: I tend to do what I love, so that I can love what I do...
Caleb McDonald: Sandi… I haven’t even seen that… 🙈 I might have to now…
Sarah | Small Changes: @Caleb McDonald Ready Player One ❤️or Ghostbusters
SamanthaJustInspire: This is good Heather,
Efrain Valles: @Sarah | Small Changes both are my faves
Sandi Thompson: @Caleb McDonald - Spaghetti Western from 1960's
Caleb McDonald: Social media posting is a pain and something that I haven’t gotten a hold of yet for a business. 🤔
David W. Ryan: Legos can be challenging
Caleb McDonald: “Pop into others streams” for a second Heather I thought you said “I have to pop into others dreams…” wow, that’s next level marketing! 😆
Thomas Schocher: 👍🙏
Ellie Calhoun: I'm here!!!
Sandi Thompson: Bats with cats talking about their ailments!🤣🤣
Caleb McDonald: Q: are you planning to implement more live streaming/vod into your own business strategy in the near future?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Ellie Calhoun! Hi @Thomas Schocher
Mommy Guide Inc: great plans Heather!
Ellie Calhoun: One on one is awesome with you. You are so not intimidating and easy going with great guidance!
Ellie Calhoun: That being said, a course someone can do on their own gives you more passive income
Sarah | Small Changes: Q: Do you think some of the art of story telling is lost in todays post it all society?
Caleb McDonald: Balance is so hard in todays world, but necessary to master. Still learning…
Cheryl French: Hey Markus and Heather! Coming in late!
Caleb McDonald: “Everything is awesome” - Lego Movie. Lies! 😆
Ana Zugheri: Hi just jumping to say hi 👋
Ana Zugheri: Can’t wait to catch the replay
Sarah | Small Changes: This has been such an amazing stream ❤️
BostonDonMTB: @Sarah | Small Changes I think you are right about the storytelling being lost, because it is now in little pieces with the posts. Quick snippets of part of a story.
Sarah | Small Changes: @BostonDonMTB YES!!! Its one thought or moment.. not a story
Paul Burke: @BostonDonMTB and @Sarah | Small Changes...it's slmost microstories now...little blips
Caleb McDonald: Heather, after you talking about Canva a while ago that I heard about for the first time, I saw a giant ad for it at the airport!! What a the chances… cue creepy advertising from The Minority Report.
BostonDonMTB: @Sarah | Small Changes It is not really fulfilling to not have the full story. It is a quick ships passing in the night rather than story telling by the campsite fire.
BostonDonMTB: @Markus Schaub You are killing it. 🙂
BostonDonMTB: As is @heatherroma
Sandi Thompson: so long everyone! Thanks Markus and Heather!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Ana Zugheri
Caleb McDonald: Great stream MARKUS and HEATHER!
Sarah | Small Changes: Thanks so much guys ❤️