Awesome Wood Things: Woot! Woot!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yeah! I really love this music!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Matt! Hi Roy!
Sandi Thompson: hi everyone!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hey John & Markus! I think I can do Markus dance groove now.
Sarah | Small Changes: MARKUS!!! JOHN!!!
Sarah | Small Changes: Fresh Cuts Markus 😉
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Lala!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Sanidi and Sara!
Magic Flyin Potato: Hey Hello everyone
Tech Troublemaker: Hey John!!!
MySnoopy80: Hi Markus
MySnoopy80: ❤️❤️❤️
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Magic Flyin Potato!
Sarah | Small Changes: Hi Moni ❤️
Magic Flyin Potato: @Mommy Guide Inc Hey there! Hope you are doing well today
BostonDonMTB: Hey Markus and John!
MySnoopy80: SARAH❤️
Mommy Guide Inc: yey we have a VI{ in the audience:). HI @MySnoopy80
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Sarah!!
MySnoopy80: LALA❤️
Sandi Thompson: love the collar John!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @BostonDonMTB !
BostonDonMTB: Hi @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: John Pullum (https://pullum.com)
Sarah | Small Changes: YES!! Examples 🙏🏻
Cheryl French: Hey Markus and John!
Sarah | Small Changes: He the people and animal whisperer
Paul Burke: GENTLEMEN!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Cheryl French 🙂
Sarah | Small Changes: PAUL! CHERYL!
Paul Burke: SARAH!
Cheryl French: Hi Lala, Paul, Sarah, Sandi and everyone!
Paul Burke: John...how many dogs did you save today?? My guess is 17
Cheryl French: People pleaser?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hey @Paul Burke \
Paul Burke: Hey Cheryl!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Paul!!
Paul Burke: hey @Mommy Guide Inc !
Cheryl French: Both genuinely good guys!
Paul Burke: hey @Tech Troublemaker
SuzanCz: hey friends!
Magic Flyin Potato: 👍
Sarah | Small Changes: ❤
Mommy Guide Inc: 🥰
Magic Flyin Potato: 😂
Tech Troublemaker: I am in the Markus fan club. 😀
BostonDonMTB: He is awesome! That very first day of crumpling up paper and throwing it into the waste basket I was sold. I just had to convince him he was going to kill it.
SuzanCz: How are you today, John?
MySnoopy80: 🥰
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @SuzanCz!
SuzanCz: @BostonDonMTB Are you actually in Boston?
SuzanCz: hey Lala! @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: Definitely part of that Fan c
BostonDonMTB: Yeah, it is Don from LEDA. 😀
Mommy Guide Inc: Definitely part of the Markus Fan Club there with you Roy!
SuzanCz: @BostonDonMTB Ahhhhhhh..... cool! I was about to say that I'm in the area, but you probably already knew that. 😉
BostonDonMTB: @SuzanCz I do. LOL
SuzanCz: Oh yeah. People love to hear their names. it triggers something in their head.
BostonDonMTB: @SuzanCz It also freaks them out, because they forget that they are wearing their name tags.
Siri Knows: G’day mates
SuzanCz: @BostonDonMTB Haha! yeah...
ConsistentAsh: Markus and John 🙂
SuzanCz: I used to go to a restaurant where the owner knew me. He would make a point of stopping by to say hi... and that got me great customer service! It was lovely.
SuzanCz: SARAH!
ConsistentAsh: Hanging out with John Ryan ? John you haven't been keeping up hahah
Sarah | Small Changes: SIRI!! SUZAN!!
Magic Flyin Potato: It's hard to remember "Channel Names" as the person if we don't use our real name. John made me jump when he said "BRAD!" at the start 😂😂
BostonDonMTB: You use names to make connections.
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed as simple as calling somebody by their names can create an awesome positive effect on our audience and customers
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ash@ConsistentAsh
ConsistentAsh: Addressing my lovelies is always a priority for me
ConsistentAsh: Hey Mommy Lala!
SuzanCz: There's a song in here: "Say my name. Say my name." #popculture (Name that group!)
Kali Co: @SuzanCz destiny's child! when no one is around you say baby i love youuuu
ConsistentAsh: TLC lol
SuzanCz: @ConsistentAsh I know a few folks who use "my lovelies". I love it!
Tech Troublemaker: So many of my favorite people on here.
Kali Co: hey 🤗
ConsistentAsh: No wait lol Destiny lol
Kali Co: breaking bad is great too. definitely a different vibe from destiny's child
SuzanCz: @Kali Co You win! I knew you'd know. ,3
SuzanCz: ❤
Mommy Guide Inc: Hey Kali!
ConsistentAsh: @SuzanCz , yeah it's my default. everyone is my lovlies lol
Kali Co: @SuzanCz ❤
Kali Co: @Mommy Guide Inc hey lala!!
ConsistentAsh: lovelies*
Magic Flyin Potato: Loved Breaking Bad. Watched it years after it was over and didn't realize what I was missing when it was still on
SuzanCz: @ConsistentAsh it's a loving statement! I like it a lot.
SuzanCz: We have Aldi here
Kali Co: @SuzanCz i love that song but i say "chicken waaang chicken waaaang"
Sarah | Small Changes: I have an insane memory which has been super helpful for live streaming and building community 😂
SuzanCz: Hahaha! @Kali Co I love it!
Cheryl French: There are a lot of holy scriptures in various religions where people are “called by name”. It’s a very deep need people have.
Kali Co: @Sarah | Small Changes i bet!!!
Cheryl French: To be seen…
Sarah | Small Changes: @Magic Flyin Potato Me Too! Now I love Better Call Saul even more
SuzanCz: @Sarah that will serve you for sure!
BostonDonMTB: @Sarah | Small Changes Yes, having a memory is quite helpful creating those connection to your community.
Ejnar Riis Hansen: Hi Markus and John😀👍
Mommy Guide Inc: and then we have @Ejnar Riis Hansen!
Magic Flyin Potato: I started watching it but then went to Germany for 5 years so it was not easy to keep up on a lot of shows
Sarah | Small Changes: EJNAR!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh I super love that video @John Pullum
Magic Flyin Potato: I did watch the Netflix show that gave closure for Jesse. El Comino? I think it was
Kali Co: i'm working so i gotta run but wanted to jump in and say YOU'RE AMAZING MARKUS!!! and of course john and all beautiful peeps in chat 🤗❤️ love you guys!
Sarah | Small Changes: Love ya Kali!
Mommy Guide Inc: aww thanks so much Kali! Enjoy the rest of the day.
SuzanCz: I do the same thing. An old friend wanted to talk to me about something and I was like: About what? It was cool in the end but my first thought was MLM. 😂
SuzanCz: See ya, @Kali Co ❤
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow that's powerful @John Pullulm. INdeed we never know who will be impacted by our words - so we should be intentional about what we say or do towards another person - kindness wins!
Tech Troublemaker: You just don't know what people are going through and you should never add negative to it.
Ellie Calhoun: Tuning in a little late! Hello everyone!
SuzanCz: I moved from Phili to Montana. I'm walking down the sidewalk in Missoula and someone said hi and I was like - WHAT DO THEY WANT? 😳 😂
SuzanCz: Hey @Ellie Calhoun!
Sandi Thompson: hey Ellie!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hey @Ellie Calhoun:).
Ejnar Riis Hansen: 🤗 hello Mommy and Sarah and all you other fantastic people👋
Sandi Thompson: John Pullum (https://pullum.com)
SuzanCz: Hi @Ejnar Riis Hansen
SuzanCz: People love being seen and noticed!
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed did John Say @thank you cards? Totally absolutely agree! A personalized form of appreciation like a nice "thank you" card is alway a great thing
Ejnar Riis Hansen: Hi @Suzan😀 Nice to see you👍👍
Sarah | Small Changes: I pride myself on sending the most perfect gifs for Birthdays and Thank you's ❤️
Sarah | Small Changes: @Sandi Thompson is brilliant 🙌🏻
Sandi Thompson: good lord! thank you!
Mommy Guide Inc: Absolutely @Sandi Thompson's short videos are super engaging and funny:)
SuzanCz: Oh wait. Homework?
Sandi Thompson: thanks everyone!😍🤩
Sandi Thompson: John has made me little videos ... I love it!! Makes me feel special!
Tech Troublemaker: It's the show within the show.
SuzanCz: @Tech Troublemaker truth!
Sarah | Small Changes: @Tech Troublemaker is the inception 😂
SuzanCz: @Sarah | Small Changes I always try to keep my gif game on point. So fun to find the exact right one.
Sarah | Small Changes: @SuzanCz I'm sure people appreciate our dedication to the art of GIFs
SuzanCz: @Sandi Thompson I've never received one. He likes you more! 😭
SuzanCz: @Sarah | Small Changes Haha! They just don't know our dedication!
Tech Troublemaker: Pat Flynn mentioned the idea in his book Super Fans, but it didn't really click until @johnpullum said something about it.
Sandi Thompson: haha @SuzanCz: i'm probably just more screwed up than you!
Cheryl French: Too late to cut it!
Magic Flyin Potato: John is so awesome. During the Owen Video fund raiser I saw some guy in chat saying "Magic Flyin Potato" needs to win something. Give "Magic Flyin Potato" something. I was like who is the guy? LOL
Magic Flyin Potato: That's how I met John was after that fund raiser
Sarah | Small Changes: John re-edited a video to help me and constantly trouble shoots things with me... He is the REAL deal!!
SuzanCz: @Sandi Thompson Haha! I doubt it.
Mommy Guide Inc: wow that's a great tip John - share testimonial videos:)
Tech Troublemaker: John and Markus both are so amazing. Both have helped me on different things. So awesome.
SuzanCz: "If I don't get the gig, I send them a bag of poop." &lt;&lt; what John's really thinking
Sarah | Small Changes: @Markus Schaub has also helped me at all hours of the night 🙈 2 of the best guys in the business
SuzanCz: (I joke!)
SuzanCz: @Sarah | Small Changes I agree! They're both amazing!
Mommy Guide Inc: "Know your customer / audience
Mommy Guide Inc: My "personalized
Mommy Guide Inc: My "personalized" handmade products are always super salable specially during the holidays. People really love small acts of kindness.
Magic Flyin Potato: 😂
Sandi Thompson: 🤣
Tech Troublemaker: You used to be able to mail children via US Mail.
Sarah | Small Changes: @Markus Schaub random take aways are my favourite part of the show 🤣
Mommy Guide Inc: Cards - Markus - I do! and make tons of them. LOL. Let's revive card making and giving:)
BostonDonMTB: I sent ransom notes and ransom videos to MTV trying to get a VJ get back in the 80's.
Mommy Guide Inc: oooh almost Thanksgiving for most of you:)
BostonDonMTB: oops get = gig
Tech Troublemaker: @BostonDonMTB hahaha
Sandi Thompson: John Pullum (https://pullum.com)
Sarah | Small Changes: Such a great stream guys! I gotta take kids to school ❤️
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Sara. Awesome inputs here today as well. Do take care and enjoy the rest of the day:)
Paul Burke: I've been lurkin and enjoying the stream guys
MySnoopy80: Bye Sarah have a nice day❤️
Mommy Guide Inc: join us on @Online Video Mastermind Group (OVMG) at Facebook
Mommy Guide Inc: Join us @Streamer Accelerator too!
Ejnar Riis Hansen: Hi @Paul Burke 😀👋
Sandi Thompson: yeah - that was frightening when i didnt realize i was live. So glad i didnt scratch my butt!
Cheryl French: Sandi! 🤣
Cheryl French: Sandi obviously spends a lot of time with dogs!
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh my @Sandi Thompson during my countdown last show I didn't know the mic was not muted - I was singing! shocked when I watched on replay.
MySnoopy80: Im ready@johnpollum
Mommy Guide Inc: OMG!!!! That was super awesome!!!
BostonDonMTB: That was crazy.
BostonDonMTB: It did.
Magic Flyin Potato: Yep lol
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes I ended up with that smiley face!
Cheryl French: It worked!
Tech Troublemaker: I had to Google what Tacos were first. 😜
Mommy Guide Inc: 😊😍 totally
Magic Flyin Potato: 😁
Ejnar Riis Hansen: LEDA is a great experience 😀👍
Tech Troublemaker: LEDA rocks!
Sandi Thompson: LEDA changed my life!
Mommy Guide Inc: LEDA - forever grateful for it! I met so many of you there!
Billy Robbins: LEDA is a special opportunity
Cheryl French: Sure is!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Billy Robbins!
Billy Robbins: Hello, hello! @Mommy Guide Inc
Cheryl French: Relatability is everything!
Ejnar Riis Hansen: Luria and Livestreaming Pros, changed my life in so many ways especially LEDA. It was such a coincidence I come across her channel, searching for camera setup😀😀 I am so happy that happened. 😀😀
Sandi Thompson: John Pullum (https://pullum.com)
Mommy Guide Inc: John - you walk the talk. Thank you so much!
Magic Flyin Potato: Thanks so much Markus and John
Cheryl French: Yep, he sure does!
Cheryl French: Thanks guys!
Tech Troublemaker: I would like it more but there is only one like button. 😞
Mommy Guide Inc: https://www.youtube.com/c/JohnPullum
Mommy Guide Inc: https://www.facebook.com/groups/onlinevideomastermindgroup
Mommy Guide Inc: Let's also support everyone in the chat today. Be nice. Be kind:)
Tech Troublemaker: Thanks guys!!!!