BostonDonMTB: Looking good you guys!
Sandi Thompson: Helllllooo!
BostonDonMTB: Hey Sandi
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Markus & Sarah!
Sandi Thompson: 👋🏻👋🏻
Ellie Calhoun: Hi everyone!
BostonDonMTB: Hi Lala
Sandi Thompson: Lala!!
BostonDonMTB: Hi Ellie
Sandi Thompson: Hi everyone!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hey @BostonDonMTB and @Sandi Thompson . Gosh Sandi your latest video is super awesome. congratulations my dear friend.
Mommy Guide Inc: 💃💃💃
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hello guys 👋
Mommy Guide Inc: And let's Live that Sttreaming Life!
Sandi Thompson: Thank you!
Sandi Thompson: My favorite part!!
Mommy Guide Inc: How are you Ana - lovin' the new thumbnail
BostonDonMTB: You guys ready
BostonDonMTB: ?
Mommy Guide Inc: yes absolutely ready @BostonDonMTB !
BostonDonMTB: @Mommy Guide Inc Good. 🙂
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: @mommy Guide Inc thank you! Doing some renovations 😁
Mommy Guide Inc: The Decluttering Challenge was super awesome although I only finished 1/3 of the challenges - I am able to maintain the ones I decluttered still clean and organized.
Sandi Thompson: It was an awesome challenge.
BostonDonMTB: @Mommy Guide Inc That is great!
Sandi Thompson: @mommy Guide Inc - me too!!
BostonDonMTB: Q: Sarah, what training do you have that helps you help your clients?
BostonDonMTB: You are not alone.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I’m learning how decluttering really helps to have clarity to feel free
Mommy Guide Inc: thanks for being here everyone - pls don't forget to like this stream:) And share this stream.:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I love it!
Mommy Guide Inc: Here is where to find Sarah: https://smallchanges.tv/
Ellie Calhoun: Great tips on building community!
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: is it time consuming to maintain a community in 2 platforms?
Caleb McDonald: MARKUS! SARAH!
Stephanie Gieseke: Hey everyone!!!
Caleb McDonald: Discord FTW 🙌🏻
Caleb McDonald: Stephanie!
Stephanie Gieseke: I LOVE discord over FB!
Stephanie Gieseke: Caleb!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Stephanie!!! hi!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I have a fb group…I only have two faithful viewers…I just can’t get track there. Not sure what I’m doing wrong there 😢
Caleb McDonald: Congratulations Markus on reaching 100+ subs 🎉
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Caleb McDonald
Stephanie Gieseke: Hi Lala!
Caleb McDonald: Hi Lala! 👋🏻
Caleb McDonald: I find discord more chatty and easy to use than Facebook.
Mommy Guide Inc: I am actually surprised that I am loving Discord too. topics can be organized and I love that about it:)
Caleb McDonald: People love a place to come and share common ideas and grow together.
Caleb McDonald: Also, the fact Discord and YouTube can be linked allows creators more control over offering perks to members.
Caleb McDonald: Growing an engagement audience is key. People who are willing to invest in you (and the community), as much as you as a creator are investing into them.
Andy Halper: So smart. No need to worry … Thanks!
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed thanks to Austin I've a bot in Discord that posts to the server when I go live on YT.
Caleb McDonald: Bots in Discord are great 👌🏻 you can really great cool experiences with them too.
Caleb McDonald: Create*
Caleb McDonald: You end up creating more “channels” than you think as your community in Discord grows too. They start wanting to engage in more topics too (e.g. funny, pets, food etc).
Caleb McDonald: Challenges REALLY promote engagement and brings your audience back wanting more.
Mommy Guide Inc: indeed Caleb. I have added I think about 5 more channels as members open up new general topics that deserve to have their own space. It's easier for the community to find topics.
Andy Halper: Right on. No lecturing. Peer to peer education and learning
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Andy!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: FF - Frugal February!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for sharing Sarah about how "challenges" can actually be used to grow and improve community engagement as well.
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes I've been using Restream for about a year now to stream to different platforms simultaneously:)
Andy Halper: Isn’t this so interesting, Lala, yes it is!!