Eaglevp: Evening Markus
Rich Vybz: Good evening Marcus... hello everyone
Eaglevp: Hi Rich
SuzanCz: Helllooooooo
Rich Vybz: Hi @Eaglevp
Rich Vybz: Hey @SuzanCz
Eaglevp: Don’t do Christmas shopping
Markus Schaub: https://jackbox.tv/
Eaglevp: Hi SuzanCz
Eaglevp: Just put money in the cards
Tim Heale 9: Hi Marcus
SuzanCz: Gimme a sec. I’ll hop onto the computer and procrastinate with you!
Tim Heale 9: Markus
Tim Heale 9: Artie the Ships cat will get you a mouse
Tim Heale 9: Not a gamer
SuzanCz: Hi @Eaglevp!
Markus Schaub: https://jackbox.tv/
SuzanCz: Hey @Tim Heale 9 !
SuzanCz: I love games!
Eaglevp: Watching but on chat with Tim
Tim Heale 9: Hi @SuzanCz you ok?
SuzanCz: Well enough. Good days and bad. Thanks for asking, @Tim Heale 9
SuzanCz: I chose!
Tim Heale 9: A dog knapper
Eaglevp: Buzzard
SuzanCz: I'm playing with a cat on my lap!
SuzanCz: Oh yeaaaahhhhh
Eaglevp: Oreos
SuzanCz: d'oh!
SuzanCz: Haha! Gotcha, @Eaglevp
SuzanCz: That was mine
SuzanCz: Bread seems very not one of a kind
SuzanCz: d'oh!
SuzanCz: Haha! We all fooled each other.
SuzanCz: You should always believe me, Marcus. That's just good sense. 😉
SuzanCz: Yesssssss
SuzanCz: Yay1
SuzanCz: !
SuzanCz: d'oh!
SuzanCz: Oh wow! Well done
SuzanCz: BWAAAAHAHA!
SuzanCz: wooohoo!
SuzanCz: oh yeaaaahhhhh
SuzanCz: That was hard!!
SuzanCz: d'oh!
SuzanCz: yesssss
SuzanCz: Nice work, Markus!
Rich Vybz: Good Game
SuzanCz: You were nipping at my heels the whole way
Eaglevp: Enjoyed that game
SuzanCz: Do they have other games?
SuzanCz: Ah!
SuzanCz: I don't know any games. Haven't played with it before
SuzanCz: I'm in for another round.
SuzanCz: but I think we do need at least 3 playing.
Markus Schaub: https://jackbox.tv/
Markus Schaub: viuy
Rich Vybz: I have to go for dinner.. was fun Markus!
SuzanCz: sure!
SuzanCz: This is me procrastinating Hahaha!
SuzanCz: Hahaha! True.