Mommy Guide Inc: Good day everyone!
Tech Zero to Hero: Hey hey!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Tech Hero to Zero!
Tech Zero to Hero: It’s Dori!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: It's Dori! OMG is this your new YT channel?
Tech Zero to Hero: It’s been a while!!
Mommy Guide Inc: How are you Dori? You are on summer break now right?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ejnar! Ana! Coach Adam!
Mommy Guide Inc: How has everyone been? In terms of our goals for the year - how's it been so far?
Mommy Guide Inc: How so much fun!
Mommy Guide Inc: How so much fun Adam!
Mommy Guide Inc: Coach Adam! May you mention your new channel name?
Mommy Guide Inc: You are an amazing artist Coach Adam. Actually in whatever you do - you crush it all the time.
Mommy Guide Inc: awesome - pivoting into something that you are passionate about - yey Coach Adam! I still believe your past videos will continue to grow traction in time coz those are ever green content
Mommy Guide Inc: Inkscape 1.2 is it like procreate?
Mommy Guide Inc: oops sorry forgot to put a Q. he he he.
Mommy Guide Inc: it does look like Illustrator more.
Mommy Guide Inc: Congratulations Coach Adam!
Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
Mommy Guide Inc: Hey Sammy Super Star of Sammy on the Street:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Sammy how about your mid year and goals for the half of the year? Would you care to share?
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for being here Dori - this is Dori's website which would take you to the rest of her socials: https://www.techherotozero.com
Mommy Guide Inc: Coach Adam what a super fun year so far. And we look forward to this new direction:)
David W. Ryan: Hi Friends, listening while I work!
Mommy Guide Inc: Tech for Seniors - that's awesome!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi David! Howdy?
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hi David!
Mommy Guide Inc: David is Spooling Around on Youtube:)
David W. Ryan: @Mommy Guide Inc Howdy!
Mommy Guide Inc: I am good David. Hope everything is well too for you.:) thanks for being here today:)
Mommy Guide Inc: David Ryan's Youtube Channel - Spooling Around - https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCEw545bbmcM8RQN31j-Bfig
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed Ejnar - cheering you on for your new job. I am not in IT nor in Sales but keep on going for it Ejnar.
Mommy Guide Inc: HI Ana!
Mommy Guide Inc: Ana you have been very consistent with things thus far. And now with a clearer view towards the last half of the year.Super awesome.
Mommy Guide Inc: LEDA paved the way for us to meet and the friendships has been such a blessing:)
Mommy Guide Inc: What an amazing journey indeed Markus. Yes, you are a great host Markus. Looking forward to more shows with interviews if you find the time.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: That's a great idea - turn some livestreams into prerecorded videos and post them as a premiere so we can have live chat engagement still.
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Coach Adam:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: You deserve it sooooo much! Can't wait to watch that blessing.
David W. Ryan: wow, that's awesome
Mommy Guide Inc: Thank you Ana and David. It's a bit scary but excited much for it.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: wow time flies by so much!