Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: This is going to be so much fun. I can't wait. ;-)
Mommy Guide Inc: And here we go!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Janet!
U Do It: hey now
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi lala
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Great music! 🎶
Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Hi Markus😀
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Markus & Kevin
Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Hi Kevin 😀👍👋👋
Ellie Calhoun: Yay!
Ellie Calhoun: Markus!!!!!
Kevin McAleer: Hey Everyone!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Ellie
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Ejnar
Kevin McAleer: Love this song!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Party time
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I love this open
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ejnar and Ellie! Living this Streaming Life!
Ellie Calhoun: Hi everyone! Is that Janet?
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey! kevin helllo!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Ellie. Yes it's me... Janet
Kevin McAleer: Hey!
Mommy Guide Inc: @U Do It hello!
Mommy Guide Inc: Please don’t forget to smash that LIKE button
U Do It: Hello Mommy Guide
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Why can't be just stay on "real" time
U Do It: Im sitting in my chair
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh no Markus your voice sounds a bit under the weather. Are you ok?
Kevin McAleer: I'm lurking
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Markus you sound a bit better. I hope you are.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Kevin
Mommy Guide Inc: Bwahaha! I hope the lurking is temporary Kevin. LOL. See you on the screen in a bit and there you are!
U Do It: imma electrical engineer n software engineer with a passion for automation
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: 🤖 Love all of those movies
Mommy Guide Inc: Isn’t this so much fun - Robotics. OMG I love Short Circuit the movie - Johnny 5
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: This is so amazing Kevin. How fun.
Mommy Guide Inc: Watching how something gets produced via 3D printing is absolutely amazing. Some of the crafters in our community own these already. One created a super nice ring for me.
Samantha JustInspire: Hey everyone!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Samantha! Wow what an awesome journey Kevin.:)
Ellie Calhoun: Your story is fascinating!
Samantha JustInspire: Lol I totally understand that
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yes love the community building. You are so fun Kevin
Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
Samantha JustInspire: Hey Sammy
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Sammy
Mommy Guide Inc: Hey Sammy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Pls let smash that LIKE button for this stream. Thanks!
Samantha JustInspire: I have that as well! Love the way you switch your cameras Kevin!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh nice Kevin. Love all of your cameras. I so want a 2nd camera.
Samantha JustInspire: Ecamm is great!
Mommy Guide Inc: This is Kevin’s YT channel if you want more of this kind of content - robots.:) https://youtube.com/c/kevinmcaleer28
Samantha JustInspire: I just got the zv e10 Animal Paradise!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @Samantha JustInspire do you use it for your 2nd cam? (It's Janet by the way. ;-)) I have been wanting to have a "kitty cam".
Mommy Guide Inc: Edited video with Live-streaming works hand in hand in growing a channel right Kevin?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Kevin, that's interesting about Twitter. I have social media posts on twitter but I stay away from it. hum..
Mommy Guide Inc: Hmmm Twitter. Thanks for sharing that Kevin.
Paul Burke: Hey Kevin...when you post on Twitter...are you using any software to help with hashtags?
Samantha JustInspire: I love that Kevin
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: PAUL!!!
Samantha JustInspire: Hi Janet yes I use I canon m50 as my main camera and the zv e10 as my overhead
Paul Burke: JANET!!
Samantha JustInspire: Oh nice to meet you as well
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Love it Samantha. thanks for sharing.
Paul Burke: Markus is huge in the foot community
Mommy Guide Inc: Hey Paul that’s a great Q
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Paul-eee
Paul Burke: thanks Lala
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: when you take the countdown timer (I do that too) doesn't it take the comments away?
Tech Troublemaker: sorry i am late
Omar Gherd: Pimorni are the nerds nerds! brilliant company!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hey Roy!
Ellie Calhoun: That's great Kevin!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Lala!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: This is so amazing Kevin. You are so amazing.
Paul Burke: wow...thats amazing Kevin
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Omar.:) that’s a great way to do get sponsors. Get them excited with the collaboration via your content
Mommy Guide Inc: Congratulations Kevin!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Congratulations Kevin. so cool and exciting 🎉🎊🎇
Mommy Guide Inc: Awesome numbers. Very exciting. And love you still use whiteboards.:)
Samantha JustInspire: So awesome 👏
Paul Burke: great way to look at it kevin....10 years out
Mommy Guide Inc: Evergreen contents. You answer the how’s and why’s.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Haha. Rasberry Pi. I thought you were talking about PIE's. 🥧
Mommy Guide Inc: It’s amazing to see how very strategic and intentional you are in growing your influence and channel Kevin. Thanks for the awesome sharing.
Ellie Calhoun: This Gold! Thanks Kevin!
Mommy Guide Inc: Absolutely agree with you there Ellie!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: fantastic about your 2 years and lots of content that you can repurpose (shorts segments, etc)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Q: what do your robots do? or are they must new friends?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh dust bunny patrol!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: These are fantastic. so facinating.
Mommy Guide Inc: Create Value in your content.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Wash! I want that machine Kevin:)
Ellie Calhoun: We had sticks and stones to play with when I was little😂 no game boys etc
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Same here Ellie. Pick up sticks!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: YES! Kevin you have the best personality and love love love what you do. It is contagious.
Mommy Guide Inc: https://youtube.com/c/kevinmcaleer28
Mommy Guide Inc: And don’t forget to like this stream as well and share this awesome video:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Thanks men! This was great.