Cheryl Wolf: Happy Anniversary🎉
Sammy Super Star: Happy Anniversary! Hey Markus
Adam Tinkoff: Hey there kids!
Cheryl Wolf: Hello all
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hello!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Cheryl - you're first wow!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Adam Tinkoff
Cheryl Wolf: Do I win a prize lol
Sammy Super Star: Oh! You have some guests
Sammy Super Star: Congrats on 1 year
Tech Troublemaker: Woo Hoo!! It's @Markus Schaub
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yeah Sammy!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Let's this get party started!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy @Tech Troublemaker!
Mommy Guide Inc: yey @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52!
Sammy Super Star: You have some dances moves today! Keep up the dancing 💃🕺💃🕺💃🕺
BostonDonMTB: Hello everyone
Mommy Guide Inc: 💃🏿🕺👯‍♀💃🏿🕺👯‍♀
Cheryl Wolf: yes dance dance
Sammy Super Star: :goodvibes:
Make and Do Crafts: Congratulations!
Sammy Super Star: You might be better dancers then luria! Lol 😆
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Don@BostonDonMTB !!!
Make and Do Crafts: One year! Woo hoo!
Mommy Guide Inc: yey Diane@Make and Do Crafts
BostonDonMTB: Hi @Mommy Guide Inc
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: 🎇🎇🎇🎇🎇🎉🎉🎉🎉
Cheryl Wolf: Go lala
Make and Do Crafts: Hi @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: Let's Go!!! Wow - 49 awesome episodes - #MarkusRules!!!
Ellie Calhoun: Hey hey!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi everyone!!! Hey Markus. Friday?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Ellie Calhoun!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: yey Janet@Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing!!!
Cheryl Wolf: Party time🎉
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: 💃💃💃💃💃💃🕺🕺🕺🕺🕺
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: lala!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: 💃🏿💃🏿💃🏿💃🏿💃🏿
Sara S: MARKUS!!!
SiShong Victor: Ok I didn't miss it. need to get food and a drink brb
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: 🥳🥳🥳🥳
Ellie Calhoun: Markus Rules!!! Happy Anniversary! 🎶🎶🎶
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey you made it @SiShong Victor!
Ellie Calhoun: 💃💃💃💃
Kali Co: ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️
Ellie Calhoun: Hi everyone!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Sara S
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Congratulations on 1 year 🎉
Kali Co: hit that like button!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Ellie
Sammy Super Star: Most of the people you interviewed you met from LSP/LEDA
Serenity Studio Art : Hey hello @Markus Schaub and everyine 👋🏼
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Kali
Mommy Guide Inc: oh yeah @Kali Co!!!
Kali Co: the gang is all here 😊
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Sammy
Kali Co: @Mommy Guide Inc hey lala!!
Mommy Guide Inc: hi Diana@Serenity Studio Art
Marga Gomez: Hi MARKUS!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: MARKUS!!!!
Kali Co: 💃💃💃💃🥳🥳🥳🥳
Make and Do Crafts: Yay!!!
Sara S: 👏👏👏👏👏👏👏
Ellie Calhoun: 💕💜💕💜💕💜
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Marga Gomez !!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Cheryl!!!!
Serenity Studio Art : Hey hello @Mommy Guide Inc 🌹
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh your colors are changing!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: ANA!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: uuuuh! check out that background light!!! LOVE it!
Sammy Super Star: You have done amazing streams Markus
Marga Gomez: ooh pretty lights.
BostonDonMTB: Exciting times for you Markus!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Victor & Sara
Mommy Guide Inc: ooh the changing lights!!!
Sammy Super Star: When Kali is here the crazy party starts and only like 3 people know what that means lol 😆
Mommy Guide Inc: I forgot to open mine! he he he
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hey! Janet! Marga! Ellie, Cheryl!!! Adam!! Roy!!!
BostonDonMTB: You've come a LONG way since that roll of paper thrown into the trash.
Make and Do Crafts: Yes it's Diane here. You got it right. Well remembered ha ha
Sara S: Love the lights
Cheryl Wolf: Hello All!!! it is a party
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh this will be fun
Mommy Guide Inc: Congratulations Markus!!!
Kali Co: yesssss!!
Marga Gomez: make up!
Kali Co: lala!!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: :elbowcough:
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yay LALA good morning
Sammy Super Star: Yesss
Sara S: Hey Lala!
Ellie Calhoun: 😂 🤣😂🤣
Make and Do Crafts: Lala has grown since then lol
Tech Troublemaker: Hit that LIKE Button!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Lala!
Marga Gomez: Hi @Mommy Guide Inc
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: too bad there is not a LOVE button
Kali Co: @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52 right?!
Mommy Guide Inc: oh yes let's smash that LIKE button everyone!!!
Kali Co: let's see it!!
Serenity Studio Art : Hey hello @Ellie Calhoun @Kali Co @Marga Gomez 👋🏼
Kali Co: @Serenity Studio Art hey!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: What a difference
Kali Co: ahhh markus wow look at the difference!!!!
Marga Gomez: Hi @Serenity Studio Art ❤️
Make and Do Crafts: Ah how sweet
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Diana!
Kali Co: that is so wild
Sammy Super Star: Your setup is so differentn
Marga Gomez: PROPS
Cheryl Wolf: You are wayyy more confident now
Sara S: What a difference!
Sammy Super Star: Everything looks different
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: lol
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: hahahaha
Kali Co: LOL
Marga Gomez: hahaha
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: LOL
Kali Co: love it
Sara S: 😂😂😂
Make and Do Crafts: Love the special effects
Tech Troublemaker: You need a BuyMeACoffee or something so we can send you gifts.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: special effect!!! love it!
Ellie Calhoun: Lol! Love it!
Serenity Studio Art : Loo
Kali Co: i'd say the you now would throw the paper at the camera and be like POW!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: 🤣🤣🤣
Serenity Studio Art : lol
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: it was our first!!!!
Ellie Calhoun: My first too!
Kali Co: yes markus!!!!
Kali Co: we need th ebuymeacoffee link!!!
Ellie Calhoun: Yes!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: that will be great.... buy me a coffee.
Make and Do Crafts: Yes let's buy a coffee!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Love the props...that was actually very smart to do on your first time
Ellie Calhoun: Yay!
Eaglevp: Hello Markus
Eaglevp: Hi Lala
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: can you put the link in the chat?
Cheryl Wolf: Hair needed love
Eaglevp: Hi Ellie
Kali Co: wow that is crazy!
Kali Co: what a difference!
Eaglevp: Hi Ana Zugheri
BostonDonMTB: I was there.
Ellie Calhoun: Hi 👋
Ellie Calhoun: Who is Eaglevp?
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I see it as an overlay but not as a link for us to click
Connecting on the Net: Mary Speegle. Hey Markus and Lala
Eaglevp: Hey@Kali Co
Mommy Guide Inc: https://www.buymeacoffee.com/markusschaub
Kali Co: @Eaglevp hey! 🤗
Kali Co: yay!!!!!
Sara S: That was your first LEDA or your first youtube?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: it's roy
Kali Co: ❤ ,3
Serenity Studio Art : @Eaglevp @Cheryl Wolf hey hello!
SiShong Victor: Kali likes here coffees eh
BostonDonMTB: Just think, you could have had a bunch of coffee's already Markus!!!
Kali Co: @SiShong Victor 😂😂
Eaglevp: Hi @Serenity Studio Art and @Cheryl Wolf
Kali Co: awwwe
Eaglevp: Hi@SiShong Victor
BostonDonMTB: Yeah, it was fun to watch.
SiShong Victor: Hi hi
Serenity Studio Art : Hey hello @SiShong Victor
Kali Co: 🔥🔥🔥🔥
Kali Co: LOL
SiShong Victor: hi @Serenity Studio Art
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: WoW I love it! you have to show us how it works!!! There is a how to tutorial for you
SiShong Victor: now I want to make a pot off coffee
Sara S: What equipment will you buy with all your coffee?
Kali Co: i love this memory lane
Serenity Studio Art : Hey hello @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52 @Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hi Serenity!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Glad you are here
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi @Serenity Studio Art so happy you are here too
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: we should had guess!!!
Cheryl Wolf: little lala
SiShong Victor: I like the Kali hair on the comment
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: look at ya'll
Serenity Studio Art : Thank you🥰@Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: LALA!!! baby lala
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I remember that stream
Kali Co: @SiShong Victor back when my hair was orange.pink
Kali Co: LOL
SiShong Victor: yes looks good on ya
Kali Co: @SiShong Victor ❤
Cheryl Wolf: Both of you have changed alot in a year!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: we have all come a long way since April 2021
Ellie Calhoun: don't drink them all at once!! ha haaa!
SiShong Victor: Wow Lala the 1st camera angle 😛
Sara S: Lala is an All Star Good Sport💜💜💜💜
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: She is always coming to the rescue!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: lol
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: so fun to see you grow Lala
Sammy Super Star: Lala stream quality has changed too!
Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Hi Markus😀
Sammy Super Star: Both of you have upgraded
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: so adorable
Eaglevp: Hello@Sammy Super Star
Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Happy anniversary 😀
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming!!!
Eaglevp: Hi@Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Ejnar!!!
SiShong Victor: I could never go live in my PJs unless its on onlyfans
Cheryl Wolf: Keith hello
Cheryl Wolf: Ejnar hi
Mommy Guide Inc: I will go in PJs for Markus and you all!
Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Hi Everyone here😀👋👋
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: moderating while live on cam ;-)
Tech Troublemaker: Yes, Lala is the OG
Sammy Super Star: Yes
Kali Co: loving the love ❤
Make and Do Crafts: You won't be able to sleep with all these coffees. But enjoy!!
Cheryl Wolf: party today great to see all of you 🎉
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: ☕☕☕☕
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Let's go!!!
Serenity Studio Art : @Cheryl Wolf if I didn’t say hello…hello !
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: 🙀☕☕☕☕☕
SiShong Victor: Sammy
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Victor!!!!?????
Make and Do Crafts: Sammy
Kali Co: sammy
Marga Gomez: Sammy @Sammy Super Star
SiShong Victor: Sammy has all the mics
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Sammy?
Cheryl Wolf: sammy
Serenity Studio Art : Victor
Ellie Calhoun: sammy
Kali Co: LOL
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: LOL
SiShong Victor: One mouth but 100 mics
Marga Gomez: The OG red curtain of @Sammy Super Star
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Sammy Cool
Mommy Guide Inc: Great Victor that was faster than lightning!!!
Cheryl Wolf: lol victor
Eaglevp: Hi@Marga Gomez
Marga Gomez: Hiya @Eaglevp
Serenity Studio Art : Lol @SiShong Victor
Tech Troublemaker: So many awesome folks here. Hey Everyone!!!!!
Eaglevp: Hi@Tech Troublemaker
Marga Gomez: Hi @Tech Troublemaker
Sammy Super Star: That was me
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: right, simple but fun!!!!
Sammy Super Star: SSS studios that’s me
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: SSSSSSSSamy!!!!
Sammy Super Star: Next year I will donate more lol 😆
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: haha @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52
Tech Troublemaker: Matt Haas
SiShong Victor: LaLa
Cheryl Wolf: Ellie
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: wow!!!
Sara S: John Pullum?
Sammy Super Star: Is that the biggest Markus stream donation?
SiShong Victor: I only know how to spell like 3 names
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Is it John Pullum?
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: That does sounded like John lol
Sammy Super Star: John Pullum is very famous
Tech Troublemaker: I totally forgot John said that.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: too funny
Ellie Calhoun: I forgot that!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: on the ball!!!⚾⚽🏀🏈
Mommy Guide Inc: Me too Roy@Tech Troublemaker I absolutely forgot about the ball
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: great idea!!! only John would come up with that
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: this is too funny and great idea
Sammy Super Star: John would have done something like that
Cheryl Wolf: So true Ana
Mommy Guide Inc: so true @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: lol
Kali Co: LOL
Sara S: 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣
Kali Co: john just lets anyone hold his balls
Cheryl Wolf: 🤣
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: we need to bring that back to the mastermind group lol
Sammy Super Star: Ahahah
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: We all should ask him...
Ellie Calhoun: 🤣😂🤣
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: 🙀
Serenity Studio Art : Lol. @Kali Co 😂
Connecting on the Net: 🏐🏐
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Connecting on the Net!!!
Ellie Calhoun: laala
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Lala
Tech Troublemaker: Lala
SiShong Victor: LaLa
Sara S: Lala
Make and Do Crafts: Lala
Cheryl Wolf: lala
Sammy Super Star: Lala
Kali Co: LOL lala already knows
Marga Gomez: A. lala
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Kali?
SiShong Victor: Only Lala does 4 hrs
Connecting on the Net: Mary speegle Hi Everyone!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: lol
Ellie Calhoun: ha ha ! who else goes for 4 hours!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @victor so true 4hrs lala
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL @Ellie Calhoun you beat me to it!
Cheryl Wolf: I love lala surprise face
Sara S: I have to go run an errand but I’m taking you all with me
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: maybe i need to add echo to my stream to get more viewers
Kali Co: @Sara S ❤
Ellie Calhoun: lol @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52
Mommy Guide Inc: ooh thanks Sara! Take care!!!
Eaglevp: Bye@Sara S have a nice weekend
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: See ya Sarah!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: @BostonDonMTB :washhands::washhands::washhands::washhands:
Kali Co: lol
Make and Do Crafts: Yay dance!1
Kali Co: *LOL
Marga Gomez: hahaha
BostonDonMTB: Hahaha
Make and Do Crafts: Let's party11
Sara S: At least if I go 4 hrs there won’t be sound. Of course, everyone will fall asleep😂😂😂
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: now you need to write a song to thank for the coffee!
Mary Speegle: More!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: international COFFEE! ☕️
Sammy Super Star: Watching while getting a new screen for my computer.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: lol
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: what's one more
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: yall are so funny
Sammy Super Star: No I need a new screen. I have been using it for many years lol 😂
Sammy Super Star: I only use 1
Cheryl Wolf: yes I am ready
Sara S: Perfect!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Paul Burke?
Tech Troublemaker: Sammy
Ellie Calhoun: Paul
Marga Gomez: A. Matt
Cheryl Wolf: paul
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: oh wow
Sammy Super Star: Paul
Sammy Super Star: Marga?
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: was it a girl or boy?
Sara S: Painting lullaby stream
Cheryl Wolf: lala beat me
Marga Gomez: haha @Sammy Super Star
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: it could only be Paul
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: ah!
Sara S: Matt Haas?
Tech Troublemaker: I am not doing too well. I missed the Paul episode. 😞
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: i remember that!! it was so much fun
Sara S: Of course!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: You did really good
Ellie Calhoun: lol!! I remember this!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: lol
Make and Do Crafts: Ha ha
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: that was great
Kali Co: LOL
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: LOL
Cheryl Wolf: 🤣🤣
Mommy Guide Inc: My mind just automatically clicked that it was Paul!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: this is great
Sara S: I’ll be driving. Kali will have to get my guesses telepathically
Make and Do Crafts: 😂😂😂
Kali Co: @Sara S 😂😂😂
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: hahah
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: lol
Mommy Guide Inc: take care Sara:)
MySnoopy80: Hi❤️❤️❤️
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @MySnoopy80 !!!
Eaglevp: Hi@MySnoopy80
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: hahaha
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: basically you beat Paul!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: yey@Eaglevp
MySnoopy80: ❤️❤️❤️
Tech Troublemaker: we have to wear makeup?
Eaglevp: lOL
Kali Co: @Tech Troublemaker ahahahaha
Kali Co: keith will be in next year's game!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: @Tech Troublemaker it's a challenge so go get some
Eaglevp: Yes I know will have to go and check the past live streams out for next year
Mary Speegle: These are great!
Marga Gomez: A. Kali
SiShong Victor: Kali
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Kali
Kali Co: no way that's not me hahahah
Ellie Calhoun: Roy?
Eaglevp: I look forward to that@Kali Co
Kali Co: i was gonna say victor but victor wouldn't say that
Kali Co: hahahhaha
Make and Do Crafts: Stephie?
Ellie Calhoun: Matt Haas
Tech Troublemaker: Matt Haas?
SiShong Victor: I just type the 1st name that comes in my head
Kali Co: oo matt is a good one
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Sarah small changes????
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: who does tidying up?
Ellie Calhoun: Sarah
Make and Do Crafts: Yes Sarah
Cheryl French: Hey everybody!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: decluttering.
Kali Co: omg sarah would totally say that!!!
Ellie Calhoun: Ana got it!
Kali Co: @Cheryl French hey!! ,3
Kali Co: * ❤
Kali Co: @Sara S i'm sorry if i let you down telepathically on that one
Sammy Super Star: Heheh
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: 💪💪💪 yeih! i got a point!!!
Cheryl Wolf: The Cheryl's are in the house!!
Kali Co: ohhh i thought "tech thing" was you filling it in to not give the answer away 😂
Mommy Guide Inc: Congratulations Ana!!!
SiShong Victor: Ya Victor never says good bye to tech
Cheryl French: Hello! Sorry I’m a bit late!
Kali Co: @SiShong Victor exactly 😂
Serenity Studio Art : lol @SiShong Victor
Cheryl French: The Cheryl’s are here!
Eaglevp: Evening@Cheryl French
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Cheryl French
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: me too!
Cheryl Wolf: yeah markus
Cheryl French: Yes! We can both talk your ears off about wellness!
Coffee Talk & Tech: hi Markus 👋 happy one year anniversary for streaming!
Cheryl Wolf: yes you too ana
Kali Co: that's me
Kali Co: hahahahha
Serenity Studio Art : Kali
SiShong Victor: Kali
Ellie Calhoun: Kali
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: oh! i don't know but that is really sweet
Kali Co: 😂😂
Cheryl French: Aw, so sweet!
Kali Co: i was like "hey that's my motto that must be me!"
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: that needs to become an overlay quote!
Kali Co: LOL
SiShong Victor: Kali doesn't count 😛
Kali Co: @SiShong Victor yuh huh look - 1, 2, 3, 4, 😌
Mommy Guide Inc: #markusrules #kalirules the origin!
Cheryl Wolf: Is writing Markus on your chest
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Love it!
SiShong Victor: only up to 4 😛
Kali Co: awe what a fun time that was ❤
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: you rule Kali
Kali Co: @SiShong Victor damn you!
Kali Co: hahahaha thank you 😌😂
Cheryl Wolf: 😍 Kali
Kali Co: @Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing baww thank you so do you janet ❤
SiShong Victor: Kali does have the best studio 🙂
Cheryl French: The human species!
Kali Co: i don't count
Kali Co: hahahhaha
MySnoopy80: I made a note for both cheryls to get interview
Ellie Calhoun: It's a tie!!
Tech Troublemaker: Now you need the tie breaker.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: everyone is a winner!!!
SiShong Victor: Tie breaker = Cage match lets go
Cheryl French: What, like a seven-way tie or something?
Kali Co: LOL
Kali Co: 😂😂😂😂
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Ah telepathy. You are speaking my language. hahaha
Tech Troublemaker: Here is your participation Trophy 🏆🏆🏆
Kali Co: @Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing LOL literally!!!!
Kali Co: that was such a great game
Ellie Calhoun: Great game!
Mommy Guide Inc: indeed!!!
Kali Co: i will still be here but lurking, bird is begging to go outside
Make and Do Crafts: What a great idea! it was fun
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Thanks so much for the game. I loved it. do it again some time.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: @Tech Troublemaker thank you
Cheryl French: @techtroublemaker 🤣
Mommy Guide Inc: OMG!!! This is it - let's do this with Ana!
SiShong Victor: I can't play that game on my channel I only interview Tech gear
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @Cheryl & Ellie we need to do the makeup challenge for 6:30 haha
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: ANA!!!
Ellie Calhoun: Lol @janet
Marga Gomez: Hi @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52
Cheryl Wolf: Ana❤️
Cheryl French: I can see Lala’s ear, anyway!
Ellie Calhoun: Yay!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: 2 moderators. yay
Tech Troublemaker: now you have global moderator coverage.
Mommy Guide Inc: yey co-mod Ana!!!!
Tech Troublemaker: Lala Nap time
SiShong Victor: Time for War Paint
Mommy Guide Inc: oh no - sleep later:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: It's live!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Victor - War Paint!
Ellie Calhoun: Lol
Cheryl Wolf: two of markus lol
Cheryl Wolf: LOL
Marga Gomez: dirty dancing
Cheryl French: Dirty Dancing!
Make and Do Crafts: Is this a makeup channel now?😂
Mommy Guide Inc: @Cheryl French sorry about that - it's another for the books right? LO
Make and Do Crafts: The magic of makeup with Marcus
Cheryl French: OMG Ana!
Marga Gomez: Ana is on am easel
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Diane@Make and Do Crafts - we're doing the make up challenge! but now Markus has a guide:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: makeup for going live
SiShong Victor: Everything starts with foundation
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yes @Marga Gomez indeed she is in an easel!
Cheryl French: Very good sponge technique, Markus!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: looking good markus.
Mommy Guide Inc: wow - Markus you're blending it really well.
SiShong Victor: No twilight vampire shininess
Cheryl Wolf: Make a face to put on make up
Make and Do Crafts: You are transformed Marcus!
Marga Gomez: yas @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52
Ellie Calhoun: 😆😂🤣 love 💕
Cheryl Wolf: 🤣🤣
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Ready for a job as a network correspondent!
MySnoopy80: You dont have that
Mommy Guide Inc: yes that one can be.
Cheryl French: Markus has nice eyebrows, anyway…
Cheryl Wolf: Markus needs to use some of his coffee money buy make up brushes
Ellie Calhoun: Looking good already!
Make and Do Crafts: 🤣🤣I'm glad I didn't join at this point. I would be wondering what's going on 🤣🤣
Cheryl Wolf: 🤣🤣This is so fun
Ellie Calhoun: Lol 😂
Cheryl French: What is that color? Is it a purple color?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Tell Markus to close one eye and watch with the other
Make and Do Crafts: Yay more coffees!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Music for LALA
Make and Do Crafts: Ha ha
Mommy Guide Inc: yey!!!
Cheryl French: The coffee dance!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: too funny
Ellie Calhoun: 💃 ☕️💃☕️💃
Cheryl French: Nice cheekbones!
Mommy Guide Inc: body make up too!!! to make us look slimmer:)
Cheryl French: I could use some on my butt, then! 🤣
Cheryl Wolf: 🤣🤣🤣
Ellie Calhoun: 🤩😍🤩😂
MySnoopy80: Im almost home should i bring you more supplies?
Mommy Guide Inc: finally Markus has buymeacoffee! https://www.buymeacoffee.com/markusschaub
Ellie Calhoun: What about 💄
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh no mascara - that's one I really have a hard time using.
Mommy Guide Inc: oh wow a makeup hack from Ana!
Cheryl French: We can’t trust Markus with an eyelash curler! Too dangerous!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I would poke my eyes out!!!
Ellie Calhoun: Wow! I'm learning something
Mommy Guide Inc: cool hack! no lash curler - no worries - just get a teaspoon!
Cheryl Wolf: I am worried about him putting mascara
Make and Do Crafts: And pull a face while doing it!
Ellie Calhoun: I'm pulling a face just watching!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: don't put it in your eye Markus! 👁
Cheryl French: Eyelash curlers are torture contraptions!
Ellie Calhoun: 😂 I've got to go... so much fu! And congratulations!!🎉
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: look with the other eye
Mommy Guide Inc: open eyes Markus!!!! LOL
Make and Do Crafts: Don't pretend you never wore mascara🤣
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for the support and dropping by @Ellie Calhoun
Cheryl Wolf: 🤣 I am going pee
MySnoopy80: Im here
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus!!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: ok help @MySnoopy80:)
Mommy Guide Inc: help is on the way Markus!
Cheryl French: Bye @Ellie Calhoun !
Make and Do Crafts: This is how I apply makeup too🤣
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: the markus school of makeup
Make and Do Crafts: Bye @Ellie Calhoun
Mommy Guide Inc: I think I just woke up everybody with my laughing so much!
Cheryl French: Don’t forget lipstick!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi!!!
Cheryl French: Hi!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi!!!!
Cheryl Wolf: Hello
Mommy Guide Inc: you can do this Markus!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: was????
Mommy Guide Inc: thanks so much @MySnoopy80!!!!
Cheryl French: So nice to meet your girlfriend!
Mommy Guide Inc: great to have finally meet you!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: see what we go thought?? hahaha
Tim Heale 9: Hi Markus, very theatrical makeup 😻
MySnoopy80: Nice to meet you too
Tim Heale 9: Go large
Eaglevp: Hi@Tim Heale 9
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: good job
Make and Do Crafts: You are just poking your eye Marcus🤣
Serenity Studio Art : Hey hello @Tim Heale 9 👋🏼
Tim Heale 9: Hi Keith
Cheryl French: So pretty!
Mommy Guide Inc: wow!!! awesome lashes!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Tim Heale 9 yey!
Make and Do Crafts: Hi @Tim Heale 9
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Tim
Mommy Guide Inc: bold color there!
Cheryl French: Dramatic shade of lipstick!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: that's dark!
MySnoopy80: Thanks LALA
Eff Guitar: Happy 1st year streaming Markus
Ellie Calhoun: I can't stay away! lol...
Cheryl French: Eff is here!!!
Cheryl Wolf: OH sooo pretty markus
Make and Do Crafts: Wow perfect lips!
Ellie Calhoun: my client is late -
Cheryl French: Welcome back @Ellie Calhoun
Eff Guitar: Cheryl is hereeeee
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: great color on you
Ellie Calhoun: great smile!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Efrain @Eff Guitar!!! perfect timing to come in. Markus is doing a great makeup challenge!!!
Eff Guitar: 🫶
Mommy Guide Inc: this is EPIC!
MySnoopy80: You look awesome
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: mascara
Tech Troublemaker: You Look Fabulous @Markus Schaub
Tim Heale 9: 😻very pantomime dame 😻
Eaglevp: This should go viral
Make and Do Crafts: You ate a raspberry ice lolly!
Mommy Guide Inc: in fairness the lipstick turned out to be a great color!
Tech Troublemaker: turn this all into a sped up short.
Cheryl French: Good idea, @Tech Troublemaker!
Eaglevp: Those lips look so kissable
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh great idea @Tech Troublemaker - sped up version!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh nooooo... work!
Make and Do Crafts: the power of makeup!!
Ellie Calhoun: I like the lipstick color!
Kali Co: dang just go tback from bird's walk
Kali Co: i missed the tutorial!
Kali Co: LOL
Mommy Guide Inc: thanks Ana & Markus! oh ok - Roy you're up next!
MySnoopy80: Yes I am😂😂
Cheryl Wolf: Markus Transformed
Mommy Guide Inc: Kali this is the finished output!
Tech Troublemaker: I would have to go with Blue hair and goth makeup
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: kissable! 👄💋💄
Eff Guitar: Markus is a light to the world of streams
Tina Wan Kenobi: All made up again Markus!
MySnoopy80: Roy that sounds awesome
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Tina Wan Kenobi!!!
Sammy Super Star: Markus looks so good!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Happy Anniversary!!! enjoy the coffee
Cheryl French: Bye Ana!
Cheryl Wolf: Great Job Ana
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: oh directing by the talent. hahaha
Mommy Guide Inc: thanks for waking up early to watch Markus' anniversary!!!
Ellie Calhoun: 😍😘😍
Make and Do Crafts: This has been so much fun! Thank you Marcus!
Tim Heale 9: TTFN Tar tar for now
MySnoopy80: Bye Ana
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: bye ana
Tina Wan Kenobi: Good morning La, and everyone!
Sammy Super Star: Next time put a wig on!
Sammy Super Star: Hahaha 🤣
Ellie Calhoun: Markus Rules!!!
Eff Guitar: You look markvelous
Tina Wan Kenobi: Red Lips 🔥
MySnoopy80: So I guess I have to wait a little longer to kiss you
Tim Heale 9: Almost perfect
Mommy Guide Inc: TTFN to our friends from the UK!
Eaglevp: Bye all
Cheryl French: Congrats, @Markus Shaub !!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks everyone for joining Markus and celebrating this awesome milestone with him!
MySnoopy80: Oh not that long then😄
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: So much fun!
Make and Do Crafts: TTFN!!🥰
Tina Wan Kenobi: Congratulations Markus 🥳
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: happy anniversary.... here's to many more