Markus Schaub: join my Discord: https://discord.gg/Pf4mtWcQn2
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi everyone!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hello! I am ready Freddy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: And here is Markus!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: 💃🏿💃🏿💃🏿
Cheryl Wolf: Dance it out 💃🏼
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Cheryl!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: 👯‍♀👯‍♀👯‍♀👯‍♀👯‍♀
Cheryl Wolf: Hi lala 💜
Cheryl Wolf: Hello Ana
Tatiana Teaches: Ring of fire 🔥
Mommy Guide Inc: If you are not yet part of Markus' Discord please click on the pinned link above!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Tatiana!!!
Cheryl Wolf: I love this opeing !!
Mommy Guide Inc: Let's Go Live Streamers!!!!
Cheryl Wolf: I love this opening video
Tatiana Teaches: Hello 🙂🙃🙂
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Cheryl!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: What an awesome journey Markus!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I love it too!!! I sing it here and there when I hear it so catchy!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hello!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Present!
Cheryl Wolf: I am excited to be here
Mommy Guide Inc: Announcements!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: PARTY!!!!!!
Cheryl Wolf: 🎉
Mommy Guide Inc: Friday!!!! - because yey - Happy 1st Year Anniversary!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Sending it out after the show:) just finished
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: It's going to be awesome!
Mommy Guide Inc: Save the Date!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: oh yeah - Markus on the hot seat!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: oh gosh...I need to figure out central time
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus is always ready. wow a spanking now mat! I love it!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Look at you!!!! you are ready Freddy!
Cheryl Wolf: Don't run with your scissors Markus
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: 🤣🤣🤣
Mommy Guide Inc: You can still join us on Markus Discord if you want to be part of this accountability program:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Links to Markus Discord pinned on top.
Mommy Guide Inc: What you think guys?
Kimbuucha: Just stopping by to show support and say hello 👋🏾
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Kimbuucha!!! Great to see you back!
Kimbuucha: I’m new here. I saw Mommy Lala shared your stream ☺️
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks @Kimbuucha. Markus Kim is an awesome content creator too!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Welcome Kimbuucha!
Mommy Guide Inc: I loved both your content. Maybe alternating them?
Kimbuucha: Have you checked out HeatherJustcreate and The Couples Table? They are doing a stream on this exact topic that might help ☺️
Mommy Guide Inc: 3 times a month interview and 1LLPGP in a month?
Kimbuucha: I don’t have much input right now though. My channel is all over the place right now and I’m too busy to create content 😭
Mommy Guide Inc: LLPGP - member reports and maybe we invite an expert halfway thru?
Eaglevp: Evening Marcus
Eaglevp: Evening Lala
Eaglevp: It's Keith from Leda
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Eaglevp!
Mommy Guide Inc: Do you love doing the interviews?
Mommy Guide Inc: I do know you are also a great tech person.
Mommy Guide Inc: there you go! Interviews then for the win:)
Mommy Guide Inc: https://youtu.be/K8Q2SUhYMVE join me and Markus tomorrow!!! it's at 8AM EST
Mommy Guide Inc: My time it's 8PM Philippine Time
Mommy Guide Inc: For Ana it's 8AM EST/ the 7AM CST
Tatiana Teaches: Best wishes as you make big decisions! I have to head out. ✌🏼
Eaglevp: Lala what time in the UK
Cheryl Wolf: You can teach me us something
Mommy Guide Inc: Let's Interview the Interviewer for tongiht
Eaglevp: Just waffle on Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Tatiana:)
Eaglevp: Hi Cheryl Wolf
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Thank you
Cheryl Wolf: Hi keith
Mommy Guide Inc: ooh nice Idea Cheryl - maybe some weeks we can do a Challenge Markus day
Eaglevp: You already have the moves Markus
Cheryl Wolf: yes lala
Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Hi Markus😀
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: yep! Markus got the moves
Eaglevp: Hi Ejnar
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Ejnar
Mommy Guide Inc: Those days - you do the challenge. We send over the challenge a week in advance.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ejnar!
Mommy Guide Inc: please don't forget to smash that LIKE button:)
Mommy Guide Inc: so you have several segments. Can Markus do it??? That's what we need to know so we need to be there!
Cheryl Wolf: Share a story with us about something you have learned
Mommy Guide Inc: LEDA - Live Everyday In April/August of Luria Petrucci's LSP
Mommy Guide Inc: Hope to see you there next year @Kimbuucha!
Mommy Guide Inc: And for any comments/suggestion/inputs - Markus Discord is pinned above we would love to see you there!
Mommy Guide Inc: wow how time flies!
Connecting on the Net: Yay I made it!
Mommy Guide Inc: If you want to see Markus crafting for a change - join us tomorrow on Mommy Guie Inc https://youtu.be/K8Q2SUhYMVE
Connecting on the Net: Mary Speegle
Connecting on the Net: Oops!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Mary @Connecting on the Net!!!
Eaglevp: Hi Mary
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus might show you another side of him you didn't know he can do! He is so prepared already:)