Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Markus! Hi Ejnar! Good day to all of you:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus Rules!
Mommy Guide Inc: Great thoughts:)
Adam Tinkoff: Hello friends
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Adam!:)
Mommy Guide Inc: absolutely Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Easier to manage for Markus I agree if we do it privately moving on. It has been a great run. I absolutely learned so much because of LLPGP:) 14 awesome episodes:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Discord? Facebook? Youtube? What's your take?
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hi guys 👋
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I’m all for whatever works best for all
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I’m jealous about Adam’s vaca!!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I’ve been out for two weeks but I’m coming back to do a soft entrance next week and full five once LEDA STARTS!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: oh yeah! LEDA let's go indeed!
Mommy Guide Inc: Organization of discussions indeed is the reason why I have a Discord for my own channel.
Mommy Guide Inc: What do you think Ana?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi everyone.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Janet!!! Hope everything is well:)
Coffee Talk & Tech: hi Markus and everyone
Coffee Talk & Tech: Markus the crafty one.
Coffee Talk & Tech: ohh Lala was the best teacher
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi John @Coffee Talk & Tech!
Coffee Talk & Tech: hiiiii
Mommy Guide Inc: I know exciting stuff is coming for Coffee Talk and Tech. Is the Streaming Studio make over done?
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I would love nothing more than being there in February ♥️ I’ll keep dreaming
Mommy Guide Inc: Please don't forget to like this stream:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes please Ana - I will pray alongside you for this! Bring the whole family. Promise Boracay is awesome!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: My update is that I’m redecorating my studio and planning content with a more precise goal
Coffee Talk & Tech: almost done. I learned so much about myself this year...I just want to never loss focus of having fun. It matters more then money to me.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Thanks to our talks here I felt the need to re focus and be more purposeful
Mommy Guide Inc: awesome news Ejnar. Just keep on pushing it my friend. Sooner or later I am sure you will find the perfect fit job for you.
Coffee Talk & Tech: Ana you need to if you have expectations
Mommy Guide Inc: Absolutely agree John! To keep us going it has to still be fun. Looking forward to seeing you back on your channel. I miss Coffee Talk and Tech:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Perfect goals Ana. Doing a redo of my craft room/streaming setup as well because of a collab with other crafters from the US for a blog hop of some sort over the weekend.
Coffee Talk & Tech: plus when you have fun it shows and things just happen as a result.
Mommy Guide Inc: Adam's pivots have made me realize that it's ok to not be ok so we can make necessary changes if needed.
Mommy Guide Inc: What can you not do Coach Adam? Really? I am still wracking my brain what I can throw at you thet you cannot do. Kidding aside, you are really an amazing artist.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: You are right @Coffee Talk & Tech
Coffee Talk & Tech: pivots are great because it usually means you been enlightened on something. some people pivot fulltime...not good.
Mommy Guide Inc: Adam that would be a great idea. Great art done in a great place and probably do a quick talk/video about the place you are in. I love learning about new things - places, food, etc.
Coffee Talk & Tech: it's just hard because you see the finish line of monetization but when you get there it's not uncommon to refocus and regroup... but the push to get to that goal can be exhausting.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Will listen to replay. Max m in dr’s office. All is well 🤩
Coffee Talk & Tech: well I really noticed that in leda...so much the same....you need to be different. I have my own thoughts and ideas.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: That is why I think LEDA is so important to do. It really reminds you who you are
Coffee Talk & Tech: the journey is complex and if you try to rush it you will definitely see yourself back tracking.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes, it can go both ways
Coffee Talk & Tech: what????🥴 not everyone loves me????
Mommy Guide Inc: Great to hear that all is well with Max Janet:)
Mommy Guide Inc: amazing views on your videos on Adam. If you want to check out Adam's new channel here it is - https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC_pC07L95WiPsEf9XJeBD1Q
Mommy Guide Inc: John @Coffee Talk & Tech LOL.
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks everyone for being super awesome!
Coffee Talk & Tech: I'm glad I caught you guys...I'm usually driving.
Mommy Guide Inc: It's not the end - just pivoting onto a different platform.:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Thank y’all ♥️🙏🌸
Mommy Guide Inc: John looking forward to the many new things for @Coffee Talk & Tech
Mommy Guide Inc: Please don't forget to hit the like button