Mommy Guide Inc: Wow! What an awesome thumbnail!
Mommy Guide Inc: Excited much!
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yeah!
Ellie Calhoun: Hey Markus!!
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ellie!
Ellie Calhoun: Favorite song!
Mommy Guide Inc: Our happy music. Let’s Go!
Eaglevp: Evening Markus
Eaglevp: HiLala and Ellie
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Eaglevp:)
Ellie Calhoun: Hi, Keith, I think 🤔
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes its Keith.:)
Tim Heale 9: Hi Marcus
Eaglevp: Tim say's hello he his watching on TV
Tim Heale 9: Waffle waffle
Mommy Guide Inc: And we have @Tim - yeah!
Ellie Calhoun: What's the weather lik? We are having a glorious fall day
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: What are your thoughts on the many changes on YT as a platform
Ellie Calhoun: Tell us a story!
MySnoopy80: Hi❤️❤️
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey @MySnoopy80
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hello friends 👋♥️
MySnoopy80: Hi LALA❤️
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Ana!
Samantha JustInspire: Hi Markus
Eaglevp: Hi@Ana Zugheri - Faith 52
Samantha JustInspire: Hi Mommy LaLa and Ana
Eaglevp: Hello@Samantha JustInspire
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Samantha!
Eaglevp: Good day@MySnoopy80
Mommy Guide Inc: Ive been loving your streams on tutorials.
MySnoopy80: Good day to you@eaglevp
Eaglevp: Q.What made you decide to make a YouTube channel Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: Great question Keith.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: I love the live coz we can ask questions immediately. He he he
Eaglevp: I think both ways Markus Live and uploads
Samantha JustInspire: How have you been doing! I miss you guys! My other channel have been keeping me so busy!
Eaglevp: Your doing well waffling on
Tim Heale 9: You can always get me on 😻
Mommy Guide Inc: Pls dont forget to smash that Like button and share this stream:)
Tim Heale 9: I now have an Amazing Quiz and fun facts on a Tuesday
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow congratulations Tim!
Ellie Calhoun: I'm on Day 17 of a 21 Day Challenge on foot health.
Tim Heale 9: I have an Amazing Scary Halloween Quiz special on Monday
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes your shorts are nice. Just put them out Markus. You also need to find the perfect time to post them.
Ellie Calhoun: It's quite the challenge for me! All prerecorded videos so I'm practicing editing in iMovie
Mommy Guide Inc: Got about 600 subscribers in the past month coz of shorts
Eaglevp: You can always get me on Live any week you are short of a guest the only thing is I might take over the show.........lol
Tim Heale 9: Already smashed the like button
Samantha JustInspire: Hi Ellie and Eaglevp!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Tim!
Samantha JustInspire: Oh, I have a channel about cash stuffing and saving challenges! It’s going really well started it in April!
Samantha JustInspire: Wow that awesome @mommy guide Inc
Ellie Calhoun: I like editing but I don't like how my computer keeps crashing 😂
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus is very good with tech. I think its time. He is crazy busy at work i think.
Eaglevp: What's your channel called@Samantha JustInspire
Eaglevp: And guess what Markus I am not on his stream on Monday
Ellie Calhoun: I'm running the challenge to help others focus on their foot health, strength and mobility...
Ellie Calhoun: Awesome Lala!
Tim Heale 9: Best I start doing shorts then
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh my Ellie. Thats frustrating. I on the other hand am very bad ay editing. Still struggling w long form content editing but with shorts its easier.
Mommy Guide Inc: Ive encouraged my community to do the shorts and everyone is growing crazy fast.
Eaglevp: Lol Markus
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I’m in the car 🚗 but glad I’m able to listen 🎧 you got this!!!! 🤩
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Smashing is funner!!!! 😂
Mommy Guide Inc: This is Samantha’s channel - https://youtu.be/RdFAFDBNphg
Samantha JustInspire: Thanks @Mommy Guide Inc😊
Mommy Guide Inc: Same here Markus. I might have pneumonia.( or a post covid thing that am really struggling with the back pains
Eaglevp: Think I will have to start doing shorts
Tim Heale 9: Perhaps repurpose some of my lives into shorts
Ellie Calhoun: Oh Lala sorry about your health issues 😞
Mommy Guide Inc: Drive safely Ana! Indeed sharing and liking is caring. He he he.
Adam Tinkoff: Good morning!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: No driving…in carline picking up my daughter from school
Adam Tinkoff: It took me a full 6 weeks to get over the COVID thing after LEDA
Eaglevp: Hi@Adam Tinkoff
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh no worries Markus i always sleep early on the day of your streams. I already got 7 hours in today of sleep:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Adam:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Prayers for full healing Lala, that is terrible.
MySnoopy80: Hope you feel better soon @mommy guide inc
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Adam for checking up on me.:) thanks Ana for the prayers.:)
Samantha JustInspire: Sorry to hear that mommy Lala! Hope you feel better. Drink lots of fluids!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes! That thing needs to vanish! From our world
Mommy Guide Inc: Its almost Christmas. Are you going to do vlogmas?
Adam Tinkoff: I'm heading to Europe next week. Come visit me in Barcelona!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Thank you!!! New job is wonderful but putting me behind in my content creation
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yes. Were crazy! Christmas half of the year.
Adam Tinkoff: I'll be there.
Adam Tinkoff: Warm up the couch for me.
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes i am. It hurt my analytics last year after the vlogmas coz inwasnt going live anymore after it but simce am doing shorts daily i think itll be fine this time.
Eaglevp: Barcelona is warmer Adam
Tim Heale 9: Queen did a song about Barcelona
Adam Tinkoff: We are producing a conference for CIO crowd. Should be fun.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Exactly!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow take us with you Adam!
Adam Tinkoff: I will be posting videos
Adam Tinkoff: on my Facebook mostly.
Mommy Guide Inc: Its my dream that we can have live face to face meetup. Lets pray for a safer 2023 and make it happen:)
Adam Tinkoff: It's always fun to hang out with you Markus. You are a blessing to this community.
MySnoopy80: Very fun
Sammy Super Star: Hey Markus!
Tim Heale 9: I have a book launch this week where I contributed to, it’s all about how to get guests and be a host on podcasts and for live streams
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Markus. Its fun. Just hanging out as your thumbnail says.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hey Sammy!!!
Eaglevp: It's always fun to hang out on live streams
Adam Tinkoff: Lala knows some nice beaches. Just saying...
Eaglevp: Hi@Sammy Super Star
Mommy Guide Inc: Congratulations Tim!
MySnoopy80: But have to go to sleep now! Bye Markus and bye chat❤️
Tim Heale 9: Did you want the link?
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yes Adam and so do you! He he he
Mommy Guide Inc: Good night @MySnoopy80:)
MySnoopy80: ❤️❤️❤️
Mommy Guide Inc: Is it on your channel Tim?
Adam Tinkoff: Are there any great beaches in Switzerland. LOL
Mommy Guide Inc: Tim we would love to share your events next time. Pls send me the links.:)
Tim Heale 9: Time flys when you are just waffling
Adam Tinkoff: I dreamed I was a Captain the Swiss Navy... it was a weird dream.
Adam Tinkoff: Yeah sometimes less is more fun.
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus is showing us that no matter ehat Go Live!
Tim Heale 9: Continuity is the key just have to do it every week
Mommy Guide Inc: Absolutely Tim.
Tim Heale 9: You end up doing LEDA again
Adam Tinkoff: Waffles are delicious.
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks everyone!!! Dont forget to smash the like button on your way out.:)
Adam Tinkoff: Best party today.
Mommy Guide Inc: Its almost breakfast for me. Waffle is a great idea Adam:)
Eaglevp: Bye all
Mommy Guide Inc: Have a great rest of the day!!!
Tim Heale 9: TTFN Tar tar for now