Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sammy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey! I really love this jazzy Christmas music. Hi Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Marga! I missed the ecamm party!:(
Sandi Thompson: Hi Lala and Sammy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey! HI Sandi!
Mommy Guide Inc: Love the sweater Markus!
Sandi Thompson: Nice sweatwer!!
Sandi Thompson: *sweater
Mommy Guide Inc: Love to see you both together!
Coffee Talk & Tech: Hi Markus and Margo
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi John@Coffee Talk & Tech
Sandi Thompson: a lot going on for ADHD Sandi
Sandi Thompson: SF in the house!!!
Coffee Talk & Tech: Hi Lala!
Sandi Thompson: 7 Up for the tree is best I hear!
Sandi Thompson: Are you still in SF?
Mommy Guide Inc: wow what an amazing journey Marga!
Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
Mommy Guide Inc: Enjoy the journey and what were doing great advice Marga:)
MySnoopy80: Hi everyone:)
Sammy Super Star: Marga is so funny people said that they loved the skit for the Ecamm vlogmas
Coffee Talk & Tech: Hi Sammy
Mommy Guide Inc: I agree Sammy I have been loving her daily vlogmas:)
Sandi Thompson: I saw Robin at the Punchline in SF! He just showed up. It was so great.
Sammy Super Star: No I think you didn’t get that lol @Mommy Guide Inc. there was a Ecamm holiday party and we did a video for it
Mommy Guide Inc: oh yes Sammy I missed the party. I will watch on replay later.:) I am sure it is great! John Pullum posted about it in OVMG:)
Sandi Thompson: youtube.com/margagomezcomedy
Mommy Guide Inc: amazing Marga.
Sammy Super Star: There is no replay Lala
Sammy Super Star: Marga has a Wikipedia so that means that she is famous!!
Sammy Super Star: Your so right
Sandi Thompson: Yay! I'll come see you!!
Sammy Super Star: Have you ever done one about live streaming!
Mommy Guide Inc: yippee! That's awesome news. 14th solo show soon!
Mommy Guide Inc: oh yes Marga's vlogmas in Ecamm Live community has been super fun. And you sound awesome Marga:)
Sammy Super Star: Oh that’s amazing
Sammy Super Star: Oh that’s why you got so many mics!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Congratulations Marga! a grant even. super excited for it.
Julie Ulrich: Hi Marcus and Marga!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Julie!
Sandi Thompson: How do we find out about the live show in SF(if it happens)?
Julie Ulrich: Hi Lala! 😊
Mommy Guide Inc: One cannot put a great performer down - you are just crushing it Marga on all platforms. so proud of you!
Mommy Guide Inc: Don't forget to hit the like button everyone! Follow Marga: Instagram.com/themargagomez
Mommy Guide Inc: And indeed Marga has a website: www.margagomez.com
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed Marga - we're so proud of Markus!
Julie Ulrich: You are both superstars Markus and Marga! 👏👏👏
Mommy Guide Inc: He is not just the best supporter to everyone in the community he is also indeed one of the best interviewers. Markus is fearless now.
Mommy Guide Inc: aww thanks Marga! Love you both!
MySnoopy80: And you did I’m very proud of you&lt;3
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh June hopefully if everything is safe I might be in California that time. Keeping my fingers crossed.
Sandi Thompson: Im in Berkeley ... not far.
Sandi Thompson: LALA _ you are coming to CA????
Mommy Guide Inc: Here it is:
Mommy Guide Inc: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A5_8zyxq3Zo
Julie Ulrich: Put the light to the wall? You just changed my glasses-wearing life 😀
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Sandi should have been the month that we got locked down.:( we go every summer holidays - that's march. Yes I'll definitely meet with you Sandi when I do come:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed Marga, we will do that if and when you are able to come visit the Philippines.
Mommy Guide Inc: Latina Stream Queens : https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCZ_9P9uqUkan76dPeK4uYYg
Sandi Thompson: @Julie = bounce the light off the ceiling!!
Julie Ulrich: Just subscribed to your channel, Marga! Can’t wait to see your our content 🎉
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hello 👋
Sandi Thompson: Hi Ana!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Just jumping in to say hi 👋
Mommy Guide Inc: Hey Ana!
Mommy Guide Inc: Bwahaha! Dr. Markus.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I’ll will watch the replay! Love you both you guys are so fun
Julie Ulrich: Everyone needs Dr Markus
Sandi Thompson: Thank you!
Mommy Guide Inc: Dont forget to hit the like button on your way out everyone:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Thank you Markus and Marga.
Mommy Guide Inc: wow that's amazing. I will definitely check it out Marga.
Sandi Thompson: Marga IS inspiring!
Julie Ulrich: 👏👏👏😊
Mommy Guide Inc: Merry Christmas everyone!