Markus Schaub: Join the Content Creators Peer Group on Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/groups/401185572148782/
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Markus Schaub!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi everyone!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Love the logo Markus!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi everyone.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: don't forget to "LIKE"
Mommy Guide Inc: Coach Adam did an awesome job with the logo indeed:)
Mommy Guide Inc: HI Janet!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: LALA!!! I saw you live this morning (my time) love the event.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Roy!
Mommy Guide Inc: yes it's an awesome event. we love love books!:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Markus... dancing!! 💃💃💃💃💃
Tech Troublemaker: I love that expression when @Markus Schaub has an idea!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Janet!
Rich Vybz: Hey Markus
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: content creator peer group
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Rich!!!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Rich Vybz
Rich Vybz: Hey Mommy.. Hey ttm
Mommy Guide Inc: It was a nice stream. The topic as well was interesting:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I love the short. You inspired me with that one.
Mommy Guide Inc: oh yes congratulations on the shorts!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I would love to know
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh boy!! 😻🎉
Mommy Guide Inc: I have been creating shorts this week too!
Mommy Guide Inc: it's easier to make indeed and am enjoying it. some got 5 digit views! it's mind blowing:)
Mommy Guide Inc: thanks for creating TCCPG program. That is where I started becoming more consistent in creating edited videos.
Mommy Guide Inc: I wouldn't have been able to create these shorts if I didnt start doing the little longer ones in our group:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh you use descript?
Mommy Guide Inc: thanks for sharing this stream everyone!
Tech Troublemaker: I am terrible at shorts. It literally feels like it takes a different part of the brain. I can't explain things with so little time by my nature.
Mommy Guide Inc: oh yes Descript I use it to repurpose my lives into podcasts:)
Mommy Guide Inc: but not for shorts. awesome tip Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Roy I love the tech short jokes:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Epic words! The birth of Markus/Kali Rules!
Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
Mommy Guide Inc: ooh fancy captions is the command.
Mommy Guide Inc: thanks Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: And here is Sammy who is crushing his shorts too!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hey Sammy!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Sammy's doing what??? hahaha and Hi Sammy
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: you can publish directly from Descript to YouTube?
Mommy Guide Inc: oops that didn't sound so right - right Janet? LOL
Mommy Guide Inc: awesome!!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Thanks Markus for sharing this. love it
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: oh those kind of shorts. hahaha
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Ohhhhhh.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: You did a great job. thank you so much
Mommy Guide Inc: oh yes Markus I am using Splice - but this is super awesome! I'll try to use this technique today and create one:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I was inspired by Lala as well and set up a calendly. so easy peasy
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: We all give each other great ideas right?
Mommy Guide Inc: yey!!! guest interviews coming again soon! but we love this solo streams too Markus and thanks for sharing these awesome tips:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I agree Lala. both!