Mommy Guide Inc: Two of my fav content creators in the house today! Weeou
Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
Mommy Guide Inc: Hey Sammy!
Ellie Calhoun: Hi 👋
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ellie!!!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Markus Schaub @Mommy Guide Inc @Sammy Super Star @Ellie Calhoun and Adam!!!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Roy@Tech Triublemaker
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hello 👋 everyone
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Ana Zugheri:)
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Lala!
hughdemand: Hey folks !
Mommy Guide Inc: Adam playing with his awesome camera! Go find Adam!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey everyone
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Janet:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Whit in the house!
hughdemand: Adam and his hitek graphics
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: You are dancing, I’m dancing everyone is dancing 💃
hughdemand: I know one who is not dancing
Mommy Guide Inc: Am finger dancing he he he - Let’s go!
Mommy Guide Inc: Don’t forget to like and share this stream everyone! Thanks.
hughdemand: All the "All Stars" in this countdown !
Mommy Guide Inc: I miss you all:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Lala
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Ellie
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Anna!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hi there!
Cheryl Wolf: Hello
hughdemand: Hi @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey @Cheryl!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Markus
Sammy Super Star: 💃🕺💃🕺💃🕺💃
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Sammy!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: So glad y’all are here!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh hi Roy
Serenity Studio Art : Hello Markus!
Cheryl Wolf: Hi lala and All
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Cheryl
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Diana @SerenityArt:)
Cheryl Wolf: Hey Janet
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Adam
Serenity Studio Art : Lijked and shared
Cheryl Wolf: Echo
Serenity Studio Art : Adam has an echo bad
Mommy Guide Inc: Love everyone is here! Don’t forget to hit the like button:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: yes Echo on Adam's mic
Cheryl Wolf: Yes better
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes better!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Better
Eaglevp: Hi Marcus
Serenity Studio Art : Good no Echo now
Eaglevp: Hello Cheryl
Eaglevp: Hi Lala
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Keith
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes segregation of trash is a must.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Eaglevp
Serenity Studio Art : Hi Lala !
Eaglevp: Hi@Serenity Studio Art
Serenity Studio Art : Hi @Eaglevp 👋🏼
Ellie Calhoun: our trash is so less stinky because we have a compost company come get our compost including meat etc.
Cheryl Wolf: My grandfather owned trash business, he found many treasures
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh Ellie that would be amazing to have someone come take the compost. we don't have that down here
Ellie Calhoun: Sara just wrote a post about cleaning out her dear departed friends home... really hard work
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow decluttering once a year! Awesome!
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh twice a year - double awesome!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: That is so true Adam.
Mary Speegle: What a great interview!
Eaglevp: Hi@Ellie Calhoun @Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing
Ellie Calhoun: I'm trying to use less paper in my planning work, but it's really hard to make that transition!
Eaglevp: Hey@Mary Speegle
Mommy Guide Inc: Adam is almost at the finish line with his sketching daily faces.:) thanks Adam I loved looking forward to your daily sketches
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Keith!
Eaglevp: How are you Ellie3
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Don't forget to LIKE!
Ellie Calhoun: good...
Mary Speegle: I loved Adam’s sketches too!
Mommy Guide Inc: Adam’s YouTube channel - https://youtube.com/c/AdamTinkoff
Eaglevp: Agree Adam;s drawing at amazing
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Mary:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I think that’s smart
Eaglevp: Hi@Ana Zugheri - Faith 52
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: You and I both! Is that a creator’s thing?
Mary Speegle: Do you sell the sketches you do youtube? Do you take requests?
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed Adam it’s almost a year since Expand Your Reach.:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Glad you are here Eaglevp!
Mary Speegle: Hi Lala! 🥳
Tech Troublemaker: I am really enjoying Adam's speedy art.
Eaglevp: Hello@Tech Troublemaker
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: It sounds like LEDA in Stone Age 😂
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Eaglevp
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Your sketches are amazing 🤩
Mommy Guide Inc: LEDA is really awesome. Learned so much specially about engagement:)
Serenity Studio Art : Your portraits are WOBDERFUL ADAM
Paul Burke: Q - Adam...do you accepet commission nudes?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Paul is in the building!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Commissioned works - where do you find the time Adam. Again here is Adam’s YT channel - https://youtube.com/c/AdamTinkoff
Paul Burke: hey @Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing 😀
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Paul!!!
Paul Burke: hey @Mommy Guide Inc 😁
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Such talent. I so admire artists
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Q where do you get your models from?
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I love that they show emotions
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: capturing the "soul"
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Q how long does it take you to do one of those?
hughdemand: Adam was my Podcast Coach. He took me from zero to 60 in no time. Far superior to most of the excellent tutorials on YT.
Mary Speegle: @Adam how do you pick your subjects?
Mommy Guide Inc: I remember asking Adam how he is able to sketch these awesome faces in just about an hour or so. He said a lifetime of practice! Such wisdom:)
Serenity Studio Art : Q-What 30 day challenge will Adam do next ?
Mommy Guide Inc: Great question Diana@Serenity Art!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Beautiful
Mommy Guide Inc: Digitizing the awesome drawings / sketches:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: You have my permission to draw me 😄
Mommy Guide Inc: Absolutely agree Whit! Adam is an awesome enabler:)
Marga Gomez: wow Lovd this interview. so passionate. yay Adam!!
Marga Gomez: haha
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: 😂
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey )Hi Marga!
Marga Gomez: hi Lala
Marga Gomez: i just 👍🏽that on ur fb page
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Omygoodness it looks great to me!!!!!
Marga Gomez: i have a crush on eyes closed lady
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I like this one. You remind me of our wedding photographer withheld my favorite photo. thankfully he did not destroy it and I was able to get the negatives.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh love that. 100 faces. one day at a time
Marga Gomez: yas don’t stop 💯💯
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: No way!!!!
Serenity Studio Art : Hey hello !@Marga Gomez
Mary Speegle: More, more, more!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey a new goal! Let’s go - 100 faces!
Mommy Guide Inc: Maybe we will see some of our faces. He he he
Marga Gomez: nice scene changing Markus!
Marga Gomez: don’t cut off your ear Adam
Marga Gomez: haha
Mary Speegle: Marga-🤣🤣
Marga Gomez: mary😂
hughdemand: Drink and drain !
Marga Gomez: Hi @Serenity Studio Art
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I learned so much from your podcast
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes it was a blessing to be with you Adam in the 90-Day Sprint. Knowing when to say No and pivot is something very hard for most but you showed us that if it doesn’t give you joy you can end and pivot
Serenity Studio Art : Q-how many marathons has Adam run?
Paul Burke: I remember when Markus said something 20 minutes ago
Ellie Calhoun: @paul 😂
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: 😂😂😂
Marga Gomez: you can stink at the end too hahaha
Paul Burke: @Ellie Calhoun 😏
hughdemand: Did Markus design the preset to blend with Adam's background?
Mommy Guide Inc: To start - just start!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: We all need to "stand in our greatness"
Marga Gomez: Inspiring fellas!
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed one day less - nice perspective there Adam.
Marga Gomez: We refuse the neg self talk
Ellie Calhoun: Yes Markus👍 give what people want but intersect with what you love
Paul Burke: I wonder if anyone is watching from a hospital bed when Adam said, "you have one day less"
Marga Gomez: haha @Paul Burke stressed me out with frozen shoulder
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Paul!!😂
Mommy Guide Inc: Powerful why - leaving a legacy
Paul Burke: @Marga Gomez ...oh no!
Paul Burke: @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52 😂😂
Marga Gomez: hahah--- well only slightly @Paul Burke
Rich Vybz: Hey guys
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Rich!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for sharing the smashing the LIKE button:)
Marga Gomez: okay I am interested in the audio range -- I like that their mics are good but different -- that's a good thing. Audio variety - personalities
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Rich Vybz
Mommy Guide Inc: Comedy? Comedian - we have Marga in the house now.:)
Rich Vybz: Hey tech.. hey Mommy
hughdemand: It's been great folks but I have to opt out. Take care. Thanks Markus and Coach Adam.
Marga Gomez: @Mommy Guide Inc and @Paul Burke
Tech Troublemaker: Marathon not a sprint but stay hydrated....
Marga Gomez: wow! Markus please do my makeup
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Whit! Take care.
Marga Gomez: DElight❤️❤️❤️
Rich Vybz: Delight= engage
Marga Gomez: LOVE THIS!
Paul Burke: If you hate it though and think it doesn't have meaning...isn't that a feeling...and then it would be art. So....anything could be art
Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Hello Everyone👍
Marga Gomez: Hi @Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming
Mommy Guide Inc: Absolutely agree @Tech Troublemaker
Rich Vybz: Dammit now i have ‘groove is in the heart’ in my head
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Ejnar!
Rich Vybz: Deelite
Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Sorry I am late. Must see the replay😀
Marga Gomez: @Rich Vybz that's a good thing
Serenity Studio Art : Hey hello @Rich Vybz
Tech Troublemaker: But I love the bots. You have to be nice to the bots as they will one day rule the world...
Marga Gomez: 90's
Marga Gomez: EPIC!
Rich Vybz: Hey Serenity.. whas cookin
Mommy Guide Inc: The feels and delight!