Eaglevp: Evening Markus
Andy Halper: Waiting to get and BE well with Cheryl (Markus too, kinda!)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hello 👋
Eaglevp: Hello@Andy Halper @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52
Andy Halper: ANA ANA ANA ANA!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: So glad y’all here! 🤩
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi everyone!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: cyeryl!! dancing
Eaglevp: Hi@Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Andy & Ana and...
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Andy Ana Janet and EagleVP!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @Eaglevp hi back
Eaglevp: Hi Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Cheryl!
Andy Halper: It's a beautiful fall day in Minnesota, good day to BE healthy, aspire to wellness~!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I love this open!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey everyone!
Andy Halper: Hey Lala!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hey Roy!
Andy Halper: ROY!\
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: 🎶
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: It’s a party 🎉
Eaglevp: Hi@Tech Troublemaker
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: 💃🕺🕺🕺💃💃💃💃💃
Mommy Guide Inc: Glad to be back on the chat! Sick but present!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Roy
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Lala are you feeling better?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @Mommy Guide Inc Luna sends healing purrs. It is "happy healing Thursday" after all
Mommy Guide Inc: Actually i feel better being with you all. Otherwise i feel awful. He he he. Being with friends is indeed a good remedy they say.:)
Andy Halper: A sick Lala is still better than most of us. Feel good soon
hughdemand: I love this intro
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Janet and Luna.:) claiming thise. Perfect topic too tonight. Let’s stay healthy!
Eaglevp: Hello@hughdemand
Andy Halper: What Hugh said
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @Mommy Guide Inc i know what you mean. I was so sick last week and yall made me feel better
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Andy.:)
hughdemand: Thanks @Eaglevp
Mommy Guide Inc: Hello Markus!
SuzanCz: hey friends!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: The one and only...
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Suzan
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi whit and Keith!
hughdemand: Hi there @Mommy Guide Inc
SuzanCz: Hi @Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing !
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Whit
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Suzan!:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Keith
Eaglevp: Hello Cheryl
SuzanCz: @Mommy Guide Inc Are you up late or up early?!
Andy Halper: CHERYL, yeah, keep move'n!
hughdemand: Hi Roy
SuzanCz: Cheryl has an amazing story!
SuzanCz: Oh! What states were you in?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh Cheryl you could write a book I'll bet
Mommy Guide Inc: Suzan early cant sleep.:( coughing fits.
SuzanCz: @Mommy Guide Inc Ugh. Sorry! I hope you're on the way to healing and feeling better.
Eaglevp: Hi@SuzanCz
Andy Halper: horrid ...
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Don’t forget to like and share!
Tim Heale 9: Hi Marcus, Cheryl 😻
SuzanCz: Hey there, @Eaglevp
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: 😂
Eaglevp: Hi@Tim Heale 9 great show tonight
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Tim!:)
Mommy Guide Inc: What a journey Cheryl. You are an inspiration.
Andy Halper: self-trust
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: That had to be hard!
Mommy Guide Inc: Our mind can really play awful tricks on us. Awesome!!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: don't forget to LIKE
SuzanCz: It's a powerful story! You've come such a long way!
Andy Halper: You tell your story very well
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: You are such an inspiration for others
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: ♥️♥️♥️♥️♥️🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉
Mommy Guide Inc: So true Cheryl.:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: What a testimony!
hughdemand: A definite inspiration
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for liking and sharing this awesome stream.
Andy Halper: This is your raison d'tera, your reason for being!
hughdemand: Addition by subraction
Mommy Guide Inc: Great perspective- positive words- gain something:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I love how you turn things around and make a positive on every level
Andy Halper: The JOY in the heart, beautifully said!
Ellie Calhoun: late but I'm here!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Ellie
Eaglevp: Hi@Ellie Calhoun
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Welcome Ellie!
SuzanCz: Ellie!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ellie:)
SuzanCz: That's a great point -- everyone is different. Our challenges and best food choices are different.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Well said!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Awareness! For wellness!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey!!!
Andy Halper: Ambiguity and risk taking can keep the bloodstream flowing, I agree!
Ellie Calhoun: thanks - good to "see" you all but mostly great to see Cheryl here!
SuzanCz: ❤️❤❤
Mommy Guide Inc: Scary indeed but when you are surrounded with amazing people like everyone here it becomes so much easier and doable.:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: 👍
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Beautiful
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: And your story is also very inspiring for us!
Andy Halper: Serious fun ... !
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Don't forget to LIKE 👍
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Your Wednesday live streams are awesome 👏
Eaglevp: It's to late for me Markus
Laura Williams: oh I need to get there-42
hughdemand: Haha
Ellie Calhoun: I'm a little more weight than before but definitely feel better now than I did in my 40's!
Andy Halper: It's ain't too early and it ain't too late Markus!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: can't wait for the group
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed that’s a great reminder Cheryl that coaches are not the answer to all our issues but they will help guide us in finding the answers to our questions. We also have to do a lot of work
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Markus!!!! 😂
SuzanCz: I was in great shape in my 30's... it's a long road trying to get back to something like that.
SuzanCz: It helps to hear that it took you 4 years, Cheryl. It's a long road, but the journey is worth it!
Andy Halper: IF NOT NOW, WHEN??
SuzanCz: Do it now! Get it done!
SuzanCz: Jump! I love it!
SuzanCz: Q: Do you have any recommendations for us over-50 folks?
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey looking forward to this wellness group:)
Tim Heale 9: Q Who do you have on next week?
SuzanCz: @Mommy Guide Inc Yes -- we still have to do the work. Cheryl is the guide we need.
Andy Halper: WHAT LALA SAID!
SuzanCz: You missed my Q, Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: And blessed to have you as a coach too Suzan.:) thanks to awesome coaches.:)
Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Sammy
Eaglevp: Hi Sammy
Ellie Calhoun: I love to sleep!
Mommy Guide Inc: A friend is encouraging me to do 20k steps in a day. Will try it out soon. Hi Sammy!
Mommy Guide Inc: I take naps - like Sammy!
Andy Halper: Your friend is a good friend, Lala!
SuzanCz: I've noticed that if I sleep well, it's easier to eat well!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Adny she is 66 but she’s so much healthier than I am.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Thanks to Cheryl I drink water
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52 thanks for the reminder about water.
SuzanCz: Good for you, @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52! I struggle to keep drinking water throughout the day.
Andy Halper: Keep on keep'n on, Lala!
SuzanCz: If you don't find time, you
Ellie Calhoun: I lost weight at 50, but now in my 60's it's harder again...
SuzanCz: If you don't find time, you'll run out of time!
Mommy Guide Inc: Dont forget to smash the like button friends:)
SuzanCz: I need 8.5 hours!
Mommy Guide Inc: A treadmill under my desk - great suggestion Cheryl. LOL kidding aside ill try to do 5k first and move up from there
SuzanCz: Good idea, @Mommy Guide Inc. Build up to it.
Ellie Calhoun: I wake up to feed the pesky cat, then nap on the couch for another hour!
SuzanCz: @Ellie Calhoun We should do some walking!
Ellie Calhoun: yes!
Ellie Calhoun: @SuzanCz yes!
Andy Halper: I'm 72, I sleep 8.5 hour a night, I weigh 5 more pounds than I did in High School, but it looks all difference. Now you know everything about me.
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Suzan. When i became a mom i stopped exercising. Now that mg kids are older i hve more time for myself.:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I hear you Andy! I'm 2 years younger than you big brother! haha.
Ellie Calhoun: Lala, striving for 20K steps a day is way too much for me. I wouldn't get anything else done. right now I get 5000 a day and maybe I'll increase that to 6k in oct. small baby steps
SuzanCz: I had that conversation with my mother this morning: I don't have to answer your text right after you've sent it! Haha! It needs to be ok to wait and reply later.
SuzanCz: @Andy - haha! Nice.
Ellie Calhoun: I have to have my phone in my pocket to track my steps lol!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Ellie. Indeed ill start w 5k once i get better.
Andy Halper: @SuzanCz ... you ain't so bad yourself!
Tim Heale 9: I start the day with a cat jumping on me wanting feeding then the dog starts
Mommy Guide Inc: Pacing indeed.:)
Andy Halper: LOVE your swinging!
SuzanCz: @Andy Halper ❤
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh good one Cheryl. I'm going to do that.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I need a swing!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Love that short too of Janet
SuzanCz: It's a great FB Group!
Mommy Guide Inc: Cheryl’s links are all in the description.:)
Ellie Calhoun: I just requested to join 🙂
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey!!!
SuzanCz: Wellness goal: don't overeat at night (my nemesis!)
Ellie Calhoun: Im going to go back to drink a glass of water first when I wake up
SuzanCz: Oh -- good one, @Ellie Calhoun !
Mommy Guide Inc: Great Ellie - will do that too! I dont think i drink enough water:(
SuzanCz: Great interview! Lots of gold. Thank you!
Ellie Calhoun: get an accountability partner. when my friend and I walked regularly together, we didn't want to disappoint each other.
Ellie Calhoun: Yay! Cheryl!!
SuzanCz: @Ellie Calhoun that's a great idea!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Thanks Cheryl - such an inspiration.
Andy Halper: Nicely done, both of you.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Thanks Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: Procrastination! Go away! Lets all start taking those baby steps.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I'm with you lala