Kali Co: 💃💃💃💃💃
Kali Co: this is a jam
Kali Co: i feel like i need to be in a room with changing lights
Kali Co: 💃💃💃💃
Kali Co: 💃❤️💃❤️💃
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Kali!!
Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
Kali Co: @Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing janet!!!
Kali Co: hi 🤗❤️
Kali Co: @Sammy Super Star hey!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: 🎉🎊💃🕺
Kali Co: daaaang this goes heavy
Kali Co: inst inst inst inst
Sammy Super Star: Hahah
Kali Co: awwweee favorite
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Sammy!!! I thought it said "super size" hahahaha. super sized super star 🌟
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I love love love this open
Sammy Super Star: 🕺💃🕺💃💃🕺💃💃💃💃💃🕺🕺🕺🕺
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I can't wait to see the wheel of names. do tell!!
Kali Co: the wheel of names is awesome
Kali Co: there are two time periods now: John Pullum before beard, and John Pullum after beard. (JPBB and JPAB)
MySnoopy80: Hi everyone
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: hahaha about John P
Kali Co: @MySnoopy80 hey!
Kali Co: @Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing 😂
MySnoopy80: Hi KALI
Kali Co: who's that hottie
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @MySnoopy80 Hi
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: surprise Markus!!
Kali Co: #MARKUSRULES
MySnoopy80: HI@Animal Paradise
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: You are my inspiration. I can't wait
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: NOT me
Kali Co: i do! wheel of names is great
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: hee hee hee
Kali Co: awe ❤
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: is it is discord?
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hi
MySnoopy80: Hi Ana
Markus Schaub: https://wheelofnames.com
Kali Co: @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52 hey!
Adam Tinkoff: Markus!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi @Anna
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hello everyone! So glad to see you here
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Wheel is so much fun!
Whit Prophet: In saw this on a stream, and billy be damned, it didn't pick up my name. So I wasn't even in the contest.
Adam Tinkoff: Elvis Costello used to tour with a Wheel of Songs suggested by the fans
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Lol
Kali Co: @Adam Tinkoff that's badass
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Maybe also to pick a topic and letting the audience build the wheel
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Kail you are red!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Moni is the only green!
Sammy Super Star: I see my name
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Don’t forget to like, share and subscribe!
Kali Co: i better win
Kali Co: AWWWWWW YEEEEEEE
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: KALI!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I feel lucky 🍀
Whit Prophet: I like it., this version is rigged if Kali wins!
Kali Co: this means i get to buy myself a nice drink today
Kali Co: @Whit Prophet LOL
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh buy a coffee!!! for Kail!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Woooo hooo congratulations 🎉 Kali!!!!
Kali Co: i win the ability to buy myself a moscow mule today
Kali Co: hahahaha
Kali Co: nooo no don't send me the cost! that's okay 😂
MySnoopy80: @kali cheers!
Kali Co: @MySnoopy80 ❤
Kali Co: dang janet got robbed twice in a row now hahaha
Adam Tinkoff: Yay!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Lol 🥳
Adam Tinkoff: My mom was right! I really am a winner
Kali Co: woahh i like your picture in thre
Kali Co: that's cool
Kali Co: @Adam Tinkoff LOL
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh that is fun
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Pretty user friendly!
Kali Co: LOL
Kali Co: oh dang now the suspense
MySnoopy80: put on makeup?
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes lol the makeup 💄
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: haha that's a good one Moni
Andy Halper: FUN!
Kali Co: HAPPY BIRTHDAY ANDY!!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Andy
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Happy birthday
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: everyone has to sing along!!!
Andy Halper: Thanks Kali! Thanks Markus!
MySnoopy80: @andy Happy Birthday
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: yay
Andy Halper: B-E-A-U-T-I-F-U-L!
Kali Co: @Andy Halper ❤
Kali Co: yes!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: yes
Kali Co: one more one more
Andy Halper: yeah yeah yeah!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: 🥳💃🧁🍰🎂🍭
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: noooooooo
Serenity Studio Art : Hi Markus
Kali Co: the wheel has spoken
Andy Halper: hahahah! Nicely done, Markus!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Lol
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Thank you for showing us!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: thank you so much
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: see you next time....
Whit Prophet: Thanks Markus