Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yeah!
Mommy Guide Inc: And it’s countdown time!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi everyone!!!
Cheryl Wolf: Hello eveyone!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Cheryl!
Success with Sunita: how do I join:)
Markus Schaub: https://clicktojoin.live/c5ef51151
Cheryl Wolf: yes!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey hi Sunita!
MySnoopy80: Hi❤️❤️
Cheryl Wolf: Hey Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: If there is an award for best intro for a live stream - this is for sure the winner!
Cheryl Wolf: totally
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi My Snoopy!!!
MySnoopy80: Hi LALA❤️
MySnoopy80: The intro is really cool👊
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks everyone for coming today. Pls don’t forget to share and like this stream:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Your audio is breaking up a bit Markus.
Cheryl Wolf: 🎉
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey now we hear you Sunita. No slapback even without the headphone from Sunita.
Cheryl Wolf: 1st time live
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sunita!
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh exciting topic.
Mommy Guide Inc: Sunita’s YT channel: https://youtube.com/user/sunnykumar77
Cheryl Wolf: yes my kind of stuff!!
Mommy Guide Inc: A cosmic guide.
Cheryl Wolf: yes human design!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Human Design sounds very interesting
Cheryl Wolf: I am MG
Mommy Guide Inc: So Sunita for it to work one needs to believe in it?
Cheryl Wolf: my husband is reflector
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Markus & Sunita
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow Cheryl knows this topic quite well too.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Janet:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh I love Human Design. Hi everyone
Cheryl Wolf: I enjoy learning
Mommy Guide Inc: Janet @AnimalParadise -Communication &Healing - are you interested also in Human Design?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @Mommy Guide I so love it. I'm a Projector. ;-)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @Mommy Guide Inc are you?
Mommy Guide Inc: First time to hear about it Janet. It sounds very interesting:)
Mommy Guide Inc: If you have a question w just put a Q: so Markus can easily see it.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: If you are interested to know more of Sunita’s content - https://youtube.com/user/sunnykumar77
Cheryl Wolf: Sturgeon full moon
Eaglevp: hI mARCUS
Eaglevp: Hi Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: Makes sense Sunita. Now we see a more solid application
Eaglevp: Good day Cheryl Wolf
Cheryl Wolf: Hello eaglevp
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Eaglevp!
Eaglevp: It's Keith from Leda Cheryl
Cheryl Wolf: Thank you , keith
Eaglevp: Hello @Mommy Guide Inc how are you today
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Keith! Thanks for dropping by:)
Eaglevp: Enjoying the the stream
Mommy Guide Inc: Absolutely awake for sure Keith@Eaglevp.:)
Cheryl Wolf: Today seems like the struggle between me and we with the full moon today. What are your thoughts
Mommy Guide Inc: Pls don’t forget to like this stream by hitting that like button.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey to first times!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: congratulations to the 13 subs
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow absolutely for a first video 3digit views - awesome!
Cheryl Wolf: lala is rockstar
Mommy Guide Inc: Aww thanks guys.:) ❤️ ❤️ ❤️
Mommy Guide Inc: True short content videos are really blowing up!
Eaglevp: Still prefer the longer format video;s
Sammy Super Star: Hey Everyone
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Sammy
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Hi Sammy!!!
Cheryl Wolf: Hey sammy
Sammy Super Star: Hey Cheryl!
Eaglevp: Hi@Sammy Super Star
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow really? Time flew by so fast!
Cheryl Wolf: Thank you !
Mommy Guide Inc: Thank you Markus and Sunita!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Thanks Markus & Sunita
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for being her everyone!!!