Sarah | Small Changes: I'm excited! 🎉
Mommy Guide Inc: yey!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Markus!!!!
Tech Troublemaker: hey everyone!
Sara S: Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy and Sarah!
MySnoopy80: Hi:))
Mommy Guide Inc: yey Sara!!!
Sarah | Small Changes: SARA!! LALA!!
Sarah | Small Changes: ROY!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Go Markus!!! I too am struggling with putting out recorded videos:(
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @MySnoopy80 !!!
MySnoopy80: Hi LALA
Abigail Marshall: vuN .Rent
Mommy Guide Inc: we love saying Hi to everyone. Missing you all so it's so nice to see you here:)
Paul Burke: SARAH! LALA! ROY!
Paul Burke: Markus....let's talk about your feelings....why the terror my man?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Paul!!
Paul Burke: why are you scared to record a video?
Sarah | Small Changes: PAUL!!
MySnoopy80: Do it
Sarah | Small Changes: LIVE therapy with Paul
Mommy Guide Inc: Do it!
Tech Troublemaker: Do It!!!
Sarah | Small Changes: DO IT!!!!!!!!
Paul Burke: DO IT!
Sarah | Small Changes: DO IT!!!!!!!
Sarah | Small Changes: LIVE streaming studio tour!!
MySnoopy80: I put the date in my calendar:)
Paul Burke: Oh. I see. Well....thank god there's no perfect idea
Paul Burke: What about..."what's my i closets behind me"
Mommy Guide Inc: Recorded video is hard for me because it entails more preparation - a script and creating Brolls etc. I can make up a million reasons not to start:(
MySnoopy80: Oh please not the closet:)))))
Paul Burke: Markus...you're talking to a bunch of people that like to see Luria's plants....I think we'll be interested in your tshirts and shoes too
MySnoopy80: Or Markus will tell me to get rid of my clothes😱
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL Paul!
MySnoopy80: I'll do that:))
Sarah | Small Changes: Declutter my studio video?
Paul Burke: Markus!! Do a How to Clutter Better video! Clutter Like a Pro
Sarah | Small Changes: bahahahaha
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL Paul! I think Markus is not so good in cluttering. Talk to a crafter - they're the best at creating clutter! Who is that???
Paul Burke: Sarah...maybe you shuld do that. on April Fools Day Sarah....a clutter pro tips tutorial
Paul Burke: @Mommy Guide Inc ....crafters....they see potential in everything...so they want to hold onto it one more day 🤣
Paul Burke: that's a ton of ideas Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Go Markus!!!
Paul Burke: good work man!
Mommy Guide Inc: Now you've mentioned the dreaded word - editing!
Mommy Guide Inc: Don't forget to hit the like button guys!!!
MySnoopy80: Bye everyone