Dwain Woode MD: Hey @@Marcus…catching you live!!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Markus.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Dwain is on fire right now
Kali Co: hi Markus!
Kali Co: and dwain and janet!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Kali!
Kali Co: ❤
Dwain Woode MD: I have to admit…sometimes comparison
Kali Co: @Dwain Woode MD i think we all have that barrier for sure. i know i do
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh I hear you Dwain. Comparison-itis! I get that disease sometimes too
Dwain Woode MD: Hey @@Kali and @Janet
Kali Co: geoguesser was so much fun
Sammy Super Star: its great to see everyone
Kali Co: hey sammy!
Sammy Super Star: I think nothing is holding me back! I post everyday LOL
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: My tech is holding me back a little bit right now. my computer can’t handle but soon will have a new set up so will not have that “excuse” ha
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Sammy
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Congrats on making it to 1000 and beyond
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: We cant go live from our phone on YouTube can we?
Sammy Super Star: growing pretty fast
Sammy Super Star: 3 subscribers away from 1,200
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh cool! So a back up if tech goes down
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh wow Sammy. Moving so fast
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Streamer Accelerator group/coaching is really helping me continue and move forward in new ways
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yes, the people that show up are the biggest motivator.
Sammy Super Star: I think after I posted my first 10 shorts I feel in love
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I really like your shorts Sammy
Dwain Woode MD: Cool @Sammy
Dwain Woode MD: Sammy is doing a great job with shorts
Sammy Super Star: I can tell you some tricks and tips
Dwain Woode MD: Go ahead, Sammy!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yes do tell SS
Sammy Super Star: make it quick, edit fast and good music
Sammy Super Star: also captons helps
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yes captions are a key
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: thanks Markus.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Great topic
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Need to do the topic again
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Ring the Bell and you will get a reminder