Sandi Thompson: front row!
Lynn Clementi: second!
Inspirational Connection TV: Third!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Canid and Lyn! I am third again. Can't beat Sandi for first but still front row;0
Markus Schaub: Hi @Sandi Thompson , welcome in the front row!
Tech Troublemaker: So exciting. I am seeing the behind the scenes behind the scenes... Inception.
Markus Schaub: @Lynn Clementi welcome!!!
Markus Schaub: Hi @Inspirational Connection TV Samantha!
Markus Schaub: Hi Lala!
Tech Troublemaker: @Mommy Guide Inc welcome, you should be sleeping. 🙂
Mommy Guide Inc: HHi Markus and Roy:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sandi not Candi. he he he
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Samantha!:). gosh you even beat me to third! he he he.
Mommy Guide Inc: Let's start smashing that like button everyone!
Mommy Guide Inc: And the dancing has started!
Ellie Calhoun: Hi everyone! Nice music!
Sammy Super Star: Ohh
Ana Zugheri: Yes
Coffee Talk & Tech: wanted to say hi...driving home.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Ellie Calhoun and @Sammy Super Star! Yey @Ana Zugheri:)
ConsistentAsh: Hey everyone
Ana Zugheri: Cool music!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: hi John @Coffee Talk & Tech drive safely!
Mommy Guide Inc: everyone let's hit that like button:)
Ana Zugheri: Hello friends 👋
Mommy Guide Inc: yey Hi Ash@ConsistentAsh:)
ConsistentAsh: Hey Mommy Lala!
Ellie Calhoun: It's like a party in here! 🎈🎶 🥳
Sammy Super Star: I see you Dancing
Inspirational Connection TV: Mommy Lala you don’t sleep!
Inspirational Connection TV: Hey everyone!
Ellie Calhoun: Hey Roy!
Inspirational Connection TV: Hey hey Roy
ConsistentAsh: Hard to hear ROy
Mommy Guide Inc: Such an exciting topic tonight! Hi Roy@Tech Troublemaker in the house!
ConsistentAsh: Roy*
Mommy Guide Inc: I agree Ash Roy your audio is a bit low
Mommy Guide Inc: https://www.youtube.com/c/TechTroublemaker
Mommy Guide Inc: that's better Roy
Sarah | Small Changes: MARKUS!!! ROY!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Sarah | Small Changes:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Put a Q before your questions so Markus and Roy can see it faster:)
Sarah | Small Changes: Can I get an amen!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Audio the bane of my streaming journey. LOL.
Sandi Thompson: @Mommy Guide Inc - audio and lighting for me!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Sandi I totally agree! Lighting and audio - are the most hard for me too.
Sarah | Small Changes: Great point! Such a great tool to make you searchable
Mommy Guide Inc: And I also like the Tech News part of Roy's streams.
Paul Burke: hey gents!
Sarah | Small Changes: PAUL!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Paul Burke!
Sandi Thompson: my problem is i have to have a talking head shot and then "on the floor shots." I cant get it right.
Sarah | Small Changes: I use a ring light... i like that it makes me look like an anime character 🤣
Paul Burke: hey @Mommy Guide Inc
Paul Burke: if you're hideous a lack of lightening can help too
Paul Burke: SARAH!!
Ana Zugheri: These are great pieces of advice
Sandi Thompson: Ahh - i have the opposite. Sony for head and webcam for floor.
Paul Burke: Sarahs new Anime Minimalism channel
Ana Zugheri: I just did that this morning with Obs ninja
Mommy Guide Inc: I totally agree Roy - save up for the best gear:) but start with what you have.
Mommy Guide Inc: https://www.youtube.com/c/TechTroublemaker
Sandi Thompson: i fell into that trap!
Sarah | Small Changes: I got to 10K subs using only an iPhone
Paul Burke: I've been shooting on the phone recently and it's been a delight not worrying about the tech (well...a small lav mic helps)
Ana Zugheri: 😂
Ellie Calhoun: Multiple choice questions
Mommy Guide Inc: No. 5 Tip - I totally agree - videos gets us more subscribers but live-streaming builds engagement more so a combination of both I guess is the way to go:).
Mommy Guide Inc: That's an awesome testimony Sarah! 10k with just a phone That's an inspiration:) No expensive stuff needed:)
Mommy Guide Inc: That's a great suggestion - my blooper video is actually one of my most viewed videos. he he he.
Paul Burke: thats so impressive @Sarah | Small Changes
Sandi Thompson: Don't forget to hit the like button!!
Sarah | Small Changes: Bahahahahaha! No guilty clutter Roy ❤️
Sarah | Small Changes: YASS ROY!!!!
Sarah | Small Changes: I've been having a huge problem with YT unsubscribing people with my channel and it is doing my head in 🙈
Sarah | Small Changes: *from
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow even at your level of subscribers YT still does that Sarah? Ive experienced that too specially when I was nearing the 500 and the 1k subscribers.
Paul Burke: How often do you put out videos Roy?
Sarah | Small Changes: @Mommy Guide Inc its so frustrating, people message me saying they didn't realise they got unsubscribed 😫
Paul Burke: 500 gets you a community tab? Oh baby! That's the one I'm excited about.
Mommy Guide Inc: Great Q @Paul Burke.
Paul Burke: thanks @Mommy Guide Inc !
Paul Burke: Saying "Thanks Mommy" is a strange thing to type 😂
Sammy Super Star: That happen to me too @Sarah | Small Changes
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Paul - it got rolled out about 2 weeks ago I think so yes Go Paul! You'll soon have that Community tab button:)
Paul Burke: Love me some Atomic Habits!
Paul Burke: thats awesome @Mommy Guide Inc can't wait to grow the community with sillyness over in that tab
Sandi Thompson: i just checked and I was unsubscribed @Sarah | Small Changes . I just re-subscribed.
Love Audio Production: hey you two 👋🤗
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Paul @Love Audio Production:)
Mommy Guide Inc: https://www.youtube.com/c/TechTroublemaker
Love Audio Production: hi Lala
Inspirational Connection TV: I’m so trying to niche down!
Mommy Guide Inc: I haven't even done basket weaving! LOL.
Mommy Guide Inc: Roy you are hilarious!
Mommy Guide Inc: Samantha @Inspirational Connection TV you are doing great! I am sure it'll even get better:)
Mommy Guide Inc: don't forget to subscribe to Roy. Watch some of his videos, like the video and then Subscribe.:) https://www.youtube.com/c/TechTroublemaker
Donna Richardson: Hi guys! Great show! Hi @Lala!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Roy you are giving me major "gas" right now. laughing out loud here.
Donna Richardson: ….hmmm yes that’s pretty accurately
Donna Richardson: *accurate
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Donna Richardson:)
Love Audio Production: and the UK! 🇬🇧
Mommy Guide Inc: yes, I love all of you! Love our community. So please share this video! let other's know about Markus and Roy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: Will you be doing a video series on how to video edit for content creators?
Sandi Thompson: Thank you!
Sarah | Small Changes: Bye guys ❤️
Mommy Guide Inc: Thank you Markus and Roy!