Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: See you all soon.
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yeah excited much.
Markus Schaub: Please stand by - technical diffiulties 🙂
Sammy Super Star: Hey Everyone!
Mommy Guide Inc: absolutely waiting Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sammy Super Star! Congratulations on your first ever virtual conference!
Mommy Guide Inc: yey! HI Markus!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi everyone. Hi Sammy & Lala
Samantha JustInspire: Hey Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Janet!
Ellie Calhoun: Hey everyone!!
Samantha JustInspire: Hello Sammy, Mommy LaLa
Mommy Guide Inc: Great to see everyone in the chat! DOnt forget to hit that like button friends!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Ellie'
Samantha JustInspire: Hello @Animal Paradise
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Ellie and Samantha:)
Samantha JustInspire: Sammy are you ready for tomorrow!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey there Samantha
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: LIKE & Subscribe ;-)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I love this open so much!
Mommy Guide Inc: Let's go - this song is just really awesome.
Samantha JustInspire: Markus I can’t see your message on Facebook I don’t know why
Mommy Guide Inc: It must be another FB issue Samantha. It happens to me sometimes also.
Markus Schaub: If you want to join: https://clicktojoin.live/c5ef51151
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Markus
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: hello...still trying
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yay you are here and we are here.
Mommy Guide Inc: oh my. tech issue really is a bane sometimes.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I like to do 2 days before for tech check. really helps
Colter Reed: Life happens. Roll with it!
Ellie Calhoun: MarkusRules!!
Andy H: Fascinating conversation ... so much to wonder about
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Sandi Thompson is going to be on my show tomorrow.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hello every one so sorry, I am really here but my browser keep saying the site can't be reached 😞
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Colter
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: ANDY!!!
Andy H: Ya just have faith ...
Mommy Guide Inc: booting up my computer
Ellie Calhoun: Sammy should go on to talk about his summit!
Ellie Calhoun: I was looking for you too Markus!
Andy H: What if you know you need faith, but have little faith that faith really helps?
Andy H: But that's another story ...
Awesome Fun Things: Hello Markus! 👋
Andy H: The show must go on is right ... faith or not
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: you are doing a great job!!!
Andy H: Spring is all about hope and faith in good things
Samantha JustInspire: There you go! Mommy LaLa always save the day!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Lala!!
Ellie Calhoun: Hey Lala!
Andy H: Faith is that Lala saves the day
Blind Guy, His Wife, Their Life: All the favorite folks in one place😊
Ellie Calhoun: Janet!!!
Samantha JustInspire: Hi Ellie!
Awesome Fun Things: We have an all-star cast! Wooo!
Andy H: FUN trio!
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Samantha
Andy H: What Matt said!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: see that is better thank you ladies from saving the day!
Tech Troublemaker: What happened to @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52?
Tech Troublemaker: Most problems are fixed by rebooting 😛
Ellie Calhoun: That's great!
Tech Troublemaker: Humans train dogs and cats train humans.
Andy H: Love your glasses, Janet!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: @Tech Troublemaker I can't open the link Markus says it says the site can't be reached
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: it won't let me log in on any of my computers nor my phone
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: So fun!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: chrome
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: lol
Samantha JustInspire: I’ve had my share of tech troubles
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Excited to see you next time here Ana!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks foe being here everyone
Sammy Super Star: Hey Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: https://youtube.com/user/KatySammy
Colter Reed: You can use your phone as a second camera. Just look for an NDI app.
Samantha JustInspire: Yes it works
Ellie Calhoun: Yes it works
Colter Reed: Or pick up an inexpensive USB webcam. It might not be quite as good, but if it means the show goes on…
Mommy Guide Inc: Absolutley Colter! So many options.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks pls like and subscribe as well to Janet’s channel
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: hahaha lala
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Thanks so much LALA
Ellie Calhoun: 😂
Tech Troublemaker: I will have to catch the replay. My day job is in the way.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: yes we can hear you
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: all 3
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: it's just you Lala
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: it'a s just you lala
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: lol
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: we can hear you lala
Markus Schaub: leave and come back
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Man I had all this prepared!!
Mommy Guide Inc: So there i cant hear janet and Markus so i am hearing you thru YT LOL
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: :elbowcough:
Mommy Guide Inc: Guys i cant hear you.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I turned off my computer and back in and still nothing...
Mommy Guide Inc: So i am just going to stay here in the chat.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Sorry Markus and Janet.:)
Colter Reed: Live to an empty room is hard.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes!!! I was so excited that today I didn't have to worry about managing all the buttons!!!
MySnoopy80: Hi❤️❤️
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: That is why I am a Christian because Jesus is in the chat even when no one is there LOL
Colter Reed: Having LEDA alumni show up and chat has also given my audience permission to chat.
Mommy Guide Inc: I really cant hear any audio so I am staying in the chat Janet and Markus:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: @Mommy Guide Inc thank you for jumping in
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed Colter.:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Thank you so much friend, I am so sorry but look at the guests you had!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: This is Ana’s YT link: https://youtube.com/channel/UCmFIklZWKRLTW9_wAQkJbjA
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: It also gave Janet an opportunity to go live with you!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: yes!! and not panic
Mommy Guide Inc: Exactly! I rebooted and I now have audio back:)
Mommy Guide Inc: But it's ok I love to be here in the chat today Markus and Janet:)
Mommy Guide Inc: It's ok Ana I know you tried everything. The tech is just not with us today. he he he.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @MySnoopy80:)
MySnoopy80: Hi Lala❤️
Mommy Guide Inc: Janet@Animal Paradise -Communicaiton & Healing & @Sandi Thompson is going live tomorrow. Hope to see you there as well:)
Colter Reed: Just hit the red button.
Mommy Guide Inc: Absolutely Janet! Perfection is not the key.
Mommy Guide Inc: @Colter Reed totally agree!
Mommy Guide Inc: @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52 Amen. Absolutely agree.
Mommy Guide Inc: What fazes Markus? Hmm I have yet to see something do that to him. Markus has found his streaming peace - doing interviews.
Colter Reed: Q So how do you grow your skills as an interviewer?
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I appreciate you all
Mommy Guide Inc: oh that's a great advice. I heard some streamers dont like watching their streams on replay. but indeed watching on replay you can see some learning points.
Mommy Guide Inc: As a host - research! thanks for that great advice Janet.
Mommy Guide Inc: oh yes - it's so easy to talk - listening is a skill every interviewer must have.
Mommy Guide Inc: Don't forget to smash that like button friends:)
Colter Reed: @Mommy Guide Inc Smashed!
Colter Reed: (That’s one click, right?)
Samantha JustInspire: We will get there soon Janet!
Ellie Calhoun: Smashed that Like button!
Colter Reed: I’m looking at having a couple of guests on. I don’t have confidence that I could interview them well, but I know I can sit down with these same people and have a great conversation IRL.
Mommy Guide Inc: Here is Ana's website: https://faith52.com
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: So sorry!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: We will definately try again!!!
MySnoopy80: Bye all❤️❤️
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yeihhhhhhh!!!
Colter Reed: This is one large trailer for Ana.
Mommy Guide Inc: Colter we will wait for that Colter. I am sure that would be great to see you on with guests as well too.
Samantha JustInspire: Lol
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: That is a great strategy!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Markus & Janet:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes!!! all works for the good!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes we will definitely see Ana soon here.