Markus Schaub: You can join the meeting here: https://us02web.zoom.us/j/83558267985?pwd=M0Y3Sm1hSXJpdDhUY01iV0VjQUZXdz09
Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sammy!!!
Ellie Calhoun: Hello everyone! Here just to watch today - don't have my camera set up.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi everyone!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: hello!
Mommy Guide Inc: Ellie! Belated Happy Birthday!!!
Ellie Calhoun: thank you Lala!
David W. Ryan: Hi everyone!
Ellie Calhoun: you look relaxed Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi David!
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed!!!
Ellie Calhoun: wow! 6th!
SiShong Victor: iMove trailer I tried using that before. Did you adjust the quality? I do it as 1080p
SiShong Victor: iMovie*
Mommy Guide Inc: I tried Victor!
SiShong Victor: HAHAHA I look at it on my side 🙂
Mommy Guide Inc: Horrible video and audio quality once uploaded in Youtube.
Mommy Guide Inc: I have almost 400 videos that i can repurpose. Its my mediocre editing skills that need mega doses of help. LOL.
Mommy Guide Inc: Pls dont forget to like and share this stream.:)
Ellie Calhoun: I like the idea of topics
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Adam! Yes Coach Adam has been very consistent and a great inspiration!
David W. Ryan: get an external drive and copy all your videos to it. It's better to not have your media on the same hard drive your software is running on
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes!!! Coach Adam is setting the bar!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes David ive all the videos on a 10 terra external hard drive.:) thanks for the reminder.:)
SiShong Victor: Only videos you should have on the computer are ones you need to or currently are editing. rest should be moved to external drives or a NAS
Ellie Calhoun: Markus, tell us how you are feeling about LLPGP. Is it going the way you imagined?
Ellie Calhoun: Go Ana! You got this -monday!
SiShong Victor: Anna get started with them videos and catch up 😛
Ellie Calhoun: I missed the Ana Andy show! I'll have to watch it in replay
SiShong Victor: I still can speak Spanish and I'm Hispanic
Ellie Calhoun: Love Lala!
Mommy Guide Inc: If you mossed Ana and Andy a few hours ago dont worry here is the link for replay:) https://youtu.be/WdH_aHdujr0
TonyRIversen one crazy dane: Hello everyone - Sorry I cannot be there going to the Doctors office
Mommy Guide Inc: Love ypu all more!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Tony! Hope everything is well. See you next stream. Take care!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Thank you so much for sharing our link!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Coach Adam’s videos really delivers amazing content and fun.:)
SiShong Victor: I try to keep my videos between 30 seconds and 3 minutes. Not so easy as I just keep talking and talking
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL VIctor! I think its really high time for you to be on my streams. I can go on and on.:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: and also helps you to get confortable streaming.
Mommy Guide Inc: Rapid progress - indeed consistency’s awesome result of
Mommy Guide Inc: Did that make sense?:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I love that color!!! my favorite
David W. Ryan: you can key that color and make it any background
Mommy Guide Inc: Lovin’ the color changes of Adam’s background and microphones.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes teal is awesome!
SiShong Victor: 2 minute topics still end up being an hour video for me. I have to chop them up more and more
Mommy Guide Inc: Go Victor! Victor would you want to join us in zoom now or next time?
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I use velcro!
SiShong Victor: I can boil water that's about all
SiShong Victor: By the time I get off work you all are done
Mommy Guide Inc: Congratulations and thanks to David Ryan for going live with us - his very first last Saturday . He taught our community how to sew!
SiShong Victor: have my department is off today and im the only one working tomorrow hahahaha
SiShong Victor: Half
Mommy Guide Inc: If you missed any of Adam’s almost daily videos check them out here: https://youtube.com/c/AdamTinkoff
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow employee of the month awardee there Victor!
Tina Wan Kenobi: Good morning 😊
Tina Wan Kenobi: ☕️
Mommy Guide Inc: Tina! OMG why are you up so early???
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for joining us.:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hi Tina, thank you for being here!
SiShong Victor: I never think about taking days off. I need an other ECAMM meetup for I can take a Vacation hahaha
Tina Wan Kenobi: I set up alarm at 4, then snoozed until now 😆
Tina Wan Kenobi: I was in bed by 10.
Tina Wan Kenobi: Hi Ana!
Mommy Guide Inc: You can check out Ejnar’s channel here: https://youtube.com/channel/UCpUK-6V6TYjBoH6SUeEqUqQ
Mommy Guide Inc: Thank you for smashing the like button and sharing this stream everyone.:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: or taking your glasses off!!! Right Andy?
Tina Wan Kenobi: I use food lol
Mommy Guide Inc: Tina we do love so much that i think we need a break from them for awhile. LOL.
Tina Wan Kenobi: The important thing is they laugh 😬
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh indeed Ana! If you want to know what Ana is talking about Andy taking his glasses off head onto their latest Conversations with Ana and Andy on Ana Zugheri-Fairh52
Tina Wan Kenobi: Lala 😆
Tina Wan Kenobi: Endorphins!
Mommy Guide Inc: Are you lovin’ the early morning stream with Markus?
Tina Wan Kenobi: Markus hello, i slept, i dunno about Lala 😆
Tina Wan Kenobi: She’s part zombie on days like today.
Mommy Guide Inc: I did Tina! I make it up during the rest of the day.:) see you later.:) Tina goes live in about 10am Philippine time later
Tina Wan Kenobi: That’s freedom of speech via podcast but must be done with responsibility and accountability.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Do a live tutorial!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Absolutely agree @Tina Wan Kenobi.:)
Tina Wan Kenobi: Andy I like that painting/photo at the back.
Tina Wan Kenobi: By the menorah
Mommy Guide Inc: Absolutely it took me quite awhile to overcome the frustration of last week’s audio issue. Markus was very gracious and so was everyone for understanding.
Mommy Guide Inc: I am so blessed to be in this accountabilty group where it is ok to not be ok.
Ellie Calhoun: that is courageous of you Andy!
Tina Wan Kenobi: You can do solo on those two extra weeks?
Mommy Guide Inc: I am really lovin’ Conversations with Ana and Andy!
SiShong Victor: Wait it just hit me Anna you have already been live on YouTube You are Here 😲
Mommy Guide Inc: That’s another great option too Andy as Tina Wan Kenobi suggested.:)
Tina Wan Kenobi: Hi Ellie and Victor!
Tina Wan Kenobi: &lt; half asleep
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: lol yes! Sir, my second stream of the day LOL
Tina Wan Kenobi: Thomas the tank?
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow Ana - two streams today. Congratulations!
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Tina
Tina Wan Kenobi: I saw your latest video Lala, it’s so hip!!!
Tina Wan Kenobi: I love it!!
SiShong Victor: I just go live in the group then take the record video to upload to YouTube later
SiShong Victor: A 3 to 4 hour live is ok as a live but not everyone will watch them on the replay
Tina Wan Kenobi: Victor true
SiShong Victor: ONLY 400 videos? 🤣
Tina Wan Kenobi: But most who do replays of our lives, crafts along with the replay.
Tina Wan Kenobi: 400 😱
SiShong Victor: Most of my videos from thought to record to upload is about 30 minutes. Im not a perfectionist
Tina Wan Kenobi: Thank you Adam for giving tips to Lala 🌻
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed sis Tina it made me feel better hat am so bad at editing. Ill get better absolutely.:)
Tina Wan Kenobi: Short term or long term goals?
Simply Sunita: great job markus
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Simply Sunita!
Ellie Calhoun: Markus, you are doing great! love this, love you!
Mommy Guide Inc: Dont forget to hit the like button and subscribe to Markus Schaub’s channel:)