Mommy Guide Inc: Hi everyone! See you in a bit:)
Mommy Guide Inc: And here goes our favorite intro music and video!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Markus! Ejnar and Ana!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Coach Adam!
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed, why live streaming?
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for sharing Ejnar:)
Mommy Guide Inc: And yes we're rooting you on to just continue creating content and going live! I am sure you'll reach those milestones sooner than later:)
Tech Troublemaker: I stream so I can bore people "live" since they don't seem to want to watch it after it was live. 😛
Mommy Guide Inc: Love it Ana! Cheering you on for the many awesome changes coming:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy@Tech Troublemaker!
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh Roy you are never a bore! Thanks for dropping by - good afternoon:)
Mommy Guide Inc: I agree with Ana - I've learned so many things from your channel Roy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Roy's channel content is evergreen.:)
Tech Troublemaker: I love your channels. I watch as often live as my day job will allow. The Ana and Andy show is a lot of fun. Coach Adam, I am loving your shows. Markus and Ejnar, I don't see you on enough. More video
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks so much Roy for the support. Indeed you are always almost in all our lives! Yahoo! Super supporter for everyone indeed just like everyone else here in LLPGP:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Our why or why's? something that is nice to really come back to every now and then to help us check if we are still on the path we had intended to.
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey to long weekends @Coach Adam:)
Tech Troublemaker: You guys are five of my favorite people in the world and i talk to you more than folks IRL.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: right back at you Roy!
Markus Schaub: ❤ @Tech Troublemaker
Mommy Guide Inc: FUN! Indeed Coach Adam:).
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes, that's a great point Ana. If its just all about numbers I don't think someone will be able to do content creation via livestreaming a long time. We need to be enjoying what were doing:)
Tech Troublemaker: AVD and AVP - Average View Duration/Average View Percentage. My lives are averaging about 40+ views each (linkedin seems to get me 6 to 10 additional views)
Tech Troublemaker: Unless Lala is on, then I get 90+ haha.
Mommy Guide Inc: Congratulations Ana and Andy for an awesome win of starting your own Youtube Channel - Conversations with Andy and Ana! https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCSmpCpYJLqZJlhwhTFTh4Zg
Tech Troublemaker: I love going live. That is the biggest thrill for me. I want it to help others, provide value and if that is all it ever is then so be it. But I want to have 500 for community tag. That is my goal.
Mommy Guide Inc: What na awesome why Roy!
Mommy Guide Inc: @Roy thanks for the trust and for opportunities for collaboration. Again, you are not boring Roy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Coach Adam - speed drawing! awesome!
Mommy Guide Inc: short form video - I agree the videos I have that have reaches at least 1k levels are my shorts. LO
Mommy Guide Inc: great thought provoking question Coach Adam.
Tech Troublemaker: I will have to be #TeamReplay. Such a busy day.