Karen italian channel: Ate margie
MARILOU FRANCISCO VLOG: :stayhome::stayhome:
MARILOU FRANCISCO VLOG: :thanksdoc::thanksdoc:
MARILOU FRANCISCO VLOG: ate margie
Ate MARGIE: raid from mommy guide
MARILOU FRANCISCO VLOG: from mommy guide
elena France maricaban: :thanksdoc::thanksdoc::thanksdoc:
Eulyn Ramos: Mommy Guide Inc
elena France maricaban: :virtualhug::virtualhug:
KusiNerie01: mommy guide
Samantha Page Fox: Mommy Guide
Mommy Guide Inc: Thank you so much @AteMargie community for the Raid on Markus Channel:)
Mommy Guide Inc: If you can join us at 4am po that would be super great:)
John Pullum: Good day, everybody!
John Pullum: Where is Andy?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi John!
John Pullum: Hi @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed where is Andy?:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Kudos Ana! So many wins this week:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Welcoming the challenge - that's a great mindset Ana and very inspiring indeed:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: @John Pullum Andy is recuperating...he's been a bit under the weather.
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh. Andy if you are watching on replay - big hugs and please get well soon.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I just got the word that he is felling better but he is in Grampa mode today.
John Pullum: Thanks for the info @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52 . I just sent him a get well video message.
Mommy Guide Inc: That's great news. Thanks Ana for the update. Grandpa mode is better than being sick:)
TonyRIversen one crazy dane: Hi everyone., Sorry that I am NOT in the group today. too much work right now.
Markus Schaub: no worries Tony, welcome in the chat!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Tony! Missing you up here. Hope is well and hope you finish all your work today:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Dont forget to hit the Like button and share the stream:)
TonyRIversen one crazy dane: 😃
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Everyone!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy@Tech Troublemaker:)
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Mommy Guide Inc Lala
Tech Troublemaker: Renee has a great topic. Macs for the win!
Tech Troublemaker: Still trying to find topic/niche
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy! Ditto. We maybe moving ever so slowly but we're moving forward. So let's just keep at it:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Amazing 100+ people and am so glad to be part of it too!
Mommy Guide Inc: Congratulations Andy and Ana!
Tech Troublemaker: Congrat! Ana
Mommy Guide Inc: Hope you feel better Ejnar.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: YOu are doing a great job @Tech Troublemaker
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes and of course Roy's Lighting Round segment is awesome:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I think we all do go for the distracting...my precious! lol
Tech Troublemaker: I love the Lightning round but I am surprised they do not get the watches I would have thought so I guess I am just doing that because I get a kick out of it.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: They are so fun!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: A timer Roy would be great and different questions every episode? though too much work right?
Tech Troublemaker: Timer agreed. I do change the questions up. Only the Ninja question always makes the cut.
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yes you're right Roy!
Mommy Guide Inc: You are always tweaking and finding ways to make your stream even better Roy:)
Tony Jacobsen #UNBREAKABLE: hello everyone
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Tony!
Tony Jacobsen #UNBREAKABLE: Yes, the bigger folks have staff so being a one-man-band means we have to streamline and be as efficient as possible
Tech Troublemaker: We all have to be our armies of one. Content Creators who dream up, write up, make and edit.
Tony Jacobsen #UNBREAKABLE: Hey there, @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: Absolutely agree Roy:).
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: keep it simple.
Mommy Guide Inc: My 5c is work from where you are - what works for you:)
Tech Troublemaker: You guys are doing great. Keep doing what you are doing and the value and your super fans will finally collide together.
Basic Networks and Streaming: Yo
Tony Jacobsen #UNBREAKABLE: Hello !!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi everyone
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Victor @Basic Networks and Streaming
Tony Jacobsen #UNBREAKABLE: It's Jay-Kob-Sin
Tony Jacobsen #UNBREAKABLE: 🙂
Mommy Guide Inc: Hola @Basic Networks and Streaming
Basic Networks and Streaming: Leaving work now so i’m listening but I’m not watching because I’m driving
Tony Jacobsen #UNBREAKABLE: Mr. #UNBREAKABLE is perfect! Thank you!
Mommy Guide Inc: oh yes Victor please dont' watch listen only!
Tech Troublemaker: Yes, I don't do an intro any more but go right into the topic after a short hook.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: the creative juices begin to flow
Tech Troublemaker: Lala, it is time to go back to bed.