John Pullum: Hello Markus!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Markus!!!
Markus Schaub: Join my Discord: https://discord.gg/TjvjWB6Z
Samantha JustInspire: Hey there Markus
Ellie Calhoun: Hey Markus!!
MySnoopy80: Hi❤️❤️❤️
John Pullum: Dance Markus, ... DANCE!!!! and drink coffee.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi everyone!!! Markus!!! Ellie!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yeeeh! Im so glad I am able to catch you Live!!!
Samantha JustInspire: Go Markus, I just love the vibe!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: hello friends!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I like that song!!!
Samantha JustInspire: Hi @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52
Ellie Calhoun: Hello 👋 friends! 🥰
Sandi Thompson: Hi!
Samantha JustInspire: Hi @John Pullum, would love to connect with you! Hope to do an interview with you!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hi @Samantha JustInspire so glad to see you here
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Such a lovely video Markus!!!
John Pullum: @Samantha JustInspire Sounds good
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana! Samantha! Glad to be back live with you all and Markus.
Mommy Guide Inc: Don't forget to hit that like. button everyone!
Tech Troublemaker: done
Sandi Thompson: all of mu fav ppl!
Mommy Guide Inc: Awesome! Thanks Roy@Tech Troublemaker !
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: That song is so perfect! It truly describes your channel.
John Pullum: ❤
Samantha JustInspire: Hey mommy Lala! Happy belated birthday!
Mommy Guide Inc: Sandi!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: aww thanks Samantha @Samantha JustInspire:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hi @Mommy Guide Inc I feel like I keep missing you lately!
Mommy Guide Inc: Don't forget to join Markus on Discord! https://discord.gg/TjvjWB6Z
John Pullum: Have your girlfriend come on the stream sometime. We want to ask her if you are as wonderful in person.
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: Hey @MySnoopy80 🙂
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52 @John Pullum @Samantha JustInspire
MySnoopy80: @johnpullum yes he is:)))
Samantha JustInspire: Hello Roy!
John Pullum: @MySnoopy80 🙂
MySnoopy80: LALA
Mommy Guide Inc: Accountability streamer partner here for you all! aww glad that you still went live Markus!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hey! @Tech Troublemaker Im so sorry about your kitty.
Mommy Guide Inc: Aww yes sorry for your loss Roy:(
Tech Troublemaker: Thanks @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I love what you just said. I had scheduled a guest last friday and she showed up right at the last minute, I panic because I didnt have backup
John Pullum: 7 watching and only 6 likes. Who didn't smash that like button yet?
Mommy Guide Inc: I actually didn't realize that Discord is actually nice. Everything is so organized:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: lesson learned, always have backup plan.
BostonDonMTB: Howdy Marku!! Catching you live Whoo Hooo.
Ellie Calhoun: Lala!!! Happy Birthday!🥳🥳🥳
Mommy Guide Inc: Thank you all for the birthday greetings! Love you all:)
Sandi Thompson: oh no..i missed it! Happy Birthday Lala!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Happy Birthday!!!
Ellie Calhoun: 😂
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I missed it too...I got confused with the days 😭
Ellie Calhoun: I will go look for Cortney!
BostonDonMTB: Nice three steps!
Ellie Calhoun: Start ❄️ Improve ❄️ Don't Stop!
Mommy Guide Inc: Don't forget to join Markus on Discord:) Join my Discord: https://discord.gg/TjvjWB6Z. And pls like this stream as well. Thank you all dear friends:)
Samantha JustInspire: @John Pullum, check your page for an email link, did not see one!
BostonDonMTB: Just like that first day in LEDA.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Don@BostonDonMTB 🙂
BostonDonMTB: Hi @Mommy Guide Inc I hope you had a great birthday.
Mommy Guide Inc: and this is Cortney's channel: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EFi73cr7wIg
Sammy Super Star: Hey Markus!
John Pullum: I just realized you have an accent after you brought it up. For all these months I just thought you were from Ohio.
Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I admire you so much!!! It's been a pleasure witnessing your growth and awesomeness!
John Pullum: Hey @Sammy Super Star
Mommy Guide Inc: @John Pullum LOL!
Mommy Guide Inc: hey Sammy our Super Star.
BostonDonMTB: T-Shirt: Be A Live Streamer Go Live Improve Keep Going
Tech Troublemaker: haha @John Pullum
BostonDonMTB: Start selling them Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: Our awesome Supporter of the year - Markus Schaub!!! How he is able to be always almost at all of our streams is beyond me. Perfect gift for Markus - sleep:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: So do you prepare questions in advance for your guests?
Samantha JustInspire: Hi Sammy!
Tech Troublemaker: Completely agree! @Mommy Guide Inc Markus is so amazing and never sleeps and is on everyone's stream at the same time somehow. Haha
Samantha JustInspire: Markus don’t sleep just like you mommy Lala…
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Join us on Feb the 25th!!!
BostonDonMTB: @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52 and @Mommy Guide Inc Do you have a word document or something like that for show flow?
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL @Samantha JustInspire. we take naps. we learned from Sammy:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I am terrible with names, I think it was your last guest...very sensitive topic, you asked really good questions.
Mommy Guide Inc: Feb 25th!!! Absolutely Ana @Faith52
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: @BostonDonMTB I do! I modified a little but I took it from the fabulous @Mommy Guide Inc
BostonDonMTB: @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52 🙂 she is fabulous.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I can totally pay it forward and send it to you if you want me to.
Mommy Guide Inc: @Don I do have a template but my Qs are just really more of guides. We also take it from the chat:)
Ellie Calhoun: How do you envision how Discord will work for you in future?
BostonDonMTB: Winner gets a ski trip to Switzerland?
Ellie Calhoun: Great idea! Thumbnail challenge. Maybe first fo a tutorial on how to make a thumbnail
Mommy Guide Inc: Just recently started my own Discord. Thanks to Austin for setting it up for me and his friend Quill. I am a member now of Markus Schaub's Discord server:) see you there as well.
Ellie Calhoun: Could be a guest who does great thumbnails
Brand with Canva: Hey there Markus 👋🏼
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: cool!!!
Ellie Calhoun: Oh yay! Kali!
Mommy Guide Inc: yey Kali! See you there as well.
Ellie Calhoun: Heather!!! I'm on canva right now playing...
Brand with Canva: Sounds like I missed the juicy stuff. I’ll watch the replay.
Mommy Guide Inc: HI Heather @Brand with Canva:).