Adam Tinkoff: Hey there kids! Ready to go?
Adam Tinkoff: :washhands:
Tech Troublemaker: What's up!
Adam Tinkoff: Woop woop!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: hello friends!!! Glad to see ya'll here!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Ready or not here we go!
Eff Guitar: 🙏🙏
Eff Guitar: Shoutouts to all 🙏🙏
Yuka Nakasone: Hi Ana and Markus.
Adam Tinkoff: Embrace the change, but you both look great to me.
David W. Ryan: Hi Ana and Markus
Yuka Nakasone: Oh, I was wondering who Tech Troublemaker was... it's Roy!
Tech Troublemaker: OH NO! @Yuka Nakasone you found my secret identity. Haha
Yuka Nakasone: 😂
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @David W. Ryan and @Eff Guitar
Eff Guitar: Hey @Tech Troublemaker
Tech Troublemaker: I love my Sony ZV-E10 but you are right, you can do everything with great light and good webcam or a phone.
Adam Tinkoff: Brilliant insight. God meets you wherever you are, when you are ready to listen.
Tech Troublemaker: You can't love people you push away and you can never talk about love while showing hate.
Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Hi Markus and Ana😀👍👋
Paul Burke: great stream guys! I've been lurking
Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
Sammy Super Star: I like the new mic Markus
David W. Ryan: love to see all the progress you both have made
Tech Troublemaker: @David W. Ryan so right. @Markus Schaub and @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52 have become rockstars
Ejnar - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Just let into the FB group now👍😀
Yuka Nakasone: Thank you my friends for the company. I will livestream after this one....
Yuka Nakasone: wow Paul, Summy and Ejiner are here as well live. 😳