Sammy Super Star: hey Everyone
BravoPup Dog Training: aww man, Sammy beat me this time! Still in front row.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sammy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sandi!
Mommy Guide Inc: Front row indeed!
Inspirational Connection TV: Hey everyone
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Samantha @Inspirational Connection TV
Mommy Guide Inc: And they're live! Hi Markus! Hi Stephy!
Sara S: Hey folks!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Sara S!
BravoPup Dog Training: Hi!
Ana Zugheri: Hi 👋 Markus
David W. Ryan: Hello friends!
Mommy Guide Inc: ANa! Hi!:)
Mommy Guide Inc: hi David!:)
Ana Zugheri: Hi Lala!!!
Ellie Calhoun: hello Markus and Stephy!!
Ellie Calhoun: Hi everyone else!
Mommy Guide Inc: https://www.stephyhogan.com
Ellie Calhoun: Love it! equally awesome experience...
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Ellie Calhoun!
Sara S: Differently abled community— “nothing about us without us”
Sara S: Universal design
Mommy Guide Inc: Never thought how accessibility could be so important in designing basically everything and anything we do or use
Ana Zugheri: Interesting
Sara S: Architects with egos often have trouble with this
Mommy Guide Inc: how very true Stephy. An eye-opener there indeed.
Ana Zugheri: I second @mommy guide inc
Mommy Guide Inc: Don't forget to smash the like button everyone:)
Ana Zugheri: Yes! PowerPoint is awesome 👏
David W. Ryan: it's never "duck"
Ellie Calhoun: There is a mom blogger on facebook. Every photo that she posts, she writes a description of the photo for those who can't see well.
Ana Zugheri: Yes! I hate when there is a light color background and white font, cannot read
Sara S: @ellie calhoun alt text
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed @Ellie Calhoun. Intentionality to make our designs inclusive is something that I should do. Specially that I am working on my website. thanks Markus and Stephy:)
Paul Burke: It's pretty impressive how many accessability options games have these days too
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Paul Burke!
Paul Burke: hey @Mommy Guide Inc 🙂
Ana Zugheri: Hi@paul
Paul Burke: hey @Ana Zugheri
Ana Zugheri: Wow!!! I had no idea 🤷🏻‍♀️
Paul Burke: it's a little ironic 'accessiblity' is such a challenging word to say
Ana Zugheri: 😂
Paul Burke: Markus...some merch you can sell..."you dont have to be ugly to be accessible"
Ellie Calhoun: 🤣
Paul Burke: AAA - Always Avoid Acronyms
Paul Burke: thats so smart about shortening the blocks
Heather Roma: Hey guys! Can't stay long but wanted to say HI. Looking forward to the replay. Great content!!
Ellie Calhoun: if someone makes their website hard to read, people won't stay
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL@Paul Burke
Paul Burke: hey @Heather Roma !
Ellie Calhoun: hi Heather!
Heather Roma: Hi @Paul Burke fancy meeting you here
Heather Roma: @Ellie Calhoun long time no see *wink*
Mommy Guide Inc: better slides vs less slides in presentations. interesting:)
Paul Burke: What's a @Heather Roma like you doing in a place like this!?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Heather Roma
Heather Roma: I have a hard time saying three words most days, so that works
Ellie Calhoun: @Heather Roma🥰😉
Ellie Calhoun: This is good stuff for you @Heather Roma
Sammy Super Star: Hey Everyone
Paul Burke: at Vidsummit....MrBeast impressed me sooooo much. His slides were SO SIMPLE wordwise... and he was direct with short messages. It really stood out
Sammy Super Star: Did Markus get a new haircut?
Heather Roma: @Ellie Calhoun Agreed! It really is.
Mommy Guide Inc: Notes! yes I use those indeed.
Ellie Calhoun: anxious people might want to hide behind the slides!
David W. Ryan: I'm dyslexic and I can't listen and take notes. I love hand outs
Ana Zugheri: 👍 yes!!! So glad to hear I’m in the right path, sometimes I feel people think a bit too much because I put so much work on my pp presentations stephy you just validate my belief!!!! Thank you 😊
Paul Burke: @Sammy Super Star ...I don't think he did. But...maybe....he must cut it sometime....
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: Are there basic rules to consider when designing for accessibility? Is there such a thing?
Ana Zugheri: There are different learning styles the slides give something for the visual learners
Mommy Guide Inc: oh yes - guidelines indeed.
Heather Roma: Bye bye friends! Wish I could stay.
Paul Burke: bye @Heather Roma
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for dropping by @Heather Roma:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Guidelines for Designing for Accessibility: thoughtful use of white space
Mommy Guide Inc: https://www.stephyhogan.com
Mommy Guide Inc: another guideline for designing for accessibility: consider people's "bias"
Sarah | Small Changes: MARKUS!!
Sarah | Small Changes: STEPH!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sarah @Small Changes
Paul Burke: SARAH!
Paul Burke: MARKUS!
Paul Burke: STEPH!
Sarah | Small Changes: PAUL!
Sammy Super Star: Paul!!
Sarah | Small Changes: SAMMY!
Paul Burke: SAMMY!
Sammy Super Star: SARAH!!
Sammy Super Star: MARKUS!!
Ellie Calhoun: That sounds great Stepy!
Mommy Guide Inc: SCHIT - sight, cognitive, ... technologically related. whew I missed the H and the I
Sarah | Small Changes: You have to get your SCHIT together!
Paul Burke: Sarah causes so much trouble from her island
Sarah | Small Changes: It's a shout out fest!
Sammy Super Star: lol this is so funny
BravoPup Dog Training: I'm behaving myself.
Paul Burke: @BravoPup Dog Training ...we'd love to shout your name....but we'll resist!
BravoPup Dog Training: @Paul - I wont bite 😜
Nourish Hive: HI Marcus
Mommy Guide Inc: oh sometimes when I wear black and white prints it seems like the design is dancing on screen. now I know why. thanks Stephy.
Paul Burke: ok then.....SANDI!
David W. Ryan: I have a similar experience with "dancing letters" if the text is too close together.
BravoPup Dog Training: hahahaha!
Paul Burke: a tv show that nver took off on ABC.....Dancing with the Letters
David W. Ryan: @Paul Burke that's the Sesame Street version
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL @Paul Burke
Paul Burke: i love the youtube channel idea Stephy!
Paul Burke: those are great titles
Mommy Guide Inc: that would go viral! saving $75k with great design.
Paul Burke: we don't HAVE to be drunk....but we can...
Sarah | Small Changes: Have we talked about language subtitles already?
Mommy Guide Inc: Don't forget to like and share this awesome video:)
Mommy Guide Inc: yes you're good Stephy no freezing from our end:)
Sarah | Small Changes: I just have so many subscribers from all over the world and I would love to make it more accessible for those that english isn't there first language
David W. Ryan: All your base are belong to us!
Sarah | Small Changes: future video Steph
Mommy Guide Inc: it takes awhile for the closed captioning in YT to apply from my experience after the video is uploaded. but it does work.
Sarah | Small Changes: @Mommy Guide Inc How does it go with 2 different languages?
Mommy Guide Inc: yes Stephy! you said it perfectly "Tagalog"
Ellie Calhoun: whoo hoo! Mommy Lala!!! @Mommy Guide Inc
Sarah | Small Changes: Are you channeling Matt Haas vibes?
Mommy Guide Inc: @Sarah sad to say that YT closed captioning -based on my experience - can't translate the other language other than the English one. it skips the other language.
David W. Ryan: could you shoot more than one episode in a day?
Sarah | Small Changes: @Mommy Guide Inc you do such a beautiful job of seamlessly merging the two ❤️
Sarah | Small Changes: My son just picked chemistry as one of his subjects next year 🙈 I'll keep you on speed dial Steph
Ellie Calhoun: Thanks Markus and Stephy! interesting and important topic!
Sarah | Small Changes: Thanks so much guys! Loved seeing you both ❤️