Mommy Guide Inc: Hi everyone!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: How's your week been?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Markus, Coach Adam and Ejnar:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Wins and goals coming right up:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hi guys! I’m so sorry I’m just pulling in…I was out of town
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Can’t connect but I’ll be here in the comments
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana! Hope you can come in if tech allows it::)
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for being in the chat. how's your week been?
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Coach Adam left me thinking 🤔 I think I should close my fb group, and just focus on my page and YT channel
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I have no track on my group and tooooo broad audience
hughdemand: Coach Adam also has me reassessing my efforts.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes! I think I need to start one with intentionality
SiShong Victor: Yo
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Whit:)Indeed it's great to do a self- audit once in awhile:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Victor!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for joining us in the chat please dont forget to like and share Markus stream. Thank you very much:)
SiShong Victor: Adam make sure the left one is on the lift ear and the right ones in the right ear
Mommy Guide Inc: Ive had several moments of burn out also in the past - but doing something that i like somehow really pushed me past those moments.
Mommy Guide Inc: that's so cool Coach Adam:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: hi everyone. Sorry I'm late
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Janet!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I have been focusing on creating my membership and finding one thing to focus on for my work. I edited several short segment from my last week live.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh "B" roll (old film term) is easy peasy. I will be happy to help you
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I’m reading a book…undistracted. And with what Adam said…it’s making me really check what I’m spending my time on
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Keep it very simple
BostonDonMTB: Hi Everyone
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yes always be true to yourself
SiShong Victor: I like tech and will stick with tech related to networks and streaming. Just need ideas from time to time.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Don@BostonDonMTB 🙂
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: NO is a complete sentence!
BostonDonMTB: Hi @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Victor your channel is a treasure throve of awesome tech advice:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: don't forget to LIKE
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: It’s not about balance is finding the rhythm
Mommy Guide Inc: awww thanks so much Janet for the reminder. Yee let's show our love by sharing and liking this stream:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I’m thinking to keep my channel and create 3 playlists
Mommy Guide Inc: Rhythm that's nice Ana.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Janet in more ways than one. I will probably tell everybody our surprise in the future when it gets here:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed - No if needed.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I'm trying to keep it a secret. but i'm so excited
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes Markus is right
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I heard this about taking advice from others: eat the meat 🥩 and spit the bones 🦴
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Meaning take what is helpful for you
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I WILL FOLLOW YOU!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I heard that
BostonDonMTB: Fulfill yourself first. Concentrate on that. Once you do that everything else will follow.
BostonDonMTB: I wish I had 100 subscribers.
SiShong Victor: 100 subs is more then me 😛
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I'm thrilled with my 60+. more would be fantastic but I'm so grateful
BostonDonMTB: I have an interview scheduled on Monday, and another on the line after next week. So I am moving in the right direction.
Mommy Guide Inc: We all walked the same path right? we will get there so let's just all try to be commit to doing the work but Enjoy what were doing:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Congratuilations Don!!!!
BostonDonMTB: 😀
Mommy Guide Inc: thanks for joining us in the chat:) Excited much for each of us.
BostonDonMTB: Plus it keeps your excitement.
Mommy Guide Inc: that's great - every day is Day 1:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Thanks Adam
SiShong Victor: &lt;------ for me its all about the tech hahahaha
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Thank you everyone. Love you all
hughdemand: Thanks foks I enjoyed listening
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh you got yours. I got mine too. It is too fun
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi lalalalala
BostonDonMTB: You joined Steve on the Rodecaster Pro II
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I did
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: It is in the mail now!!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: no
BostonDonMTB: I think so.
BostonDonMTB: Now you need to buy more microphones.
SiShong Victor: The rode hardware should work better then the Rode software Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: waah! Indeed Don:)