Mommy Guide Inc: See you in a bit everyone!
Mommy Guide Inc: Love this intro music so much!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Markus!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Pls do join us in the chat here or in Zoom if you want.:)
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Everyone!
Tech Troublemaker: That is my goal. Plan my live stream enough to have it be very easy to edit.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Roy would you want to join us in Zoom?
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hello Roy!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: That is so cool Adam!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thank you for the awesome list Adam!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ejnar, Andy, Ana, Tony, Adam
Mommy Guide Inc: Accountability is awesome. It has become my constant reminder to do it coz I will have to show you guys what I’ve done on a weekly basis!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi everyone. sorry I'm late.
Mommy Guide Inc: Please don’t forget to hit the like button!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Janet!
Mommy Guide Inc: Janet you want to join us in Zoom?
Mommy Guide Inc: That’s great Ana!
Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hey Sammy! Sammy you want to join us in Zoom?
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for dropping by Sammy.:)
Ileane Smith: Hello beautiful people 🙋🏽‍♀️
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ileana!
Mommy Guide Inc: Oops sorry Ileane:)
Sammy Super Star: I'm doing 3 things at one time so maybe in like 3 minutes. Working on my next interview guest
Mommy Guide Inc: Ileane we’re trying to help each other by giving gentle push and suggestions for our content creation.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Awesome! I’ll send you the link Sammy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Ileane do you want to join us in Zoom?
Ileane Smith: @Mommy Guide Inc no this time. I can't stay but wanted to pop in and say HI!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Got it that is so great Ileane. Thanks for saying Hi and hope to see you here again in the chat! Have a great day!
Mommy Guide Inc: The experience itself am sure was amazing Andy!
Mommy Guide Inc: You are an awesome speaker.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I agree Lala. great speaker. Maybe try again another time?
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed sometimes we are our own issue right - keeping it simple what a great advice:)
Mommy Guide Inc: I agree Janet!
Mommy Guide Inc: Don’t forget to like this stream! And if you like what you’ve seeing so far it would be great to see you in Markus community and hit that subscribe and notification bell as well.:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hi Sammy
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Calendly has been super helpful for me
Mommy Guide Inc: Sammy is super amazing. I often forget he is just 17!
BostonDonMTB: Hi everyone
Mommy Guide Inc: Sammy is really an inspiration. Go for it Sammy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Don!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for joining us.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed Ana. I should have gotten that earlier.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: LinkedIn. Hmmm I’ve not really focused on getting content in there. Thanks Roy.
BostonDonMTB: Hi Lala, sorry I am late. I was watching some tutorial videos on vMix.
SiShong Victor: Im not late shhhhh
SiShong Victor: I use Linkedin
SiShong Victor: I was told I needed a Linkedin when I was looking for work
Mommy Guide Inc: He he he Victor. Really it’s fine Victor and Don glad you both are here.:)
SiShong Victor: so hard to sell my self
Awesome Wood Things: Is everyone here being accountable? Haha. Hi everyone!!!!
SiShong Victor: Im in IT but I don't know what im doing 90% of the time. Don't tell my Boss
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: IT secret. I thought you all worked for CIA, etc as most of my neighbors do.
BostonDonMTB: Yes, that is a good idea for LinkedIn.
BostonDonMTB: Be more direct to the people who use LinkedIn.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Matt! Yes being accountable is great!
Mommy Guide Inc: Excellent plans Roy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Victor! LOL
Mommy Guide Inc: Pls don’t forget to like these stream everyone.
BostonDonMTB: What about putting those ideas that are in the Google Doc, and put them on a calendar in two week intervals?
SiShong Victor: I buy, test, record a video and post Bam not much planning on my port
SiShong Victor: part8
SiShong Victor: ok I give up on spelling
Mommy Guide Inc: Great idea Don!
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed Victor. We should have that mindset right. To not over think things
BostonDonMTB: @Mommy Guide Inc Thank you
BostonDonMTB: I OVERTHINK everything.
SiShong Victor: Channels by Topic not people that's my thoghts
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes!!! Keep me accountable!
SiShong Victor: LALAA nice Roy we both working and on YT
SiShong Victor: hahaha*
Mommy Guide Inc: He he he multi tasking is so real for us right now
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks so much for joining us. Unbelievable. 1 hour is done???
SiShong Victor: Im a happy guy when Im eating so anyone with a cooking show im free for taste testing