Samantha JustInspire: Hey Markus
Samantha JustInspire: Hey everyone
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hello Sam! Glad you are here today
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi everyone
Markus Schaub: If you want to join: https://us02web.zoom.us/j/87179104128?pwd=dGlxTHJMdmNyMnBWNzdWSFM0bkNUQT09
Samantha JustInspire: Hey Ana, I’ve been so busy! Glad to be here
Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: hi Sammy!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: what's going on ]with power today? We lost power for a bit as well and... our hot water heater sprung a leak. funny day.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Sammy
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Lala is not here to say hi so I wil. ;-)
Tech Troublemaker: I love Thumbnails. One day I will get good at them. 😛
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: we all will right? keep practicing. it's so fun
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: less consuming more creating
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: @Tech Troublemaker You are heading the right way!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @Ana I like that one. I wrote it down and ... that is what I have been trying to do too.
Tech Troublemaker: four words or less, always show a face, build suspense if that is an option in the thumbnail. Canva for the Win!!
Tech Troublemaker: the right bottom corner is my achilles heel. How to keep stuff out of that corner, so tough as I like things centered.
Sammy Super Star: I have been using photoshop more then canva
Sammy Super Star: Some people don’t even use text and that’s very interesting
Sammy Super Star: Less is more
Sammy Super Star: What’s very interesting is the late night thumbnail style did pretty good on my channel and got great results. I might go back to that
Tech Troublemaker: I never use them so far but arrows seem to make a difference to try and tell a story in the thumbnail
Sammy Super Star: Yes
Sammy Super Star: Great thumbnails
Tech Troublemaker: Adam, love the consistent colors
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: ugh! man have it so easy wearing the same type of shirts all the time LOL
Tech Troublemaker: yes, you just have to Charlie Brown it...
Tech Troublemaker: same shirt every day
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I agree Ana and... most men don't wear makeup!
Coffee Talk & Tech: hi Markus!!! 👋 hi guys. .
Tech Troublemaker: Hey John!
Coffee Talk & Tech: hello Roy! how are ya?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Andy?
Tech Troublemaker: good, so far, good. @Coffee Talk & Tech
Coffee Talk & Tech: 😆 good is 👍
Coffee Talk & Tech: Ana I wish ....so many things going on so hard to plan much ahead. I'd love too though
Tech Troublemaker: thumbnail and title days before the live usually.
Tech Troublemaker: then if it doesn't do well the first 24 hours, I will change my thumbail and/or title
Coffee Talk & Tech: I've streamed hundreds of hours without a topic lol
Tech Troublemaker: I have changed thumbnails and titles on old videos and sometimes it gives them new life.
Coffee Talk & Tech: Roy I change titles sometimes too...especially when I over think.
Coffee Talk & Tech: my feeling is the more you stream the better you get...so stressing over a topic...I don't...I let the conversation take over and it's never a problem.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I hope one day I get there @Coffee Talk & Tech
Coffee Talk & Tech: Ana you are there if you let yourself be. trust me.
Tech Troublemaker: If my live show isn't going well, I shut up and let others talk. 😛
Coffee Talk & Tech: A focused passion goes a long way. this shows in your streaming.
Coffee Talk & Tech: fade to black ⚫️ lol
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Thank you!!! That's empowering.
Tech Troublemaker: @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52 like John says, you are on the path, just keep moving forward.
Markus Schaub: https://www.facebook.com/AndyandTony
Coffee Talk & Tech: Roy your humor is your superpower.
Tech Troublemaker: John, that explains why I keep flying into walls.
Coffee Talk & Tech: and don't forget to just be human.
Coffee Talk & Tech: also remember to view your thumbnail on mobile since most watch on mobile.
Sammy Super Star: Hey John
Coffee Talk & Tech: hi Sammy
Tech Troublemaker: capitalize the first letter of each word in title
Sammy Super Star: Hahhha
Tech Troublemaker: yes, capitalize the entire important word
Sammy Super Star: Heheheh
Coffee Talk & Tech: if I misspell it's not on purpose 😅
Sammy Super Star: Show a face
Tech Troublemaker: you guys are awesome. I enjoy all of your shows. I don't always get to see them live but I try to get back on replay. Just keep doing what you are doing
Coffee Talk & Tech: great seeing you all!! ❤️
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Thank you guys! Such a great chat!