Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hello 👋 friend!
Ileane Smith: Hi Markus
Ileane Smith: Hey @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52
Ileane Smith: eye - leen 😍
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: 🤓
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey everyone sorry to be late to the party
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: don't forget to LIKE
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Love the laughter
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Sorry to be late. what editor is this?
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Great tutorial!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I was driving so I missed it, not sure just from the phone or YouTube
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: It must be YouTube. cool
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Oh! @animal paradise it’s YouTube
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yes really good. I will refer back to this
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh that is cool.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: It looks simple enough, let’s see if I can really do it. 😋
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: So you edit it in You Tube Studio on your phone?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Can you do You Tube "shorts" on our computer or only on the phone?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: thanks
Ileane Smith: What is the link to their channel?
Markus Schaub: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uNkRW_9pHRQ
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Thank you
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh nice and a little Wagner is also nice
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Love it!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Nice
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Thanks Markus for the great tip
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: THis was fantastic. Thanks for helping us with shorts and captions.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yeihhhhhh 🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉