Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
austinator: this is gonna be a good one
Mommy Guide Inc: Hii CK!
BravoPup Dog Training: hi!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sammy & Markus! Hi Austine. My alarm woke me up already coz its 5minutes to 4am! So it means its almost time for Markus & Sammy to go live!
ConsistentAsh: Hey everyone!
GoJohnnyGo2021: Helloooo
Mommy Guide Inc: Here we go!
ConsistentAsh: Got some awesome dance moves going on up there!
BravoPup Dog Training: @Mommy Guide Inc - you are dedicated!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ash@consistentash! Hi @Go Johnny Go 2021
ConsistentAsh: Hey Mommy Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sandi@BravoPup!
Inspirational Connection TV: Hi guys…
Inspirational Connection TV: Ash, Sammy, Mommy Lala, how’s it going?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Samantha @Inspirational Connection TV!
austinator: wooo!!!
Sparkle Rise Thrive: hey Markus and Sammy!
ConsistentAsh: Not too bad, just working and catching the stream
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Stephanie @Spartkle Rise Thrive:)
BravoPup Dog Training: I like your lighting!
Sparkle Rise Thrive: LOOOOOOVE the curtain reveal!
austinator: Sammy!!
Sarah | Small Changes: MARKUS, SAMMY!!!!
ConsistentAsh: The curtain effect is really nice
austinator: Sarah!!!
ConsistentAsh: Oh I know it's real haha
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sarah @Small Changes:)
austinator: OBS.... I hate it so much, but I have to use it
Mommy Guide Inc: Don’t forget to like this stream.:)
Andy Halper: Hello Boys!
austinator: really Sammy? you have a team? who's in it?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Andy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Auston. Indeed? Who?
Andy Halper: Mammy Mommy Mommy!
austinator: I won't accept a Bonus Sammy, I've told you that
Mommy Guide Inc: I meant Austin. Who is Auston?LOL
Andy Halper: Mommy Mommy Mommy!
austinator: Sammy you don't play Videogames other than Minecraft
austinator: @Mommy Guide Inc Auston is my evil twin brother
David W. Ryan: Hi guys!
Andy Halper: David Walter in the house!
Mommy Guide Inc: Bwahahaz no o the evil Auston.:) Hi David!
ConsistentAsh: Sammy loves his mics
Mommy Guide Inc: Another new mic for Sammy - a lav one this time.:) nice
austinator: rip Sony a6100
austinator: I make it seem like the camera died
austinator: I killed the camera to get a pay raise
Ana Zugheri: Hi 👋
Mommy Guide Inc: https://www.pressnsow.com/sammysuperstar
Mommy Guide Inc: https://www.youtube.com/SammySuperStar
David W. Ryan: Hi lala! Hi Andy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Ana:) nice shirt @Sammy!
austinator: where's my hat Sammy?
Sarah | Small Changes: Q: Any recommendations for getting merch made?
Mommy Guide Inc: excited for my shirt to arrive @Sammy:). that's the color I ordered - the same one you're wearing now.:)
Ana Zugheri: So can we get your hat there?
Ana Zugheri: I’m glad I’m catching y’all
ConsistentAsh: Poor Markus is up so late due to us haha
Sarah | Small Changes: Can i get one shipped to Australia?
Ana Zugheri: Lol
Mommy Guide Inc: Ana yes the hat is also available on Sammy's Merch Store at https://www.pressnsow.com/sammysuperstar
Ana Zugheri: We always se you two!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed Ash:). We love Markus for always being there for us no matter what time.:).
ConsistentAsh: I agree, I love how we all connect no matter the time
Ana Zugheri: It fits you well!!!
BravoPup Dog Training: i think i was on the SA zoom call when Sammy announced he was Sammy Superstar!
Ana Zugheri: That was a super and organic interview.
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus every week thus far has been awesome! congratulations on your 5th stream. Going live consistently:)
David W. Ryan: Your name makes your audience expect fun. It's like a 1970's DJ name!
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yeah @Paul Burke in the house next week with Markus!
David W. Ryan: you can prepare for Paul Burke! it's impossible
Ana Zugheri: Sammy, how many LEDAS have you done?
ConsistentAsh: I get distracted all the time with my streams lol
Ana Zugheri: The clap is Sammy’s signature move!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yes, Sammy always tweaking his tech stuff - live!
Ana Zugheri: Lol
Mommy Guide Inc: lovin' both your new background! Markus with the lights and Sammy with the curtains:)
Ana Zugheri: I second that
Mommy Guide Inc: that's great! Austin directing. Go Austin!
Ana Zugheri: Dream big!!!! Yes!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: wow Congratulations @Sammy Super Star and @austinator - almost time for graduation:) awesome:)
Ana Zugheri: You two seem like a great team
David W. Ryan: How is Austin on camera? Could he be your on screen sidekick?
Ana Zugheri: Great things come out of crazy ideas 💡
ConsistentAsh: Can I take a nap now lol ? This mama needs sleep!
Sarah | Small Changes: I like to take naps!
BravoPup Dog Training: Sammy is a genius! We all knew that!
Mommy Guide Inc: wow a take over on Sammy Super Star's stream:)Are you ready @Austinator?
Ana Zugheri: When did you start streaming?
Sarah | Small Changes: https://youtu.be/LeIRbuRznSg
David W. Ryan: I had one of those G4 macs!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes that's the link to the first part of the Mac Romance. Thanks Sara @Small Changes:)
Sarah | Small Changes: Thats the Mac Romance Pilot ☝🏻
Sarah | Small Changes: Its very early here 🤣
Ana Zugheri: Thank you for sharing, lol funnier than Paul 😂
Ana Zugheri: Yes! All kinds of funny
Ana Zugheri: I’m funny too!!!…I say that to myself
Sarah | Small Changes: Markus is an offical superstar now
Mommy Guide Inc: Don't forget to like this stream! and share Markus channel:)
Ana Zugheri: Yes! Markus, you are doing so good and so quickly!
Ana Zugheri: Lol
ConsistentAsh: I have to head back to work now but awesome stream you guys! You guys are awesome
Ana Zugheri: 😆
Ana Zugheri: I’m not even famous and I forget to respond
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Ash@ConsistentAsh for dropping by. See you!
David W. Ryan: wow
Mommy Guide Inc: Sammy Super Star streams weekly. - Mondays at 9AM EST:)
Inspirational Connection TV: Is it 9am or 9pm mommy Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: oops sorry 9PM EST. LOL
Mommy Guide Inc: 9AM is my time:) Philippine time. LOL
ConsistentAsh: I decided to come back, don't tell my work lol
Sarah | Small Changes: Its early for me and Lala 🤣
Inspirational Connection TV: Lol @ConsistentAsh
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL - we're not going to say a word Ash!
Inspirational Connection TV: I am calling now Ash
ConsistentAsh: My productivity is horrible lol
ConsistentAsh: Sammy's audio is always still there lol even when his camera or himself isn't lol
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL Samantha @Inspirational Connection TV:). multi tasking mode on for Ash:).
ConsistentAsh: Oh i saw that on his IG story today
Inspirational Connection TV: Nice Sammy
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow Sammy! Cool! would love that big bowl of popcorn too!
ConsistentAsh: At least Markus is way better than keeping up on this chat compared to me lol
Ana Zugheri: That is cool!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: oh it's a new intro. Sammy where are you?
Ana Zugheri: Does it take you a long time to make?
ConsistentAsh: Dance dance!
Sarah | Small Changes: I gotta go premiere a video guys, thanks so much for a fun time 🎉
ConsistentAsh: Have a good one everyone!!!!
Inspirational Connection TV: Have a good rest of your days guys!
Mommy Guide Inc: Go Sara @Small changes. Let's all head there after the dance!
Inspirational Connection TV: Later Ash