Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hi guys joining you in the chat! 👋🎉
Samantha JustInspire: Hey Markus
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hi Sam
Samantha JustInspire: Hey Ana
MySnoopy80: Hi❤️❤️❤️
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Sadly I need to report I haven’t do a recording yet…but I have been going live ask Andy 🤗
Samantha JustInspire: No audio
Samantha JustInspire: From mommy LaLa
Samantha JustInspire: Yes I can hear now
Samantha JustInspire: It’s gone again Markus
Samantha JustInspire: Ok back now
Markus Schaub: sorry, fixed it 🙂
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: My internet is awful 😞
BostonDonMTB: Hey everyone!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi everyone. I will be with you as soon as the membership meeting is done.
Samantha JustInspire: Can’t wait to watch it mommy Lala
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yay Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Samantha! Congratulations!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Snoopy!
MySnoopy80: Hi Lala!
Mommy Guide Inc: thanks Ellie! Ejnar! Andy! Tony and Adam in zoom with us:)
BostonDonMTB: Thank you so much!
Mommy Guide Inc: Please dont forget to like and share this stream:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Howdy Adam!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Don!
BostonDonMTB: Adam, be sure to take time so that you can recharge.
Mommy Guide Inc: Monday Mindset, Tuesday Technology, Wednesday,Thursday and Friday - Planning, Production and Promotion!
Mommy Guide Inc: awesome plan and content Adam!
Mommy Guide Inc: Exactly Don right. Adam is just crushing it:)
BostonDonMTB: I love my 2004 and 2006 iPods. I don't know where my 2004 iPod is, but I am sure it is in my closet somewhere.
Mommy Guide Inc: me too Don! I still have my iPods:)
Mommy Guide Inc: so many wins this week Adam!
Mommy Guide Inc: speaking of wins if you haven't been able to watch Ana and Andy's live a few hours back I highly suggest you do so as well:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Ellie!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey! Super awesome win Ellie!
Mommy Guide Inc: Consistency - a day a week. Great plan Ellie:)
Samantha JustInspire: Yes consistently doing a livestream at the same time is best!
SiShong Victor: I post recorded videos when ever I can. Mostly when I notice my views start dropping in the last 48 hrs. Just me
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Samantha! And Congratulations again for having a new channel that is amazing on top of still maintaining your original channel.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Victor!!!
SiShong Victor: Hola
Mommy Guide Inc: thanks for everyone for being here in Markus Schaub's channel. Please don't forget to like this stream:)
Mommy Guide Inc: That's a great start Victor. Looking forward to many more videos from BASICNAS
Samantha JustInspire: Thanks Mommy LaLa! It’s going great with the new channel, I guess it’s a win for me! I’m doing more videos, something I struggle with!
Mommy Guide Inc: Here are our friends channel to follow and check: out https://www.youtube.com/c/AdamTinkoff
Mommy Guide Inc: For Ana Zugheri's channel where she collaborates with Andy Halper as well every other week: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCmFIklZWKRLTW9_wAQkJbjA
Mommy Guide Inc: thanks Tony for this reminder:)
Mommy Guide Inc: cooking set? wow awesome plans Tony:)
Mommy Guide Inc: thanks for inspiring us Tony. yes, just do what feels good for us.:).
Mommy Guide Inc: Congratulations Tony. Slowly but surely indeed:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Wins, Goals and Next Steps indeed for everyone today was amazing:)
Mommy Guide Inc: To check on Ellie Calhou's programs: https://www.mybodyworksnatick.com
Mommy Guide Inc: Ejnar!
Mommy Guide Inc: For Tony's weekly shows on FB with his lovely wife: https://www.facebook.com/AndyandTony/
Mommy Guide Inc: Please do check out Ejnar
Mommy Guide Inc: Please check out Ejnar's Youtube channel: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCpUK-6V6TYjBoH6SUeEqUqQ
Mommy Guide Inc: What an amazing updates from Ejnar. Just continue on Ejnar:)
Mommy Guide Inc: oh yes. how are you all doing on engaging with post comments on either your livestreams or edited videos?
Mommy Guide Inc: we have homework? oh no! Just kidding. Preparation is key right guys?
Mommy Guide Inc: If you are interested in joining Markus Schaub's Discord just put it in the comments and he will respond to you for sure!
MySnoopy80: 😂😂
SiShong Victor: Even when I'm live im lucky to have anyone watching
Mommy Guide Inc: Victor we all walked that path in the beginning right? but we just choose to go on and continue.:)
SiShong Victor: Ill still stream an hour with no one watching
Mommy Guide Inc: there you go - just go on. You are an inspiration Victor.
Mommy Guide Inc: If you have questions about tech and live-streaming - try and check out Victor's channel: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC-68Hj7R4ICBBbNDo497v2Q
Coffee Talk & Tech: look at this fantastic crew!🤟
Mommy Guide Inc: yey! Hi John @Coffee Talk & Tech!
Coffee Talk & Tech: hello Lala and friends
Love Audio Production: Good evening everyone! Hope you're all well. ~ Paul
Mommy Guide Inc: thank you so much everyone for dropping by today. Markus is leading us in this Peer Group Meeting and talk about our wins, goals and next steps!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Paul @Love Audio Production !
Coffee Talk & Tech: thanks Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: wow were already at the top of the hour!
Mommy Guide Inc: thanks everyone! Please dont forget to like this stream:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I’ll be watching the replay