Mommy Guide Inc: Yey first row seats finally!
Mommy Guide Inc: Super excited for this stream. now with my chips and tea:)
axelsson80: SaltyCorn
Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
RAYM Music Official: Hellooo 😀
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sammy!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi RAYM!
axelsson80: This is going to be fun!
RAYM Music Official: heeeey axelsson!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: yey!!!
Ellie Calhoun: I'm here!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @axelsson80
axelsson80: Heey Raym!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Ellie!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: This song and video just keeps me smiling!
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Lala, hi Sammy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Live That Streaming Life!!!
Ellie Calhoun: 🎶🎶🎶🎶🎶🎶🎶
axelsson80: Hi @Mommy Guide Inc
Scott Rogers: lalalal
RAYM Music Official: Hi everyone! Happy to be hear 😀
Mommy Guide Inc: 💃💃💃
Scott Rogers: hear!
Mommy Guide Inc: yey Scott!!!
Sammy Super Star: 🕺💃
Scott Rogers: no twitch emotes here 😞
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: https://www.twitch.tv/raymmusic
Ellie Calhoun: Whoo hoo! Great song!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi again RAYM!
M Wong: hi
Mommy Guide Inc: thanks everyone for supporting Markus and RAYM! Let's hit that like button:)
Ellie Calhoun: I don't know twitch. Sounds interesting!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @M Wong
Scott Rogers: Can we troll raym here?
M Wong: hi
Mommy Guide Inc: https://www.youtube.com/c/RAYMMusicOfficial
Scott Rogers: ohhh Hiya momaraym!!
axelsson80: Hi MomaRaym!
M Wong: sorry difficult to type in my phone every one
Mommy Guide Inc: MomaRaym! You are super awesome!
Scott Rogers: Except when she's fishing or losing at majong!
M Wong: hahaaaaa
Scott Rogers: ok, let's get to a 10 minute Violin solo!!!
Ellie Calhoun: Now I need to go to Twitch just to watch you, RAYM and be a part of your tribe :)
Scott Rogers: You'll love it. And get addicted to Twitch.
M Wong: hahaaa
Mommy Guide Inc: that's interesting channel points and rating.
Scott Rogers: Ask her to demonstrate Torture as an example. But I take no responsibility for what you will hear!
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL! @Scott Rogers now you got us curious. what is Torture!
Scott Rogers: oh it's BAD. Trust me.
Ellie Calhoun: Would love to hear it!
Ellie Calhoun: Ha ha!
Ellie Calhoun: 💕🎶💕🎶
Ellie Calhoun: 🤣😂love it!!!
Scott Rogers: I regret mentioning it 😞
Mommy Guide Inc: RAYM that sounds like me!
M Wong: hahaaaa
Mommy Guide Inc: thanks for mentioning it @Scott!
Ellie Calhoun: Yes Markus, eerily beautiful. Me too!
Scott Rogers: my pleasure. Well, not exactly pleasure... but...
Scott Rogers: Yeah, it gives us something to talk about which is a big part of the interaction
Dash With Ash in Canada: Markus!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: We love the song you created for Markus' channel. Hoping to have my own channel music too by you!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ash@Dash With Ash in Canada!
Dash With Ash in Canada: Hey Mommy Lala! How are you ?
Mommy Guide Inc: Everything is great Ash. Hope all is well and not too cold.
Ellie Calhoun: It sounds like a lot of work. Is it lucrative?
Dash With Ash in Canada: It's freezing here but I guess I am use to it by now lol
Dash With Ash in Canada: When no one knows your name, you have to take baby steps, including in price.
Scott Rogers: Is it time for a dance break yet?!
Mommy Guide Inc: I am sure your business will just grow more because you are very talented RAYM. I am not on twitch but subscribed to your YT channel already:)
Ellie Calhoun: Woah, 140 reviews is great!
Dash With Ash in Canada: I have to get back to work but I look forward to catching up with what you have been up to Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: stay safe Ash.Thanks for dropping by on the live stream.
Scott Rogers: Welllll, I'll think about it!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks RAYM. Learned so much about twitch community and song creation.
RAYM Music Official: LOL scott
Ellie Calhoun: Your community is following you, for who you are. I bet they would continue to support you because you are so personable and easy to connect with!
RAYM Music Official: @Mommy Guide Inc thank youuu!! It was a pleasure~