Mommy Guide Inc: And we’re live!!!
Eaglevp: Evening Markus & Lal
Eaglevp: Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Keith!
Mommy Guide Inc: Let’s go! Good afternoon Keith and Good evening Markus!
Motif Music Studios: Hello! Here from Vancouver Island, Canada!
Eaglevp: Hi@Motif Music Studios
Stannex: Here we go ... let's start the show! :^)
Eaglevp: Good day@Stannex
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey! Hi @Motif Music Studios
Motif Music Studios: @Eaglevp hello!
Motif Music Studios: @Mommy Guide Inc nice to see you here!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Stan!
Eaglevp: Hope everyone as had a great day
Eaglevp: Hope your feeling better Markus
Stannex: Hi, Keith! Hi, Lala!
Mommy Guide Inc: Howdy Markus and friends.:)
Eaglevp: How's the edit going on with your film Markus?
Fishstick USA: Hello
Eaglevp: Hi@Fishstick USA
Motif Music Studios: Oh, 4am. That's so early!
Stannex: Lala saved the show!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Philip!
Motif Music Studios: Ah, sweet encouragement in the journey!
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh its fine. Nap is key! We miss Markus show right? On that note pls dont forget to hit the Like button.:)
Stannex: Yes, being sick is a GOOD reason to skip (take care of yourself first). But the danger is the loss of motivation that comes the following week (like you're describing).
Fishstick USA: Markus, thanks for your encouragement. I started my my YT channel
Motif Music Studios: Yes! Always sweet encouragement. I am SO keen to get back to livestreams, but my oldest son has been very sick, so it's been minimal uploads and no livestreams! [starting to get better!!!]
Stannex: Yay @Fishstick USA !
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow!!! Markus confetti moment for @FishstickUSA
Fishstick USA: @NextStepOfFaith
Rich Vybz: hello everyone!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh my Amy hope your son fully recovers soon. Big virtual hugs.
Fishstick USA: I realized like you said to begin and be publish. I have a Bible verse challenge.
Motif Music Studios: @Mommy Guide Inc thanks so much. A very terrifying brush with meningitis, but seeing miraculous improvements.
Eaglevp: https://www.youtube.com/@NextStepofFaith
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Rich our friend.:)
Stannex: You never FEEL ready ... but once you dive in, you realize you WERE ready all along!
Motif Music Studios: Next Step of Faith sounds like a great encouraging topic! 😉
Rich Vybz: hey Mommy Lala
Fishstick USA: I plan on doing different types of videos. I started with the challenges because they are something i wanted to do. I want to do more but this will come in time.
Mommy Guide Inc: Awesome challenge! Ill share to my community Philip
Tech Troublemaker: Hey! Sorry work is well, very worky today.
Eaglevp: Showed my support Phillip
Motif Music Studios: @Tech Troublemaker in the house! Nice to see you here!
Mommy Guide Inc: So true Stan! I absolutely agree.:)
Eaglevp: Hi@Rich Vybz
Tech Troublemaker: Hey everyone!
Eaglevp: Hi@Tech Troublemaker
Fishstick USA: @eaglevp thank you
Rich Vybz: hey eaglevp
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: 👋
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Great job
Motif Music Studios: So many awesome details.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello friends
Andrea Nunn: Hi all!👍
Tech Troublemaker: Wow, I likey! Has it gone live yet?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @AndreaNunn
Eaglevp: Hello@Ana Zugheri - Faith52
Eaglevp: Hi@Andrea Nunn
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yep!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: It’s raining 🌧️
Motif Music Studios: So many steps to complete projects, however it's so valid to also have projects that are 'skill building' and guilt free!
Mommy Guide Inc: Editing - slowly overcoming the fear
Motif Music Studios: @Ana Zugheri - Faith52 nice to see you here!
Sammy Super Star: Hey Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: So true Amy.:) Hi Sammy! How’s
Eaglevp: Hi@Sammy Super Star how's the filming course going?
Mommy Guide Inc: How’s film school Sammy?
Stannex: "It's new, and it's supposed to be hard." ... SO tough to remember in the heat of the moment.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: It’s hard but you can do it
Motif Music Studios: Yes! SO true and I hear you in the action taking side so you don't get stuck too long!
Eaglevp: I love editing
Sammy Super Star: Going well so far
Sven Jessen: Hi!
Eaglevp: Hello@Sven Jessen
Mommy Guide Inc: That’s great Sammy.:) I should be able to say that in a few more
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: PPP
Stannex: Do it! :^)
Mommy Guide Inc: In a few more years Keith - i love editing. He he he. It is very exciting when i learn new stuff but takes up a lot of time.:)
Eaglevp: Do you do a rough storyboard Markus
Andrea Nunn: I have been recording more b-roll. Kind of random but for future use. Not sure if I should edit into clips now later
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: You are already ahead of the game by trying it out
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: You have a basic story…you just need to add a little extra 😋
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow layering! Love it!
Mommy Guide Inc: Great idea Andrea to create your own broll library
Motif Music Studios: That's such a gift to enjoy that editing! Definitely has been my tougher part of being a creator!
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: when you get broll from pexels do you put in the descriptipn for credits if its free?
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Pray Plan Prepare
Stannex: Sounds like you're worried about the end product meeting your expectations, so you're balking at writing the first draft.
Paul Burke: hey Markus! You keep growing man and showing up consistent...good work!
Eaglevp: Hi@Paul Burke
Fishstick USA: What is your editing software
Fishstick USA: What do others use
Paul Burke: hey @Eaglevp
Andrea Nunn: 👍
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Paul! Our dear Improv guru. Howdy.:)
Paul Burke: hey @Mommy Guide Inc ...it's always great to see you!
Sammy Super Star: I'm using the Top of the top editor now and you need a lot of time to learn but remember story telling is key while editing
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Have you tried chat gpt? It has helped me a lot for putting ideas together
Mommy Guide Inc: Agree Ana. Then tweak it a bit more to personalize it further
Fishstick USA: Thanks Sammy i will check it out
Paul Burke: Lala is the best cheerleader!
Paul Burke: password game? I'll look into it
Fishstick USA: I try to not buy much at this point. I use Microsoft clip editor (free) and I have Canva, which I did buy. My editing needs at the present are minimal.
Mommy Guide Inc: Aww thanks Paul. I just use iMovie but slowly learning FCP
Paul Burke: chatgpt is great....AND....I've been enjoying claude ai too.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: @Fishtick USA you are doing great 👍 you are focusing on the content rather than the tech that’s important when you start
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Lala🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉♥️♥️♥️♥️♥️
Fishstick USA: Thanks Ana
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: That Lala is the ultimate cheerleader 📣
Stannex: Lala IS the best! ❤ ❤
Mommy Guide Inc: I learn all the basics from Ana with a little bit of extra.:)
Tech Troublemaker: Lala is the BEST!!!
Tech Troublemaker: But this is a chat full of amazing people
Stannex: Ok, Markus ... go DO it! One step at a time!
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh i love supporting you all my dear friends. Am blushing now