Marielou Mandl: I’m proud of your commitment !!
Marielou Mandl: Almost the same orange!
Tech Troublemaker: yeah! Plan plan Do Do Do Fail Succeed, Fail Succeed, Refine Plan.
Marielou Mandl: Nice
Tech Troublemaker: You have to pay someone if you fail. You are going to give money to your significant other if you fail to do something you planned.
Tech Troublemaker: I am paying my wife $2 for every day I don't work out.
Fishstick USA: Hello Markus
Marielou Mandl: I love your mindset about this!
Markus Schaub: www.markusschaub.live/mail
Marielou Mandl: I started trying reformer Pilates class
elle naturally: Hi
elle naturally: Halloween scares me so I’m glad you’re all here 🤓🤣😂
Marielou Mandl: Hahah you’re like hey kids here’s some pins from creator camp
Fishstick USA: By the way, that is is really good photo of you on the mail subscription site.
Marielou Mandl: Slimmer!
Marielou Mandl: Gil sounds like hill
elle naturally: Newsletter??
Markus Schaub: www.markusschaub.live/mail
elle naturally: Ty
Marielou Mandl: Signed up!
Marielou Mandl: We’re always the trendsetters
Marielou Mandl: Oooon I love to do that - email bankruptcy
Marielou Mandl: Yes! Use the clip of us walking from the drone
elle naturally: Ok third person to sign up is this 🧟‍♀️
Fishstick USA: I signed up too
elle naturally: That’s me being ghoulish for today 🧟‍♀️🦇👀
elle naturally: Nice ambiance
Eaglevp: Evening Markus
Eaglevp: Hello Ellie
Marielou Mandl: Haha yes just do
CSLiveDK : Hi Markus. Good evening to everyone here😀
Eaglevp: Hey Marielou
Eaglevp: Hi Fishstick
Eaglevp: Hello Ejnar
elle naturally: Is the audio gone?
CSLiveDK : Hi Keith. Hope you’re doing fine😀
Fishstick USA: No audio for me
elle naturally: Audio is back
Eaglevp: Okay thanks Ejnar getting there thanks
CSLiveDK : Sounds Good Keith😀
Fishstick USA: 👍
Eaglevp: Just wish I could get motivate into doing live streams again
CSLiveDK : It was only the sound of silence😀👍👻👻👻
Markus Schaub: www.markusschaub.live/mail
Eaglevp: Just don't feel I have the energy at present to do anything Markus
Eaglevp: Still grieving
Eaglevp: Yes I do
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: hello boy and girls from the world of livestreaming 🙂
Eaglevp: Yes would love that Markus
Eaglevp: Hi Eric
Eaglevp: Will do that Markus
Eaglevp: Yes we all help each other
CSLiveDK : We must get up and going again, Keith. Like the good old days😀 For me it is more than four years since it all started. Sometimes really miss the good old LEDA days. My first LEDA was August 2021.👍
Eaglevp: Thanks Ejnar the good old days of Leda
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: @CSLiveDK you could create "advent livestream" daily 😛
Eaglevp: December everyday good challenge
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: we all can do it 🙂 mini Leda :P
Eaglevp: How is the walking going Markus have you been round the lake yet?
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: during covid19 lookdown i had 5 month daily livestream - for me its not a real challenge 😛 but yes i can do it again
CSLiveDK : The great LEDA revival December 2024. 🥂😀🙏
Tech Troublemaker: don't forget to hit that LIKE button, pretty please.
Eaglevp: Set the goal of walking around the lake by the 25th,December Markus
Eaglevp: Hi Roy
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Keith!