Eaglevp: Evening Markus
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi everyone! happy Groundhog Day! Happy Birthday Lala
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Markus
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: great topic today!
Eaglevp: Hello@Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing hope you are keeping well
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @eglevp hi back and same to you... being well.
Cheryl Wolf: Hello
Eaglevp: Hi@Cheryl Wolf
Cheryl Wolf: Hey Keith
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Cheryl!!!!]
Ellie Calhoun: Hey all!!! Opened it up just as I'm on screen in the song. Love it!
Cheryl Wolf: Ellie!!
Eaglevp: Hi Ellie
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I so love this song. and the video too
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Ellie!!!!
Ellie Calhoun: Cheryl!!! And Janet!!! 😂
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: righit? hahahaha
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Keith! 👋
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: :face-blue-smiling::face-purple-crying:
Ellie Calhoun: I can't stay long, I have a client coming in 10 minutes
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Keith!!! I did not know you were Eaglevp. Now I do! 😉
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Obsess with numbers???? us??? haha!
Cheryl Wolf: Looks like your having fun with your shorts Markus
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: it is funny how shorts respond in different platforms
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I di dnot know about activating numbers on ticktok
Tech Troublemaker: Chase the numbers!!!!
Eaglevp: Evening@Tech Troublemaker
Cheryl Wolf: Germany 🇩🇪 ❤️
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Eaglevp
Cheryl Wolf: Hey Roy
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Haha Roy
Tech Troublemaker: Actually the numbers makes it feel like you are just riding the hamster wheel. No thank you!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I am loving your shorts Markus
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Roy you are rocking shorts too. so fun yall
Eaglevp: Agree numbers are not worth chasing puts to much pressure on you
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: oh I thought that was the best
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: look at you go!
Sammy Super Star: Hey Markus
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Sammy
Cheryl Wolf: Hey Sammy
Eaglevp: Hi@Sammy Super Star
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Cheryl Wolf
Ellie Calhoun: Awesome!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: oh fun. Suzan will be here.
Cheryl Wolf: That’s be a good conversation
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Janet!
Ellie Calhoun: It sure is fun to see the numbers go up though! 😂
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: OH the numbers are really fun when they go up.
Tech Troublemaker: Statistics are really Sadistics! We are gluttons for punishment to watch them.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: wow people have short attention spans
Cheryl Wolf: It’s like a slot machine watching numbers
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @Cheryl then I should NEVER watch numbers! I'm really bad at gambling. haha.
Ellie Calhoun: Yes Cheryl! Dopamine hit?
Tech Troublemaker: I am sure as soon as I get a personality, I will do better.
Ellie Calhoun: Gotta go! Glad I caught part of your live!
Cheryl Wolf: Bye Ellie
Eaglevp: Bye Ellie have a nice weekend
Cheryl Wolf: Roy your doing it !
Eaglevp: Just wish I was Sammys age may have more appeal then........lol
Cheryl Wolf: Age is also just a number!! Doesn’t define us, Bring our magic 🪄
Tech Troublemaker: I am stalled this week on shorts but I loved my livestream this week.
Cheryl Wolf: No I need to start doing shorts
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Cheryl we need to talk!
Cheryl Wolf: Give me ideas today everybody!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: My last one did not do good on IG or TickTok but 1.1k on YouTube!! go figure
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I know... I freaked out
Cheryl Wolf: 🎉🎉Janet
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: oh no you area not!!! it was a repurpose. from a life
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I was surprised and I did get subscribes.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I'm just playing around. I have don't both.
Tech Troublemaker: I haven't asked for subscribers as I need every second to get the idea across.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: and that was the one that went over 1K the ones without the sub ask did not. so we just experiment
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I would not use the sub on IG or TickTok. I only do it on YouTube
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: how do you see your analytics on a short on youtube
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I got it. Go into analytics. got it
Cheryl Wolf: Women like Markus
Cheryl Wolf: You said it in your analytics I’m just agreeing
Cheryl Wolf: Thank you !!