Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
Ellie Calhoun: Hi 👋 Markus!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hey Sammy! How’s film school so far?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Elle.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Ellie:)
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Lala!
Budgeting Momma: Hi everyone
Tatiana Teaches: Hello hello 👋🏼 folks 🙂
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Budgeting Momma and Tatiana:)
Tim Heale 9: Hi Everyone
Tatiana Teaches: Hi Lala! 😁
Mommy Guide Inc: Let’s Go!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Tim!
Eaglevp: Hi Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh the makeup episode! That’s epic!
Eaglevp: Hey Sammy
Budgeting Momma: Hi @mommy guide inc
Eaglevp: Hello Ellie
Eaglevp: Hi@Tatiana Teaches
Eaglevp: Hello9@Budgeting Momma
Tatiana Teaches: 👋🏼 Hi @eaglevp. On mobile and can’t tag.
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Keith, Sammy, Tim, Tatiana and everyone!!
Sammy Super Star: 🕺💃🕺💃🕺
Tatiana Teaches: Hi Ellie!
Tim Heale 9: Did I miss something?
Eaglevp: How's filming school going Sammy
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello 👋
Eaglevp: Hi@Ana Zugheri - Faith52
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana dear;)
Fishstick USA: Gruezi
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Philip!
Eaglevp: Hi@Fishstick USA
Stannex: Made it just in time for the good stuff!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Stan!
Stannex: Hi, Lala!
Tatiana Teaches: Thanks for showing us how! ✅
Eaglevp: Hi Stan
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow so to clarify Markus this can only be done thru desktop YouTube Studio for now?
Eaglevp: Just done it on a few of my shorts thanks Markus
Stannex: Hi, @Eaglevp
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow that’s great Tim! How’s it impacted your channel so far Tim?;)
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Markus!
Sammy Super Star: I’m going to try it and test it out, I’m working on a video so I will be doing a short with a link to the long form
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh sorry it’s Keith. He he he. Sorry my friend.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey go Sammy and pls share with us your result:)
Sammy Super Star: Yes I will! @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Sammy!
Stannex: Creating havoc. 😜
Stannex: Thanks, Markus ... but I hope you're asleep.
Mommy Guide Inc: Excited for LSP’s 5Day challenge. And prepping tons of stuff for Sept 16.:)
Sammy Super Star: That looks like you!
Stannex: My pleasure.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Great job!
Tim Heale 9: I so busy I don't know wether I'm coming or going, I edit in Premier Pro and Adobe Audition as I repurpose my lives and video cast into podcasts
Mariane Cresp: Hi Markus 👋🏼
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Mariane!
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL @Tim!
Tim Heale 9: Depends on the amount of work one does
Stannex: Hi @Mariane Cresp
Mommy Guide Inc: Oooh will you show us Da Vinci Resolve next Markus?
Mariane Cresp: Hi Lala and Stan
Tim Heale 9: Does Devinci edit audio as well?
Eaglevp: Hi@Mariane Cresp
Mommy Guide Inc: Ohh looks like a very interesting video coming up
Mariane Cresp: Hello Keith
Ellie Calhoun: Yup just get it done!
Mommy Guide Inc: I can so relate just like my planner pages right Mariane? When to stop embellishing it? He he he
Tim Heale 9: I have done something new where I interviewed a guest live using 3 cameras and then edited it, worked great 😻
Mommy Guide Inc: Spot on Markus!
Tim Heale 9: Yep in the same room
Mommy Guide Inc: Awesome Tim! Just look at you. Becoming really techie.:) love it. Continue to crush it Tim.:)
Tatiana Teaches: Invite us to your country Markus for an in person interview 😁
Tatiana Teaches: Have a great end of week everyone ✌🏼
Mommy Guide Inc: Great idea Tatiana!
Tim Heale 9: TTFN Tar tar for now 😻