Eaglevp: Evening Markus
Tim Heale 9: Hi Keith, Markus
Eaglevp: Evening Sir Tim
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello 👋
Eaglevp: I am still dancing
Ellie Calhoun: Hi everyone!
Eaglevp: Hi@Ana Zugheri - Faith52
Eaglevp: Hello Ellie
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: About to get a haircut 💇‍♀️ won’t be able to chat but will be listening 👂
Eaglevp: Will watch the replay
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Markus!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Keith!!!
Eaglevp: Hi Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana And Tim! Sorry for being late.;) yey congratulations Markus!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: That was indeed awesome!
Tim Heale 9: Hi Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: For a change it’s only 10pm in Barcelona.:) will meet up with Yuka Tom.:)
Tim Heale 9: How often do you invite a guest back?
Mommy Guide Inc: I always have fun in your streams Markus!
Eaglevp: You should have a panel on Markus
Eaglevp: If you ask they can say yes or no.......
Eaglevp: Just be cheeky
Mommy Guide Inc: Absolutely smashing the like button.:) and share!
Tim Heale 9: Don't ask for money 😂
Mary Speegle: Great job!
Eaglevp: Hi Mary
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Mary!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Lol 😂
Adam Tinkoff: Hey there, Markus. Good to see you LIVE
Adam Tinkoff: Nice haircut!
Eaglevp: That's right Tim it's buy me a coffee......or a Gin & Tonic
Mommy Guide Inc: Let’s Make Another live challenge Markus!
Eaglevp: Hi Adam
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Thinking about getting a haircut like Markus 😎
BostonDonMTB: Hi Markus, hope all is well with you. Hi Lala.
Eaglevp: Hi@BostonDonMTB
BostonDonMTB: @Eaglevp howdy.
BostonDonMTB: Wow, you guys will be in the area. Will the Ecamm thing cost money?
BostonDonMTB: I will have to keep in touch with you all.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Lala i hope you take videos of your travels and show us beautiful Barcelona.
Eaglevp: Where you live Markus would like to see your area
Adam Tinkoff: Being a streamer in Switzerland
Adam Tinkoff: What are the challenges? High cost?
Eaglevp: That's a good one Adam
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes! @Eaglevp that is a great idea
Eaglevp: What your interests are beside live streaming
Adam Tinkoff: iOS vs Desktop? Where do you draw the line on how you get things done - which platform, etc.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Having two channels when you are bilingual?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi everyone. Sorry I’m late. I brought animal crackers 🐶🐈‍⬛🐩🐖🐏🐄🐪🦛🦘🐋🐳🦄
Eaglevp: Hi@Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: The lier that comes to kill and destroy. We need to shut him down.
Tim Heale 9: I've got 2 channels 😻
Ellie Calhoun: Tips for interviewing others or experiences you've had
Budgeting Momma: Hi Markus
Eaglevp: Hi@Budgeting Momma
Adam Tinkoff: Good to see you as always