Eaglevp: Evening Markus and Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: and we're live! Hi Markus and Keith!
Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
Eaglevp: Hi@Sammy Super Star
Mommy Guide Inc: Not?Ready Go! isn't that an awesome hoodie? oh yes - you can have one of that - here you go - grab one or two of these here - https://markusschaub.shop
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sammy:)
Mommy Guide Inc: our feel good music video:) all the feels - love it:)
Mommy Guide Inc: aww Colter's dance moves - the best!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hope everyone is warm enough and safe. for me though hoping for cooler weather today. not cold just cool is enough:)
Mommy Guide Inc: oh my!
Mommy Guide Inc: handle is broken but still useable - pen holder etc:) repurpose
Rich Vybz: How is everyone today!!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello 👋
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Rich and Ana!
Eaglevp: Hi@Ana Zugheri - Faith52 & @Rich Vybz
Rich Vybz: HEY Lala and eaglevp
Mommy Guide Inc: join us and be a member: https://markusschaub.shop
Mommy Guide Inc: Don't forget to hit the LIKE button friends:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus the screen is not centered
Mommy Guide Inc: yey there:)
Mommy Guide Inc: thanks Markus:) you got it. tweaking live:)
Mommy Guide Inc: friends a question for you - do you use end cards for your videos or livestreams?
Mommy Guide Inc: hey Markus figured it out:)
Eaglevp: Yes for my video's but not on the live streams Lal
Mommy Guide Inc: I add the end cards to my livestream after it airs when it becomes a video on demand:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: Markus when you started, did you use start or create a new file? sorry I don't use keynote.
Mommy Guide Inc: so that's thru keynote. I thought I needed to use iMovie or something to create that.
Mommy Guide Inc: yey!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Looks pretty good to me
Mommy Guide Inc: that's awesome. I'll use this Markus to give a shoutout to my channel members too! Thanks so much.
Mommy Guide Inc: yes please Markus - a process video would be awesome:)
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Hello Markus. Late but glad to see you
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Philip:)
Eaglevp: Hello@Fishstick ~ Phillip
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Hahahahaha
Mommy Guide Inc: My craft getaway coming up soon!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: But…you showed up!!!! That is huge
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes you did it Markus! thank you
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Soccer ⚽️ is super demanding but enjoy this phase of motherhood
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I’m only able to do my podcast but I hope soon I can pick up a rhythm and start making videos and live streams again
Mommy Guide Inc: so true Ana. the kids grow up so fast.
Mariane Cresp: Hello Markus!
Eaglevp: Hi@Mariane Cresp
Mariane Cresp: Hello Keith!
Mommy Guide Inc: Oops laptop died so now on phone:) Hi Mariane:)
Mariane Cresp: Hi Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Good morning Mariane:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Also request process video - how to bring in zoom to ecamm with audio pls
Mommy Guide Inc: You did great Markus!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: You did!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes you did it. Thanks for sharing this with us and friends dont forget to LIKE this video.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes not perfection but creation.:)