Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @TimHeale9!
Tim Heale 9: Hi Lala, are you well?
Mommy Guide Inc: All is well
Eaglevp: Hi zYim and Lals
Mommy Guide Inc: All is well in the future Tim!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello friends! Happy Thursday 😀
Mommy Guide Inc: Go Keith! Let’s Go! 💃 🕺
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana!
Mommy Guide Inc: It’s a Friyay already for me but indeed Happy Thursday for you all.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Aww miss Stephanie.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I should say happy day 😋
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh the makeup episode. That’s was so much fun.:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Lol 😂 it was
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I remember that one too…when you and Markus are adjusting the screen
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Sammy!!! Haven’t seen him lately
Mommy Guide Inc: Sammy busy busy editing and doing photography lately.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Keith!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: That is right..🚖🚖🚖🚖
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello Keith 🤗
Tim Heale 9: Boom Keith’s in the room 😻
Mommy Guide Inc: He he he - Ana in the 🚘.:) take care my friend.:)
Tim Heale 9: Have I missed the show?
Tim Heale 9: TTFN
Mommy Guide Inc: We should have Coke as a sponsor in the future.:) and other 🥤:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: It’s the last time I’ll be watching in the car until next school year…my daughter is goin on vacation next week🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉
Ellie Calhoun: Hey everyone! Just listening as I drive!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Keith is doing a 30-day in May on his channel.:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hi Ellie ❤️🫶
Mommy Guide Inc: If you are not yet following Keith here is his channel https://www.youtube.com/live/k-iaqCYfEKk?feature=share
Tim Heale 9: Numb the nerves instead of calm them 😂
Tim Heale 9: Don’t forget the colabs
Mommy Guide Inc: Here is Keith’s channel https://www.youtube.com/live/wa8LGacvd00?feature=share
Mommy Guide Inc: Smashing the Like 👍 button helps out Markus’ channel. Thanks.
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey @Mariane Cresp!
Mariane Cresp: Hello Lala @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: How’s the future like Mariane? thanks for joining us today.:)
Mariane Cresp: Woo-hoo! Thank you Markus
Tim Heale 9: This is my first time 😻
Mommy Guide Inc: Friends @MarianeCresp is another awesome content creator. Highly suggest you check her out as well.
Tim Heale 9: Lol
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Welcome @mariane
Mommy Guide Inc: Keith’s LEDM is awesome. Short but sweet daily tidbits of awesome information:)
Tim Heale 9: I started with podcasts now I do both YT and podcasts
Mariane Cresp: Hello @Ana Zugheri - Faith52 ☺
Mommy Guide Inc: I agree Keith - one won’t know unless we try.:)
Tim Heale 9: Not to mention the others from LEDA carried on LEDM 👍
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Hi Markus and Keith😀
Mommy Guide Inc: Keith has done the full circle - from edited videos to livestreaming. Very inspiring.:) Encouraging me to start doing edited videos more often
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ejnar @CSLive-CommunicationSocialMediaLivestreaming
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Hi Lala😀
Mommy Guide Inc: 1k views per video - you got this Keith!
Tim Heale 9: I have a goal of getting back to England tomorrow 🤔
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Q do views in live stream have more value than videos?
Mommy Guide Inc: Safe travels Tim.
Tim Heale 9: Thanks Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Great question Ana:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I’m waiting for Lala and Markus to come visit!!!
Stannex: Hi, all! Sorry to be late ... I'll catch up on the replay!
Mommy Guide Inc: Ana just say when! We will be there.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Stan@Stannex!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: And friends!!!
Ellie Calhoun: Keith, this is great information! So not just looking for numbers but you're looking for connection and actual relationship! Love it!
Mommy Guide Inc: OMG Stan!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: That is a great idea 💡
Mommy Guide Inc: Sorry i accidentally timed out you my phone fell! Sorry my friend.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I was like… oh Stan what did you say????😂😂😂
Mommy Guide Inc: Livestream booboos from the moderator!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Lala you are awesome 👏
Tim Heale 9: And all day as well
Tim Heale 9: Alls Uber de platz
Mommy Guide Inc: CPM changes per niche indeed.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Stan are you back with us? Can you make a comment again? Sorry my friend.
Stannex: This is my first "time out" ... LOL
Mommy Guide Inc: Cartoon piece Stan.:) he he he
Tim Heale 9: It’s fun to get a few guests in for a chat
Mariane Cresp: Yes, I've stopped looking at the numbers.
Mommy Guide Inc: That’s great Stan. Try it out.:)
Stannex: "Don't drop your phone" is good general advice, too. :^)
Tim Heale 9: I’ve done it a few times it’s fun
Mommy Guide Inc: 😂 @Stannex. That will be a great meme too.:)
Stannex: Modify the "couch" style show that Graham Norton uses on TV
Tim Heale 9: G & T helps lol
Mommy Guide Inc: Great take away from Keith - preparation in terms of research on a new topic helps
Tim Heale 9: How often do you corpse?
Stannex: As long as you don't snore while your eyes are closed, I'm sure people will understand that you're organizing your thoughts. :^)
Mommy Guide Inc: It’s time to smash the LIKE 👍 button if you find this livestream impactful. It really helps Markus channel
Mommy Guide Inc: I used to do 5hour livestreams and i also wondered if people
Mommy Guide Inc: Have gone to take naps in between.:) LOL
Stannex: 👍
Stannex: This show is proof that people are interesting!
Mommy Guide Inc: Or do remixes from the livestreams and create shorts.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: I agree Stan:)
Mariane Cresp: If you just stop and listen, you can learn so much from others.
Tim Heale 9: It’s cos you waffle on lol
Mommy Guide Inc: So true Mariane. We can find inspiration and learn from others.:)
Tim Heale 9: 1
Tim Heale 9: Oh I ment 10
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh wow its the top of the hour already? Time flies when were having fun! A 10 indeed!
Stannex: It's funny. We may not have fascinating "life stories" ... but all our lives are filled with fascinating stories!
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: 10😉
Mommy Guide Inc: Thank you do much Markus and Keith! Thanks everyone!
Stannex: 8.5 ... but I missed the first half-hour, so it's probably even better!
Tim Heale 9: She know her stuff