Fishstick ~ Phillip: Hello my friend
Neil Farrimond: Hi Markus!
Stannex: Hi, Markus! Congrats on a successful April!!!!
Stannex: VEDIA NOW!!!!
Enda Trading: Hi all
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello 👋
Stannex: So it not only worked as a challenge ... it worked as a primer for your creativity going forward!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: So happy to see you!!! ♥️ I’ve been able to see here and there what you have been doing! Great job! 👏
Stannex: GOOD humorous timing in that video!
Neil Farrimond: I applaud you for creating so many videos last month. It's not an easy undertaking. Congrats Markus!
Run Adam Run: Hey there Markus!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: The quality is really really good
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: It’s so hard to be consistent. I failed miserably on my 30 day challenge…i missed 3 days 😞
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: That takes a lot of concentration confidence and creativity. Well done 👍
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Ana, listen to Adam. You succeeded 27 times
Mariane Cresp: Hello Markus!
Mariane Cresp: 🤣
Neil Farrimond: You had me with that title 🙂
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Thank you so much for the encouragement! A very difficult life situation has keeping me from creating and just being able to be on sm but hopefully soon I’ll get back…stronger!
Run Adam Run: Is Spotify next?
Run Adam Run: Love the snappy tune. It fits your style.
Stannex: I love that music!
Run Adam Run: I would watch you doing mundane things around your town with a song like that.
Run Adam Run: Are you familiar with the famous film by Andy Warhol eating a hamburger?
Tech Troublemaker: All of my videos are based on Andy Warhol's ethos. 😛
Run Adam Run: It's on YouTube, and it's exactly what the title suggests
Run Adam Run: what makes it amazing is that it's just Andy eating a hamburger which in itself is a miracle.
Run Adam Run: 44,000 years of evolution and we can make hamburgers. Astonishing!
Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
Tech Troublemaker: zoy
Tech Troublemaker: It's the ultimate Burger King Commercial. Andy Warhol
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: hello crazy people around the world
Tech Troublemaker: Hit that LIKE button everyone! Please.
Stannex: Go, Markus, go!
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: we are all crazy livestreamer / video content creator 😛 thats part of the job
Run Adam Run: What a cool museum!
Run Adam Run: Swiss trains are so cool. I would watch you riding them. They are not a big deal here in California.
Tech Troublemaker: Haha, for my Morning Thoughts this morning the front camera was on instead of the rear camera so my video was showing my dashboard and not me. Haha.
Run Adam Run: That Pocket 3 is a real champ. The image quality is incredible.
Run Adam Run: What camera will you bring to Creator Camp?
Tech Troublemaker: #CreatorCamp
Tech Troublemaker: I didn't realize there were so many blurry people in Switzerland.
Run Adam Run: It's a rare side effect of Swiss chocolate.
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: @Tech Troublemaker blurry is that a other word for drunk? rofl
Neil Farrimond: Creator Camp 2024 !
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: @Markus Schaub thats why you need a blog 😛
Stannex: That YOU'RE satisfied is the only measure of success that matters.
Tech Troublemaker: I used to stress so much about perfection but now I just do it and called it art.
Run Adam Run: Is "Art House Film" is a fancy way of saying "bad film" lol?
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Helooooo
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Hi friends
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: How is everyone? You’ve done AHMAZZZING Marcus
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: You have really inspired me! Thank you so much
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Your challenge has taught me a lot
Tech Troublemaker: You did great Markus! I really enjoyed your videos.
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: I hadn’t gone live in a few months and I’ve gone live more than 4 times doing beauty stuff: out of my comfort zone
Stannex: Build on success!
Tech Troublemaker: I no longer do beauty videos.
Run Adam Run: Yay!