Cheryl Wolf: Hey Markus & Suzan🎉🎉
Cheryl Wolf: 💃💃💃
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi everyone
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Mariane
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Janet
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Cheryl!!!
Mariane Cresp: Tuning in from Sydney, Australia!
Mariane Cresp: Hello Cheryl and Janet
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi mariane
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Markus
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Suzan
Mariane Cresp: Hello Suzan
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: don't forget to hit that LIKE 👍🏻
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh love that, "playing with intention"
Fishstick USA: Hello Markus and Suzan
Tech Troublemaker: Hey, I know you guys! Hey everyone!
Mariane Cresp: For me: playing small is not getting out of my comfort zone
Tech Troublemaker: There is a big difference between starting small and starting slow.
Cheryl Wolf: avoiding risk, undervalue, lack of confidence
Eaglevp: Evening Markus and Susan
Eaglevp: Hi Cheryl and Roy
Cheryl Wolf: Hey fishstick
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Roy
Eaglevp: Hello Mariane Cresp
Fishstick USA: A: no risk, not leaving comfort
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Keith
Eaglevp: Hi Janet
Mariane Cresp: Hello @Eaglevp, Roy and @Fishstick USA
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Eaglevp
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh Keith!!! that's you. haha
Tech Troublemaker: I officially become a business today. I am taking the risks and I have big plans.
Eaglevp: Hi Fishstick USA
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Congrats Roy. very exciting. what made you "official"? LLC or something else?
Eaglevp: All the best Roy
Tech Troublemaker: I don't have skills yet but I have plans. Tech Troublemaker, LLC.
Cheryl Wolf: Lol washing or stuck in learning instead of working on what will move me forward
Fishstick USA: C: It is wise to develop a project in manageable steps, but you should not require every step to be perfect or an unrealistic ideal before moving on to the next step.
Eaglevp: Congratulations Markus on the 200 subscribers mark
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: YAY!! LLC is so important. congradts 🎉
Fishstick USA: Roy, Congrats!
Cheryl Wolf: Congratulations 🎉 Roy
Kali : woohoo!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: KALI!!!!!
Cheryl Wolf: True Fishstick
Tech Troublemaker: Thank you all. You all inspire me.
Cheryl Wolf: Hey Kali
Kali : @Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing janet!!! ❤️
Kali : @Cheryl Wolf hey!! ❤
Kali : @Tech Troublemaker hi roy! 🤗 ❤
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Kali
Eaglevp: Hi Kali
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Washing IS working!!!
Mariane Cresp: I know I am in my own way when I get resentful when others are doing the things I WANTED/NEEDED to do, but are not doing myself
Mariane Cresp: Hi @Kali
Fishstick USA: Personal comment: I am an avid reader. But I remember being told in high school that I should not read about life and start truly living it.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Feel the FEAR and do it anyway!
Fishstick USA: Do not live it fear is a good statement
Fishstick USA: *in fear
Kali : @Mariane Cresp hey!! 🤗 ❤️
Tech Troublemaker: Have BHAG (Big Hairy Audacious Goals) and go for it.
Fishstick USA: Suzan, your response to my comment is correct. I did move to college which helped me tremendously.
Cheryl Wolf: Q Do you think the speed that we pivot after we fail is important to help overcome some of the fear
Fishstick USA: I came out of my shell.
Fishstick USA: BTW, People cannot believe I was or am introverted.
Cheryl Wolf: Same fishstick
Tech Troublemaker: But Fishsticks have batter, not shells, just an observation 😛
Fishstick USA: Roy haha
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Markus and Suzan. So good to see you both😀😀😉
Eaglevp: Hi Ejnar
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi @CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Ejnar!
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Ejnar
Fishstick USA: Ejnar, been watching your videos. Good work.
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hey Keith😀👋
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Ejar!!!
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Cheryl. 👍😀 Nice to see you all here😉
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Roy👋😀
Cheryl Wolf: Nice to see you!
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Thank you so much @fishstick😀
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Is there a link for the video? I clicked the website link and can't find it
Fishstick USA: Ejnar, appreciate your english videos.😜
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi @Animal Paradise👍👋
Fishstick USA: A: Develop a work - life - and hobby balance. Work and daily family tasks have been taking up a lot of my bandwith
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Glad you can understand me well, @fishstick😉
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: KITTEN!!! 😻
Paul Burke: do you think it's helpful to have a coach that can politely slap you in the face and help you set bigger goals and can see them clearly?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: PAULIE!!!
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: You are doing excellent, Markus😀👍
Fishstick USA: I have not been procrastinating. I am letting others know I need time for myself. I have 30 days of vacation plus more holidays to take before the end of the year. I can use my time for my hobbies.
Cheryl Wolf: Hey Paul!
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Paul Burke👍😀 👋 hi. Long time no seen., happy to see you here😀
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: oh YOUTUBE. got it. sorry. I thought it was on the website. yay
Paul Burke: hey animal Paradise! hey Cheryl!
Paul Burke: hey SliveDK!
Cheryl Wolf: 💯
Mariane Cresp: I think the Coach help keeps asking the questions you don't want to answer
Fishstick USA: Markus, I am very interested in your tech for older people. I have a friend in France who would like to develop a channel for tech for the disabled. Such as better tech for sight and hearing.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I thought you were having the model look
Paul Burke: great points!
Paul Burke: so true Mariane!
Mary Speegle: Two of my favorite live streamers!!!! 👏 Yay!
Fishstick USA: Mary, I agree
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I always love your gray kitty. Always reminds me of our kitty CLEO. She always shows up to remind me to "Remember The Mission". That gets me back on track and gives me courage.
Fishstick USA: Markus invents the “long short”
Paul Burke: maybe babystep it Markus...just get it done...regardless of "quality" level. markus...if you do a video I'll do a video. this will be like the NATO of video creation...we'll work as a team
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Love that idea and challenge Paul. NATO accountability
Cheryl Wolf: Can't wait to see your video Sunday Markus🎉
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Markus never sleeps, so Sunday is far away😉
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: We will all be ready for the premiere on Sunday. 😀👍
Paul Burke: don't play with our hearts Markus. lookin forward to that video. Hot Takes with Markus
Mary Speegle: I'm interested in your commitment to when you're going to do it versus when you'll publish.
Cheryl Wolf: Good question Mary
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Great show again Markus. Look forward to your video release on Sunday 😀👍
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Nice to see you again Suzan😀
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: A short short😂🤣
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hi 👋 jumping in late. I’m on vacation on a different time zone 🤦🏻‍♀️ but glad I caught y’all live
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: ANA!!!
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Ana😀👍👋👋
Stannex: Gah! I missed it! (Thank goodness I still have the replay!)
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Ana
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hi friends!!! ♥️
Fishstick USA: Thank you for the livecast. Enjoyed it.