CSLiveDK : Hi Markus. 50 years and still going strong💪💪
CSLiveDK : I am 61 and still not feeling any difference. Only legs an knees hurts. But the head still working. 😉
BostonDonMTB: Hello Markus, Happy Belated Birthday!!!
BostonDonMTB: I will be 59 on August 3rd. I am biking, I had a ride yesterday, and I might be meeting a friend to ride tomorrow. We have to work on the logistics. Rain has kept at bay until Sat and Sun.
CSLiveDK : A long way it’s just a number, but we unfortunately know there is a limit. Guess no one wants to think about that. Try to enjoy life instead of thinking too much about it. 😉
Fishstick USA: Hello Markus
BostonDonMTB: Why not?
Fishstick USA: 50 years old is still a baby
BostonDonMTB: 50 was pretty cool.
Fishstick USA: I feel better at 65 than at 50
BostonDonMTB: My motto that I lost sight of for awhile is "Live Life with the 3 F's: Friends, Family, and Fun. The why not question was for you not having anything to talk about? You probably have stories.
Mariane Cresp: Hello Markus!
BostonDonMTB: @Fishstick USA I hope that I will be the same at 65 as I am at 58. I think moving will help us all accomplish that.
Mariane Cresp: Welcome to 50s
Fishstick USA: BostonDon, grandchildchildr
CSLiveDK : The only thing that bother me is that everyone under 50 now suddenly think you are old and worthless. Especially if you loose your job after 50 it’s a hopeless task to get back to the working market.
BostonDonMTB: @Fishstick USA I am sure that helps too. That is one of my big regrets not having kids. Still haven't met the right one.
Mariane Cresp: Grandchildren, you can give them back to their parents 🤣
Fishstick USA: BostonDon, i have all 8 grandchildren since then. I am stronger now. Lifting and playing with children has helped.
BostonDonMTB: @CSLiveDK I am in that boat too. I am feeling quite lost. Even at 58, I feel like I need a mentor that can see the good in me, and help guide me. I should have made better decisions in the past.
Mariane Cresp: 50 is not old. Well, I don’t feel old.
BostonDonMTB: @Markus Schaub How do you spend time with him? My nephew is turning 15 in a week.
CSLiveDK : No, we don’t feel old but others think we are and we cannot do normal things. 😉
BostonDonMTB: @Markus Schaub Thank you.
Fishstick USA: Markus, i am not certain if you take any prescribed meds, but be cautious about side effects. I was taking meds in my 50’s whose side effects caused
BostonDonMTB: @Markus Schaub Yeah it is. I should make more of an effort. He is a great kid.
Fishstick USA: …leg pains and foggy thinking
Fishstick USA: I stopped taking two years ago and feel better. Blood sugar, blood pressure, acid reflux are all better without or with different meds
Fishstick USA: You are awesome!