Ellie Calhoun: Hey hey! Markus!! Unfortunately I have a client coming in, in a minutes so I can't stay, but as always I'll watch the replay!
Tim Heale 9: Hi Markus, did you catch any of my live earlier?
Ellie Calhoun: My favorite song! 🎶
Fishstick USA: Greetings from the U.S.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Happy Thursday!!!! 👋🎉
Tim Heale 9: You missed a great show
Stannex: Markus & Mariane ... two of my favorite people!
Ellie Calhoun: Hey Mariane!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Friends don’t forget to like 👍 and share!!!!
Eaglevp: Evening Markus & Mariane
Eaglevp: Hi Tim & Stan
Eaglevp: Hello Ellie
Tim Heale 9: Hi Keith
Eaglevp: Hi@Ana Zugheri - Faith52
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello 👋 hello 👋 @eaglevp! So glad you are here!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Sharing is caring!!! I love that concept of getting inspired through others.
Angelo Allen: It *is* lovely to augment the family income!
Eaglevp: Hi@Angelo Allen
Stannex: Hi, Keith
Angelo Allen: Hi @Eaglevp !
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi everyone.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hi 👋
Eaglevp: Hello@Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing
Angelo Allen: Yeah. Figuring out how to strike a balance between strategic business perfection and honoring what makes your heart sing (having fun!)
Stannex: It's sometimes tough to remember that when you take a course you're adding to your toolbox. But you don't need to use ALL the tools ALL the time.
Stannex: "A watched pot never boils"
Fishstick USA: C: Mariane, your points are very relatable. Enjoy listening to you. Very encouraging.
Angelo Allen: The trick is to not let the analytics turn your creative efforts into drudgery!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes!!! Markus is a wonderful host!!!
Tim Heale 9: You would be surprised how much rubbish people watch and get thousands of views yet really good channels with great content hardly get any views 😏
Eaglevp: Agree with you Tim
Stuart Video -Tech Installation: Markus!
Angelo Allen: Yes! Being in it to help others -- even one person -- proves that you are providing value in your content. That's the real joy of it!
Eaglevp: Hi@Stuart Video -Tech Installation
Stuart Video -Tech Installation: Hi @Eaglevp
Eaglevp: How are you today@Stuart Video -Tech Installation ?
David W. Ryan: Hi Markus and Mariane!.
Eaglevp: Hello@David W. Ryan
Angelo Allen: Mental wellbeing is everything.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Welcome everyone, we are glad you are here 🎉🎉🎉🎉
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: LEDA changes lives!!!!!
Angelo Allen: I find that I have to give myself some grace...a lot!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I lately go for a walk…
Stannex: Planning is always flexible ... you put down what you hope to do, and you adjust for what you actually do (and what life has thrown at you).
Tim Heale 9: You can put off today what you can do tomorrow 😻
Angelo Allen: Yes!
Tim Heale 9: Mariane is welcome to come on my show to talk about your mental wellbeing ❤️
Angelo Allen: REAL TALK! As a content creator myself, I appreciate this wonderful conversation! Thank you, Mariane and Markus!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Great insights!
Fishstick USA: This a fascinating. Very real. Thank you both.
Stannex: Your community is there for you ... trolls may pop up, but they AREN'T part of your community.
David W. Ryan: I'm trying to build a community on Facebook but has been slow. I haven't been able to put a lot of effort into it because of my work.
Angelo Allen: Those things are a tribute to your perseverance!
Budgeting Momma: Hi everyone
Eaglevp: Hello@Budgeting Momma
Stannex: "Am I wearing pants?" is now my new touchstone.
Tech Troublemaker: Realistically? Is anything real?
Eaglevp: Hi Roy
Tim Heale 9: TTFN Tar tar for now 😻🐶😻
Stannex: thanks, Mariane!
Stannex: Thanks, Markus!
Stannex: Another GREAT hour!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Thank you so much 😊
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Don’t forget to like and subscribe 👍👍👍👍
Tech Troublemaker: Claire is awesome
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Eaglevp!
Fishstick USA: Markus, great episode. You brought us an excellent interview.