Mommy Guide Inc: And here we go!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Party time!!!
Claire Sara: Ooh this is very fun!
itdair.network: Excellent! 🙂 Yay!
Cheryl Wolf: hello
Mommy Guide Inc: yey @Cheryl Wolf in the house!
itdair.network: Hello @Cheryl Wolf
Claire Sara: Wow this is my first pre-stream dance, how am i doing??
Cheryl Wolf: 🎂HAPPY BIRTHAY LALAL
Cheryl Wolf: OOPS EXTRA L
Nature Photo Studios: Wow, I’d be staring blankly into the camera if it were me! Great job Claire
Mommy Guide Inc: You're doing absolutely awesome @Claire Sara. Awesome background too @Claire Sara
Cheryl Wolf: Hi all
Tech Troublemaker: the circle is on fire.
itdair.network: Awesome @Claire Sara and @Markus Schaub
Mommy Guide Inc: awww thanks @Cheryl Wolf
Eaglevp: Hello all
Nina McCann: Haha, nailing the intro dancing!
Cheryl Wolf: lala glad you understood my fat finger typing lol
itdair.network: Hello @Eaglevp
Eaglevp: Hi Lala
Eaglevp: Hey Cheryl
Claire Sara: That is a very fun way to get started haha
Mommy Guide Inc: this is our all-time-favorite intro music! gosh it's so nice to see everyone
Mommy Guide Inc: Streaming Life is awesome!!!
Tech Troublemaker: Yah! Live Streaming!
Tech Troublemaker: Live is Life.
Mommy Guide Inc: love that @Roy - Lives Life!
Mommy Guide Inc: yey! Hi @Markus Schaub @Claire Sara!!!
Eaglevp: Hi@Nature Photo Studios
itdair.network: Hey Markus!
Nina McCann: Whoop whoop! Hello!! What a fun intro!!
Cheryl Wolf: Hi All
Eaglevp: Hi@Nina McCann
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Claire
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Claire
itdair.network: Hello @Nina McCann
itdair.network: Thank you for the link @Mommy Guide Inc ❤
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Thanks Lala. I was going to ask for her link. Yay
Awesome Wood Things: Hello awesome people 👋
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi-5 @Claire Sara -in PJs us both. LOL.
itdair.network: Hello @Awesome Wood Things
Mommy Guide Inc: yey Hi Matt @Awesome Wood Things
Awesome Wood Things: Hi itdair Hi Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: For questions don't forget to put a Q: before it so Markus can easily see it:)
Cheryl Wolf: Claire is action taker
Mommy Guide Inc: Financial stability - specially during these times is a must. What an awesome mission - teach the world how to do it - and to start with your parents - epic!
Tech Troublemaker: That's what I need to do, ask my therapist to be my accountability partner. Genius! Expensive, but genius!
Mommy Guide Inc: thousands of views on videos - awesome!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @Roy too funny!
Mommy Guide Inc: oh my. I am glad that it didn't stop you from creating content.
Mommy Guide Inc: on point - absolutely agree - our topic should be one we are passionate about to keep us going. Awesome passionate people in the chat right now:)
Nature Photo Studios: The thing I love about Claire is that her advice is practical and actionable
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: It's nice to have that balance between guests and solo
Mommy Guide Inc: great mind set. It doesn't matter if there is one or so many watching - just have fun and enjoy the interview.
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: How do you keep those nerves at bay?
Mommy Guide Inc: awww Janet@Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing look at her coffee mug:) so cute.
Xanthi S: Hello
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Xanthi S
Mommy Guide Inc: great advice - get a drink! tea also for me:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Xanthi S
Xanthi S: Hey everyone :)
Xanthi S: Wow thank you ☺️
Cheryl Wolf: Q what camera does claire use, she is placed perfectly in her screen
Nina McCann: Love the welcome confetti! Hey Xanthi!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Being authentic is so important.
Xanthi S: It really feels welcoming
Cheryl Wolf: yes totally agree @Nina McCann
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yes together
The Creator Classroom: Claire being interviewed. the tables have turned
Mommy Guide Inc: oh yeah welcome @The Creator Classroom
The Creator Classroom: thanks everybody. had to at least pop in.
Xanthi S: Yes, that, documenting!
Mommy Guide Inc: yes, absolutely relatable Claire. Gary V - I find him such a visionary fellow specially in biz and content creation
Xanthi S: I have the zv1 and that convenience, to just plug it in the computer is invaluable 🙌
Mommy Guide Inc: oh yes studio tour is always so fun.
Xanthi S: I love both your backgrounds
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Love behind the scenes. thanks.
The Creator Classroom: love the pull back
Tech Troublemaker: Elgato has a new stand alone Green Screen XL but Green Screen is such a pain lighting wise.
Nina McCann: Hahahahaaaa oh my goodness the antlers 😂😂
The Creator Classroom: I wish that elgato pull up thing was not in green. that it was dual side grey blue
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Or invite doggies over!
Cheryl Wolf: Roller derby sooo fun
The Creator Classroom: Budget don't Buy
The Creator Classroom: talking with me. 🤣🤣🤣
The Creator Classroom: that was so much fun. that stream.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @Mommy Guide Inc Lala you crack me up
Cheryl Wolf: Q Do you have community outside of YT for your followers
Mary Speegle: Q How does Claire pick her guests? . Has any fool said no??
The Creator Classroom: bloody legend
Mommy Guide Inc: ooh Jennifer@The Creator Classroom - great a Canva master
Nina McCann: Haha, bloody legend indeed Jennifer!
Tech Troublemaker: Mommy can.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh nice. Grow on Youtube on FB
The Creator Classroom: absolutely the canva legend. according to Claire
Mommy Guide Inc: yes I can share the community. wait a minute:)
The Creator Classroom: the FB Community is amazing.
The Creator Classroom: I actually said no. well I said not yet
Mommy Guide Inc: and this is Claire's awesome community - https://www.facebook.com/groups/growonyoutubecommunity
Cheryl Wolf: lala your rockstar
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Claire's community!!! so happy yall are here
Nina McCann: 👋👋👋 heyyy! So lovely to be here with you all! 😊
The Creator Classroom: Claire is a Rockstar
Cheryl Wolf: Great point Claire!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Don't forget to like 👍
Mommy Guide Inc: being part of an awesome community is empowering and inspiring indeed. Please don't forget to subscribe Markus channel. Oh yeah and let's hit that LIKE button:) 18 awesome people watching:)
The Creator Classroom: my motto is every expert was once a beginner. whether it's youtube or canva
Mommy Guide Inc: great motto Jennifer@The Creator Classroom
Cheryl Wolf: @The Creator Classroom Great motto
Nina McCann: 👍👍
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Love that motto 😻
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh I love that. the positive take on the hate comments. I did not take my first well. I know know better. we have to have fun right?
Mommy Guide Inc: hate comments and trolls - it'll come rather than it may come. so focus on the ones that really appreciates your content.
The Creator Classroom: the negative Nancy's or Nelson's are hurting in their own way so bless and release.
Cheryl Wolf: Janet you do that also keeping comments
Mommy Guide Inc: Bless and release - love that Jennifer. thanks for sharing that
Nina McCann: Absolutely Jennifer! 🙌
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hurt people, hurt people!
The Creator Classroom: doesn't mean it doesn't hurt, but still.
The Creator Classroom: wait Bless & Release. Claire did I come up with my merch idea? 🤣
Nina McCann: Very true Animal Paradise 🙌 so good to look at it all with kindness and keep on keeping on hey 😊😊
Mommy Guide Inc: Go for it Jennifer!
Tech Troublemaker: Trolls mean someone is watching.
The Creator Classroom: I have my other merch idea on lock down. 🔐
The Creator Classroom: Q: are you getting them more on your shorts or videos?
Mommy Guide Inc: Isn't Sara awesome - don't forget to visit her channel and subscribe https://www.youtube.com/@ClaireSara
Cheryl Wolf: That is wonderful !!
Mommy Guide Inc: oh Community Tab - great reminder to actually use it!
Tim Heale 9: G-Day guys 😻
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Tim@Tim Heale 9
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yes! @Mommy Guide Inc Lala. reminders of everything in YouTube. I have not been that active with my community tab. this is great inspiration.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Tim
Cheryl Wolf: Hey Tim
The Creator Classroom: you had a joke. I think it could have been me. 🤣🤣🤣🤣
Tim Heale 9: Thanks guys
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I did miss you last week
Eaglevp: Evening Tim
Mommy Guide Inc: authenticity absolutely resonates with both Markus and Claire. And I believe that's why you both have a great community.:) yes, give oneself grace when we cannot go live or make a video
Mommy Guide Inc: don't worry no audio.
Cheryl Wolf: Claire you always upload video or live interviews?
The Creator Classroom: I have to cancel my live streams a lot due to health or weather. I feel bad, but also know it's necessary. no one needs to see my "kidney stone moving" face ot hear massive thunder.
Cheryl Wolf: Oh @The Creator Classroom poor thing
Tim Heale 9: Hi Keith are you up for a chat after?
Mommy Guide Inc: Thank you for being here - please don't forget to smash the LIKE button. It absolutely helps Markus' channel when you do so.:)
Eaglevp: Ok Tim
The Creator Classroom: Cheryl it's okay. I've lived with chronic health issues my whole adult life. sometimes I cope well. sometimes I don't.
Cheryl Wolf: your strong person
The Creator Classroom: Cheryl in case she doesn't get to it she actually does lives, videos and shorts.
Mommy Guide Inc: Jennifer @The Creator Classroom - Cheryl has an awesome channel about wellness:) She is very inspiring as well.
Tech Troublemaker: Being you is part of your authenticity.
Cheryl Wolf: Thank you
Mommy Guide Inc: everyone should have a mindset of inclusivity rather than exclusivity. love not hate.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: So true Roy. hard choices sometimes but I feel it is better to be authentic. we love you even more right?
Mommy Guide Inc: Claire absolutely agree - nobody should be in a "closet" so to speak right? so much better being out in the open.
Nina McCann: ❤️❤️ thanks for being kind and inclusive humans y’all. So very appreciated 😊😊🙌🙌
The Creator Classroom: I say my husband. it's part of my life. so for Claire to say my wife. it's Claire's life
Tech Troublemaker: Evil Bots! Yikes!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh really? not real? what a world! ah bots!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: bots and trolls - whatever - just continue creating.
Cheryl Wolf: 😍
Tim Heale 9: I don't have to worry about getting more views than anyone else 😂
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: :face-red-heart-shape:
Cheryl Wolf: So enjoyed Claire , Thank you for being you
Mommy Guide Inc: wow we're at the top of the hour! time indeed flew by so fast
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: This was great. the time did fly. Thanks Claire and Markus. so Claire has to come back!
Tech Troublemaker: Great show!
Eaglevp: Excellent interview
Mommy Guide Inc: thanks so much everyone! You are all awesome:)
itdair.network: Awesome stream @Markus Schaub and @Claire Sara thank you so much for your time! Everyone enjoy, the weekend!
Nina McCann: Such a wonderful conversation, thanks Markus and Claire and everyone! 💖💖