Mommy Guide Inc: Love love love the thumbnail Markus! And yes am back! Great to be back:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy!
Mariane Cresp: Hi Markus and Roy 👋🏼
Mommy Guide Inc: More confident indeed.:) Hi Mariane;)
Stuart Video -Tech Installations: Hey Guys!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Stuart:)
Stuart Video -Tech Installations: Hi @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: LEDA started it all for most of us indeed. Thanks LSP | Luria:)
Mommy Guide Inc: OVMG has been a great platform to actually practice. Thanks John Pullum:)
Mariane Cresp: It’s good to take a break
Sammy Super Star: Hey Everyone!
Mommy Guide Inc: Roy Victor has this dashcam that can record both the road and himself and the passenger with audio.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sammy.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: I love the series of Roy In The Car:
Eaglevp: Hi Markus and Roy
Eaglevp: Hello Lala
Eaglevp: Hello@Mariane Cresp
Eaglevp: Hey Sammy
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Keith! Miss you my friend.
Office Cooking: Hello Friends!
Eaglevp: Welcome @Office Cooking
Mommy Guide Inc: Spring is our January - love that! Let’s go!
Mariane Cresp: Now that you know that pattern, you can put a contingency plan in place now to put yourself in a burnt out position.
Mommy Guide Inc: OMG John! How are you? We miss you:)
Mariane Cresp: *not
Office Cooking: Doing great, Lala. How are you?
Motif Music Studios: Ahhh. Fun to catch you both on the SAME livestream!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello friends!!! so glad to catch you live!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: how do you keep the “wheels moving”?
Mariane Cresp: You ARE amazing Roy!
Eaglevp: Hello@Ana Zugheri - Faith52
Eaglevp: Hi@Motif Music Studios
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana! Loving your challenge
Mariane Cresp: I love my online community
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Amy@MotifMusic
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes! Marcus is my friend that I have never met and yet, I know I can count on him! So glad you are on my circle too Roy! Im so blessed.
Stannex: ::Comes in quietly and grabs a seat in the back::
Eaglevp: Hi Stan
Stannex: Hi, Keith!
Mommy Guide Inc: Love the community and friends I’ve met thru content creation. Victor has been super awesome helping me with all the tech in my recent event and you all - thank you so so much for the unending support
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Thank you @Lala, I sneaked picked during your craft retreat! Wow! amazing!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I need one of those!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Stan!
Motif Music Studios: @Eaglevp Hello! Great to be here!
Motif Music Studios: @Mommy Guide Inc ahhh. Thanks for the welcome!
Motif Music Studios: @Stannex hello from the front row. haha.
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: How did you find the balance Roy?
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes! the struggle is real, balance.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: or give you an ultimatum lol
Mommy Guide Inc: Accountability indeed so true. Donna and you make a really good team indeed.:) pls don’t forgot to check out Roy - https://youtube.com/@TechTroublemaker?si=qHvqov2N7-FzDUCd
Motif Music Studios: Oh that's neat. You'd be such a warm officiant!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: How awesome Roy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Also thank you all for being here but don’t forget to smash the LIKE button to support Markus.:)
Stuart Video -Tech Installations: Rev Roy!
Stannex: Hi, Lala! Congratulations on your recently completed Crafty Weekend!
Adam El Gringo: Good morning, everyone!
Adam El Gringo: Two of my favorite people.
Mommy Guide Inc: Congratulations Pastor Roy. Love it. And love your amazing ministry work like the one you recently did I. Costa Rica.:)
Stannex: Hi @Motif Music Studios ... bet you've got a good view up in the front row!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Coach Adam!
Adam El Gringo: I can't figure out how to switch my persona back to Adam Tinkoff (my alter ego)
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: El gringo there, la mexicana here lol
Eaglevp: Hello@Adam El Gringo
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Stan! I can now be back in your streams as well.:)
Motif Music Studios: @Stannex hahah. RIGHT? 😉 But you can cause all the trouble there in the back row!
Neil Farrimond: Hey Markus & Roy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Neil. Sorry to miss your live episode with Markus. Team replay.:)
Motif Music Studios: Ah, I am on team random too!
Neil Farrimond: @Mommy Guide Inc no worries 🙂
Motif Music Studios: Ironically [or not] I just got my OWN ADHD diagnosis this past month and my autistic sounds says that I am predictably unpredictable! ;)
Eaglevp: Evening again@Neil Farrimond
Neil Farrimond: Q&A is a good idea Roy.
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus and Roy am super proud of both of you! The encouragement you have for us all - amazing. That in itself has been such a great help to our community
Motif Music Studios: You guys are both such wonderful community builders. What a gift!
Neil Farrimond: Hello again indeed @Eaglevp 🙂
Motif Music Studios: Yes, the chat is such a fun way to connect with the community and I love that familiar faces become friends!
Mommy Guide Inc: Agree Amy! Being able to rally others to keep going is a gift! T thanks Markus and Roy! Thanks everyone.:)
Motif Music Studios: @Mariane Cresp love seeing you here too!
Stuart Video -Tech Installations: aww thanks
Coach Adam: Some topics attract more chatty viewers. Sometimes it depends on what you are talking about.
Motif Music Studios: "Trolls are ones we know" hahaha
Mommy Guide Inc: Maybe today our content May not be so relevant but who knows? In the future their situations may change and then we beck
Eaglevp: Hello@Coach Adam
Mommy Guide Inc: And then we become relevant.
Motif Music Studios: "my autistic son" [that should say]
Motif Music Studios: Yes Q&A tough without an audience. I too prepped some in advance and it was helpful!
Coach Adam: For example my new "running" content is attracting more comments mostly because runners tend to be more chatty and passionate about their activities.
Office Cooking: Marcus is awesome!!!
Office Cooking: I have to run, but it's been great seeing you two.
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yes- Markus has the awesome ability to be in all the places.:) kidding aside thank you Markus! Often times we feel so down and the support really makes a difference:)
Motif Music Studios: @Office Cooking see ya later!
Stuart Video -Tech Installations: Q: what you think off pineapple on pizza?
Coach Adam: See - John's a runner too! Right on!
Mommy Guide Inc: Th sis John! Congratulations also. I always have a great time watching your shorts @office cooking
Mommy Guide Inc: What? Sorry Joh I meant Thanks John not sis John. He he he
Eaglevp: I would to see more vlogs on Markus channel
Coach Adam: Make sure to give a plug to Ana's incredible 30 Day Challenge! There's still time to join her.
Motif Music Studios: Yes, it takes courage to just create for the sake of creating.
Eaglevp: I think you have a very relaxed style of vlogging Markus
Motif Music Studios: I saw a big creator remind the audience that it's "okay to create without trying to monetize everything' - it was a good reminder too.
Mommy Guide Inc: I agree Amy.:).
Eaglevp: I enjoy Roy's vlogs from the car
Coach Adam: Ana Zugheri's "30 Day Mindset Challenge" starts tomorrow!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Thank you for the shout out! You all are so amazing!!
Neil Farrimond: Be yourselves that's what we come and view you for!
Mommy Guide Inc: We love po dapple with pizza!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Pineapple on pizza is a must! for me lol
Mommy Guide Inc: So true Neil - encourages us to see that being “us” is ok. Not perfection at all.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: you saw it and ignored me lol
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Hello to my Two biggest influences.
Eaglevp: Hello@Fishstick ~ Phillip
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: So i took LEDA's format and I am starting tomorrow a challenge to change mindset to a more positive one so basic lol
Mommy Guide Inc: Philip! Hi @Fishstick!
Mary Speegle: Ana Can you post a link?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Mary! Yes Ana pls put the link pls.:)
Coach Adam: There's still time to join Ana's amazing challenge. JOIN US!
Mommy Guide Inc: Roy goes live weekly Tuesday nights for most of you. Best not to miss his lives and videos - subscribe and hit the notification bell:)
Mary Speegle: hi Marcus and Tech troublemaker!!
Eaglevp: Hi@Mary Speegle
Mommy Guide Inc: On that note pls don’t forget to subscribe and like Markus livestream right now friends.:)
Eaglevp: I love a meat feast pizza
Mommy Guide Inc: Meat feast pizza - sounds delicious Keith@eaglevp
Stannex: You've definitely influenced ME, Markus ... and in a TERRIFIC way!
Mary Speegle: I love the Tech Troublemaker's shooting stars in the background.
Mary Speegle: Hi Eaglevp!
Eaglevp: Q.Ana are you going live on your challenge
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: cookies will be provided by your computer lol
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: https://mailchi.mp/6b6c7.../faith52-30-day-mindset-challenge
Mary Speegle: Roy where did you get your background?
Coach Adam: Mom jokes are funnier. Thanks' Ana!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Thank you for letting me share the link here. It should be fun and I would love to see you there!
Mary Speegle: @Ana that link didn't work for me.
Eaglevp: Ana the link did not work
Mommy Guide Inc: Ana can you reshape the link? The link is broken.
Mommy Guide Inc: Love mo and dad jokes Adam.:) he he he
Mommy Guide Inc: Govee light curtains Mary.:)
Motif Music Studios: It's such a cool look!
Eaglevp: Good idea that Roy will have to try that myself.......lol
Mommy Guide Inc: Buy the gift we want - that’s clever indeed Roy.:)
Motif Music Studios: Ah, keep at it! It's loads of fun and it's takes a lot of courage to stay creative.
Mary Speegle: They are Groovy! I have a birthday in April. 😉
Motif Music Studios: Try not to let that discouragement tackle you! You've GOT this!
Mommy Guide Inc: Go Roy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Happy Birthday in advance Mary.:)
Mary Speegle: Go Marcus!
Eaglevp: Q. What's your goal Markus for the next 6 months?
Eaglevp: More video content Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes let’s help our fiends with their goals:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes we wait for you Markus!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Support one another!
Stannex: You always brighten my Thursdays!
Creative Amplifiers: Hello everyone
Eaglevp: Hi@Creative Amplifiers
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: hi
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Got to run now but I loved hanging out with you friends! Have a super awesome "extra" day. Happy leap day!
Creative Amplifiers: Sorry to be late. 😞
Eaglevp: Hey@Eric Maechler - Online Marketing
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Eric! Great to see you in the chat:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @creativeamplifiers:)
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: hi @Mommy Guide Inc nice to see you again 🙂
Motif Music Studios: YES! Watch hours are a whole challenge in itself!
Creative Amplifiers: Yes will do 👍🏻
Motif Music Studios: Yay Lala and crew of supporters!!!
Motif Music Studios: woohoo
Mary Speegle: Marcus Do you know how many hours you have?
Stannex: Great show, gents ... even from here in the back row!
Mommy Guide Inc: Mark the date and time friends - better yet hit that notification bell for Markus so we won’t miss his lives and videos:)
Eaglevp: Thanks Markus and Roy for a good and interesting stream
Mommy Guide Inc: Agree Stan. See you later Stan - he goes live later as well.:)