Tech Troublemaker: I see/saw earlier. Does that mean you got to sleep until 4am Lala? 🙂
Ellie Calhoun: Here! Yay! But I'm multitasking
Eaglevp: Evening Markus
Stannex: Hey ... I'm not late today! Hello, everyone!
Eaglevp: Hi Stan
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Keith! Hey Stan! Hey Lala! Hey Pierre!
Stannex: I love this theme song sooooooo much!
Eaglevp: Loving your car vlogs Roy
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Markus. 😀
Eaglevp: Enjoyed your interview the other day as well Roy
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hello and goodevening everybody😀👍
Eaglevp: Hi Ejnar
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Heith😀
Neil Farrimond: Thought I’d join here instead!
Neil Farrimond: Hi everyone
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Keith😀
Eaglevp: Hi Neil enjoyed your stream today
Neil Farrimond: Thanks Keith!
Pierre Kelly: hey neil
Pierre Kelly: didn't know you had a video earlier
Andrea Nunn: hi Markus. what time is it where you are?
Eaglevp: You and Brian make a great team Neil
Eaglevp: Hi Andrea Nunn
Stannex: Videa NOW!
Andrea Nunn: ooh. late. its 430pm here
Pierre Kelly: Andrea he started it on 3:30 central
Eaglevp: It’s nice we are seeing a bit of Lucerne Markus
Neil Farrimond: I love the longer nights.
Neil Farrimond: Really enjoying your challenge Markus!
Andrea Nunn: yes the bus video was fun
Eaglevp: Weekends in May Markus
Eaglevp: That sounds like a good idea Markus
joana.kunz: are you live often?
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: I Really wanted to make lives outside when I was on vacation in Brazil, but it is to dangerous. It you take your mobile up from your pocket, you risk it is gone. It’s a shame. 😞
Tech Troublemaker: For your channel to grow, you just have to water it.
Eaglevp: Now that was a shame Ejnar
Tech Troublemaker: I think my morning thoughts videos may start leaving the car some.
Neil Farrimond: Doing what I can 👌
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Yes, Keith. 👍
Eaglevp: Roy I would love to hear about your faith journey
Stannex: I've been thinking about adding in short morning videos, too ... just haven't figured out what I want the focus of them to be.
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: I am working on video courses about how to use Ecamm. I want to make them in Danish, so I can show people here what it can do👍
Tech Troublemaker: Wow, that would be awesome @CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream
Eaglevp: Shaving in a good niche to be in Markus
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Yes, Roy. People need to know it. 😀
Sammy Super Star: Hey Markus !!!
Eaglevp: Hi Sammy
Sammy Super Star: Thank you so much the other day for telling me about the hacked channel
Sammy Super Star: Did you get a nice hair cut? You look good
Neil Farrimond: @CSLiveDK great idea!
Tech Troublemaker: Yes @Eaglevp it is something I don't talk about much online. I don't hide it but I don't advertise it. Maybe it is time for a video just about that.
Sammy Super Star: I have restart
Andrea Nunn: my exercise updates 'vlogs' are viewed more than my curated weekly 'advise' videos. going to do an update today. lets test the theory
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Thank you Neil. 👍
Eaglevp: Q.Markus why do you wear headphones when you are live on your own?
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hey Sammy. Hope the keep up doing your good work😀👍
Sammy Super Star: It’s very sad I lost 3K subscribers then YouTube isn’t helping
Eaglevp: I am think about talking about my faith journey
Eaglevp: Sammy that’s why you need a mailing list of all your subscribers
Neil Farrimond: Hi Sammy. Can you post your new channel name here?
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: What is the name on the channel @Sammy?
Sammy Super Star: It’s @cinematicsammy
Sammy Super Star: Most of my viewers came from YouTube shorts after the first 700ish
Sammy Super Star: Harder to reach them
Tech Troublemaker: do you have a backup of any of your shorts @Sammy Super Star ? Release them again.
Markus Schaub: https://www.youtube.com/@CinematicSammy
Sammy Super Star: I might have like 15 or 30 of them saved on the phone
Tech Troublemaker: Maybe it is time to pivot and go bigger with all your camera skills @Sammy Super Star
The Honest Accomplice: Hey Markus
Eaglevp: Like the new banner Sammy
Tech Troublemaker: It's Dan! Hey Dan!!!!!
Sammy Super Star: I’m doing focus on the short films
Eaglevp: Hey The Honest Accomplice
The Honest Accomplice: Hey Roy. Sorry for the silence. Rough patch right now
Tech Troublemaker: I am so sorry sir. I hope better days are heading your way. @The Honest Accomplice
Sammy Super Star: A lot of people came from the shorts about the live streaming content
The Honest Accomplice: Second or third
The Honest Accomplice: It’s amazing what Sammy has accomplished before he is even allowed in a bar.
Sammy Super Star: Yeah I made a TV show before the age of 18
Sammy Super Star: Don’t even like alcohol lol 😆
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Just watching todays video form you and saw on your thumbnail that you are LIVE!
Eaglevp: Evening Katy
Neil Farrimond: Hi Katy!
The Honest Accomplice: Sammy you grew up in a Jewish family. Wine is the only way to get through get togethers
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Hi Keith, hi all. I’m at the seaside. I’m hoping it doesn’t rain the whole time we’re here!
The Honest Accomplice: The famous Farrimond
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Thank you ☀️☀️☀️☀️
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Hi Neil 👋
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: I love the lighter evenings too. Good for video creation!
The Honest Accomplice: Have a wonderful night Markus
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Take care friends 🤗
Stannex: Great seeing you, Markus! And everyone else, too!
Eaglevp: Hope you all have a nice weekend
Sammy Super Star: Always great stream Markus