elle naturally: hi! time to get moving again, perfect season to start a new walking routine too.
elle naturally: I'm doing more steps each day/week. love the challenge.
Mommy Guide Inc: Good morning!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi elllie!
elle naturally: hiiii
elle naturally: hi @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: I was here an hour ago
Mommy Guide Inc: Still winter right?
elle naturally: would you wish that daylight saving time was the constant time all year or the regular time be the constant?
elle naturally: same same, I prefer the later light rather than early
Awesome Fun Things: Are you stuck?!?!
elle naturally: @Awesome Fun Things is a nice name
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Matt!
Awesome Fun Things: I'll get you unstuck, Markus! I got you, my friend!
Awesome Fun Things: Hi @elle naturally (you have a cool channel name)... just sayin
elle naturally: thanks but it's not awesome like your's!
Awesome Fun Things: Q: Will buying expensive Video/Audio gear get you unstuck? Hmmm
elle naturally: Markus I really like the blue lighting in your space
Awesome Fun Things: I like having FUN... "Fun" is in my channel name. Haha
Mommy Guide Inc: Didn’t go live last Sat and this Wed. My aunt is here another Au t so I’ve been touring her around
Awesome Fun Things: TEAM BLUE!!!!!!!!!!!!
Awesome Fun Things: 🦄 (If you know, you know) haha
Awesome Fun Things: I just walked my two puppies in the snow. The neighbors were worried about the puppies. They're snow dogs.
Awesome Fun Things: They LOVE the snow
elle naturally: lol
Awesome Fun Things: YES!!!!!
Awesome Fun Things: Great shield!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Beautiful crafted piece:)
Awesome Fun Things: Are you going to do any interview content?
elle naturally: I have a Norwegian Forest Cat and she won't even touch the snow! It's weird.
Mariane Cresp: Hello 👋🏼 Markus
Awesome Fun Things: I like being interviewed. The offer is open to any YouTuber. I can talk, and talk.
Awesome Fun Things: Hi LALA!!!!
elle naturally: Hi @Mariane Cresp
Awesome Fun Things: Every time I use my CriCut, I think of you Lala.
Mariane Cresp: Hi 👋🏼 El
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Marianne and am so glad ur team Ecamm now:)
Mariane Cresp: Yes, Ecamm has been great!
Awesome Fun Things: Hi Mariane. Were you on "the stream show" recently?
elle naturally: yes please get Mariane to your camp, it's in Massachusetts and I could finally meet her in person.
Mariane Cresp: Yes, I was on DJ Strick’s show a few weeks back
Awesome Fun Things: I think I was on the show with you. I'm moving so fast things are a blur. Haha
Awesome Fun Things: It's good to see you again, Mariane.
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes I’ll be back in Creator Camp this year.:)
Awesome Fun Things: I have some things to talk about regarding my health journey. I had a few bumps in the road recently.
Mommy Guide Inc: Pls don’t forget to hit the LIKE button my friends.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Missed you all too! Watching virtually is fun but nothing beats being there in IRL
Awesome Fun Things: Now that Lala is going to CC in 2025, how can I stay away?!?! I'll be there!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: December was very busy. Now with family obligations I think I’ll go back to regular programming in Feb.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Matt - we finally will meet IRL:)
Awesome Fun Things: I got to spend a lot of time with Ken/Glenn. We took a 40 minute walk with a very small group... like 6 people.
Mommy Guide Inc: You got this Markus!
Awesome Fun Things: Woot, woot! @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus what does the group of Marilou do? I am not sure if I am there already
Markus Schaub: https://videocreator.club
Mommy Guide Inc: I want to restart my podcast this year.
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: hoi markus - hello friends
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Eric! Thanks for the link Markus.
Awesome Fun Things: Hi Eric
Awesome Fun Things: I need to make a few more YouTube channels. Haha. I'm kidding. I'm kidding. Haha
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: what is a few? 10-50? @Awesome Fun Things
Awesome Fun Things: I lost count
Awesome Fun Things: Ha! One is too many. I have 3 active channels. 2 mostly inactive.
Awesome Fun Things: So... 5-ish
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: uff - you are weired :P
Awesome Fun Things: I don't recommend multiple channels. Seriously, I don't. It's not for most people. Just being real.
Awesome Fun Things: I don't dispute that. Haha @Eric Maechler - Online Marketing
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: many people say i should split my youtube channel into several and focus on one topic / channel. but it's no fun
Awesome Fun Things: I should start a YouTube channel about how to run multiple YouTube channels.
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: weird is good @Awesome Fun Things the other is booring
Awesome Fun Things: Wait... no I shouldn't. Haha
Awesome Fun Things: 200%
Mommy Guide Inc: Same here Eric!
Awesome Fun Things: I should start a YouTube channel to see how many Follows I can get without posting a single video.
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: if you are cute - then that is not a problem - i am not - for that it will probably zero sub @Awesome Fun Things
Awesome Fun Things: Someone got a Silver play button with zero videos. True story.
Awesome Fun Things: YouTube make a rule after that.
Awesome Fun Things: Yes... Jack Sucks at Life did that.
Awesome Fun Things: That guy is ridiculous.
Awesome Fun Things: Totally bonkers.
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: hahaha
Awesome Fun Things: The forced him to upload one video... so, he made toast. It got 500k views.
Awesome Fun Things: toast 🍞
elle naturally: nice seeing everyone
Mommy Guide Inc: Thank you for going live today Markus! Thanks friends for coming by
Awesome Fun Things: Thanks Markus! Stay awesome, my friend!!! xo
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: i dont need a button from youtube - i would be content with 10k subs:P
Awesome Fun Things: DROP A LIKE
Mommy Guide Inc: Pls don’t forget to hit the LIKE button on your way out.:)
Awesome Fun Things: 👍