Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
Ellie Calhoun: 👋 hello! My favorite YouTuber!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: And here we go! Hi Sammy and Ellie!
Mommy Guide Inc: Don’t forget to smash the 👍 button friends:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Let’s Go!
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Markus and all the fine people here😀👍
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ejnar!
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Lala😀 Como Estes😀
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: I am in the middle of the sea on our way to Livorno, Pisa
Mommy Guide Inc: But great to be with you all for this awesome update. I didn’t know about this - I’ve been so out of the loop for 2 weeks now. Thanks for this update
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: who can do vertical livestreams? All?
Sammy Super Star: Q: When is this coming out?
Sammy Super Star: You know who would know about it Rene
Mommy Guide Inc: I can already go live on tiktok but haven’t tried it. I’ll try it when I get back . But I can’t add it to my multi stream on ecamm
Sammy Super Star: I think you might be able to do this with ecamm, you can live stream vertically in ecamm to other platforms so if YouTube allows you to do that it might be cool
Mommy Guide Inc: I tried adding tiktok on top of YT and Fb it won’t let me Sammy.
Sammy Super Star: Maybe because you have to switch settings
Mommy Guide Inc: So true Sammy. I might not have the right settings.
Mommy Guide Inc: But what are your thoughts Markus on this new format?
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow these are awesome updates on the YT shorts - very “TikTok” feels. He he he.
Mommy Guide Inc: That’s great Markus - looking forward to your updates. I’ll try Markus. Let’s test this out.
Ileane Smith: Hey!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Hi Ileane!
Adam Tinkoff: Hey Markus. Vertical format is slimming. I take what I can get.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Coach Adam!
Ileane Smith: Yay!
Ileane Smith: I have done vertical live streams before
Adam Tinkoff: It all depends on what your audience wants.
Mommy Guide Inc: Ileane how did it go? Do you like it?
Ileane Smith: I've gone live on YouTube, Facebook and Amazon in vertical format -- also Instagram and Tumblr
Adam Tinkoff: I'm not counting on the Shorts audience to turn into deeper relationships. I'm not discounting them either but use on other ways to grow
Budgeting Momma: Hi everyone
Ileane Smith: @Mommy Guide Inc it was ok - I don't like it but I did it for my audience and because the platforms were pushing it.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @BudgetingMomma! What an executing channel name.:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi everyone. Yep I’m late ⏰
Ileane Smith: I forgot to say Twitch 😂
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Lala you have a signal at sea? Cool
Adam Tinkoff: While there will always be a desktop (horizontal) format available, I think the majority of viewers are on mobile devices.
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Ileane for sharing your thoughts.
Mommy Guide Inc: Janet!!! Yes I go the Wi-Fi plus package so I can go live and be here with you all:)
Ileane Smith: The good thing is we can look at the stats in YouTube studio to see what format our audience likes to watch
Budgeting Momma: Hi @mommy guide inc
Mommy Guide Inc: I meant I “got” not go. Fat fingers problem. He he he.
Adam Tinkoff: For me Vertical feels more intimate - horizontal more like TV.
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh a great thought Adam.
Budgeting Momma: I haven’t done a live in years. Not ready to do that again.
Mommy Guide Inc: I hope we can just use one set up and the platforms will push it to both so less tech for us
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Coming in a little late! Hello everybody 😊
Ellie Calhoun: Thanks for sharing this Markus. I'm not sure what any of this will mean for me. Lol
Adam Tinkoff: Vertical feel like I'm peeking through a door slot, not that I do that. Creepy.
Ileane Smith: @Adam Tinkoff that's interesting!
Budgeting Momma: Slow internet
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ellie and Ana:)
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Lala!
Adam Tinkoff: I predict that Vertical lives will look far more informal, fewer overlays, widgets, etc.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Less work
Adam Tinkoff: I also feel that vertical format is less archive friendly. Harder to tell someone to go back and look, etc.
Mommy Guide Inc: I like the chat overlay.
Adam Tinkoff: Face it. We all need to be a whole lot cuter to become super stars. LOL!!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I see a guy doing his videos in the car vertical and it has 5k followers
Mommy Guide Inc: Please don’t forget to smash the LIKE button friends:)
Budgeting Momma: So it will look like Instagram live.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Lol cute!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Can’t get cutter in my case 😂
Mommy Guide Inc: Adam 😂
Adam Tinkoff: Do you think we will ever have Vertical TVs in our homes or will it just be for handheld devices?
Budgeting Momma: Good point Adam. Hope not.
Adam Tinkoff: For me it feels like it's replacing what we lost with Periscope which was very popular.
Adam Tinkoff: I agree about the quality of TikTok, but I've learned some very fancy dance moves.
Fishstick USA: Hello. I watch again on the replay. Want you to know you are supported by folks like me.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yep! I agree the quality in tik tok is lower…
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Philip! I also learned several dance steps from TikTok Adam. He he he.
Stannex: I arrived late and have been listening for awhile. Just didn't have anything worthwhile to add. ;^)
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Lol we want to see your dance moves!!!
Budgeting Momma: Hi stannex
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Stan! Missing your shows sorry but will be back hopefully next wrek
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes! Among friends ♥️
Adam Tinkoff: ❤️❤️❤️❤️❤️