Mariane Cresp: Hello Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: And here we go!
Mariane Cresp: Hello Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Mariane Cresp!
Mommy Guide Inc: And that finger flick - Let’s go!
Kali : hi!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Hi Kali!
Kali : @Mommy Guide Inc hey lala!! ❤
Kali : hi mariane!!!
Kali : #MARKUSRULES
Mariane Cresp: Hi Kali!
Kali : 💃 💃 💃 💃
Kali : yay!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hello Markus!
Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
Kali : @Sammy Super Star hey!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey! Sammy!!!
Kali : so happy to be here FINALLY!!
Kali : i am usually busy at this time but when the cat is away the mice will play hehehe
Kali : (not that luria is a cat - she's the nicest cat ever)
Sammy Super Star: It’s great to see everyone
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Markus😀👍
Kali : Hi ejnar!!
Mommy Guide Inc: So true Kali. So great to see you here again.:)
Kali : @Mommy Guide Inc ❤ ❤
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ejnar @CSLiveDK
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hi 👋👋
Kali : hi Ana!!
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Lala. 😀
Kali : ooo i love this idea - what would you like reviewers to say about you
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Ana😀
Mommy Guide Inc: If you find this topic interesting please dont forget to smash that Like button.:) Thanks again for being here everyone.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Markus brings community together!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Markus is an encouragement!!!
Kali : Markus is always engaging and inspiring. He cares about the success of others, and his passion for community shines like no other. He makes everyone feel welcome and special
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: We’ll said Kali!!! 🎉🎉🎉
Mommy Guide Inc: Hmmm let’s make a revjew… Markus Schaub’s last show with Mariane Cresp really created an awesome impact on me because i absolutely resonated with the struggles they shared and wins as well.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Markus doesn’t need fake reviews… for real!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana @Fairh 52!
Kali : A fake review of myself? oh gosh that's hard
Mommy Guide Inc: Ana @Faith52 brings so much inspiration to everyday life with a little bit of extra of course!
Mariane Cresp: I can't believe we are all here to celebrate our 100K milestone!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: We should go to each other’s channel to leave reviews
Kali : @Mariane Cresp LOVE!!!
Kali : wait, are reviews a thing on youtube???
Kali : have i been living under a rock???
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: You are so sweet
Mommy Guide Inc: I am writing non-fake news! He he he
Kali : ohhh okay hahaha
Kali : i was gonna say - that could potentially be a dumpster fire LOL
Mommy Guide Inc: Here’s one for me - Mommy Lala finally niches down!!!
Mariane Cresp: Great, right? If we visualise it... the gap between now and the dream get closer
Kali : LOL lala
Kali : Kali future review: has cool animations that make people feel like they're stepping into a cute, fun world
Kali : ideally there would be more to it but that's all i got for now 😂
Kali : ❤
Mommy Guide Inc: Kidding aside I agree Mariane. Visualization can be a really powerful tool in helping us reach our goals. Yey nice one Kali!
Mommy Guide Inc: Here’s one for Sammy - Sammy create’s his first block buster movie!
Tim Heale 9: Hi Markus, evening all
Kali : Hi tim! great to see you :)
Kali : @Mommy Guide Inc omg yes!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Tim!!!
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Being a guest on Lalas show was a great experience she is doing great. 😀
Tim Heale 9: I don't get enough viewers to have fake comments
Mommy Guide Inc: Aww thanks Ejnar.:) Yes let’s do this.
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Markus i know i need to niche down to grow but I am just enjoying this journey thus far. So let’s flip the coin Markus and we ask you?:)
Tim Heale 9: It's tough when a guest doesn't turn up and you are scheduled to live
Tim Heale 9: When you stop enjoying it stop doing it
Tech Troublemaker: Hey everyone! What is your focus? What can you talk about for hours without prompting?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy!
Kali : Hey @Tech Troublemaker !!
Tim Heale 9: I have and one has to adlib to get through it
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Kali!
Mommy Guide Inc: Your almost didn’t have a guest during your first show!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: It’s mutual
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes the 27
Mommy Guide Inc: He he he. But that was still so much fun!
Tim Heale 9: I can rant for hours but I would be taken down
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I can’t wait is going to be so much fun 🤩
Tech Troublemaker: @Mommy Guide Inc is so awesome!
Tech Troublemaker: 😸I can talk about YouTube for hours and it makes my wife a little crazy.
Tim Heale 9: You are welcome to come on my show
Mommy Guide Inc: OMG!!! Set notify everyone for Ana and Markus on @Fairh 52!
Kali : @Tech Troublemaker LOL
Mommy Guide Inc: For me -its crafting and my journey with the Lord! Energizer bunny cant stop me. LOL
Tech Troublemaker: Especially live. The audio from four live streams is hard to understand at once.
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL oh yes absolutely when several shows go on all at the same time! And i mix up the comments on the show. LOL
Tech Troublemaker: 8pm I meant.
Kali : 😂 😂 😂 😂
Motif Music Studios: Hello all! Always nice to be here!
Kali : @Motif Music Studios hey!
Motif Music Studios: @Tech Troublemaker is in the house too! Fun!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Hi @Motif Music Studios
Motif Music Studios: Heyyy! YES, Amie is correct! Nice work!
Tech Troublemaker: I could run now.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Amie! Finally i got to know your name.:)
Motif Music Studios: Reviews! That's a great topic! Are you directing reviews a certain direction?
Tim Heale 9: Fake review 'Tim was left speechless from his guests story' 😂
Motif Music Studios: Oh that's so neat!
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL Tim! 😂
Tech Troublemaker: Markus inspires me. He is so amazing and I have met such amazing folks thanks to his guests.
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks in advance for smashing the LIKE 👍:)
Motif Music Studios: I think I love hearing, "you gave me the courage to be more creative in my music teaching and my work alongside my music students."
Tech Troublemaker: @Motif Music Studios my wife is a big fan of Ed Sheeran so I forwarded her video.
Tech Troublemaker: Markus, that isn't a fake review. It is true.
Motif Music Studios: or "Thank you for inspiring me by introducing me to new contemporary composers and their music."
Motif Music Studios: What a great clarifier - amazing!
Motif Music Studios: @Tech Troublemaker oh that's awesome she's an Ed Sheeran fan! I had fun creating that.
Mommy Guide Inc: Fake news for now - reality soon! Great idea Markus
Motif Music Studios: Fake news for now. Hahaha Love it.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: What I have found it’s a lot easier to create content when you have a product to sell…rather than idea 💡
Kali : i can't wait!!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Even reviews…that is easier to write ✍️
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus - I am
Mommy Guide Inc: Coming to Examm Camp!!!
Kali : OMG LALA!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Got my visa renewed last week! Excited so much to see most of you fibally face to face!
Kali : wow that's crazy that you had to do that D:
Kali : you cannot just fly to the us with your passport??
Kali : wow that's insane. just to visit????
Kali : WHAT
Kali : i had no idea
Kali : i cannot believe you need a visa just to travel to the us @lala
Tim Heale 9: $27 they saw you coming 😂
Kali : wow
Kali : your first time int he US&gt;!&gt;!&gt; I CAN'T WAIT AHHH!!!!
Kali : omg i cannot wait to be there for your first US experience
Kali : boston is the epitome of the US haha
Tim Heale 9: Nobody walk in the USA
Tech Troublemaker: Creator Camp in October. I will be there.
Kali : everyone walks in new york, but also the metro
Kali : @Tech Troublemaker woohoo!!! see you there!!
Kali : boston has walkable things yeah it's a big city!
Tim Heale 9: Boston has a tea party
Tech Troublemaker: And Lala and Markus and you. Incredible
Motif Music Studios: Oh that's neat that you have some travel plans!
Mommy Guide Inc: But hope to meet you still in. Barcelona last week of July Markus only of you can
Kali : oh yeah tips are expected for sure
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: @Tech Troublemaker always pushes me to research and try things. Discover how to work smarter not harder.
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yes i should have kept it a secret! He he he
Motif Music Studios: Totally helpful exercise and really loved that flipped way of thinking of what you'd love your audience to be impacted by!
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Tips are not needed here. It’s included in the price. I give it to people who really makes a difference. In restaurants for example 😀👍
Mommy Guide Inc: I agree Amie.:) a great exercise indeed. Let’s ponder on this some more:)
Motif Music Studios: That was my biggest surprise about becoming a content creator - an international community of encouragers and friendships built!
Motif Music Studios: @Mommy Guide Inc totally love it!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: @kali she has such a sweet spirit! She represents a sense of freedom and I love she loves plants 🪴
Motif Music Studios: SO wise and appreciated!
Kali : @Ana Zugheri - Faith52 awwwe 😭 ❤️ thank you so much
Tech Troublemaker: I hope I am as amazing in person as I tell people I am.
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: I follow an American family on YouTube moved to Denmark. It really shows the differences. 👍
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes!!! Meeting so many wonderful people in this broken world gives me hope! ❤️
Mommy Guide Inc: One for Kali - The best community tech hero launches her first art collection exhibit!
Motif Music Studios: 💕
Tim Heale 9: I have a tip, 'Move fast stay low and watch where you put your feet' 😂
Mommy Guide Inc: Great tip Tim!
Kali : @Mommy Guide Inc bawwwe ❤ ❤ thank you!!!
Kali : @Tech Troublemaker 😂 bahahahaha
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I’m so jealous!!!
Kali : oooo! yes!! i will work on this 😊