Eaglevp: Hi Markus and Lala
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello 👋
Eaglevp: Evening Ana
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Keith! Ana!
Mommy Guide Inc: All Mods present!
Eaglevp: Yep Lala
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: @Eaglevp glad you are here!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: @lala love your nails! My favorite color!
Fishstick USA: C: ASMR is the calmness you get from watching Bob Ross painting programs in the US.
Fishstick USA: Boss Ross whispered and painted
Paul Burke: Markus...are you thinking about doing ASMR?
Eaglevp: Hi Paul
Paul Burke: hey @Eaglevp
Ellie Calhoun: Hey Markus and LaLa!
Eaglevp: Hello Ellie
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hey Ellie! Glad to see you here! ♥️ you are doing great on your videos!
Ellie Calhoun: 👋
Fishstick USA: Q: Do you eat all of the candy in your shorts?
Paul Burke: 🙂
Ellie Calhoun: Lol @Fishstick that's what I'm wondering
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Q how do you choose what products you will do?
Paul Burke: some ideas Markus.... the crunch of swiss snow...the yodel in the mountains...the sound of melting chocolate...and sound of a clock working
Fishstick USA: Hahaha 😂
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: My daughter said I should do a asmr about my snoring 😴😊😄
Ellie Calhoun: Have you said what asmr actually is or do I need to replay since I got here late...
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: She did
Ellie Calhoun: Can you do it with opening up your craft supplies? Think popsicle sticks etc
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Q Lala can you repeat what amsr stand for?
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Q do you have to have a 🎤 or does the phone work?
Ellie Calhoun: Good question Ana, I'm wondering that too
Cheryl Wolf: Hey lala Markus and all sorry I’m late
Ellie Calhoun: I like the sounds but saying "don't forget to subscribe" over and over again is annoying
Eaglevp: Hello Cheryl
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Keith
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Cheryl!!!! Welcome 🤗
Cheryl Wolf: The other Cheryl ❤️
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Ana
Coffee Talk & Tech: phone isnt great. Stereo gives you the best ASMR. A affordable why is a blue yeti mic.
Eaglevp: Hi Coffee Talk & Tech
Coffee Talk & Tech: hi guys
Ellie Calhoun: Q: Do you spread out when you publish the shorts through out the day?
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Q has those help you drive people to your channel?
Tech Troublemaker: Hey everyone!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hi 👋
Coffee Talk & Tech: Lala what's the most subscribers you have gotten from a short?
Eaglevp: Hi Roy
Ellie Calhoun: Flipping bread! 😂
Tech Troublemaker: I did a reverse unboxing. I thought it was hilarious but no one else seemed to. Very few views.
Tech Troublemaker: I watch your ASMR shorts but they aren't about crafting so that seems confusing.
Andrea Nunn: Good to know re posting times of multiples
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Eaglevp
Eaglevp: Hello Andrea Nunn
Andrea Nunn: Hello!
Ellie Calhoun: Your Asmr shorts are beautifully colorful!
Cheryl Wolf: What about breathing as an ASMR??
Tech Troublemaker: Because of the AI, I don't think YouTube cares any more. It can find your video if it wants to find it.
Tech Troublemaker: Breathing is important because gasping for air would be a terrible ASMR
Cheryl Wolf: Lol Roy
Fishstick USA: Tech Troublemaker — 😆
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: It’s raining 🌧️ here right now, I should be out there recoding my first asmr 😂
Coffee Talk & Tech: I started a ASMR channel last year. It can be fun. It really helps many people.
Cheryl Wolf: Oh yes Ana
Ellie Calhoun: It's very interesting...
SuzanCz: Helloooooo!!!
SuzanCz: What platform are you doing this editing in?
Ellie Calhoun: This is awesome! Thanks Lala!
SuzanCz: Great nails, Lala!
Tim Heale 9: Hi Guys
SuzanCz: Thanks, @Markus Schaub!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: So cool!
Tech Troublemaker: I use the Captions app. It is my favorite.
Tech Troublemaker: And I found out you can have it do captions for horizontal videos too.
Tech Troublemaker: You can edit the captions it produces, yes.