Mommy Guide Inc: oooh it's so nice to see this again:)
Mommy Guide Inc: what a lovely journey thus far Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Congratulations Markus! You have keps at it - exercise thru walking and soon you'll be jogging:)
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Go Markus
Mariane Cresp: Hello Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: we do live on earth which is on a retrograde motion so sometimes our life. LOL.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Marian!
Mariane Cresp: Hi Lala!
Mommy Guide Inc: I was going thru my planners and saw that it was in September that had you as a guest:)
Fishstick ~ Phillip: *how people
Mariane Cresp: Markus, are you joining in today’s lesson? Not sure what time it’ll be there in 4 hours’ time
Mariane Cresp: 🥰
Mariane Cresp: Yes, watch today’s replay as it works through those thoughts 💭
Mommy Guide Inc: That's very inspiring Markus. It's never too late to start.
Mariane Cresp: Sleep and recharge!
Mommy Guide Inc: Cheering you on Markus! 8 hours sleep - next up!
Images by Gretchen: Hi Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Gretchen! Congratulations on editing and putting up 2 edited videos on your Art Shed creation.
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for being here friends. Please don't forget to smash the LIKE button:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Thank YOU Markus! You've been an integral part of a lot of our' journey here in Youtube and other platforms.
Mommy Guide Inc: Keep going. Sometimes we get stuck or we just need to rest and it's ok to rest awhile but pick it up again after and continue going on.
Mommy Guide Inc: You are looking absolutely glowing Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Great to hear you doing this also with your loved ones.''
Mommy Guide Inc: Having fun doing the right thing is also very important.
Mommy Guide Inc: Thank you so much to our awesome friends! How can we support you further Markus?
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Markus walking is now an integral part of our life. Now to work on fixing or altering the eating habits:)
Enda Trading: 😎
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Enda - good morning!