Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello!!! :hand-pink-waving::hand-pink-waving::hand-pink-waving::hand-pink-waving::hand-pink-waving:
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi friends! Good morning!
BostonDonMTB: Hi Markus and Ana
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi ;Don!
BostonDonMTB: Hi Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi hi Matkus!
Ellie Calhoun: Hello!👋
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hi friends, so glad to see you here.
Mommy Guide Inc: Sent video already:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus music very louder than ur voice:)
Ellie Calhoun: I can't hear you over the music
BostonDonMTB: Tough to hear you with the song playing still.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Rllie:)
BostonDonMTB: New song
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: oh! I thought it was just me....lol
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: nice song though!
BostonDonMTB: You are good.
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed very nice song indeed
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: oh no!!!! I am so sorry.
Ellie Calhoun: 💕😢😢😢😢💕
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh my.:( sad to hear this.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I don't think I have his name on my FB if you can share I would love to send him a note.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Tough times, for sure.
Mommy Guide Inc: Sorry need to put whose link Markus?
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: @Mommy Guide Inc if you have how Keith's name on FB to reach out you can DM me if you have it.
Mommy Guide Inc: Keiyh Grimmer
Mommy Guide Inc: Keith Grimmer
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Found him, thank you.
Mommy Guide Inc: Welcome sis Ana.
Pierre Kelly: afternoon all
BostonDonMTB: I have a thunderstorm coming through now.
Mommy Guide Inc: seeing you find your rhythm is awesome. See the difference already.
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh my stay safe Don. Probably no biking out today
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Pierre.:)
BostonDonMTB: I was going to try to beat the rain, but I didn't make it.
Pierre Kelly: for me, it's hot outside
Ellie Calhoun: Pouring thunderstorm right now!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: My daughter started school yesterday so my walking schedule needs to be modified too.
BostonDonMTB: I think it is helpful to have my smart trainer, because I have no excuse. Tonight I could pull the bike out of the SUV, and ride tonight on the trainer.
BostonDonMTB: Ellie and I are close in distance to each other so we are sharing the rain storm. 😄
Mommy Guide Inc: Stay safe Ellie and Don.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I love walking in the cold rather than the heat. I also started to be challenged by the rain...as long as is not lighting.
Mommy Guide Inc: Friends how’s your own walking | health journey?
Mommy Guide Inc: Please don’t forget to hit the LIKE button friends:)
BostonDonMTB: I like walking in the rain, but biking on the trails in the rain can be treacherous with the wet roots and rocks.
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes we’ve been alternating Mall and campus walking with my son and daughter:)
BostonDonMTB: I measure my risks.
Mommy Guide Inc: Ive been having a bit of gout Attacks so its kinda harder to walk but still pushing at it
BostonDonMTB: @Mommy Guide Inc Way to go Lala
Ellie Calhoun: I have a mini trampoline I'm "walking" on
Mommy Guide Inc: Thats great to know Don that you put safety first too.:) awesome:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I have been going up and down the stairs and around the kitchen island to meet my steps the days I am busy to go out lol
Coach Adam Runs: Hey there kids!
Coach Adam Runs: I want 15 pushups! EVERYONE
Ellie Calhoun: @ana I do that too!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Coach Adam. Congratulations on getting your official license
Mommy Guide Inc: Coach Adam i cant do push ups! He he he
BostonDonMTB: @Ana Zugheri - Faith52 That is smart. I don't think people realize you can walk in your home especially up and down the stairs.
Mommy Guide Inc: Still very weak core.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: uhhh! @Ellie Calhoun I was reading about the trampoline studies...it makes you happier person while excercising. Considering to get one.
Ellie Calhoun: I love thunderstorms ⛈️ but Im staying in.
Coach Adam Runs: Schedule them in your calendar just like any high priority event. Think of them like catching a flight. Just as important.
BostonDonMTB: I just saw a guy running by my house in the rain. He is dedicated.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Right! @BostonDonMTB I learned that raising your heart beat for 10 minutes right after you eat, it helps you decrease your glucose spikes and the stairs surely does the trick lol
BostonDonMTB: @Ana Zugheri - Faith52 Good info on the glucose.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes! @Coach Adam Runs rocks!!! He is a true inspiration!
Coach Adam Runs: I love running in the rain, but don't like puddles.
Ellie Calhoun: Yes! Definitely a good idea for your music video!!
Coach Adam Runs: Ana - check out the "rebounder". It's a very good mini trampoline if you can do it.
Coach Adam Runs: TMI - I know... but some folks have bladder issues with all the jumping.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: uuuh, I just did @Coach Adam Runs and its on sale right now.
Down To Earth With Katy : Hi! I’ve just finished my livestream
Down To Earth With Katy : You’re looking so healthy Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: I have spine issues and herniated colon so not allowed to have too strenuous activity.:(
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Katy!
Down To Earth With Katy : Hi Lala xx
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Got to go friends, but so nice to chatting with ya'lll have a wonderful rest of your day! Thank you Markus for the fun space to be a community!
Images by Gretchen: If you live where I do running in the rain is something you have to accept
Mommy Guide Inc: Have a grrat weekend Ana!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Gretchen!
Down To Earth With Katy : It’s a new channel
Mommy Guide Inc: Katy is on a goal to reach YPP by the end of the year.
Down To Earth With Katy : That sounds really painful Lala
Awesome Fun Things: Hi Markus!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: If you haven’t checked Katy out yes pls do:)
Down To Earth With Katy : Thank you friends xx
Rich Vybz: Hey Markus!!!
Down To Earth With Katy : I got a whole load of WIERD comments as I went live vertically on YT!
Awesome Fun Things: 👋
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Matt! Congratulations on the Ecamm guesting
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Rich!
Awesome Fun Things: Hi everyone 👋
Rich Vybz: Hey Lala!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Katy you need to have a moderator to kick those out when youre live. My friend got line 60 people live but lots of weirdos ive to kick them out.
Coach Adam Runs: Happy Swiss National Day!
Awesome Fun Things: Yep… someone let me on the ECAMM Live channel. Not sure if that’s a good or bad thing. Hahahaha. Just kidding. I had fun!! 🤩
Awesome Fun Things: Thanks, Lala
Rich Vybz: i’m currently DJing at day2 of the British fireworks championships here in Plymouth!!!
Down To Earth With Katy : Thanks Lala. 60 is a lot! I got 12 people which is much more than normal
Coach Adam Runs: It's Assumption Day
Coach Adam Runs: So if you can't assume which holiday it is, you have to work.
Awesome Fun Things: How can you DJ with fireworks popping off!? Haha
Awesome Fun Things: Hi Adam
Coach Adam Runs: Hey Mr. Awesome
Mommy Guide Inc: Katy it was just for awhile then it went down to 20 which were real supporters
Coach Adam Runs: On this day Christians all over the world celebrate the passing of Mary from this world to heaven. It's a beautiful holiday.
Awesome Fun Things: Markus: your gray comment overly background color is the same as my logo. Good choice. Do not eye dropper the hex color code. It’s PG-13. 😬
Down To Earth With Katy : Ah, I need to do my video. I forgot! (Thank you Lala x)
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes congratulations Markus the videos are indeed going up coz people are getting truly inspired
BostonDonMTB: Sometimes it is hard to keep the rhythm. I had a hard ride on Monday at my favorite state forest. A lot of uphill climbing, technical rocks and roots. So I was extra sore in my arms, and the core.
Awesome Fun Things: Haha
BostonDonMTB: Don't beat ourselves up for the missed movements.
Awesome Fun Things: I count my steps each day.
Pierre Kelly: how did matt sneak in here?
Awesome Fun Things: Walking is good for me and my two puppies.
BostonDonMTB: That happened to me for a couple of years and let it all get to me.
Awesome Fun Things: I’m sneaky like that Pierre Kelly. Haha
BostonDonMTB: I figured when things shut down I had all the time in the world to get fit, Never got on it like I am now.
Awesome Fun Things: 🥇 First! Wooo!! 🥳
Images by Gretchen: It is fun hanging out with you and hearing what you are up to. Helps me focus. I got my thumbnail done for my live tonight! Thanks
Ellie Calhoun: :hand-pink-waving::hand-pink-waving::hand-pink-waving::hand-pink-waving::hand-pink-waving::hand-pink-waving::hand-pink-waving:
Mommy Guide Inc: Looking forward to the new video next week Markus.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: I need to get ur link Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks so much Markus for hanging out with us.
Awesome Fun Things: What’s your website address?
Mommy Guide Inc: Bye! Happy weekend friends:)
Ellie Calhoun: I'll send you a video !
Pierre Kelly: bye all
Markus Schaub: https://markusschaub.shop/en-eur/