Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh finally my cp and tv signal are in sync today.;) Hi Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Let’s go creators!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello 👋 from Virginia!! Traveling but can’t miss Markus stream!!! 🤗
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow Markus - what an awesome journey it has been so far.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana!!! Love Virginia! Safe travels and enjoy.:) thanks for dropping by my friend.:)
Fishstick USA: Hello
Cheryl Wolf: Hello Markus and lala
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: @mommy guide inc thank you friend. Love the video too. The journey is so inspiring 🎉🥰
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Philip and Cheryl!
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Ana and Fishstick
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes it was super awesome Markus but am super tired from the heat and all the walking. He he he. Glad to be back:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi everyone.
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Markus😀
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Welcome back Lala
Eaglevp: Hi Markus no internet here watching on phone
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ejnar! Janet my sister from another mother! Yey let the party start.:)
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi to all The great people here😀
Eaglevp: Hello everyone
Mommy Guide Inc: Gosh I’ve been away for 2 weeks and when I get back so many updates on YT. Have to catch up.
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Janet , keith, Ejnar!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Keith!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey fam!
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Cheryl👍
Eaglevp: Hi Cheryl,Janet,Lala and Ejnar
Eaglevp: Hi Ana
Cheryl Wolf: Please share Markus
Eaglevp: Hello Janet
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh awesome. Looking forward to that video Markus.
Cheryl Wolf: Planning out the rest of the year
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Lala. Buenas noches 🌙
Andy Halper: Hip Markus!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I’m watching from the lobby of my dr. I will stay as long as I can
Fishstick USA: That is painful
Cheryl Wolf: Hey Andy
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Andy!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: They are AI?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Andy!!!
Andy Halper: HELLO HELLO HELLO!
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh they pretend to be robots. Millions? Billions?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Sounds fun
Planning_Erin: Hi Markus. 1st time here (from Marianne's channel. )
Cheryl Wolf: 5k
Andy Halper: Honestly, not that I know, women are better rappers than men are.
Planning_Erin: 25k
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Planning.Erin -welcome!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: She goes live just doing that? Pretending to be a robot?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: That is funny
Planning_Erin: Thank you Mommy Guide. yes they go live just doing that. it's all over tiktok now.
Mommy Guide Inc: Oooh live updates on planner.:) nice. Marianne can do that for sure.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Bwahaha!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Got to go but so nice to see y’all 👋🎉♥️
Andy Halper: You’re a fantastic collector of the human species!
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Bye bye Ana😀
Mommy Guide Inc: So Markus is this the same videos that vertical livestreams in YT has to be like?
Mommy Guide Inc: Take care Ana! Enjoy. Godspeed.
Mary Speegle: Are any of them LSP grads????
Planning_Erin: They have set phrases for whatever people "gift" them for. I dont know how they keep track. sometimes they "recalibrate " and start over when things get super crazy.
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: 😟 oh no. Not on YouTube, 🙏 please.
Mary Speegle: I wonder how long it takes to build their following.
Paul Burke: little late....Markus have you had a chance to experiment with vertical live?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Mary and Paul!
Mommy Guide Inc: Paul have you tried it?
Mommy Guide Inc: I think improv might be a good topic for vertical live?
Andy Halper: Pee-wee Herman wanna be …
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes I agree Andy.
Cheryl Wolf: we enjoy watching people work now ?
Fishstick USA: Q: How long are TikTok videos
Andy Halper: Always in sync with one another, Lala!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi David!
Andy Halper: WALTER!!!
Paul Burke: I haven't Lala...not yet
Tech Troublemaker: I wish my day job allowed me to host "Work with me" videos but so much PII and IP.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hehehe hi Roy!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey everyone!
Andy Halper: ROY!
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Roy😀👍
Fishstick USA: As for me, life-related update: We have a new grandchild. He came a few weeks early.
Ned Zeppelin:  Fun drum-practice buddy: Marcus!
Mommy Guide Inc: I will try going live in tiktok and YT vertical live this week. On what topic? That we will see. He he he
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Lala, Phillip, Andy, Ejnar, David, Paul, Markus, Cheryl, Janet, who did I miss?
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow congratulations Philip!!!
Andy Halper: Sorry, I have to go change a diaper, not my own. Thanks Markus, you’re FABULOUS!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sara! Hi Ned!
Tech Troublemaker: If you get 1% better every day eventually you will be 354% better!
Coffee Talk & Tech: hi peeps hi Markus 👋
Tech Troublemaker: Congrats @Fishstick USA
David W. Ryan: you are getting better Markus!
Tech Troublemaker: hey John!
Sarra Jerad: congrats!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Andy! See you again soon! Hugs to the grand children:)
Sarra Jerad: welcome !!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi John @CoffeeTalkandTech
Tech Troublemaker: @Fishstick USA why not just be a guest on my show one Tuesday night and get your feet wet with Live. 😛
Fishstick USA: Starting a channel Delayed but coming soon
Mary Speegle: I love the confetti!
David W. Ryan: I have been so busy with my day job, it's been difficult to create content
Mommy Guide Inc: Great Idea Roy. Go for it Philip.:)
Tech Troublemaker: YouTube links gone. Mine have already disappeared.
Stannex: Hi to all!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Stan!
Mommy Guide Inc: Haven’t checked mine yet Roy but thanks for the advice on how to apply thieve new updates.
Sarra Jerad: happy for you ☺️
Coffee Talk & Tech: hi Lala hi Roy hope you all are enjoying the summer.
Mommy Guide Inc: Friends don’t forget to smash that like button.:)
Mary Speegle: I can't wait to see your TikTok video.
Mommy Guide Inc: And join Markus YT family by subscribing to his channel and hitting that notification bell for updates and uploads:)
Stannex: I was just a guest this morning on Claudio S's show
Mommy Guide Inc: That am sure is super awesome Stan. Congratulations we will watch on replay for sure.:)
Fishstick USA: Tech Troublemaker, I will talk to you on the side
Sarra Jerad: it's a marathon, not a sprint!
Stannex: Hi, Lala!
Tech Troublemaker: I am not very popular yet; no one seems to be spoofing my channel 😛
Tech Troublemaker: So previously you could put links in the banner of your channel and also on shorts videos. YouTube is taking this away. This may also affect links in Descriptions. Still seeing them so far.
Tech Troublemaker: Links to your web sites or social media.
Mommy Guide Inc: Roy they’ll remove only on the banner but in the about it’s still there?
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh only on the shorts feed. But in regular videos we can still put links?
Mommy Guide Inc: Got it! Thanks Markus.
Cheryl Wolf: Luria said it will be a setup on YT will be kinda like IG link in bio ? d
Coffee Talk & Tech: youtube doesn't want to make it easy to for people to click a link to leave the platform.
Mommy Guide Inc: Makes sense John.
Cheryl Wolf: Banners for shorts are gone or does that mean the channel Banner , Sorry I didn't understand.
Cheryl Wolf: Thanks John
Mommy Guide Inc: I think links in shorts and channel banners Cheryl.:)
Cheryl Wolf: Hi John !!
Mommy Guide Inc: Will try that out Markus this week.
Cheryl Wolf: Your Trip in oct
Fishstick USA: When will share more about your tech videos for older people
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow love those fireworks!
Fishstick USA: Q: When will you share more about your tech videos for older people
Fishstick USA: I have a friend who knows tech for hearing and sight impaired.
Coffee Talk & Tech: anyone going to the expo in nyc that B&H are hosting? Sept 6th and 7th. I can't wait.
Fishstick USA: How can I reach out to you?
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow that’s awesome John! Please share the event via your
Mommy Guide Inc: Videos John.:)
Fishstick USA: That is true. We are FB friends. That will easy
David W. Ryan: I don't have the budget for the B&H expo!
Sara S: OMG - did I make it here live?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sara! Yes you did!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hope all is well Sara.:)
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Sara!
Cheryl Wolf: Sara is rocking it
Sara S: Doesn't usually happen
Sara S: Hu Cheryl and everybody!
Sara S: Markus was MVP times 10
Coffee Talk & Tech: David I was sent free ticket. from b&h Patrick from everyday tech and I going.
Sven Jessen: Hi, greetings from the baltic sea...
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sven!
Eaglevp: Hello Sven
Stannex: Are you going to do anything in the U.S. besides the eCamm conference?
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for dropping by everyone and joining Markus on a “casual talk” please don’t forget to smash the Likr button
Sara S: SMASHED
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Sara:)
Sarra Jerad: I understand. I am very bad with silence 🥲
Sven Jessen: I watched your video about vulnerability and was was really touched.
Mommy Guide Inc: Aww thanks Sven. Hope to see you here again regularly.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: This is inspiring Markus right? Your videos are impacting people.:) more pls.
Coffee Talk & Tech: I'm glad your pushing through....I see so many think they need to have more people on their stream. when all they wanted was just you...
Stannex: My weeks are always better when I'm able to make it to your livestream
Cheryl Wolf: Markus Thank you
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Stan for the support.:) thank you all.:)
Coffee Talk & Tech: I mean as guests markus not watching
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus has such a great big heart - he really cares and supports big time.
Mommy Guide Inc: It takes awhile but they’ll come - field of dreams - build it and they will come.:)
Cheryl Wolf: yes I agree, I need the butt kick
Coffee Talk & Tech: I've done lives that 8 people are watching and thats fine and it got 1k views you never know.
Cheryl Wolf: Next week
Stannex: ::butt kick:: ... Go, Cheryl!!!!
Cheryl Wolf: record or live not sure , vote ?
Mommy Guide Inc: Live this week and recorded next week Cheryl.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Cheryl:)
Coffee Talk & Tech: the key is a little bit of everything if you have time Cheryl if you don't have time just do videos.
Sara S: live
Sara S: yes, what's easier
Stannex: I really like that you have a good mix of interviews and extemporaneous conversational chats, Markus.
Cheryl Wolf: Ok I will take that in thanks john and lala
Cheryl Wolf: Sara Thanks
Coffee Talk & Tech: I say don't do whatever your comfortable with but you all know how I am. 😊 it'd hard to do uncomfortable
Coffee Talk & Tech: if I ever told you how hard it was to do my videos you might be surprised 😮
Coffee Talk & Tech: not yet ....I walk upstairs fustrating all the time still maybe after a couple hundred video. livestreaming soooo easy for me.
Stannex: I agree, Markus ... to get started, do what's easiest for you .... to get better, push your comfort zones.
Sara S: Yes. For me live-streaming is easier because I just have to flow with mistakes.
Pierre Kelly: afternoon all
Sara S: Although I NEVER would have live-streamed without having done LEDA
Cheryl Wolf: Same Sara
Coffee Talk & Tech: that's why I stopped lives so much...I need to push out videos.
Pierre Kelly: Agreed sara
Pierre Kelly: How did you stop CT&T?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Pierre:)
Pierre Kelly: I did find you around Paul Burke's channel's comments and Sarahs Small Changes channel
Cheryl Wolf: welcome new peps to Markus playground we have so much fun here
Sarra Jerad: I am from Switzerland too !!
Coffee Talk & Tech: It wasn't easy. I miss livestreaming and do it less but I have plans to do a bit more like one time a month for subscribers only.
Sara S: Sorry I have to go all, but I'm glad I got here live instead of a replay today!
Cheryl Wolf: Are you near Ascona ?
Mommy Guide Inc: Welcome and hope you will join Markus YT family by subscribing to his channel. See you all in the chat and comments again soon.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Sara S.:)
Pierre Kelly: Bye Sara S
Coffee Talk & Tech: its a great way to give back....members only will come a little more down the road.
Sarra Jerad: I am from the French part of Switzerland. So not a good German speaker 😅
Stannex: Thanks for another great show, Markus! I've gotta go, too. See you'all next time! :^)
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Stan! I’ll be back in the comments this week.:)
Coffee Talk & Tech: I gotta run 🏃‍♂️ I was off work today .. but family is waiting on me. take care all. thanks Marcus
Sarra Jerad: it was a great live thank to you !!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thank you Markus! Thanks friends and see you all next week!