Mary Speegle: Hi Markus, Your last show was great!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Mary thanks!
Mommy Guide Inc: We’re vertical tonight. Yey!
Mommy Guide Inc: I must agree. Marielou and Markus - that M2 show was aweso
Mary Speegle: Your intro is a walk down LSP lane.
Mommy Guide Inc: Streaming Life! I have to agree Mary.:) glad to see most of you here. LSP reunion feels
stressedoutstressfree: Hi Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh it’s absolutely fine. I just sleep earthy.:) I love love love being here.:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I’m here too with busy hands but listening
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello friends 👋♥️
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes! Last week was awesome 👏
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Vincent and Ana!
Mommy Guide Inc: Ana has an awesome challenge.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Oooh thanks Markus the vertical livestreams have made my views blow up
Mariane Cresp: Hello Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Mariane:)
Fishstick ~ Phillip: C: I have had an eventful first quarter. My brother died. I retired. Went on a vacation. Now, I need to reinvent my channel. I need a word of encouragement.
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Markus😀
Mary Speegle: Mommy you are going to college?
Mariane Cresp: Sorry for your loss Phillip. Make sure you give yourself space and grace.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: She is super woman!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Congratulations Mariane on being featured in a magazine in Australia. So so proud of you sis!
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Spring is a time for rebirth and growth
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Philip am so sorry for your loss. Biggest virtual hugs
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ejnar.:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: @fishtick you have wonderful content! It’s just a matter to get back on the horse 🐴
Mariane Cresp: Missed you in the first lesson Markus!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Start little by little
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Thank you are your kind words.
Mariane Cresp: Thank you @Mommy Guide Inc
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Thank you for asking Markus! It’s going great!!! I don’t have a big amount of people by I know it’s because I haven’t done the promotion it deserves
rich_vybz_dj: Hey Mommy lala
Mommy Guide Inc: No Mary I prepare students to enter top universities here in the Philippines;)
Sammy Super Star: Hello Markus
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: But “do it for the one” ☝️ I’m challenging myself and I’m getting private messages from people telling me how helpful it is and encouraging so for me that is a win 🏆
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sammy!
Fishstick ~ Phillip: C: I need to make additional content in order to have a reserve. I have bought a Shure microphone, Dell webcam, and a new iPhone 15 pro. Equipment is not a concern.
Mary Speegle: Fishstick-I'm sorry for your loss. I understand prioritizing after retirement.
Mariane Cresp: 🤣🤣🤣
Fishstick ~ Phillip: I will publish by next week. It is Spring.
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Thank you Mary
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow Philip - go my friend!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: This challenge is a gift to myself. It is my birthday month so I loving doing this!
Mommy Guide Inc: Ana it has been a very inspiring one and perfect prep for the Holy Week.:)
Fishstick ~ Phillip: I recorded some b-roll while on vacation. I am happy with that.
Mommy Guide Inc: Perfect time for self reflection. Advance Happy Birthday dear Ana:)
Mary Speegle: Mommy you are amazing!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Rich!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Thank you 😊 sweet friend
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for the shoutout in the grp also Ana.:) love you!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I am working on a strategy. I will do it again with more promo and the content is there so I don’t have to re-record everything
Sammy Super Star: Yes
Fishstick ~ Phillip: C or Q: Markus, I would to change some of the format or template. I like your use of vertical display. What app do you use for graphics and your videos?
Rich Vybz: i have switched over..
Mary Speegle: Ana-that is great that your site is personal to people.
Mommy Guide Inc: Sammy went live last Wednesday again after a long time and did an interview with another film maker. Just in case any one wants to check it ou;)
Mommy Guide Inc: Ana pls
Mommy Guide Inc: Ana pls come in and let’s do the promo for your next one.
Coach Adam: Good morning!
Mary Speegle: phillip- what is your channel?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Coach Adam! I will start my daily walk around the campus nearby - not prepping for a marathon but inspired by your own prep
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: @Phillip if you don’t mind me saying…you already have lots of content. How did you handle the loss of loved one. How to transition to retirement. How to enjoy grandparenting. Vacation time!
Coach Adam: Are you finding there is more engagement going LIVE in vertical?
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Nope it’s the 30th I will posting my wishlist on my facebook page 😂
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Ana, good point. Life is handing me content.
Coach Adam: @Mommy Guide Inc Way to go! I'm so proud of your commitment to your fitness.
Mommy Guide Inc: Adam doctor also told me to do cardio exercises to strengthen my heart. So thanks - I can’t jog but definitely can walk.:)
Coach Adam: @Mommy Guide Inc You don't need to run, in fact it's too much for most joints... but you can always walk... until you can't. Don't let that be you!
Fishstick ~ Phillip: My videos will be recorded. I have Canva Pro. I am not proficient.
Tech Troublemaker: Hey everyone!
Tech Troublemaker: I hate vertical live streams. 😎
Mommy Guide Inc: Go Philip.:) am sure you’ll get used to Canva soon.:) Hi Roy!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Phillip and Lala
Coach Adam: If I lie down watching vertical live streams - are they still vertical?
Mommy Guide Inc: He he he. The vertical livestream is something to get used to indeed Roy. But starting to get used to it. Thanks Markus and LSP for the tips how and Roy for helping me out and test it out.
Coach Adam: You're just so much smaller on the YouTube desktop view.
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Coach it’s vertical all the time so it’s kinda tiny and have black bars on the side
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: @phillip if you need help with Canva reach out I will be happy to help
Mary Speegle: We can't see as much of you on vertical. :(
Mommy Guide Inc: I feel YT has been pushing the vertical livestreams - I’ve seen boost on my livestreams views.
Coach Adam: FYI Capcut is owned by TicTok, which is currently in a legal battle in the US.
Coach Adam: or I should say "ByteDance"
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Markus, Thank you for the suggestion to focus on the content. I will bring in more editing.
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh do you think Tiktok will lose its presence in the US?
Mommy Guide Inc: Lol Roy:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Was in a YT led seminar earlier today for content creators in my region. The topic was vertical livestream.
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: when we do a remix on shorts can you download it and edit further?
mommyguideinc: Hi Dr Elo! Hi Markus here on IG too:)
mommyguideinc: Hi Vincent!
Tech Troublemaker: Yes
Tech Troublemaker: If it shows on your channel you can download it.
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: I’ve come to say HIIIII
Tech Troublemaker: And there are tools to download via YT links
mommyguideinc: How are you all loving the vertical livestreams? Will any of you planning on watching more on  vertical?
dwryan71: I just had a TikTok video  with 3k views the most I’ve gotten there
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: You could do a dance or some crafting Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Roy can you show us how soon? Hi Katy!
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Hi Lala x
Tech Troublemaker: Yes, I will do a remix to play with it
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: I’m famous at last 😝😝😝
Tech Troublemaker: Woot David.
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Roy! I wanted to do a remix of a shorts dance but wanted to added some stuff to it and edit but didn’t know how.
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Thank YOU!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes not my own content. Remix from another channel
Mommy Guide Inc: Like those famous dances - it’s for a birthday greeting for a friend. So I wanted to add the extra greeting. But couldn’t.
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Great to see and hear from everyone.
Fishstick ~ Phillip: This has been very helpful. I appreciate you all.
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Enjoying hanging out
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh it’s going to be for Youtube upload as shorts. We’re going to have a shorts hop. And I was planning to do a dance with a greeting.:) he he he
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: What’s a Shorts Hop? Is it a dance???💃 🕺
Mommy Guide Inc: Awww thanks Markus for going live.
Tech Troublemaker: As long as you are live @Markus, I will watch in any format.
Mommy Guide Inc: Katy a hop is a set of creators doing some project - mostly crafters - we jump from watching one content to another via a playlist
Mommy Guide Inc: You get included in the playlist and automatically it will play all the videos from the playlist if you join.
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Ah, that sounds great Lala
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: "come and say hi" ok "hi"
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi!
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: @Markus Schaub titel chlaue isch immer e gueti idee 😛 funktioniert meischtens
Mommy Guide Inc: On Sat I’ll be part of a YT Hop for Kendra’s Card Challenge.:)
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: #markusfanclub hanging out
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: wow thats a big fanclub
Mommy Guide Inc: He he he can’t put link coz this hop is kinda private til it goes live. He he he
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks so much Markus and everyone!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Markus is world-famous! Thanks for being here friends. Pls don’t forget to smash the LIKE button.:)
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: good to know 😛 big creator big fanclub - i also big 😛
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Next merch words #markusfanclub
Mommy Guide Inc: See you!!!