Mommy Guide Inc: Hang in there friends.
John Westhaver: We lots your signal Markus.
Mommy Guide Inc: Too much awesome sa up on screen.:)
Stannex: Too much awesomeness on one screen
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Oh I thought it was mine
Eaglevp: Hi John Westhaver
Yuka Nakasone: Noooo... we didn't Adam. Maybe we broke Markus' computer.
Mommy Guide Inc: There you go yes Stan! The internet couldn’t handle the awesomeness!
Ellie Calhoun: Yay!! 2 Cheryl's!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: John!!’ Yey thanks for joining us.:)
Yuka Nakasone: Where is Andy?
John Westhaver: @Eaglevp Hi.
Stannex: This is a test ... you're learning the limits of your system
Cheryl Wolf: Andy 🎉
Eaglevp: Just do it off the cuff
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Well we learned something new today
Yuka Nakasone: Andy 🎉
Tech Troublemaker: For this many guests, make sure you have shutdown all non-essential programs. I even say reboot before you start your stream.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Andy 🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉
Cheryl Wolf: I happy to give my seat to Andy
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes changing the world man!!!!
John Westhaver: I was.
John Westhaver: I came over here though.
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yes. That too Markus. I learned this the hard way. Everyone has to be on earphones.
Eaglevp: Hi Andy
Mommy Guide Inc: And close your YouTube monitors. Use another gadget to monitor
Stannex: If you're on the show, you have to mute window you were watching in.
Mommy Guide Inc: You can survive this Andy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Great advice too Stan. But best not to monitor on the same computer
Coffee Talk & Tech: hello Markus 👋 and crew
Mommy Guide Inc: Omg - hi John!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: We miss you Andy!!!!
Tech Troublemaker: Close one ear Andy so you won't have as much Echo!
Cheryl Wolf: Hi John!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey John @Coffee Talk & Tech
Coffee Talk & Tech: don't say window open Andy will check the whole house!
Coffee Talk & Tech: hi 👋 everyone
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes!!! 🎉🎉🎉
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Andy makes the makes the live alive😃😃
Cheryl Wolf: We need some Andy wisdom
Mommy Guide Inc: Anything and everything is a go for today.:) Star-studded show tonight.
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: There is a lot of things you cannot talk about🤔
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks all for being here pls don’t forget to smash the LIKR button.
Cheryl Wolf: Don’t forget to Hit the like Button!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Wow! We need the link to watch the replay for that!
Coffee Talk & Tech: if I wasn't on the road I'd come say hi.
John Westhaver: Hi @Cheryl Wolf
Cheryl Wolf: Lala we must been typing at the same time lol
Cheryl Wolf: Hello
Mommy Guide Inc: Awww that would have been great John. Safe travels though. Maybe you can join next time:)
John Westhaver: What software are you running Markus?
Mommy Guide Inc: John Markus is on ecamm:)
Cheryl Wolf: Markus Rocks 🎉🎉
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: That is good info to know
John Westhaver: What your talking about is duplexing with your speakers.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I love the color changing Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Cheryl go back in if you can.:) the more the merrier.:)
Stannex: I'm the one who broke the system ... unlucky number five. ;^)
Mommy Guide Inc: Stan were so excited to see you with Markus next week.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: I think Stan will have one in a few hours from now?
Stannex: I was live Tuesday ... and I'll be live again tonight with a Star Wars themed show
Fishstick USA: Sali Markus
Stannex: Too kind of you to say. :😊:
Mommy Guide Inc: I would love too it’s just the kids are sleeping in with me now and so I can’t turn on the lights. My studio is in my room. He he he
Mommy Guide Inc: On it Markus
Sara S: I’ll have to figure out what I’ll use. I have the Mee earbuds and a number of other headphones.I wonder which headset will work best. I work!🤣🤣🤣
Stannex: Live tonight at 7pm Pacific Time
Mommy Guide Inc: Here is the link to Stan’s coming live - https://www.youtube.com/live/dg7iXXO0P2M?feature=share
Stannex: The hardest part is keeping an eye on the chat stream!
Mommy Guide Inc: Nothing can break Markus coolness - he just keeps going.:)
Stannex: Markus is unflappable ... he can't be flapped!
Cheryl Wolf: So right lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Congratulations Tim!
Sara S: Absolutely. Markus is supremely cool in every way.
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks awesome people
Cheryl Wolf: Another one bites, the dust
Sara S: Bring Cheryl back!
Mommy Guide Inc: What a tease from Tim! Now we have to wait eagerly for the rest of his message
Stannex: That's what happens when you insult A.!. .... the computers are always listening!
Sara S: We need women represented here
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL @Stan
John Westhaver: Tim we can hear you.
Eaglevp: We can hear you Tim
John Westhaver: Markus Maybe zoom next time. You just can't control the cams.
Mommy Guide Inc: Go for that Markus. I turned all my interviews as part of my video podcasts on YouTube
Eaglevp: Who’s going to the wrap party tomorrow?
Eaglevp: Me
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes will be partying from bed Keith at 2am my time.:)
Yuka Nakasone: That's good. One after another, one by one... if you know the "direction" you would like to go and if you can do one, after another, it's much better than having a wrong goal
Sara S: Hi Yuka!
Yuka Nakasone: Yes, you can go, just figure out the DIRECTION... Asia or America or Europe.
Eaglevp: That’s great Lala
Yuka Nakasone: Hi Sara!
Sara S: Lala’s everywhere all the time
Stannex: Yes ... "riding around" can be fun ... but if you want to "get somewhere," you need to have a "goal"
Eaglevp: What’s your goal for the next 3 months Adam
Stannex: Lala is an incredible force of nature!
Sara S: Time to go teach. Bye👋
Cheryl Wolf: Flexible goals
Sara S: Yes Cheryl
Yuka Nakasone: Of course!
Mommy Guide Inc: I agree Markus is a great enabler and supporter.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Sara thanks for being here have a great day!!!
Yuka Nakasone: That's why we are here.....
John Westhaver: We love you Markus!
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Markus Rocks😀👍
Stannex: 🥰
Mommy Guide Inc: Aww love that. If we are able to help even one single person - that would be more than enough
Yuka Nakasone: 🌹
Eaglevp: Hi Ejnar
John Westhaver: You are making me blush!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes. John indeed is that and more.:)
John Westhaver: Thanks for the love and support!
Yuka Nakasone: Not our limit but tech limit...LOL
Stannex: There's no limit on creativity ... but bandwidth is highly regulated.
Cheryl Wolf: Thanks Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: This was an amazing stream - learned so much.:) thanks everyone. Don’t forget to smash the LIKE button on your way out my friends:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Coach Adam, Cheryl, Tim, Keith, Andy - thanks for joining Markus live today:)
Eaglevp: Bye all