Mommy Guide Inc: Hello Markus!
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Hello Markus.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Philip:)
Eaglevp: Evening Markus & Lala
Eaglevp: Hi@Fishstick ~ Phillip
Mommy Guide Inc: Howdy Keith:)
Adam El Gringo: Markus!
Eaglevp: Hello@Adam El Gringo
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Coach Adam! Are you back from Mexico?
Adam El Gringo: I'm back, but heading to India soon. My adventures continue!
Eaglevp: Did you have a nice holiday in Mexico Adam
Eaglevp: Wow a globetrotter then Adam
Adam El Gringo: Mexico City. was amazing as always. I ate all the tacos. They are having a national crisis now because there are none left.
Mommy Guide Inc: Little adaptations and tweaks. Love that!
Fishstick ~ Phillip: C: I have not posted for the past month due to my brother being in the hospital and his passing earlier this week. I will be back soon. I am changing my format to be able to handle such events.
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Adam: What part of India?
Mariane Cresp: Hello Markus!
Eaglevp: Sorry to hear that@Fishstick ~ Phillip
Eaglevp: Hi@Mariane Cresp
Eaglevp: Looking forward to next month Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: My deepest condolences Philip. Sorry for your loss.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Mariane!
Adam El Gringo: Exciting! I look forward to heading about how Lala is creating her event. Very cool.
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Markus for the invite! I am excited already:)
Eaglevp: I need some motivation had a bit of a burnout
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello 👋
Eaglevp: Hi@Ana Zugheri - Faith52
Fishstick ~ Phillip: C: I enjoyed your video last week. You shared a broken mug and tutorial you were not happy with. I found the video REAL and it actually encouraged me to be down on myself.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana!
Mommy Guide Inc: Being with you all are great motivation. It’s so nice to have people you can sound off your ideas with.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: It seems I came in at the perfect time!!! 😂
Mommy Guide Inc: Friends don’t forget to smash the LIKE button:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: You are talking to me????!!!!!! 😂
Mommy Guide Inc: Ana’s podcasts and Adam’s are great source of motivation
Eaglevp: I miss your vlogs Markus
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: You guys are all amazing 🤩
Eaglevp: Have you learnt how to live stream from the pocket 3 yet?
Mommy Guide Inc: Sorry I meant Adam’s - Mindset Mondays on YT:) yes we miss your vlogs Markus.
Mommy Guide Inc: Your videos are so much fun Markus.
Mommy Guide Inc: More editing live with Markus?
Eaglevp: Are you going to have a panel on some of your interviews Markus?
Fishstick ~ Phillip: I am retired. I have more time for family and developing videos for my channel.
Adam El Gringo: For me, it's keeping a healthy work/stream balance. I'm traveling so much for my job, it's hard to keep up with the weekly habit.
Mariane Cresp: Bless you Markus, thank you 😊
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh Marianne’s authenticity in her livestreams is something that I really like.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Am working on my vision board
Mommy Guide Inc: Go Philip.:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I have one year left to get to half of my life according to statistics…so I have to get serious 🧐….ok you know I can’t 😂😂😂😂
Mariane Cresp: Buy a planner ! LOL
Mariane Cresp: They will be discounted now
Mommy Guide Inc: Great idea Markus.:)
Eaglevp: Like me Markus I always watch @Mariane Cresp content and I always tell myself that's what I should do but never get round to it.
Mariane Cresp: Go the 49-ers!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yep!!! Let’s do it 💪🙏
Mariane Cresp: Done! Markus ... I'll go on your live and plan for content creation scheduling.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I like that! I’m about to turn a 49er!!!!! 🫶
Mariane Cresp: As in age! I turned 49 earlier this month.
Mariane Cresp: 🤣🤣🤣
Mommy Guide Inc: Belated Happy Birthday Mariane fellow Aquarian?
Mariane Cresp: Capricorn @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh really early Jan. Mariane. Sorry missed greeting you on your special day Mariane. I am sure it was great.:)
Mariane Cresp: We'll PLAN. DO. REVIEW
Mommy Guide Inc: Go Markus! Mariane is so awesome with planners - not just decorating but really using them.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Perfect time to start with a planner - it’s this time of the year that I feel everyone tried to reboot starting with creating plans in a planner.:)
Coffee Talk & Tech: create!! on your own terms
Eaglevp: HI@Coffee Talk & Tech
Mommy Guide Inc: Love your shirt by the way Markus. That’s available on Markus merch shop by the way.:) he he he.
Coffee Talk & Tech: hi guy's
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi John @ Coffee Talk & Tech
Coffee Talk & Tech: yep who cares!!! as long as your going in the right direction
Mommy Guide Inc: I am so excited to share the journey and get feed back friends.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes pls join me and Markus next week for that:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Right, it is harder to do the work and get results that stay the same…that is easy
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Steady and slowly…but STRONG 💪
Coffee Talk & Tech: just remember people come for you not for you have on or interview....you that's the truth
Coffee Talk & Tech: you have gown so much...pat yourself on the back!!!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey everyone. Markus is the show and anything else is just extra.
Eaglevp: hI rOY
Coffee Talk & Tech: exactly Roy
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy!
BostonDonMTB: I already liked it. :D
Coffee Talk & Tech: It's a process and put your energy into you. Do for you not for others. not in a selfish way...it's your channel.
BostonDonMTB: Hey everyone
Coffee Talk & Tech: 👋
Eaglevp: hI@BostonDonMTB
Mariane Cresp: Markus. Here's a challenge ... create a reel you buying a planner and promoting upcoming planning livestream ... then get people to subscribe and hit the bell to get notified. Let's build a hype.
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh my Hi Don! Great to see you again:)
Mariane Cresp: *** oops I meant shorts
Tech Troublemaker: We are growing slow but we are growing and on our own terms. If it stops being fun we shouldn’t do it.
Coffee Talk & Tech: it makes sense
BostonDonMTB: I haven't put any time towards it. I have 5 interviews that I did last year and I haven't posted them. I am being really hard on myself.
Mommy Guide Inc: Mariane yes he did that with our Vlogmas - buying supplies
Ellie Calhoun: Better late than never!
BostonDonMTB: I am in a funk.
Mommy Guide Inc: And it was really nice. Hi Ellie!
Mariane Cresp: we'll figure it out along the way ... sometimes we get stuck in the planning and not actioning.
BostonDonMTB: Hi Lala, Hi @Eaglevp, Roy and John.
Coffee Talk & Tech: I was getting stressed by companies reaching out. So I started turning things down. which I thought I'd never do.
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Don. How can we encourage you?
BostonDonMTB: Hard on myself for not posting them.
Coffee Talk & Tech: my point was listen to yourself more.
BostonDonMTB: Roy, I am not sure.
Eaglevp: Hi Ellie
Ellie Calhoun: Yes, the Not? Ready Go mousepad. How do I get my address to you?
Tech Troublemaker: Don, reach out man. I know a content creator support group. 😃
Coffee Talk & Tech: Don I think we all do that...I'm getting better at letting it go...life happens....
BostonDonMTB: John, sure does. I need do another round of invites for my guests. That will get me excited.
BostonDonMTB: I need to finish editing.
Tech Troublemaker: Done is better than none.
Mommy Guide Inc: I feel you with finish editing part Don. Me too.
Coffee Talk & Tech: Don most of the bigger youtubers tell us ...doesn't even matter. they also love selling themselves. it's a business.
Ellie Calhoun: 👍
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Keith
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus you created so much this past week - creating your merch shop and all. That’s an absolute win. Just keep moving forward my friend.:)
Tech Troublemaker: Ugh four hours of editing to make a less than 8 minute video. That is my problem
BostonDonMTB: Yeah it is a terrible loop that happens.
Mariane Cresp: I am okay now not being perfect ... I did my podcast where I was looking at my iPad for my notes and not worry about looking at the camera the whole video.
BostonDonMTB: Let it Go, Let it Go, Let it Go. :D
Tech Troublemaker: I have had a great week. Trying to keep it going.
Coffee Talk & Tech: I try to get better with how I approach everything. The hook 🪝 the editing...videos are hard.
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh my “actually” has to definitely go - I begin and end with “actually” ugh
Tech Troublemaker: Love my Markus sweat shirt
Mariane Cresp: 🤣
Mariane Cresp: make sure to hit that LIKE button everybody!
Ellie Calhoun: This is such a supportive encouraging community.
Tech Troublemaker: I was trying to become 1% better every time. Now I settle for .000001 % better 🤪
Ellie Calhoun: Roy, I think you made big strides during vlogmas!
Mommy Guide Inc: My journey with content creation is just move forward - just like life there are good and not so good ones but I just move forward.
Mommy Guide Inc: So true Ellie.:)
Mariane Cresp: Mine filler words are "So ..." or "Like I said ..."
Coffee Talk & Tech: I love livestreaming but learning how to get better at videos is important. livestreams don't usually become evergreen. where videos gain subscribers for years.
Pierre Kelly: Afternoon all
BostonDonMTB: @Coffee Talk & Tech very true on the differences between lives and video. You are still learning something with either.
Coffee Talk & Tech: ohh yes but let's be honest we are all looking for growth.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Pierre.:)
BostonDonMTB: Markus, you are probably doing this for connection with the world, and it's FUN. 😃
Coffee Talk & Tech: so after many tests...both my shorts and livestreams will connect with a long form video. that's the best for me.
Ellie Calhoun: Markus, you might not have hundreds of subscribers but I think you have a high # of people consistently coming to interact with you in your lives
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Markus😀👋
Coffee Talk & Tech: growing comes many ways too. I don't want 3k subscribers if I'm get 50 hours of watch time. that would eat me up.
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Don’t stop, you’re doing great😀👍
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ejnar:)
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Lala😀
Eaglevp: Hi Ejnar
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hey Keith😀👍
Coffee Talk & Tech: peace ✌️ got a basketball game to watch!! nite all
BostonDonMTB: Thank you Markus.
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks John.:) enjoy the game.
Pierre Kelly: Thanks Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Do t forget to like and share friends!
BostonDonMTB: Thank you everyone!
Ellie Calhoun: Thanks!
Mommy Guide Inc: See you all!