Mommy Guide Inc: Good day everyone!
elle naturally: ☺️💜
Mommy Guide Inc: H Markus! Are you back from vacation?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Elle:)
elle naturally: Hi mommy guide inc 💜💜
Eaglevp: Evening Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Keith!
elle naturally: I was just about to watch Marcus’ recent video “are you too boring to make content”
Images by Gretchen: Hi @Markus Schaub Hi @Mommy Guide Inc
Rich Vybz: Good evening everyone
joana.kunz: heeey
elle naturally: ☺️☺️☺️
Eaglevp: Hi Ellie and Rich
Mommy Guide Inc: Elle it was so nice. I am sure you'll love it. I can actually relate to the video it's as if Markus was talking directly to me:)
Stannex: Hiya, hiya, hiya!
Eaglevp: Hi Lala and Stan
Mommy Guide Inc: Stan!!! I miss you my friend.
elle naturally: Hi Eagle
Rich Vybz: Hey Ellie & Eagle
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Rich!
elle naturally: Hey Rich
Images by Gretchen: First time catching you live...
Rich Vybz: Daaaaaa Vyyyyyyyyybz!! lol
Eaglevp: You definitely not boring Markus
Stannex: It's going GREAT!
Mommy Guide Inc: Gretchen hi! Congratulations my friend for the awesome milestone of 500 lives1
Rich Vybz: That’s Kali’s fault
Images by Gretchen: Thx LaLa I appreciate your support
elle naturally: Woooaa 500 lives Gretchen!!!
Stannex: Lala is AMAZING!
Mommy Guide Inc: Going live daily crafting is a tribute to LEDA where it all started for me:)
Eaglevp: Agree Stan Lala is amazing
Mommy Guide Inc: awww thanks Stan. I am blushing.:)
Rich Vybz: Unfortunately I have hit a bump with live streaming.. im trying to start again
Eaglevp: Can we have a photo of that Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Celebrating your awesome videos and lives Markus. Indeed life happens. I feel doing daily videos is much harder than going live everyday. editing is long and hard.
Mommy Guide Inc: Rich cheering you on my friend.:)
Images by Gretchen: Go for it @Rich Vybz I did a year straight then took a break and restarted a month later at just 2 times a week. that I can stick to .. Lives only for me, NO editing: )
Stannex: When you had that 130 person group, what were you talking about?
Mommy Guide Inc: love that = I am In Netflix! I actually looked for you on Netflix!
Eaglevp: Like you Rich I will have to get back doing lives
Rich Vybz: yes i think post covid life is part of the problem, but because its not on you tube it is harder to get a fan base
Rich Vybz: The people that do watch always say its entertaining but getting people onto my platform is hard work
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Rich I think the platform also is harder for you coz of the music. wish Youtube would allow creators like you to also be on YouTube without getting copyright issues.
Mommy Guide Inc: oh yes Rich is really a great host and DJ!
Rich Vybz: thank you Lala.. there is some good news… twitch is getting music copyright sorted soon.
Mommy Guide Inc: ooh that's great! Something to look forward to. please keep us updated Rich:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yes - titles. Mine can go on forever! I tend to max out the allowed words. LOL
Rich Vybz: yes what you say is true Markus.. may just start on there
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks friends for being here with us in the live. Please don't forget to hit the LIKE button.
Rich Vybz: Maybe this sunday!?! stay tuned
Mommy Guide Inc: "mukbang" a Korean term for filming oneself while eating I think.
Mommy Guide Inc: your mini vacation place is so awesome.
Rich Vybz: Oh no not mukbang… my niece used to watch them … just bizarre
Mommy Guide Inc: ooh the shorts from the museum was FUN.
Mommy Guide Inc: My craft room tour / organisation is now 2 years in the making. LOL editing is truly a struggle for me.
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL. I also am baffled how one would want to watch me eat but it's something that apparently like watching I think the different dishes something like that.
Stannex: It's amazing how quickly these things add up when you commit to doing something regularly.
Mommy Guide Inc: The raw footage Markus is about 6 hours Long. Need to compile to a 20-30min video. LOL
Stannex: Tonight is my 52nd weekly "Improv Cartooning" livestream. 52 weeks ... that's a YEAR! How did THAT happen?!?
Mommy Guide Inc: Stan congratulations my friend for having another segment on your show celebrating D&D
Images by Gretchen: @Mommy Guide Inc Lala craft room & studio organization is an organic living thing that changes daily and never ends 🤦‍♀️
Mommy Guide Inc: So true Gretchen!
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: Is anyone coming to Creator Camp?
Rich Vybz: Ooh stannex that sounds like a fun channel.. will subscribe
Mommy Guide Inc: Congratulations Stan!!! one full year of going live and more! Stan also has another show about Sumo with his friend Troy:)
Images by Gretchen: @Mommy Guide Inc LaLa break it into a series, then speed it up to X20 and make it into a bunch of shorter videos.
Stannex: Yeah ... I haven't missed a week yet. (I did recorded shows 3 times, I think)
Images by Gretchen: Yes !! Camp OG's returning!!
Mommy Guide Inc: oh I remember Stan one of them was Christmas I think or New Year that you had a video coz of family event:) but otherwise you have gone live all the time. awesome!!!
Rich Vybz: thanks.. all done
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Rich:)
Images by Gretchen: Not open quite yet but OG's get an early notification ... coming soon I think
Mommy Guide Inc: I think in less than 2 weeks it will open. I am praying I can return. still trying to fix logistics etc. I do want to be back.
Mommy Guide Inc: I remember I brought my dji pocket 2 but wasn't really able to use it coz I didn't know how.
Mommy Guide Inc: so I ended up just doing everything on my phone. he he he.
Mommy Guide Inc: yes Victor just recently got an insta 360 and he is loving it so much.
Cheryl Wolf: Hello 👋
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Cheryl!!! Great to see you back in the chat:)
Cheryl Wolf: Hi lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks friends again for being here - please don't forget to click on the LIKE button:)
Cheryl Wolf: Miss you all
Cheryl Wolf: Loving your videos Markus
Images by Gretchen: hi @Cheryl Wolf !
Mommy Guide Inc: just 11 days to go Markus!
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Gretchen
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes - every video and every livestream is a learning experience:)
Office Cooking: Hi!
Cheryl Wolf: Hi John
Mommy Guide Inc: OMG Hi John!
Cheryl Wolf: Mercury is retrograde so that means old friends will reappear
Mommy Guide Inc: Congratulations John - Office Cooking is doing so well on all platforms!
Office Cooking: Hi everyone! Going great. Just deciding what to cook for lunch. Yes, more views and traction.
Office Cooking: Not amazing, but very good.
elle naturally: Lost my interwebs connection but back again
Mommy Guide Inc: John's channel name - same on all platforms. but on YT it's https://www.youtube.com/@officecooking
Mommy Guide Inc: How about some food from other countries John?
Mommy Guide Inc: From the Philippines famous ones are - Pancit, Adobo and Sinigang:)
Office Cooking: I plan on it. I'm getting people in Pakistan and other countries asking me to make their favorite dish.
Office Cooking: I made a Japanese breakfast last time.
Office Cooking: That sounds great.
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes love your Japanese recipes and the way John delivers the cooking is super awesome! You just have to check office cooking:)
Rich Vybz: Oh I didn’t realise! Mr Pullum how are you sir
Cheryl Wolf: Now I’m hungry
Office Cooking: HA
Mommy Guide Inc: Cheryl same here. I might have an early breakfast:)
Office Cooking: What's new with you, Marcus?
Cheryl Wolf: No john can cook
Mommy Guide Inc: For crafters - livestreams always include a drink and some sort of food. he he he.
Cheryl Wolf: Nice lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Coke Zero. my guilty pleasure too. at least no sugar. he he he.
Cheryl Wolf: What is your challenge is video a day ? Markus
Rich Vybz: Nice to see everyone on here!
Cheryl Wolf: Mine is soda water with fresh fruit
Mommy Guide Inc: yes 1 video and 1 livestream for Markus after April - ok we will help Markus with that:)
Rich Vybz: Take care guys!
Markus Schaub: https://youtu.be/ntGr2RQuYOs?si=LcYfKZUTP1HnHV6G
Cheryl Wolf: What is the hardest part for you Markus?
Mommy Guide Inc: ooh that sounds very refreshing Cheryl:)
Mommy Guide Inc: ooh yes that's the latest video that came out a few minutes before Markus' live today. Yes pls do watch my friends:)
Stannex: My suggestion is to increase quality in small steps. Little by little. If you put too much "quality pressure" on yourself, you're more likely to get "creative freeze"
Office Cooking: Nice seeing you Marcus and reconnecting with everyone else. :)
Images by Gretchen: @Stannex I'll catch the first half hour of yours tonight at 6pst before I go live at 6:30..looking forward to it!
Stannex: Thank you kindly, Gretchen! :^)
Mommy Guide Inc: Stan that is so true. "creative freeze" that's a term I heard only now but so true.
elle naturally: 💜💜💜
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Gretchen. Do you know that Gretchen also draws Stan? She is awesome!
elle naturally: ☺️☺️☺️
Images by Gretchen: Thank you Marcus. fun hanging out with you
Stannex: I hope you're asleep, Markus (as much as I always love seeing you)