Mommy Guide Inc: Good day Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: No audio!
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: huhuu @Mommy Guide Inc
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: hello no audio markus
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Eric!
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: yessssss
Mommy Guide Inc: Ok. Now you have
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: we hear you now
Fishstick USA: Hello Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Eric!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Philip!
Ketia Francis-Johnson: Hi Markus and Lala!
Mommy Guide Inc: Makes sense. Do them in bite sizes:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ketia:)
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: #rotsee - nice little lake - i have already swum the length of it
Mommy Guide Inc: Let’s go - One Big goal before the year end. Nice Markus!
Ketia Francis-Johnson: YES! One BIG Goal!:text-yellow-goal:
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: that was in the 90is - i dont know how its now
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow that’s awesome Eric:)
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: @Mommy Guide Inc i am one of the people of the mountain goats and i am a water rat
Ketia Francis-Johnson: You've got me thinking Markus...I'll let you know in the Creator Club Accountability group.
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: @Markus Schaub come here and we'll hike up the säntis - small mountain here at 2501.9 metres above sea level 😛
Stan!: Hello, Markus ... and everyone!
Stan!: Curling wears a body out!
Stan!: My cousin is on a team that has gone to the Canadian National Amateur Curling Championships a couple of times.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Stan!
Stan!: Hi, @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: I see and feel Markus intentionality in making this happen. You can and will make this happen indeed Markus:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Eating better something I should look into as well.
CSLiveDK : Hello everyone😀
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ejnar!
CSLiveDK : Hi Lala😀
Mommy Guide Inc: Oooh so true Markus - knowing and doing are two different things indeed.
Mommy Guide Inc: Ejnar I love the shorter channel name.:)
CSLiveDK : I am fine Marcus.
Fishstick USA: I do have some things I want to accomplish by year end. I was not prepared to say all today. I will message you.
Fishstick USA: But a
Fishstick USA: But I want to share with you. You are such an encouragement
Mommy Guide Inc: 🙏 alongside everyone’s goals. We can do this. I will contemplate about this one goal - as you know my issue is there’s so many goals. Lol
Ketia Francis-Johnson: Yes Lala! WE can do this!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Ketia! All together now friends. Step at a time.
CSLiveDK : I am working as producer for a Danish woman in Spain, and hope we can make some money out of it. I also make a little for my self and would like to stream more in English too. LEDA in December, Markus
CSLiveDK : You can run it😀🙏👍
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey go for it Ejnar. I know you did it already several times and cheering you on for this year.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Friends don’t forget to hit the LIKE a button:)
Stan!: The first step is the most important.
elle naturally: Happy Thursday
elle naturally: Hello
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Elle!
elle naturally: Hiiii
Stan!: Happy birthday, @elle naturally
Ketia Francis-Johnson: Bye!
elle naturally: ☺️☺️☺️☺️
CSLiveDK : Wamping up or wrapping up🤣
elle naturally: It’s not my birthday
Mommy Guide Inc: So true Stan! Congratulations by the way my friend. The channel is doing great:) yey!
elle naturally: I didn’t know either hahaha
CSLiveDK : Happy Birthday 🎁🎈🎂🎊
Stan!: Everyone deserves to be sung at! :^)