Eaglevp: Evening Markus
Ellie Calhoun: Hello!
Eaglevp: Looking forward to hearing all about your trip
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Keith 👋
Eaglevp: Hello Ellie
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Everyone!
Stannex: Dance it out, Markus!
Stannex: Hi, Keith & Ellie!
Eaglevp: Hi Roy
Eaglevp: Evening Stan
Kali : CREATIVE AMPLIFIERS
Kali : 4 THE PEOPLE!!!!!!!
Pierre Kelly: Oh hi
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hello Everyone 😀
Kali : last week was AWESOME and then i came home and had food poisoning bahahaha
Eaglevp: Hi Kali
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Stan and Kali 👋
Eaglevp: Hello Ejnar
Kali : @Ellie Calhoun @Eaglevp hey!! ❤
Ellie Calhoun: My favorite part! 🎶🎶🎶
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello 👋
Eaglevp: Hi@Pierre Kelly
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Keith😀👍
Ellie Calhoun: Ana!!!
Eaglevp: Hi@Ana Zugheri - Faith52
Ellie Calhoun: Oh no Kali! 🤢
Tech Troublemaker: Wait, did Markus go somewhere recently?
Kali : hahahaha @Tech Troublemaker
Eaglevp: Was'nt he with you Roy?
Fishstick USA: Hello all
Eaglevp: Hi@Fishstick USA
Tech Troublemaker: @Kali I thought what happens at EcammCreatorCamp stays at EcammCreatorCamp
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Great music and music video.😀🙏 Love this😀
Kali : @Tech Troublemaker hahahaha oh yeah true 😂
Eaglevp: Liked your live Roy about creator camp
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hey Roy😀 We will see about that 😀
Tech Troublemaker: "And one time at Ecamm Creator Camp..."
Kali : hahahaha
Kali : REPPIN THE SHIRT
Kali : Q did a ghost follow you home
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Can’t wait to hear it all!!!!
Eaglevp: Hope you enjoyed your flight Markus
Tech Troublemaker: Now I want Creator Camp shirts in every color...
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yeih!!!! I pray 🙏 we get to meet in person one day!!! I was so happy 😀 to see y’all together
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: But I was a little jelly 🤪
Kali : @Ana Zugheri - Faith52 !! ❤ ❤
Tech Troublemaker: Let's all meet at VidSummit in Dallas next year...
Pierre Kelly: Guess you're not prone to taking pictures on vacation
Tech Troublemaker: I was so nnnnneeeerrrvvvvooouuusss meeting new people so I forgot to take pictures day 1, better by day three.
Ellie Calhoun: Wow! Quite a process!
Tech Troublemaker: Everyone was so incredible. I did like the smaller group environment. Creators helping creators.
Cheryl Wolf: I am late , hello all
Eaglevp: Hi Cheryl
Cheryl Wolf: Lucky you Markus
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Safe back in Europe and Tipping is no more a problem. Here we give tip to people who really deserve it. 😀👍
Stannex: Can't get enough Kali!
Kali : so much fun!!
Kali : best breakfast burrito ever at that place
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Great picture, Kali😀
Tech Troublemaker: @kali sees the world in technicolor, some of us are stuck at gray scale.
Kali : hahahaha
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Love it
Kali : 😂
Kali : awwwe such great times
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: How fun!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: The fantastic 4!!!!!!!
Cheryl Wolf: sleepy eyes
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Right! What kind of parents did you have that you don’t know to wash your hands after using the bathroom lol 😂
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Ana. How fun can this have been without us?😂😂🤣 Really wanted to be there😀🙏
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: That is why I head…it gets bad when you get back
Stannex: We're a little gross over here in the U.S. ... 🤣
Cheryl Wolf: You forgot to fly my way Markus
Tech Troublemaker: it is so bad I don't touch door knobs in bathrooms. 😛
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: @cslivedk right???
Stannex: For the people!!!!
Cheryl Wolf: Love that Logo
Ellie Calhoun: Great photos!that is awesome!!!
Ellie Calhoun: Fabulous flag!
Pierre Kelly: cool pennant flag
Stannex: LOVE it! Now I want to be a Creative Amplifier, too!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Wait what????? You don’t like slides???? I knew you couldn’t be that perfect!!! I love slides 😂
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: USA 🇺🇸 is a little extra 😂
Tech Troublemaker: The US is a lot of extra compared to the calmness of some countries.
Ellie Calhoun: So great to see you in person!!
Ellie Calhoun: Quack quack!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Party animals lol
Paul Burke: sounds like a great trip!
Eaglevp: Hi @Paul Burke
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Aaaah the duck tour!!!! We have those here in Tx
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Interesting 🤨
Adam Tinkoff: Hey everyone. Loving the recaps.
Eaglevp: Hi Adam
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: No naked statues??? Have you seen spring break??? Lol
Adam Tinkoff: Maybe next year after I sell a few more paintings. 🙂
Ellie Calhoun: Get the travel bug!!!
Cheryl Wolf: I would love to go back to Switzerland
Stannex: Sounds like a GREAT trip! Hopefully next time I can join the fun, too!
Stannex: But I'd LOVE to visit Switzerland, too!
Sara S: Just getting here. I’ll replay.
Eaglevp: Q.So Markus what did you learn from the creator camp?
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Sara
Eaglevp: Hi@Sara S
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I hope I can go too!!!
Adam Tinkoff: What do you think you'll implement first?
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: We can make it European Camp. 😀 You are not that far away from here in Denmark. 😀
Sara S: When did you get home?
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: I have just bought a green screen. Need to learn more about using that. 😀