Mommy Guide Inc: And here we go!
Mommy Guide Inc: Awesome dancing Markus & Stan!
Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sammy!!!!
Kali : heyo!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: 💃 💃
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Kali!!!
Eaglevp: Hi Lala
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Lala!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Sammy!!! Long time!
Eaglevp: Hi Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: Janet my friend:) Hello:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Markus & Stan. party on
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Keith!
Eaglevp: Hello Animal Paradise
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Peeps!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey there Keith
Eaglevp: Hi Tech Troublemaker
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: 💃💃💃💃💃👯👯👯👯👯
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy! The party has just started:)
Win Harwood: Hi all!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Eaglevp
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: Don’t forget to smash the LIKE button friends:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: let's go!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Win!;)
Eaglevp: Hope your all dancing and singing
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Win!!! & Roy!!!
Kali : hey party peeps!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: KALI!!!!
Eaglevp: Hi Kali
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Everyone!
Eaglevp: HimEllie
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing and @Kali
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: :face-red-heart-shape:
Kali : @Eaglevp hey!!
Kali : @Tech Troublemaker hi roy!!
Kali : @Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing JANET!!!! ❤
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: ELLIE!!!
Kali : @Mommy Guide Inc hey lala!! ❤
Kali : @Ellie Calhoun hi!! ❤
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh my that’s epic- the first episode! Lots of fun:)
Ellie Calhoun: hey Janet!!!!!
Kali : wow i just noticed the reaction buttons!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: oh I need to feel alive and on an adventure with yall
Ellie Calhoun: and Kali!!! and Keith and Win and Roy and and and... Everyone!
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed Ellie - yey everyone!!!
Eaglevp: Markus rules the waves
Ellie Calhoun: Markus!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I'm back to the life!! yall are an inspiration. I AM going live tomorrow after 2 months off.
Eaglevp: Hi Sammy
Kali : @Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing yesss!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey!!! That’s awesome Janet!
Kali : STAN IS AWESOME
Kali : #MARKUSRULES
Ellie Calhoun: @Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing yay! Janet!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow for DND - jaw drop!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: You have been an inspiration Kali. Of cousre Markus always makes me remember the importance of showing up. Sometimes we just can't but... here we are. this is a great show
Kali : stan is so insanely talented
Eaglevp: Hi Stan
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi STAN!!!
Ellie Calhoun: hey Stan!
Kali : @Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing ❤ you inspire me every day janet
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Markus & Stan!
Tim Heale 9: Hi Guys
Kali : hey tim!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I so admire people that can draw/paint.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hello 👋
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Ana
Eaglevp: Hello Ana
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Hi Markus😊
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Good to see y’all 🎉
Eaglevp: Hi Ejnar
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana and Ejnar!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Ejnar! so happy to see you
Kali : LOL that's awesome
Kali : LOL
Tim Heale 9: Hi @Kali are you ok after all that time waiting around in the hospital?
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Hi Keith and Lala😊
Kali : @Tim Heale 9 yes! i survived LOL
Kali : @CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming hey ejnar!
Sammy Super Star: its great to see everyone
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Tim!
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow inspiration can come from anywhere, anytime. I wish I can draw.
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Sammy Super Star
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: stick people!
Tech Troublemaker: I make amazing stick people. They almost look like real sticks.
Kali : @Tech Troublemaker bahahahahhaha
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Haha roy
Kali : @CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming always lovely to see you!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: :face-purple-crying:
Kali : love that stan
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL Roy@TechTroublemaker I can so relate. My stick figures are very much unrecognizable
Win Harwood: I got my first bad mark in school in art and that discouraged any drawing in the future.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: That is so sad Win. so wrong
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Thank you 🙏 @Kali 🫠
Kali : i agree 10000% stan
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Don't forget to hit that LIKE button! I did until now. hahaha
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Janet yes liking the livestream
Kali : i remember i loved (and still love) using watercolor with acrylic and my art teachers told me to never do that and that they would take my grade down if i did. so i did it some more
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Those of you that got to take art in school are so lucky. I was a musician so didn't have time and would love loved those courses.
Win Harwood: You were gutsy even then ,Kali!
Mommy Guide Inc: I would have done the same Kali! You are an amazing artist too.:) water color is so so hard.
Kali : @Win Harwood hahahaha! got it from my mama
Kali : @Mommy Guide Inc you're an amazing artist too! You've inspired me to start a scrap book but mine isn't as good as the ones you make at ALL
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Amazing mom!
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: Stan is there an activity that can help one start in drawing better?
Ellie Calhoun: my daughter doodled during classes. her French teacher at first thought it was a problem but then my daughter could actually remember words others didn't, so she decided it was ok
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Good question Lala. 😉
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: too funny. I can picture that
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow Kali! That’s so great! I would love to take a peek:)
Kali : @Ellie Calhoun omg i had that same experience as a student!! drawing helps some of us compute things better!
Sara S: Hey- Hi!
Eaglevp: Hi Sara
Kali : @Sara S hey!!
Win Harwood: @Kali🤗
Mommy Guide Inc: Here’s another awesome artist - hi Sara:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I love a cartoon style. Who Shot Roger Rabbit! or is that animation? sorry. never mind.
Sara S: Hi All👋
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Sara!
Mommy Guide Inc: Have you seen Stan’s channel? All his links are in the description and I have had the honor of watching him draw live with challenges. It’s super nice. If you’re not yet following Stan pls do!:)
Mommy Guide Inc: On YouTube Stan is @Stannex
Ellie Calhoun: that's so cool Stan!
Kali : Q how old were you when you started your career as a professional artist? (sorry if this was answered - i just lost signal and got it back so i missed a bit)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: THanks Lala. I sub'd
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @Kali. never too old. trust me. most great "artists
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: most great artists started after 60 or so
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Janet:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: didn't mean to say most. how about many great 'artists"
Kali : wow awesome
Mommy Guide Inc: Cartooning as the main thing - absolutely Stan!
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh my. Maybe some of the gameboards we love were drawn by you Stan!
Mommy Guide Inc: My son has just started playing DND.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: It’s now full circle Stan. To see you draw live on your livestream is mesmerizing. You make it look so easy.
Ellie Calhoun: both my kids plan DnD
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: oh the life of a freelancer. 😉
Mommy Guide Inc: Awesome Ellie am
Mommy Guide Inc: I am still learning how to play it with my kids.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Tons of books on DND just got released here in the past couple of months and almost
Mommy Guide Inc: Sold out!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: a union shop would not allow that even if we wanted.
Ellie Calhoun: @Mommy Guide Inc I have no interest! 🤣 it was one of the things that kept them busy and not asking me for things!
Sara S: Publishing is hard. I’ve both self-published, licensed to pubs and done contract work since 1979
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed table top gaming isn’t really mainstream. So not too much traction in terms of business. That’s why I never entertain knock offs. There’s abundance of knock offs in my part of the world.
Mommy Guide Inc: Let’s support our awesome artists and companies that support them.:)
Sara S: So true!!!
Sara S: Is it like the old syndicator model?
Mommy Guide Inc: @StannexStan on Youttube
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I'm with you Stan. I never even took a speech class. Ah teaching is what did it for me too. so fun
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow Stan’s awesome talent is endless - a great singer too! Let’s do karaoke 🎤:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yes I love that in Stan’s show. He will have a dice to see what he does next on his drawings. It’s super fun.
Ellie Calhoun: when's your next show?
Mommy Guide Inc: Ellie and everyone here is Stan’s next show https://www.youtube.com/live/p2e7oHlG39k?feature=share
Sara S: I have found it hard to grow my Patreon
Mommy Guide Inc: Let’s support Markus by liking and sharing this awesome livestream. Thank you.
Sara S: You’re such a good mod Lala 😊
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Where is Markus' Buy Me A Coffee???
Sara S: @animal paradise Yes!!
Kali : I WANT A STAN STICKER
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow!!! Stan I would be over the moon to see a caricature of me in my show done by you - a great perk Stan.:) I am joining.
Kali : i will buy one
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Great ideas Stan. I will go to your Patreon for sure
Sara S: Great idea Stan
Mommy Guide Inc: Me too Kali!
Tim Heale 9: Normally men can't multitask 😂
Kali : i'm joining right now
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus I need your BMAC link. We want to send you coffee:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: You go Kali!
Kali : yay!! i'm on your patreon now!! I WANT MY STICKER WOOHOOO LET'S GOOOO!!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: This is good info about how to grow your patreon or buy me a coffee.
Kali : stan's drawings always rule they make my day
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow Kali you are fast!
Kali : yeah i've seen them hahaha love!!
Kali : @Mommy Guide Inc i'm quick! hehehehehe
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: you are funny
Sara S: Stan, how do you make stickers?
Mommy Guide Inc: I will ask Markus for the link and put it down next time - promise!
Kali : i remember that one!! so cute i love it
Ellie Calhoun: love it!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: this is great. I love it
Eaglevp: Amazing Stan
Kali : woah these are awesome!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey it is Luria!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: oh sweet
Kali : is that rod serling
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: oh wow.
Mommy Guide Inc: I have caricatures done during travels and hang them on our walls.:)
Kali : Q what software do you use for your illustrations
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh that would be so much fun! Maybe become a for Members only stream.:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: oh wow. love love love
Sara S: Wow! Die cut
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: what was the name of the company again? or the app
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: thanks
Kali : ah okay
Tim Heale 9: Not sure my by me a coffee works even with the QR code 😂
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: we could have a practice session on someone's channel. right? fun? yes?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: could be a fun membership
Mommy Guide Inc: Janet let’s do that!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: yes!
Mommy Guide Inc: Live drawing with other content creators!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: that's amazing... better than photoshop. wow
Sara S: Is Procreate Adobe?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: it would be fun
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes like we do with crafting Stan! At the end of the show we can submit our drawings on your discord
Sara S: How would you show their work live?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Thanks Stan. and Markus. so good...
Mommy Guide Inc: Then you can showcase them at the end of the show
Sara S: Sorry I came in late
Mommy Guide Inc: Sara I do it via Discord. I pull up the projects on the show from Discord.:) it’s fun
Eaglevp: Great stream Markus shame next weeks will be a let down……lol
Sara S: This is great guys. Thanks
Kali : #MARKUSRULES
Ellie Calhoun: Great Stream! so nice to hear about whaat you do Stan and Markus, always a pleasure!
Mommy Guide Inc: It’s the top of the hour. Oh man. We want more.:)
Sara S: No one is NOT a fan of Markus
Eaglevp: Yes
Kali : @Sara S truth!!!