elle naturally: Hello
Tech Troublemaker: Bring on the dancers and the band.
Rich Vybz: hey markus
Sammy Super Star: Hello!!
elle naturally: Nice lime green back lighting
Eaglevp: Hi@elle naturally
Down To Earth With Katy : Hello friends! we’re on a hol and it’s my birthday tomorrow!
elle naturally: Hi eagle
Eaglevp: Hello Roy and SDammy
Eaglevp: Hi Katy
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Rich Vybz @Sammy Super Star and @Eaglevp
Eaglevp: Hi@Rich Vybz
Rich Vybz: hey roy
Sammy Super Star: You need people dancing
Rich Vybz: hey eaglevp
Sammy Super Star: Hey Rich
Sammy Super Star: You do the fast dancing and then slow it down
Rich Vybz: Sammy twodays in a row! lol
Eaglevp: Happy Birthday Katy for tomorrow hope you have a nice one.
BostonDonMTB: Hi Everyone
Eaglevp: Hi@BostonDonMTB
Eaglevp: Nice song Markus
BostonDonMTB: Hi @Eaglevp
Down To Earth With Katy : It’s nice Markus! Great words
Down To Earth With Katy : Thank you Keith! Thank you Marcus!
Down To Earth With Katy : I will do a dancing video short!
Sammy Super Star: Yes @Rich Vybz
Eaglevp: I am on board
Sammy Super Star: Great new song
BostonDonMTB: Missed your live last week, wasn't the same kind of Thursday without it.
BostonDonMTB: Not allowed. 😜
Eaglevp: How's the walking going ?
Eaglevp: That's great news Markus
Down To Earth With Katy : I’m going to dance
Sammy Super Star: I walk a lot in the spring time and in the fall
Eaglevp: How do you want the footage sent to you Markus
BostonDonMTB: I will be part of it. When do you need the video and how long a clip? We have rain today, but over the weekend it looks good to maybe shoot
Markus Schaub: markus@markusschaub.live
BostonDonMTB: Ok, that is great.
BostonDonMTB: I rode my local trails yesterday and they were still wet. It was difficult on the wet rocks and roots.
BostonDonMTB: @Markus Schaub what are you editing in?
Marielou Mandl: the song is SO GOOD! Hi friends 🙂
BostonDonMTB: @Marielou Mandl
BostonDonMTB: hi
Eaglevp: Hello@Marielou Mandl
Marielou Mandl: Cheering messages! love that
Stan!: New theme song, eh?
Eaglevp: Hi Stan
Stan!: Hi, @Eaglevp
Down To Earth With Katy : This is going to be great Markus
Down To Earth With Katy : Very motivating
Down To Earth With Katy : Because of you I’ve just set up my own Fourthwall website and membership
Down To Earth With Katy : I’m not pouring water over my head though 🤣🤣
Stan!: What a great song!
elle naturally: ✨✨
BostonDonMTB: Now that you have been doing this for a month, do you now crave the walking?
BostonDonMTB: Whoo hoo
BostonDonMTB: Do you have a bike?
BostonDonMTB: You could add that.
elle naturally: I love running but now mostly speed walk
elle naturally: Protecting knees
Stan!: woo hoo! You and Adam are such inspirations!
Run Adam Run: I made it!
Run Adam Run: I will watch the replay.
Run Adam Run: You are definitely looking thinner.
Run Adam Run: I have tons of footage
Eaglevp: Hi Adam congrats on the run
Run Adam Run: Thanks
Run Adam Run: Footage... of foot age. (running humor)
Mommy Guide Inc: Good morning! Hi Marlus! Hi Keith, Stan, Don, Adam, and Sammy
Run Adam Run: Look at that beautiful line. Upwards!
Eaglevp: Hi Lala
Stan!: Editing note: It should be "shoes and clothes" ... 😁
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy, Rich, Elle, Katy,
Stan!: Hi, Lala!
elle naturally: Hey lala
BostonDonMTB: Hi Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yes i will. 7k min.:)
Stan!: Ohhhh ... I see ... it's placeholder text! Got it.
Stan!: Sorry
Mommy Guide Inc: Congratulations to us all.
BostonDonMTB: Send you Google Drive links?
Budgeting Momma: Hi Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Budgeting Momma
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh my have to rewatch on replah