Mommy Guide Inc: Good morning!!!!
Rich Vybz: Good evening Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Markus and Roy! Still walking every other day
elle naturally: hello
BostonDonMTB: Hi all.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Rich!
Rich Vybz: Hi Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Elle and Don
Mommy Guide Inc: How’s everyone’s health journey this da
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hi 👋 I’m here but multitasking too 🤗
Shanna Makes It: Hello, I left the room and came back and you are all here!
elle naturally: Hi @mommy Guide
Shanna Makes It: I’m doing the work out along with you
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello Shanna! It’s a party 🎉
Shanna Makes It: Yes Ana
Tech Troublemaker: hey everyone!
Andrea Nunn: who is the trainer? he looks familiar!
Ellie Calhoun: Hi everyone!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I just got a new set of dumbbells and bands in pretty purple color, believe it or not that has motivated me to move!
elle naturally: I use the free version of Caliber app and do two to three strength trainings a week and follow with 30 minutes of speed walking on the treadmill. I also do one day of 55 minutes of the treadmill.
elle naturally: Resting in between is key
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: That’s wonderful @Elle
elle naturally: It’s been eight weeks consistently doing this and it became easier and easier each week
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I want to get there. I’m starting slowly but I’m really praying for consistency.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Go Markus!!! 💪
elle naturally: You’ve got this
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I also started to try tai chi….now that’s hard, I have so little coordination and balance 😔
Down To Earth With Katy : Woohoo! 🎉🎉
Down To Earth With Katy : Hello friends!
Mommy Guide Inc:
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi everyone. Sorry I’m late. Yay Markus.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I was at PT!
Down To Earth With Katy : Oh, I missed Adam 😢
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana? ThT’s wonderful Elle!
Down To Earth With Katy : Cool exercises!
Mommy Guide Inc: Elle sorry!!! Accidentally deleted your message. Fat fingers issue:(
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Physical therapy
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Walking with a cane now.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: You are amazing
Mommy Guide Inc: Elle if you can kindly reshape your awesome wins
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus is absolutely looking leaner
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Lala!!!!😻😻🥳🥳
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ellie and Shanna!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Andrea!
elle naturally: ✨✨✨
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks friends for being here! Pls don’t forget to smash that LIKE button
BostonDonMTB: Do you have an example of what they sent you?
Down To Earth With Katy : I’ll do it tomoz. Promise!
BostonDonMTB: Ok.
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus is super awesome! And yes pls do share your videos of your awesome health journey as well to help inspire others thru Markus’ future new video
Mommy Guide Inc: Elle yey!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Sorry again for accidentally deleting your awesome message
Down To Earth With Katy : Really nice song again!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Katy and Don:) yes pls do send your awesome video
Mommy Guide Inc: Elle was sending awesome words of encouragement Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: It’s hard when am using the phone. It’s so small. He he he. I think I’ve not lost any weight coz I’ve not changed my eating habits
Mommy Guide Inc: Exercise is good but I think I also have to lessen my snacking
Mommy Guide Inc: But I feel stronger with the walking and great bonding time with my kids