Tech Troublemaker: Now if I could just think vertically.
Eaglevp: HI roy
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Keith!
Ileane Smith: Hi Markus! Hello everyone
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Ileane Smith
Eaglevp: Ileane Smith hello
Stannex: Hey, hey! Hello Markus and Keith and everyone!
Eaglevp: Hi Stan
Ileane Smith: Yes! I went live sharing my vertical live streaming tips 😍
Eaglevp: No not tried vertical live stream yet
Tech Troublemaker: I played around with it. Some of my subscribers fussed because of the bars on the side as they were watching on computer.
Sammy Super Star: Hey Everyone
Stannex: Double Marksu! What a great day it is!
Eaglevp: Hi Sammy
Eaglevp: double the views Markus
Ellie Calhoun: Hello! Late but here!
Eaglevp: Hi Ellie
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Keith and everyone!
Stannex: Hi, ellie!
Eaglevp: I watched all the live last week Markus
Eaglevp: You where very steady filming last weeks live.
Ileane Smith: Have you ever seen lives in the SHORTS feed?
Eaglevp: Will have to take a look at that
Ileane Smith: Great guests to look forward too
Ellie Calhoun: good to see you!
Ileane Smith: Bye for now!
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Enjoyed it.
Eaglevp: Hi@Fishstick ~ Phillip