Pierre Kelly: Afternoon guys!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Lala Hey Pierre!
Mommy Guide Inc: Good day everyone!
Mariane Cresp: Hello all!
Eaglevp: Evening Markus
Eaglevp: Hi Lala
Eaglevp: Hello@Mariane Cresp
Eaglevp: Hi Roy
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy:) Hi Mariane hope you’re feeling better sis.
Stannex: Hi, everyone!
Mariane Cresp: Hi Keith!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Keith and Stan!
Eaglevp: Hi@Pierre Kelly
Mariane Cresp: Much better thank you @Mommy Guide Inc
Stannex: Hi @Mommy Guide Inc
Stannex: Hi @Eaglevp
Eaglevp: Hi Stan
Stannex: Hi @Mariane Cresp
Mommy Guide Inc: That’s great looking forward to seeing Markus guest on Marianne’s channel;)
Mariane Cresp: Stan! Hello 🖐
Stannex: And, of course, hi @Markus Schaub
Mommy Guide Inc: Happy New Year everyone! Wasn’t able to join the NY episode last week. Sorry.
Eaglevp: Happy New year all
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey!!!
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Happy New Year, Markus!
Eaglevp: Hello Phillip
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Philip!
Mommy Guide Inc: Let’s Go! And Streamers Life - printed on the merch
Mommy Guide Inc: I am on spreadshop but this looks nicer!
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Q: Markus, Is the worldwide or just Switzerland or maybe Europe?
Mommy Guide Inc: Great question Philip.:)
Motif Music Studios: You are TAKING ACTION! Woohoo!
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus what’s the link?
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: merch store link?
Eaglevp: Hello@Motif Music Studios
Motif Music Studios: @Eaglevp hello! Hope you are easing into your new year gently!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Amy!
Tech Troublemaker: Love Fourthwall! But I am also thinking of doing Etsy/Printify for some specific special items
Mommy Guide Inc: Ok Markus! Excited much.:)
Stannex: I missed the part where you said what site this is.
Tim Heale 9: Happy New Year everyone
Fishstick ~ Phillip: C:i
Eaglevp: hI tIM
Mommy Guide Inc: I like the first one. Kinda unique that the “?l is ahead to make it a block
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Tim!
Tech Troublemaker: Hit that LIKE Button Y'all!
Fishstick ~ Phillip: It inspired me to get started
Mommy Guide Inc: Awww that’s right Philip. It indeed is very inspiring right?
Pierre Kelly: A t shirt
Pierre Kelly: A hat
Pierre Kelly: a blue one
Mommy Guide Inc: Stan’s caricature - with Not? ready Let’s Go! on a shirt
Mariane Cresp: don't forget to tick transparent backfgroun in canva
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh can we remove the background on Canva first?
Mariane Cresp: it'll work
Stannex: We can work with it, Markus ... I'll send you a file with a transparent background.
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh thanks Mariane - transparent background
Mariane Cresp: ok, try magic grab
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey thanks Stan! You’re the best!
Stannex: Yeah ... save that one for another day. ;^)
Mommy Guide Inc: Stan by the way goes live later.:(
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Stan! Stan by the way goes live later:)
Mariane Cresp: LOL .. Stan can save the day!
Mommy Guide Inc: Random Encounters show later for Stan - https://www.youtube.com/live/wtWyTwCJINI?si=f4zxuYMd1v2X9993
Mariane Cresp: Can you have something different at the back from the front? At the back you can have Go! Go! Go! ... or something like that
Stannex: Thank you, Lala!
Mommy Guide Inc: See you later Stan!
Ellie Calhoun: Here! A little late - Happy New Year to everyone!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ellie!
Eaglevp: hELLO eLLIE
Eaglevp: Hello Ellie
Mommy Guide Inc: Friends thanks for being here please don’t forget to smash the LIKE button.:)
Stannex: Hi @Ellie Calhoun
Stannex: Like, like, like ... ❤❤❤
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey thanks Stan for the LIKE:)
Stannex: Go swimming with Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks everyone!
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh a cap! This year I need to start a collection - a merch from you all.:)
Stannex: We should do an inversed version of your caricature on the front of the cap ... and "Not Ready? Go!" on the back!
Mommy Guide Inc: Stan maybe you can make a special episode where in the dice instead of the usual characters - you can put creators?
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey - you did it Markus!
Motif Music Studios: amazing!
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Markus. 😀
Eaglevp: Hi Ejnar
Mommy Guide Inc: The shipping for me is about the same as the product’s price! He he he. I’ll order and send to Victor’s. Need to ask him first his details. Maybe cheaper shipping if to the US
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ejnar
Mommy Guide Inc: Coz Victor coming over in Feb
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Eaglevp😀
Mommy Guide Inc: But no matter what - I will have that mug and shirt!
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: How’s the vacation Ejnar? Hope you’re having fun.
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus you did it!!! What a great start of the year!!!
Andrea Nunn: late to the merch party!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Andrea! Markus has merch now!
Eaglevp: Hi@Andrea Nunn