Eaglevp: Evening Markus
Coach Adam: Today is Stan's birthday!
Eaglevp: Hi Adam and Phillip
CSLiveDK : Hello everyone. Hi Markus. Wonderful to see you back on track😀🙏
Eaglevp: Evening Ejnar
CSLiveDK : Good evening, Keith😀
Coach Adam: If you are up for it, I'd love to hear more about your experience at Creator Camp. How was it compared to other years? What (or who) inspired you most? What's your biggest take away?
CSLiveDK : Maybe you will be the next on Spotify. Who knows?😀
Fishstick USA (Phillip): I can relate. Many ideas. Removing obstacles to make video production easier. Then I realize that I am the obstacle. I do not need motivation. I need to just do it.
Fishstick USA (Phillip): I think like you. I need to just do it. I know I will have fun. I enjoy videos.
elle naturally: Hiii
Coach Adam: I appreciate how you bring your humanity (vs AI) back to YouTube. I look forward to watching your future videos. Make is so! (or give me some push-ups)
Eaglevp: Hi Ellie
elle naturally: Hi Eagle
elle naturally: Happy to see you all again
Neil Farrimond: Hey Markus!
Eaglevp: Hi Neil
Neil Farrimond: Hey @Eaglevp - how are you doing?
CSLiveDK : Maybe there is an idea in blowing life in the Zoom part of your show, mix it with talking live with people who are here. You did it before and that was really fun. 😀🙏
Eaglevp: Okay Neil
Neil Farrimond: Going Live and setting to unlisted in YouTube is a good way to get over the "Live" fear - just to help with the process of it all.
Coach Adam: With patience and persistence, anything is possible.
Coach Adam: I would recommend starting with your friends to have them talk about anything they are stuck with... then ask them to invite someone.
Fishstick USA (Phillip): I like Enjar’s idea of a chat
Markus Schaub: markusschaub.live/mail
Markus Schaub: www.markusschaub.live/mail
CSLiveDK : I’m also a kind of stuck. Even though I am live producer for someone else I miss to get back on my own also. 😀
CSLiveDK : Thanks @Fishstick😀
Coach Adam: Markus, as your friend I would always make myself available if you need a guest. I just need an invite.
Coach Adam: Well, I was just laid off from a 23 year career and have no idea what's next.
Eaglevp: Same here always love coming on your live streams Markus
CSLiveDK : I am ready for that challenge😀 Our advantage is that we are in the same time zone. 😀
Eaglevp: Yes would talk about anything
Coach Adam: It's all about the reps. Just get it going and the rest will fall into place.
Eaglevp: Can you stream earlier Markus
elle naturally: This is good or anytime in the afternoon too
Eaglevp: j ust thought we could try an earlier time to see if that would get more people in
Fishstick USA (Phillip): It is 4 PM here. I am good with any time you choose.
Coach Adam: It's 1:37pm here
Coach Adam: Here being San Diego.
Coach Adam: I'm not wearing pants... but yes it's still warm.
Coach Adam: How is the weather in Switzerland? Is it cold now? Any snow?
Coach Adam: I'll be sure to pack pants if I go.
Eaglevp: Markus did you ever run around the lake?
Eaglevp: Will have to come over next year and do a live in person
elle naturally: I’m hoping to hike through the Dolomites. Have you done this yet?
Coach Adam: Great LIVE, Markus. Well done brother. Keep it going.
Eaglevp: Great stream bye all
elle naturally: See you soon!!!