elle naturally: Hi there Markus
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Hello, hello!!!
CSLiveDK : Hi Markus😀 So good to see you back🙏👍
Stan!: Hello, Markus ... and everyone!
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Hi @CSLiveDK , Welcome Stan
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: @elle naturally so glad you are able to join us!
Stan!: My pleasure
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Stan you are so talented!
elle naturally: Hi Ana
Stan!: :😊:
CSLiveDK : Hi @Ana😀
Stan!: It's like anything else ... it takes time and practice
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Markus fam/fan club
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Markus!!!
Stan!: The key is to have fun while you're practicing. Enjoy making fun stuff and don't worry about making "good" stuff
Fishstick USA: Uphill is tough but it will become easier
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Fun! yes, that is the key...you start dreading doing something when it becomes a chore...but the thing is that chores can also be fun 😊
Stan!: Truth @Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra
CSLiveDK : I am right now producing a show for a Dane living in Spain every Tuesday evening. Educating people in how to use Zoom as stand alone and together with Ecamm. I also want to teach people to use Ecamm😀
elle naturally: I’m at 11k steps a day up from 10k. I speed walk mostly and it does wear on the toes. I can’t stop once I start though.
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: One thing that has helped me, is gratitude, when I shift my way of thinking from what I have to do, to what I get to do, I become motivated.
elle naturally: ☺️☺️
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Yeih! @elle naturally I still have to put in my steps today, good reminder.
elle naturally: 🫶🏽
elle naturally: Hahha
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: I got an office treadmill, so I do them while I work or before bed
CSLiveDK : I also hope to find time to make something in English again. Sometimes really miss the fun LEDA days😀 I hope to start af 5 hour job five days a week training AI I Danish language. Have many plans. 👍
Fishstick USA: How is the weather in Switzerland? Make a video of you sitting outside. Show us something interesting from your neighborhood or city. Share a video of a short walk.
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: I was scared that walking at night would keep me from sleeping, but I give myself an hour in between and it works really well for me.
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: The places you have taken us, are wonderful! I hope you can share some more soon.
Pierre Kelly: good afternoon everybody
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: 50 is such a great age. We must celebrate.
elle naturally: Hello Pierre
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: I think Im finally to pick up a rhythm to create content, my goal is to release a video once a week and have some shorts in between.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: just wait... I have 2 more of those "0" years on you!!! yikes!!! but we have to celebrate
Pierre Kelly: approaching 50 is a good milestone, isnt it?
CSLiveDK : Good evening from Denmark, @Pierre. I am in the same time zone as Markus😉
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Fifty and fabulous!!! I was so scared and freaked out about it but now that I've been in the 50's for a whole month I can testify...It really is a time to be fabulous!
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Yes! it kind of is a waking up moment, specially to do a good inventory of where you are as far as your health and where you want to get
CSLiveDK : I am close to 62. A little scary. Hope to get much more years, now everything is getting more fun😀 Do things more important that work😀
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Yep! let's party!!!! 50s theme party.
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: lol I tell my husband that if I had the body I had at 20 and the wisdom I have now...I could totally be Ms. Universe lol
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: hey markus welcome back - long time no see
Pierre Kelly: where did you go Eric?
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: i was always here @Pierre Kelly - do crazy business stuff and more crazy youtube stuff 😛
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Because everything you give, it comes back, my friend!
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: yes crazyness is like peper and salt in food 😛
Neil Farrimond: Hey Markus!
Pierre Kelly: mommy guide is absent
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: You showed up and that counts! Don't forget to like
Stan!: Showing up is always the first step
Stuart Video -Tech Installations: Hey hey!
Enda Trading: Hello from Ireland
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: There is so much material out there to talk about.
CSLiveDK : Change to use zoom with Ecamm and then we all can interact shown on YouTube. You did something like that in the good old streaming days😀👍
Enda Trading: Talk with other European Creators, many US creators on Ecamm, not sure about Europe
Neil Farrimond: Q: Have you been playing with any new software or hardware?
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: @CSLiveDK yes thats fun this discussion group on zoom
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: there are many ecamm user from europe
Neil Farrimond: Yes we lost power for 13 hours - no cell service also. Quite scary considering the hole country went offline!
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: yess affinity suite is the best !! us it since 2020
Enda Trading: Interview your Girlfriend hehe
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Wow! that sounds scary @Neil Farrimond
Enda Trading: Streamyard
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: I use streamyard because I am a windows user too
Neil Farrimond: @Enda Trading try Meld Studio also 🙂
Pierre Kelly: get Paul Burke on the show
CSLiveDK : vMix
Enda Trading: Thanks Neil, Ill have a look
Enda Trading: Matt Haas?
Neil Farrimond: Yes I made a video on Meld Studio - over on my channel. Also had the CEO on the Live show. Good software.
Enda Trading: And that fun girl from LSP
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Yes, I used to get so wrapt up on the tech that my content was being compromised. Now I focus on the content and ease of use of tech.
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: yes, video (VOD) recording is easier - i have a list of over 300 video ideas - but they're not really good for livestreaming
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Those were the days...so many fun and lovely people!
Stuart Video -Tech Installations: Vmix for PC!
CSLiveDK : Matt Haas look for people who would like to interview him on their channel. May be we can interview each other and row our channels that way😀👍
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: You need to do some social media platform reviews
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: What software goes with what?
Enda Trading: There are also website where you can connect with people that want to be interviewed
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: haha i learned that nothing is perfect - i also 🙂 thats why my video are not perfect 😛
Stan!: Sometimes that's the best way ... it's like "treading water" while you prepare to continue swimming
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: I am a facebook user, but it seems that IG and TikTok are some where I need to put my content too...Im just like, ugh! I don't want to but maybe I need to.
Stan!: It's better than "getting out of the pool"
Enda Trading: The channel is about you, and your personality, YouTube channel doesnt need a theme, YouTube treats everything video by video
Enda Trading: If not a business
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: @Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra use meta business suite - you cn schedule and crossposting fb and insta
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: @Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra use meta business suite - there you can schendule and crossposting fb and inst
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: True! I do think that my targeted audience is mainly on Fb and IG...@Eric Maechler - Online Marketing I do, do that but I wonder if I should create the videos in IG so it's not the same content
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: @Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra if you have the same audience - yes that would be good. but otherwise its a detail. invest the time in your content 😛
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Thank you, ya'll are awesome.
Stan!: Thank you, Markus! Always good to see you!
elle naturally: Thanks Markus
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Take care everyone! Thank you, Markus.
CSLiveDK : Fun hour. Good you are back🙏
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: bye bye