elle naturally: Hi just on an outdoor long walk after work and saw your live!!
Eaglevp: Evening Markus
Eaglevp: Hi Ellie
elle naturally: Hiii Eagle
Eaglevp: Fine thanks mate
Tech Troublemaker: @Markus Schaub It's you!
Eaglevp: Hi Roy
CSLiveDK : Hi Markus. Finally catch your live again😀👍
Tech Troublemaker: Keith!
Eaglevp: Enjoyed your creator camp review Roy
Eaglevp: Hi Ejnar
Ravens Talk With Yolanda: Hello everyone!
Eaglevp: Hello@Ravens Talk With Yolanda
Eaglevp: Really looking forward to see you both progress Markus and Roy
CSLiveDK : Hi Keith 😀👋
Tech Troublemaker: Me too Keith, me too. 🙂
Eaglevp: Wow business class and all the perks that go with that
Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
Eaglevp: Hope you get to the 1k before Christmas Roy,I think you will after what you learnt at creator camp
Eaglevp: Hi Sammy
Mariane Cresp: Hello 👋🏼 Markus
CSLiveDK : Hi Sammy😀
Eaglevp: Hey@Mariane Cresp
Ellie Calhoun: Hi everyone!
Mariane Cresp: Hi 👋🏼 Keith!
Eaglevp: What films did you watch on the flight Markus?
Sammy Super Star: Next year I will try and make it
elle naturally: Mile two,.. walking speedily still
Stan!: Coooo!
Eaglevp: Hi Stan
Stan!: Hi, Keith!
elle naturally: Will you do some more lives whilst you walk?
Neil Farrimond: Markus!
Coach Adam Runs: Markus! I'm late
Neil Farrimond: Hey sorry I am late
Coach Adam Runs: but I'm here now
Neil Farrimond: Hahahaha
Eaglevp: Hey Neil
Neil Farrimond: Hey Keith!
Eaglevp: Hello Adam
Coach Adam Runs: I'm pulling together your exercise routine as we speak
Coach Adam Runs: Of course, of course - we will talk through all of that.
Coach Adam Runs: Same time tomorrow will work well for me too.
Coach Adam Runs: 1pm PST/4pm EST/10pm GMT+2
Sammy Super Star: don't quit!!
elle naturally: Mile three 5km no quitting
Coach Adam Runs: Can you share about what cameras you preferred using. Was that the DJI Pocket 3?
elle naturally: You’re my motivation
Coach Adam Runs: You might need a gimbal for your gimbal camera. LOL
Coach Adam Runs: 360 cameras are amazing, but require far more time and work to reframe for the edit.
Coach Adam Runs: Super cool. Thanks for sharing the details.
Coach Adam Runs: Wow - they dug up the shopping mall and put in all those wonderful trees. Wonderful
Coach Adam Runs: lol. You can't outrun the machine!
Coach Adam Runs: Are you now energized to make tons of new content or are you exhausted - or a bit of both?
Coach Adam Runs: How long was your flight?
Coach Adam Runs: Did you watch some good movies? I bet the food was delicious on the plane. LOL
BostonDonMTB: Hey Markus, Lala
BostonDonMTB: ooops no Lala today.
Eaglevp: Hi BostonDomMTB
BostonDonMTB: Hi @Eaglevp
Eaglevp: Now to the Importance part of the live Markus
Coach Adam Runs: Did anything surprise you? Something you learned that you did not expect?
BostonDonMTB: It can inspire you and get you thinking of what is possible without even knowing.
Neil Farrimond: Notion
Neil Farrimond: Or Apple Notes
BostonDonMTB: Using your phone.
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: hello and welcome back in switzerland:P
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: i love obisidan for my notice
BostonDonMTB: What caused you to miss weeks?
BostonDonMTB: Is it fixable?
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: i am ä zettelimaster / master of notes
Ketia Francis-Johnson: Hi Markus!
Neil Farrimond: Careful now.... hahaha hey Ketia!
Ketia Francis-Johnson: 🤣🤣🤣
Eaglevp: Hello@Ketia Francis-Johnson
Ketia Francis-Johnson: Hi Neil!
Ketia Francis-Johnson: He's playing it safe Neil!
David W. Ryan: Hi Markus and friends
Eaglevp: Hi@David W. Ryan
Neil Farrimond: Get some rest my friend and it was wonderful to see you again at Camp!
Coach Adam Runs: I will see you tomorrow!
BostonDonMTB: Whoo hoo 22 lb club