Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: 👋
Stan!: Markus! You're looking amazing!
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: I’m in carline but here! 🤗
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Yes, thank God temperature is going down over here.
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: It sounds like a big adventure!!! Driving on the other side would be very challenging for me
Pierre Kelly: Cyprus feels like a fall holiday
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: lol 😂 concentrate!!!! Me???? Squirrels 🐿️!!!
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Unacceptable!!! lol
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: I’m so glad you got to enjoy your time there! Even great live streamers like you…need a little holiday! 😊
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Nice!
Stan!: oooo ... Nice pool area!
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Wow!!!
Stan!: How loud is that little drone?
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Look at that beautiful water!!!!
Stan!: Seems like you had a great time!
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Funny thing….im in cypress right now lol 😂 the area where I’m right now in Houston is called cypress 😊
Pierre Kelly: really ana?
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Yep lol
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: No no passport required but not as beautiful as your Cyprus
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: So sad 😞 full of history I’m sure
elle naturally: Hello all
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: How far is from you?
elle naturally: Health goals!!
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: have fun
Stan!: Woo hoo! Wish I could go to Boston and join you! But I'm going to be at a game convention in Wisconsin.
Stan!: WOW ... Big selfie stick!
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: dont get arrested 😛 with this weapons
elle naturally: I’m in a forest part of new england and the leaves are just changing in Massachusetts. I hope you have the chance to see some foliage.
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: dont worry nobody will miss you #nostream 👻
Pierre Kelly: there's a Patriots game this Sunday when you get there
Stan!: If it's peak leaf-turning season, you're going to be blown away.
John Ong: Hello Markus. Looking forward to meeting you.
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: teams?
John Ong: Orange and Blue are complimentary colors! LOL.
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: soso
John Ong: Do you get jetlag?
John Ong: Which hotel are you in?
John Ong: I'm originally from Malaysia. Singapore's neighbor. Where you can get food anytime in the night!
John Ong: Same hotel as me.
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: thats "shitty" planing my friend 😛
Fishstick USA: Hello
Ravens Talk With Yolanda: Hi Markus. I’m looking forward to meeting you at Creator Camp!
John Ong: Hi Yolanda. Looking forward to meet you too!
Stan!: Bon voyage, Markus!
Stan!: Have fun!
Ravens Talk With Yolanda: Hi John! Likewise!!
Pierre Kelly: save travels!
Ravens Talk With Yolanda: Team Purple!
Pierre Kelly: team titans!!!
Ravens Talk With Yolanda: 🙂