Mommy Guide Inc: awww big virtual hugs Keith.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Adam:)
Pierre Kelly: Afternoon all
Neil Farrimond: Hey Markus
Markus Schaub: https://us02web.zoom.us/j/86508597509?pwd=xE0uXdnkCCSWsbaTbNNMKEuwX7bhTa.1
Eaglevp: Hey @Pierre Kelly
Mommy Guide Inc: And Markus is back in his studio today:)
Eaglevp: Hello Neil
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Pierre and Neil:)
Eaglevp: You have an echo Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: Hmmm I didn't hear an echo.
Neil Farrimond: No each at all from my side
Markus Schaub: https://us02web.zoom.us/j/87155541007?pwd=6WiEnbQGBk1Z9GqDizymHIyTIYoMuQ.1
Eaglevp: It's ok now
Mommy Guide Inc: Sorry I can't join zoom coz am still in bed and the kids are with me:(
Eaglevp: I was getting feed back on my TV
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL yes I am awake absolutely but watching Markus in the big TV from bed. Best vantage point:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Friends join Markus on Zoom and let's check out live the Ecamm from Zoom integration - now absolutely out for everyone. No longer on beta.
CSLiveDK : Hello Everyone😀
Neil Farrimond: I can join if you want - give me 5 🙂
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ejnar:) yen thanks Neil:)
Cheryl Wolf: Hello , I am in the waiting room
Neil Farrimond: I am joining now
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Cheryl:) Yey Cheryl and Neil in the waiting room:)
Cheryl Wolf: hey lalal hello
Eaglevp: Hi@Cheryl Wolf
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks friends for joining Markus today - please don't forget to smash the LIKE button:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey I see Cheryl!, Neil and Keith!
Mommy Guide Inc: So, Cheryl, Keith and Neil are all coming in from Zoom right Markus?
Mommy Guide Inc: You can check out our friends channel as well - Neil https://www.youtube.com/@NeilFarrimond/videos
Mommy Guide Inc: Keith's channel - https://www.youtube.com/@eaglevp
Mommy Guide Inc: Cheryl's all about wellness - https://www.cherylwolfwellness.com/
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Keith, Cheryl and Neil for joining Markus show the awesome Ecamm From Zoom integration:)
Images by Gretchen: Hi Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: Can one of the guests share screen? How will that look coming from zoom?
Images by Gretchen: Hey Cheryl !!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Gretchen!!!
Images by Gretchen: Hi LaLa!
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL
Images by Gretchen: I finally have internet back!! yea! Great to be on computr rather than phone cell
Mommy Guide Inc: oh yes - Its June 7 - 1 long form video and 6 shorts:)
Mommy Guide Inc: I want daily long form. As usual, the editing is hard:(
Mommy Guide Inc: I am going back to my Conversations with Lala starting this week. My interview segment:) Hope to have you all there as guest soon:)
Mommy Guide Inc: oh yes, burn out is real. So we do need to take breaks. Absolutely:)
Mommy Guide Inc: oh my. sorry to hear that Keith:(
Images by Gretchen: i"ve been on the road for a month so I took a break from my show. Got back last Sat. ready to get back at it & the internet was OUT. So now it's fixed I"m excited to get back to live schedule tonight!
Images by Gretchen: Needed more time:)
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Sitting here watching and listening closely. Enjoying this. I want to say hello to all.
Mommy Guide Inc: thanks Neil!
Images by Gretchen: Cheryl. that new moon is giving us the lowest tide of the year so far today! so fun
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes you all look and sound great. Yes now guests will not find it difficult to come in:)
Mommy Guide Inc: coz almost everyone knows how to do zoom:)
Images by Gretchen: I went down to the beach earlier and did a YT live from my phone to show how low it was. Sunny day at the beach in the Pacific Northwest can be a rare thing .
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: all of zoom's functionality will be ok on the Ecamm integration?
Mommy Guide Inc: thanks Cheryl it was so great to hear from you:)
Mommy Guide Inc: yes I caught it Keith!
Mommy Guide Inc: was able to hear about 5 or more songs
Mommy Guide Inc: it was on FB live:)
Mommy Guide Inc: On Katy's FB:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes I agree - Markus vlogs and editing is so much fun:)
CSLiveDK : Maybe more casual streams is the way forward. I think I sometimes plan it too much. 😀
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes I agree Ejnar:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Keith and Markus!
CSLiveDK : Thank you 🙏 for a good stream. 😀
Mommy Guide Inc: Cheering you on Keith:)
Images by Gretchen: 👋. thanks !
Mommy Guide Inc: Have a great weekend my friends:)