Mommy Guide Inc: And here we go. Good day everyone!
Mommy Guide Inc: Let’s Go!
Kali : multitasking but wanted to have this on so i can see this new thumbnail! hi @Mommy Guide Inc @eaglevp and of course #MARKUSRULES
Kali : 💃 🪩 💃 🪩
Kali : this theme song gets better and better
Kali : ❤
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: dancing course? 😛 auneiiiiiiii
Mommy Guide Inc: Just like wine right Kali? Just gets better with age.:)
Mariane Cresp: Hello Markus and all!
Kali : @Mariane Cresp hey!
Kali : @Mommy Guide Inc hahaha yes!!! exactly!!
Mariane Cresp: Hi @Kali
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Eric!
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: hi @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Mariane!
Mariane Cresp: Lala, hello!
Eaglevp: Hi Kali
Kali : @Eaglevp hey 🤗
Kali : #MARKUSRULES
Eaglevp: Hey @Mariane Cresp
Mariane Cresp: Hi Keith!
Eaglevp: Hello@Eric Maechler - Online Marketing
Kali : multitasking monster!
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: hi @Eaglevp
Fishstick USA: Hello Markus
Eaglevp: Hi@Fishstick USA
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Pholip@FishStickUSA
Eaglevp: I am useless at thumbnails
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: me too - rofl @Eaglevp
Eaglevp: So I am hoping I am going to learn tonight@Eric Maechler - Online Marketing
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: total pervers 😛
Mommy Guide Inc: I can make
Eaglevp: Wow that's great work Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: I can make thumbnails but not very impactful.
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: it is 2023 - everyone is crezy as f*** - sry
Mariane Cresp: have you tried using AI to get ideas on what to put in the thumbnail?
Mommy Guide Inc: Canva! Great suggestion Mariane. Havent used AI specifically for thumbnails making
Mariane Cresp: I use Magic Write in Canva and that's how I get the ball rolling with what elements to put in
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello 👋 from carline
Eaglevp: Hi@Ana Zugheri - Faith52
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana! Are you back home? Loved your family vacay posts.:)
Pierre Kelly: hello all
Eaglevp: Hello@Pierre Kelly
Kali : i feel like you should make the first three (counting from the left) bigger to take up the whole rectangle, then put a face picture of you pointing or looking shocked and white outline around you
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Pierre Kelly welcome!
Kali : what will that stream be about? sorry i missed that part D:
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yep! Back at it 🤗 thanks it was so much fun what I needed to get back into the busyness. I love your traveling videos to you doing great.
Kali : oh yeah you could use her instead of the blonde girl
Pierre Kelly: @Kali making a thumbnail
Kali : use her instead of the blonde girl
Kali : ah okay that's what i thought!
Kali : tiktok live has been WILD
Kali : is it possible to make them larger so they take up the whole rectangle?
Kali : very true
Kali : @Pierre Kelly 😂
Kali : yaaasssss
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: the swiss tiktok livestream scene is completely crazy - they all hate each other and call each other names. first thought it was a show but they are total enemies. pretty amusing
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: i like the usa crowd more 😛 more normal
Kali : tweak em so they're even
Kali : you don't have to do the things i'm saying though 😂 sorry i'm not trying to take control!
Kali : i realized i'm like "do this and do that and what about htis?" 😂
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: possible #rofl
Mommy Guide Inc: It’s ok Kali. We like reading your suggestions.:)
Kali : @Mommy Guide Inc ❤ ❤ 🤗 bawww ty ty
Mommy Guide Inc: Odd numbered elements thus look nicer.:)
Kali : you don't have to have your face on this. it might be overwhelming
Kali : LOL "i watch tiktok live so you don't have to" haha
Kali : i think the thumbnail should have something like "what's happening?!" like a shock text
Kali : and the title something like what's happening on (or with) tiktok live??
Kali : you have to talk about the NPC ones and the weird sleeping/dance prompt ones 😂 although those sleeping/dance promtps ones i am pretty sure they are being forced to do and it is sad
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: "why tiktok threatens your sanity" titel idea 😛
Kali : i block all the npc ones when they come up on my fyp
Kali : @Eric Maechler - Online Marketing 😂
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: a smartphone in your freezer - that would be a greath thumbnail
Kali : the "what's happening" can just be big (white with black outline) across the thumbnail on the bottom
Kali : (if you wanted to write "what's happening?!")
Kali : or maybe "is tiktok okay??" with the title of what's happening on tiktok live etc
Kali : do this: ?!
Kali : if it's a question
Mommy Guide Inc: Was watching Derral awhile ago on Nick Nimmin’s ahow and he mentioned about having 6 people create thumbnails - thats how impt it is. Never reallg put that much importance on my thumbnails.
Kali : @Mommy Guide Inc sometimes i think putting THAT much into thumbnails is just bs to make people think they need to join their program
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: Are questions better as titles?
Kali : thumbnails are important, sure, but 6 people working on it? that's just ridiculous imo
Kali : oh sorry i meant each letter having a black outline
Mommy Guide Inc: I was shocked as well Kali.:)
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: i need max 10-15min for my thumbnails and then it's done
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hello Everyone😀👍
Kali : @CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream hey ejnar!
Eaglevp: Hello Ejnar
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hi Ejnar 👋
Mommy Guide Inc: That’s fast Eric. Awesome:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ejnar:)
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Thank you Markus😀👍
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Nice to see all the great people here😀👍🙏
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Q So do you think is vital to have your logo/name/photo on thumbnail?
Kali : @Sammy Kravitz hey sammy!
Kali : @Ana Zugheri - Faith52 definitely not imo
Eaglevp: Hello@Sammy Kravitz
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: U r famous!!!!
Kali : in fact, i think people adding their logos to their thumbnail is harmful
Sammy Kravitz: I haven't made a thumbanil in a bir
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sammy!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Mmmm..i need to te evaluate mine. Great info!
Kali : i don't like the alternating look for this. it would either have to be in the same square, or black text with white outline (per letter, not a box)
Kali : do ?! instead of only ?
Kali : what's happening?!
Kali : 😂 i'm a multitasking monster!
Sammy Super Star: that I never use
Sammy Super Star: didn't know that I never use that account
Eaglevp: Hi@Sammy Super Star
Kali : can you put the live in the upper right? just to see what it looks like
Sammy Super Star: Hey @Eaglevp
Mariane Cresp: you can also make the space between the lines a bit closer using "spacing" button at the top - if you want
Mommy Guide Inc: W: Is it better to use all caps?
Sammy Super Star: I'm working on a new re brand maybe so I will be making more thumbnails
Budgeting Momma: Hi everyone
Kali : @Mommy Guide Inc i think it depends on context but usually yes
Kali : @Budgeting Momma hey!
Mommy Guide Inc: Why W? I meant Q: he he he
Kali : @Sammy Kravitz a rebrand?!
Kali : can you move the "live" to the upper right to see what it would look like? 👀
Budgeting Momma: Hi Kali
Sammy Super Star: No that isn't @Kali
Mommy Guide Inc: Thats awesome Sammy. Excited for the rebrand. Thnks Kali!
Sammy Super Star: That isn't wasn't the wrong account. @Kali Going to be doing more short films
Kali : that's okay that it's over the hat
Kali : @Sammy Super Star 😲 😲 omg yesssss!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Budgeting Momma.:)
Kali : hmmmm the live stands out more in the upper right and isn't covered by the timestamp
Sammy Super Star: Only short films, going to do it more like weekly
Kali : yeah do that one
Budgeting Momma: Hi @Mommy guide inc
Mommy Guide Inc: Friends don’y forget to smash the LIKE button on this livestream.:)
Ellie Calhoun: Hello 👋
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: 👋
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Rllie!
Mariane Cresp: Hello Irene @Budgeting Momma
Crazy Sexy Menopause: Hi Everyone!!!
Mariane Cresp: Hello Bette
Cheryl Wolf: HI everyone
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: hi everyone. I'm late but I brought Reiki cookies!
Kali : @Cheryl Wolf @Crazy Sexy Menopause @Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing hey!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ellie! I need to find my eyeglasses. Cant spell right. Keep hitting the wrong letters. He he he
Ellie Calhoun: How's it been going? Sorry to be late!
Kali : yay!! love the thumbnail! looks great
Cheryl Wolf: Hey Kali
Eaglevp: Hello@Cheryl Wolf
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Kali
Kali : @Ellie Calhoun hey!!
Kali : the gang is all here!
Mommy Guide Inc: Janet!!! Howdy my friend.:)
Mariane Cresp: Looks good Markus
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Lala!!! welcome back
Eaglevp: Hello@Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Cheryl.:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: everyone is here. love you all
Kali : ❤ ❤
Ellie Calhoun: Will watch the replay 😊
Crazy Sexy Menopause: The gang’s all here! 😃
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I'm watching the replay too.
Kali : i think the white makes it pop and look less busy
Cheryl Wolf: yes !
Kali : i'd keep the white and black tbh
Eaglevp: Hi Ellie
Sammy Super Star: White I like it
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: Are there certain elements that should always be present in a thumbnail?;)
Kali : @Mommy Guide Inc text!
Kali : keep the white and black like how you had it i promise you
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: It’s a party 🎉 love seeing all of you here!!!!🥳🥳🥳🥳🥳
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Listen to Kali the artist and graphics person
Kali : it pops out with the black and white from before
Mariane Cresp: I agree with Kali ... the white and black was good against the busy photos
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Kali. Text indeed.:)
Kali : ya!!!
Kali : this is fun with thumbnails
Cheryl Wolf: true kali
Budgeting Momma: Looks good
Crazy Sexy Menopause: I agree that looks much better
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Bette@CrazySexyMenopause
Sammy Super Star: Yes!
Crazy Sexy Menopause: Hi Lala!!!
Kali : the title should be something like "waht's happening with tiktok live?!" and the description can say i watch tiktok live so you don't have to
Kali : (along with other thing sint he description)
Mariane Cresp: that's a great find Markus ... will start using it moving forward
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: can you put that link in the description?
Cheryl Wolf: Yes Kali
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: really good Kalil.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: thanks markus.
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Markus! It’s really nice to see a preview of the finished thumbnail.
Mariane Cresp: You did a great job Markus!
Cheryl Wolf: description : I watched so you don't have to
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey!!! Thumbnail done.:) Thanks everyone also for the suggestions. Collaborative thumbnail - done!
Kali : this was way fun 🤗
Fishstick USA: Thank you
Cheryl Wolf: Very good Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: You ate getting so good at doing things live Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Kali is superb at multi tasking. So many awesome inputs.:) Learned do much.:)
Eaglevp: Great stream Markus