Mommy Guide Inc: Yey! Hi @Ellie!
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed! And here we go!
Tim Heale 9: Hi Ellie
Tech Troublemaker: Hey, Markus is back on Thursdays at 4pm!
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Tim, hi Roy
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed Roy! Hello! Were back to regular programming.:)
Eaglevp: Hi Markus,Tim ,Lal and Ellie
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Keith!!!
itdair.network: Hello @Tech Troublemaker Mr. Roy!
Eaglevp: Hey@Tech Troublemaker
Rich Vybz: Hey Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yeah! Hi @Rich Vynbz.
Rich Vybz: Hey Mommy lala
itdair.network: Mr. Markus! Glad to see you Live again!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey everyone! @itdair.network and @Eaglevp @Mommy Guide Inc @Ellie Calhoun @Rich Vybz and everyone else I may have missed
Ellie Calhoun: Love seeing the new faces in your song!
Mommy Guide Inc: Awww Markus updated the video!!! Love it Markus!
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Keith 👋
Tim Heale 9: Hi Keith
Ellie Calhoun: It seems easy but hard to be consistent!
Mommy Guide Inc: The hard part for me is the fact that YT constantly changes its algortihm. He he he. So constant tweaking is needed to grow. Do you feel the same way?
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hi friend
Tim Heale 9: Consistant is the easy bit, the hard bit is YouTube it’s self 😂
Rich Vybz: It’s even harder when you stream on a different platform
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Ana!
Tech Troublemaker: I need to do some VOD and I just can't get focused enough. The Lives are the fun for me.
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Hi Markus😀
Mommy Guide Inc: That’s why really hats off to you Rich!
Eaglevp: Hi@CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming
Rich Vybz: Thank you mommy
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Both also. 👍
Tim Heale 9: It’s funny that you watch some absolute rubbish and it fly’s and excellent content hardly gets any views, no sense at all 😏
Eaglevp: Agree with you Tim
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Hi @eaglevp👋
Mommy Guide Inc: So true Tim. So as long as we enjoy doing what were doing - itll keep us going:)
itdair.network: Each one of you are Excellent! 🏆
Rich Vybz: Yeah not as good as you tube
Tim Heale 9: That’s not working for my quiz channel!
Tech Troublemaker: Sadly my rubbish isn't flying consistently yet.
Tim Heale 9: I’m having so much fun with the quizzes and conversations about mental health is a great time
BostonDonMTB: Howdy Markus
BostonDonMTB: Hi everyone
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Don@BostonDonMTB
BostonDonMTB: Yes, I did.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Sorry I was driving…but 😱 I made it into the intro video????? What a privilege ♥️♥️♥️♥️🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Don! Yes by God’s grace everything is well. Hope the same for you Don. We miss you.
BostonDonMTB: It is doing ok, not huge.
Mommy Guide Inc: Its ok Ana. Hope you arrived safely
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I’m glad you decided to go live!!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I think it’s a lot easier to do interviews than going live by ourselves
Ellie Calhoun: Markus you have an innate ability to create community. We look forward to seeing you go live!
Mommy Guide Inc: Agree - our week isnt complete without a dash of inspiration from Markus. So pls dont forget to smash the like button everyone.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I second that!
Eaglevp: Hi@Ana Zugheri - Faith 52
BostonDonMTB: @Tim Heale 9 teach your dog to edit and you will have millions of views. LOL
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hello 👋 so glad y’all are here!!!
Tim Heale 9: The dog isn’t as much of a super star as the Artie The Ship’s Cat 😻
Mary Speegle: 💕
Mommy Guide Inc: I love watching dog and cat videos also.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Mary! Yey!
Tim Heale 9: @BostonDonMTB if only 😂
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: 🤣🤣🤣 yes dogs and cats are a good hook to have on your streams….the problem is my dog has to be on the mood to go live
Tim Heale 9: Guest what? we are rapidly approaching LEDA, who’s going for it?
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yeah! Absolutely hope to see everyone in LEDA this year:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: @Tim I was just thinking about it
Tim Heale 9: Hudson tends to be a troll while I’m live 😂
BostonDonMTB: I get upset about not knowing things. Like how to edit better. Be more creative with the look of the text in the shorts I am trying to do.
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: I Want to do it one more time. 😀😀👍 That will be my fifth LEDA 😀
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes! You have to have fun, that is FUNdamental!
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Learning something new every time.
Tim Heale 9: Quality rather than quantity
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow Ejnar! Your 5th kudos!
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Thanks Lala😀🙏
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes, be basic and then add a little extra 😋
Tim Heale 9: I just do it on my phone and pop the captions in after
BostonDonMTB: @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52 Thank you.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: @markus Q what do you use to make your shorts 🩳?
Tim Heale 9: My podcasts are rapidly approaching 20K with almost 300 episodes over 3 years, just need to get the same traction with my videos...
Mommy Guide Inc: Congratulations Tim!
Tim Heale 9: No the videos are the podcasts
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: I have problems with captions when I make videos in Danish. Need to tap it in in English and work from there. But it is very time consuming
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I’m still doing my podcast at least once a month. Thank you for listening 👂
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: 🤔
BostonDonMTB: @Markus Schaub How come you stopped?
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: 👏👏👏👏 Tim
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes love your shorts Markus! Go for it!
Tim Heale 9: I release 1 podcast every Sunday
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes!!!!! You are doing fantastic with your shorts! Love them.
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yes insaw a separate button for podcasts the other day
Mommy Guide Inc: Need to update my podcasts
Tech Troublemaker: I am still turning livestreams into podcasts weekly. I took a month off on the podcasts to bank some.
Mommy Guide Inc: Ive tons of livestreams that can be turned into podcasts but procrastinating on it sadly.:(
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Smart !!! Tech Troublemaker, repurpose content is key 🔑
Tim Heale 9: Yep the same, I record my podcasts on either Ecamm or StreamYard then put them up on YouTube and Buzzsprout, as well as the quizzes and mental health conversations
Tim Heale 9: Mind you to put this much content out you have to be retired 😂
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: 😂
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL @Tirm Heale 9
BostonDonMTB: I have an idea for us doing interviews, we have a section of our interview where you have questions that are easily answered in less than a minute.
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey 12 people! Thanks dont forget to like this livestream:)
BostonDonMTB: I have in my last three interviews talked to my guests about music, so that could be a place for quick reactions or answer.
Ellie Calhoun: 😂
Ellie Calhoun: I've got to get back on the wagon and be consistent.
Tim Heale 9: At the end of the day it’s all about enjoying what you are doing and the day you stop enjoying it stop doing it
Mommy Guide Inc: Take breaks , repurpose, don’t overthink - thanks Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Great wisdom there @Tim Heale 9
Tim Heale 9: @Ellie Calhoun LEDA is coming
Tim Heale 9: Just have fun