Neil Farrimond: Hey Markus & Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Let's Go!
Neil Farrimond: :hand-pink-waving:
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Neil!
elle naturally: hi
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Elle!
elle naturally: hello @Mommy Guide Inc
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hello Everyone. 😀
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ejnar:)
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Lala😀
Neil Farrimond: FOR THE PEOPLE!
Neil Farrimond: Will see you there Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: All road leads to the US in October
Mommy Guide Inc: yes!
Neil Farrimond: Cool!
elle naturally: us in october?
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Life is good. Sitting in a school pickup line to get my granddaughter. Spent the day at home babysitting three grandbabies. I need more Fishstick-time for video creation.
elle naturally: ohhhhhhh creator camp!
elle naturally: wait what!
elle naturally: near boston??? tell me details please so I can research this
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: salut @Markus Schaub hello fellow livestreamer
elle naturally: there are short walks to schools and school buses but it depends if your child attends a school further away AND if you have concerns about students being alone on the bus
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Maybe I should create some NextStepOfFaith videos with my grandchildren. I will consider this.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Eric!
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: huhuuu @Mommy Guide Inc
elle naturally: some kids deal with bullying :(
elle naturally: I lived in Switzerland and walked everywhere and LOVED it (and biked)
Tech Troublemaker: We are still vertical live. How is that working out?
elle naturally: Baden
sleepforthesoul: I want to visit Vienna!!!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Lala Hey Phillip!
sleepforthesoul: Saltzburg
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Kristina!
sleepforthesoul: IG live
Tech Troublemaker: I hear the have really good Vienna Sausages in Vienna.
Mommy Guide Inc: Go for it Philip:)
Markus Schaub: https://www.ecamm.com/camp/
Tech Troublemaker: I'm planning to go. I have my calendar set to sign up as soon as it is open.
elle naturally: How much does it usually cost?
Neil Farrimond: Excellent @Tech Troublemaker - you can sign up now.
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Roy!
elle naturally: Thank you
Neil Farrimond: One day longer than last year
Tech Troublemaker: Sorry things are so crazy I didn't see it.
Mommy Guide Inc: the price increased but it's super worth it as food and all the classes are included plus a tour!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes, congratulations Markus1
Tech Troublemaker: do I need to arrive October 14? Is it a full day on the 15th?
Mommy Guide Inc: I can't find my eyeglasses - he he he I hope I am typing things correctly
elle naturally: I’m looking at the creator camp website and very curious about this!
Ellie Calhoun: What's up?
Enda Trading: Hello all
Eaglevp: Hi Markus and all in the chat
elle naturally: I have a pc
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Keith and Ellie:)
Eaglevp: Hi Lala and Ellie
Mommy Guide Inc: We should meet up with Ellie this time:)
Ellie Calhoun: Been a while since I've seen you live!
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Lala and Keith and everyone
Ellie Calhoun: When is camp opening?
Mommy Guide Inc: Speaking of Ecamm is anyone attending Ecamm's LEAP into Tactic? It's super awesome!
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi @Keith😀👍
Eaglevp: Hi Ejnar
elle naturally: I may check in to see about meeting up if there is an evening event
Neil Farrimond: I've attended a couple of the Leap sessions.
Eaglevp: Evening Neil
Neil Farrimond: Hey @Eaglevp nice to see you again Keith!
Mommy Guide Inc: It's Day 2 and it's so awesome. You can get the replay option. amazing speakers. I cannot also attend all the sessions coz it coincides with my livestreams and sleep! he he he but some I've attended
Tech Troublemaker: It's that Neil guy! I have been at the hospital so much this week. I just haven't been able to do Leap.
Ellie Calhoun: Markus are you coming back in October this year?
Eaglevp: Enjoyed watching your live earlier Neil
Eaglevp: Hi Roy
Ellie Calhoun: Roy I hope everything thing is ok!
Mommy Guide Inc: I pray for continued healing for your mom.
Neil Farrimond: Thank you Markus, very kind of you!
Eaglevp: I am hoping to get back into lives next week as my wife is going into a nursing home Monday
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yes Victor and I and some craters are testing out the new zoom integration with Ecamm on Saturday.
Mommy Guide Inc: wow that's great Keith!
Ellie Calhoun: I've been so busy- I miss everyone! Roy, I'll check on your videos
Neil Farrimond: Sorry to hear that Keith.
Eaglevp: It is a tough time here Dementia as taken a turn for the worse
Neil Farrimond: Best to both Roy & Keith.
Neil Farrimond: Sorry to hear that Keith.
Pierre Kelly: Afternoon all
Eaglevp: Hello Pierre
Mommy Guide Inc: Here is the link for Neil's livestream a few hours ago testing it - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sb6jD7u1oeE
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Pierre!
Ellie Calhoun: I'm so sorry Keith, dementia is a tough thing on everyone involved sending 💕
Mommy Guide Inc: big hugs Keith.
Eaglevp: Thank you Ellie
Eaglevp: Appreciate your hugs Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Question for you Markus - what's your favourite takeaway so far on the April challenge?
Mommy Guide Inc: For the poplin the chat - what's your favourite episode so far of Markus' videos this April?
Mommy Guide Inc: My favourite is the short but sweet video of the museum of transportation
Neil Farrimond: It's not easy filming yourself, especially in public. You did a great job Markus!
SuzanCz: Hey hey!
Eaglevp: I loved the museum one as well
Mommy Guide Inc: Coach Suzan!
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Suzan!
SuzanCz: Hi @Ellie Calhoun and @Mommy Guide Inc
Eaglevp: Hi Suzan
Tech Troublemaker: It is hard filming myself but filters help hide my ugly. 😛
SuzanCz: Helllooooooo Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi SuzanCz:)
SuzanCz: I'm in editing for my next video.
Pierre Kelly: nice @SuzanCz
Mommy Guide Inc: Roy reminder to bring back the screwdriver back into the house:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Kidding aside Roy, you have been doing an awesome thing with your journey thus far - Congratulations on 3 years of live-streaming!
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi @Suzan😀
SuzanCz: I think we need to remember to be nice to ourselves. We wouldn't criticize others that way...how dare we be that mean to ourselves?
SuzanCz: Hi @CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream
Neil Farrimond: @SuzanCz agreed. Let's be kind to ourselves 🙂
SuzanCz: I'm not at all on your every-day pace. Right now it's about every 3 weeks... but I'll get there. Tough to do when I was also launching.
Mommy Guide Inc: Please don't forget to watch that epic 3rd year anniversary of Roy with Mikey!https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R_-fvWkaoPs
Budgeting Momma: Hi Markus
SuzanCz: @Neil Farrimond ❤
SuzanCz: Oh yes...self-deprication aside.
Tech Troublemaker: I am very nice to myself. I just don't take myself very seriously.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi budgeting Momma:)
SuzanCz: @Tech Troublemaker That sounds like an excellent balance.
Mommy Guide Inc: I just let Mikey's community literally take over the chat Roy. I couldn't catch up - there were so many:) it's so much fun just watching the chat fly by
Budgeting Momma: Hi mommy guide
SuzanCz: nah - vert looks weird on yT
Budgeting Momma: Vertical looks good.
SuzanCz: YES! Registered for Creator Camp! Who's with me?
Mommy Guide Inc: Coach SuzanC is the launch done?
SuzanCz: Oh -- yay!
SuzanCz: @Mommy Guide Inc
Ellie Calhoun: Yeah I'm not a fan of vertical either
Fishstick ~ Phillip: I liked the vertical while in school line on my phone
Mommy Guide Inc: another road trip Suzan and Markus?
Ellie Calhoun: Is creator camp good for beginners?
Pierre Kelly: It is @Ellie Calhoun
SuzanCz: @Mommy Guide Inc The masterclass was Tuesday and it went very, very well! So now I'm just talking to people that I might be able to help.
SuzanCz: @Ellie Calhoun YES!
SuzanCz: @Mommy Guide Inc #RoadTrip
Ellie Calhoun: Yup. I have a Mac and ecamm just not good at using it yet
SuzanCz: Last year, I wasn't active on YT but it was still a great event
Mommy Guide Inc: awesome!!! Congratulations Suzan!
SuzanCz: @Mommy Guide Inc Thank you. I celebrated with a Limoncello Martini. 🍹
Ellie Calhoun: I'll take a look
SuzanCz: I think the goal is to get more people using it and to connect the community.
Mommy Guide Inc: ooooh nice Suzan.
SuzanCz: YAY! I'm SO excited! Seriuosly -- Boston on Saturday?
elle naturally: Woooaa who is 1.5 hours away?
Ellie Calhoun: Hey Markus, how far are you from Copenhagen
elle naturally: Anyone in new england here?
Budgeting Momma: Hi Elle
Ellie Calhoun: Yes Elle I'm in Boston area
SuzanCz: @Ellie Calhoun Why? Are we going to Copenhagen? 😜
Mommy Guide Inc: Elle - Ellie I think and Suzan are very near:)
Ellie Calhoun: My son will be there next school year and I'm planning to visit!
elle naturally: Ellie I am also
SuzanCz: @elle naturally Yes - both @Ellie Calhoun and I are just outside of Boston
SuzanCz: @elle naturally where are you located?
Ellie Calhoun: He was awarded a Fulbright Scholarship!
SuzanCz: That's amazing, @Ellie Calhoun! Congratulations to him!
elle naturally: I’m either in NH RI or MA and today MA south of boston. I love knowing other new englanders are about!
Mommy Guide Inc: oh wow Ellie! I feel that would be doable for a meet up with Markus!
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Welcome Copenhagen @Ellie😀
SuzanCz: I want to do some traveling this Fall. Don't know where to go yet.
SuzanCz: NH - New Hampshire
SuzanCz: RI - Rhode Island
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Elle there were several from he last Ecamm camp who live very near. I travelled the farthest last time:) he he he just a few thousand miles away:)
elle naturally: Where are you Ellie and Suzan?
Sammy Super Star: Hello Markus
Eaglevp: Hi Sammy
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Keith!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Susan!
SuzanCz: @Mommy Guide Inc Are you coming to Creator Camp again?
Ellie Calhoun: @elle west of Boston- we should meet up sometime for coffee!
SuzanCz: Hey @Tech Troublemaker
Sammy Super Star: Hello Markus, it took long enough but my channel is back
Mommy Guide Inc: HI Sammy! I know you have an incoming video premiere right?
Budgeting Momma: Tx - Texas
Mommy Guide Inc: Congratulations Sammy!!!
Neil Farrimond: Hey @Sammy Super Star
Mommy Guide Inc: Suzan yes:)
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Nice to hear that Sammy😀
SuzanCz: @Mommy Guide Inc YESSSSSSS
Neil Farrimond: @Tech Troublemaker congrats on the 3 years of live streaming!
SuzanCz: @Tech Troublemaker Are you going to CC again?
Sammy Super Star: Yes!!
elle naturally: Ellie yes meeting up!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Ejnar also doing a live everyday in April right Ejnar?
Tech Troublemaker: I will be there.
Tech Troublemaker: Can't wait on #CreatorCamp
Run Adam Run: Hey Markus! Are you going again?
Run Adam Run: What was the price of Creator Camp last year?
SuzanCz: You seem to be doing ok from an accountability standpoint. Will you keep pre-recording? Or are you going to stay just Live?
SuzanCz: Last year, CC was $500
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Neil! Exciting. So much non-work and non-content creation stuff this week. Stretched so think the last two weeks.
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Yes Lala. I run through my first LEDA in August 2020😀
Run Adam Run: Not including the hotel, right?
SuzanCz: @Tech Troublemaker and @Run Adam Run Yay -- see you both at CC!
Run Adam Run: Did that include meals?
Neil Farrimond: @SuzanCz see you at CC too!
SuzanCz: @Neil Farrimond Yay!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Sammy's premiere - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wh3KjQkU3XA
SuzanCz: I haven't seen the hotel info for CC. Did anyone else get that info?
Run Adam Run: I'm in the conference industry, so it's not out of line for what you get.
Run Adam Run: I want to go but it might overlap dates with a conference I'm producing.
Run Adam Run: What are the dates?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Adam!
SuzanCz: Ah -- I'll hop onto their discord
Mommy Guide Inc: I heard no more 120 people for CC2 this year.
Mommy Guide Inc: 120 including staff
SuzanCz: @Mommy Guide Inc Their info says it tops out at 100
SuzanCz: Can't wait to see the schedule and the staff.
Mommy Guide Inc: yes 100 participants and the staff about 120:)
Eaglevp: Bye all
SuzanCz: My sister's alpaca farm isn't too far from Amesbury. Should we go?
Neil Farrimond: You can repurpose your stream as a new video :-)
Run Adam Run: Ugh - we take over DisneyWorld Oct 20th... so it's not likely I can go
elle naturally: Thank you
SuzanCz: Ah - bye everyone!
Mommy Guide Inc: Congratulations to everyone for an amazing April
Neil Farrimond: Take it easy. See you all soon.
SuzanCz: Markus - what's the link to your website where we can buy stuff?
Mommy Guide Inc: See you all! Bye!
Markus Schaub: https://markusschaub.shop/
Ellie Calhoun: 😂