Mommy Guide Inc: Hi droends! Lets go!
Tech Troublemaker: It is a really old reference.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Droends? I meant friends.
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Hello Markus
Tech Troublemaker: Google "is it live or memorex commercial"
CSLiveDK : Hi Markus and all the good people here😀
Mommy Guide Inc: Was able to edit 10 videos the other day so its a yey!
Tech Troublemaker: Woot! @Mommy Guide Inc
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Phillip!
Mommy Guide Inc: I ended up with an oucjy legs - had to ask Vimcent help to eelieve thre pain from
Mommy Guide Inc: Sitting down the whole day.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Philip and Ejnar.
Fishstick ~ Phillip: I led our devotion group livestream this morning. I like hosting the livestream. It is a private livestream with 20-30 people.
Mommy Guide Inc: Ok i dont know how to spell today. Lol
Fishstick ~ Phillip: I have 10 grandchildren. 😳
CSLiveDK : It has subtitles in German and other automatic languages 😀
Mommy Guide Inc: The legs. I couldnt stand after. The legs cramped
CSLiveDK : Hi Lala😀
Mommy Guide Inc: Philip that trumped everything! Congratulations!!!
Fishstick ~ Phillip: I will lead the devotions one day each week.
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Haha Markus. I lose count of my grandchildren too.
Mommy Guide Inc: Philip thats super awesome.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: So how does it feel to be a year older Markus?
Tech Troublemaker: I am planning to start using 2 cameras for my morning thoughts unless that winds up a pain to edit. 🙂
Tech Troublemaker: Just remember a birthday is just one day older than the previous day.
Mommy Guide Inc: Lol so true Roy about our age.:)
Tech Troublemaker: 2 angles. I will mount to the passenger's window
Tech Troublemaker: And tomorrow I premier a huge leap in video for me. I am trying to go a new direction but it takes a lot of work. So maybe one per month.
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow 2 cameras! I feel thats harder to shoot but probably ok on the editing. Go Roy:)
Enda Trading: Hello for Malaysia 4:20am 🙂 Early bird here
Mommy Guide Inc: That was really a thought provoking video Markus. Midlife crisis happens
Enda Trading: Early yo bed early to rise makes a man healthy, wealthy and wise
Enda Trading: *to
Mommy Guide Inc: Roy’s epic video premiere is tomorrow friemds.:) hope to see you there in the premiere too:)
Tech Troublemaker: Remember, the longer you wait to have your midlife crisis, the obviously you are going to live longer as well, it happened at the midpoint of your life. Right?!?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Enda!
Enda Trading: Hey @Mommy Guide Inc I am in Port Dickson, lovely spot beside the beach
Mommy Guide Inc: https://youtu.be/cmn4NOE2VKQ?si=i0VrJ-l_qMz-rNMN
Enda Trading: Nice breeze for the hot season
Mommy Guide Inc: Thats the lonk for Roy’s premiere you may set notification friends:)
Tech Troublemaker: I loved her video of your video. It was awesome.
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow Enda sounds so nice.:)
Tech Troublemaker: We should start remixing each others videos and see if it does anything for us.
Fishstick ~ Phillip: BTW. I used YouTubeStudio to livestream and shared a second screen for several slides. The group has never had this before. I want to try Streamyard and include a second host. I am Windows. Dont judge
Run Adam Run: Hey there, Markus! You deserve all the love.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Adam!
Run Adam Run: Fish, Streamyard is a great platform. I'm sure you will enjoy using it.
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow Philip yey! No judgment my friend.:) you are doing great:)
Tech Troublemaker: Every creator should use the camera they have and the computer they have and don't let other creators kick sand in their eyes for doing it their way.
Fishstick ~ Phillip: I told the group we try to improve 1% at a time…. Roy 😉
Run Adam Run: You can run the length of Switzerland!
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Adam and Roy, I really enjoyed your livestream on Tuesday. I learned a lot.
Run Adam Run: Well, I'd argue that Markus is the best. Right?!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow thats a great thought Adam. Markus running around Switzerland.:)
Run Adam Run: You can run in your car...
Fishstick ~ Phillip: The flat distance of Switzerland is one thing. Running the Alps would be another.
Mommy Guide Inc: Absolutely - no question about that Adam.:) yes thanks Adam for that awesome walkthrough of Descript:)
Run Adam Run: I'd be happy to take you through it, Markus - just let me know.
Enda Trading: Does everyone in switzerland have a swiss army knife
Eaglevp: Evening Markus
Eaglevp: Hi Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: The mix of edited videos and livestreams for most of us i feel is a great way to learn:)
Eaglevp: Hello Adam
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Keith hope all is well my friend.:)
Run Adam Run: Hello, Keith
Eaglevp: Hey Phillip
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Hello
Tech Troublemaker: In Switzerland they don't call them swiss army knives, they just call them knives. 😛
Mommy Guide Inc: The casual livestream series Markus i feel is doing great for you too:)
Eaglevp: Have you got an idea for Monday's video
Mommy Guide Inc: Monday blues. A new series? He he he
Tech Troublemaker: In China they call Chinese food, just food.
Eaglevp: Hi Roy
Enda Trading: Ah now, its a brand haha
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Keith!
Enda Trading: Swiss army is so famous, I dont know if so in the US haha
Eaglevp: Idea for Monday's video what is current price of a pint of beer
Tech Troublemaker: new series idea, Chinese Food In Switzerland (each episode you just meet a friend at a restaurant and chat)
Eaglevp: Or cost of living in Switzerland
Tech Troublemaker: @Enda Trading Swiss Army Knives used to be very popular in US. Now it is Leatherman Multitools.
Enda Trading: Got it
Tech Troublemaker: One day I will make it to Europe.
Enda Trading: Go to Ireland too
Tech Troublemaker: Kind of "Chicken Shop Date" style videos.
Mommy Guide Inc: You can do that in creator camp. Try to meet all 100 people Markus and create a shorts or short video. Maybe ask them Ll the same questions?
Enda Trading: But during the summer months only
Mommy Guide Inc: I love learning about different places and cultires TTh ats why i love to travel.
Mommy Guide Inc: And the spelling bug continues on for me. Promise i do know how to spell. LOL
Mommy Guide Inc: I still have a ton of travel
Budgeting Momma: Hi Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Budgeting Momma.:) love that budgeting:)
Budgeting Momma: Hi @Mommy guide Inc
Run Adam Run: Could you teach us German?
Enda Trading: In the Summer you could do Live streams out in the beautiful landscape over there
Mommy Guide Inc: Thats great idea Adam - like common words that are useful foe travellers
Mommy Guide Inc: Line word for the day.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Like word for the day. This is now irritating. Lala - check spelling! Note to self.
Tech Troublemaker: today's word is Strudel
Mommy Guide Inc: Roy a strudel is a food?
Run Adam Run: What's the german word for "click thru rate" LOL
Tech Troublemaker: yes Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Really? Kindergarten has german origins? Awesome. Learned something new today.
Budgeting Momma: German can be useful… I go to this restaurant that is all German… der lind bum…. I think is the name.
Run Adam Run: SO in
Run Adam Run: So in German you don't need to work about CTR
Run Adam Run: I'm moving
Tech Troublemaker: yes, we put kids into gardens but we aren't very kind about it.
Mommy Guide Inc: Theres a channel i watch she’s so big now mostly shorts about how it is different living in Germany shes originally from Vietnam. Funny videos. Love it! Learned so many about Germany from her videos
Mommy Guide Inc: One of my best shorts are on kinderjoy! People love kinderjoy and surprise gift inside
Run Adam Run: I've seen that creator - it's really funny, she finds local Asian food in Germany
Enda Trading: Kinder bueno means Kids Good lol and mix of Spanish never taught about this till now
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh really Enda rhats what bueno means? Awesome.
Budgeting Momma: It’s all German. No one really speaks English… alls of music and German food… yes it was found by German.
Run Adam Run: We are a Large Language Model with natural intelligence.
Run Adam Run: Kraftwerk is German music too.
Budgeting Momma: We call it polka music in the America
Mommy Guide Inc: I remember in one of Markus’ libestreams he mentioned about Switzerland has 4 major languages. Do you speak all Markus?
Run Adam Run: What is the love language of Switerland? Time?
Enda Trading: We had 4 language classes in school, English, Irish, German and French, too many haha
Mommy Guide Inc: Speaking of languages do you use the captioning for different languages for hour videos friends?
Mommy Guide Inc: I guess my spelling woes will
Budgeting Momma: Who speaks more than one language in the same conversation?
Mommy Guide Inc: Continue on for the whole duration of Markus’ livestream. lol!
Tech Troublemaker: I think I will start captioning mine in UK english and Canadian English
Mommy Guide Inc: I can speak only English and Filipino fluently. A bit of chinese and spanish.
Run Adam Run: I live on the border and we speak Spanish and English in the same sentence in my house.
Mommy Guide Inc: Canada has a different English Roy? I know about UK English but didnt know that Canad/
Mommy Guide Inc: Awesome Adam.:)
Budgeting Momma: Adam you in the USA
Run Adam Run: Yes, I live in San Diego next to Tijuana.
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks friends. Don’t forget to smash the LIKE for this live friends.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Bathroom
Mommy Guide Inc: Bathroom as toilets etc. Emma Cruises a channel
Mommy Guide Inc: A channel
Budgeting Momma: Texas people speak English and Spanish at the same time. Many words are Tex-Mex
Budgeting Momma: @ Adam… so cool
Mommy Guide Inc: A channel i watch she always has like Brit word segment in all her videos.:) love it.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: @Budgeting Momma we call ours Taglish something like TexMex:)
Tech Troublemaker: Hot Ones
Tech Troublemaker: Yes, Challenge Accepted.
Budgeting Momma: @adam never hear of Tanisha. Very interesting
Run Adam Run: I really like "One Pack Wanderers" a travel couple. They are currently driving around Australia.
Tech Troublemaker: Michelle Khare
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh love travel, tech, DIY, history, arts and crafts:)
Tech Troublemaker: Post Modern Jukebox (I love their reinterpretations of popular songs)
Mommy Guide Inc: So just like me - i love to watch a ton of different content.:)
Run Adam Run: I love really great storytelling and inspired editing
Tech Troublemaker: Life of Riza
Run Adam Run: Life of Riza is on a different level for sure.
Run Adam Run: I just can't relate to her.
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow its already top of the hour? Wow that went by fast. Time indeed flies by when you’re having fun
Tech Troublemaker: Digital Spagetti
Mommy Guide Inc: Roy thanks for sharing these channels aill
Mommy Guide Inc: Will check them
Tech Troublemaker: Hit LIKE already!!!!
Eaglevp: bye all
Mommy Guide Inc: Waah!!!! I keep smashing the send button too early grrr
Run Adam Run: Another high quality hour in the can. Thank You Markus
Tech Troublemaker: Everyone should like themselves, maybe not on YouTube but in Life.
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Roy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Markus and friends!!!