Mommy Guide Inc: Awww I’ll miss this but you’re right Markus - it’ll always be in our hearts and memories. Looking forward to the new one.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Don! Today my sister, daughter and nanny joined me and my son in our walking routine.:)
BostonDonMTB: @Mommy Guide Inc That is awesome. The more the merrier.
Spooling Around: Hi Markus, Lala and Friends!
CSLiveDK : Hello and goodevening everyone 😀
Mommy Guide Inc: They got curious I think what me and my son do every other day - min of 7k walk around the mall complex so that rain or shine as long as there is no flood - we can go and walk.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi David and Ejnar.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Has it been a month already?
CSLiveDK : Hi Lala😀
Run Adam Run: The Coach is in the Building!
Run Adam Run: Hey everyone. Give me 10 pushups.
Run Adam Run: (Markus is looking thinner, right?!!)
Mommy Guide Inc: That’s awesome. Love seeing you happy about this pivot.:)
Run Adam Run: Taking care of yourself will take care of your community. Be the role model you want to be.
Mommy Guide Inc: Sounds very cliche but truly - health is wealth.
Run Adam Run: Exactly Lala - it's worth more than money.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Coach Adam.:)
Neil Farrimond: Hey Markus! Hope all is well with you.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Neil!
Neil Farrimond: Hi LaLa!
Mommy Guide Inc: That’s good - slow is better in losing weight. A fast one can harm our organs.
Run Adam Run: Gen AI will makeup and answer if you don't have one. 😂
Enda Trading: Woo I woke up too early @Mommy Guide Inc What are you doing up lol
Enda Trading: Its 4:14am
Enda Trading: What am I doing up too haha
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Hello Markus…. Are you starting a yodeling channel?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Enda! Oh Fridays I wake up early.;)
Enda Trading: 🤣 happy Friday!
Run Adam Run: You are also an inspirational channel now. People will be inspired by you and follow your lead.
Mommy Guide Inc: Coach Adam has a Fitness for Creators in FB.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Congratulations Markus - you have not missed putting up also your weekly videos! Yey!
Tim Heale 9: How's the diet going?
Eaglevp: Sorry I AM LATE BEEN TALKING TO tIM
Eaglevp: Hi Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Exercise is something we all want to do but often always put it aside. But when we see Markus doing it very consistently - we also get reminded to be mo
Eaglevp: Liked the number games on your walk the other day
Enda Trading: Your editing skill are on point!
Run Adam Run: I loved the Number Game video - one of your best. It was also a great way to show the beauty of your home town.
Eaglevp: Hi Adam
Mommy Guide Inc: That checker indeed was cool!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Keith!
Eaglevp: Hello @Enda Trading
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Happy Thursday friends!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Happy to join you today.
Eaglevp: Hi@Ana Zugheri - Faith52
Spooling Around: I've had far too many false starts
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana!
BostonDonMTB: Markus Schaub's "Obvious Things Diet"
Eaglevp: Hi@Spooling Around
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for supporting Markus pivot friends - please don’t forget to hit the LIKE button.:)
Eaglevp: Hi@BostonDonMTB
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: You are so inspiring, Markus! You are doing awesome.
Mommy Guide Inc: I can no
BostonDonMTB: Hi @Eaglevp
Tim Heale 9: You will be running round before you know it
Eaglevp: He will Tim
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes! the number game was awesome! great idea.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Tim!
BostonDonMTB: @Run Adam Run You should give Markus a sentence that he has to take pictures of individual letters like the numbers game.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I was about to leave for my walk today but I saw you were on, so I'll go after your live...I can't type and walk lol
Pierre Kelly: hey everyone, why are you pivoting?
Tim Heale 9: But don't over do it as you will pick up an injury and won't want to start again
Pierre Kelly: @spoolingaround too many false starts, too many yards penalized
Rich Vybz: Hey everyone, hey Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: So Markus moving forward - the channel will now be on being healthier - and sharing your own walk “literally”
Spooling Around: I have a demanding day job that gets in the way
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: So glad you are very aware of that, I strongly believe that is why so many of us don't follow through.
Tim Heale 9: Cut down on sugar, carbs and fat intake and more exercise
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Rich:)
Rich Vybz: Hi Lala
Rich Vybz: hope you are doing well
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I strongly recommend the book atomic habits., so basic and maybe logical but it has helped me to stay on track. Great reminder on how little steps get you far.
Mommy Guide Inc: Tim - sugar and carbs - my kryptonite to a better health
Tim Heale 9: The 'Fast 800' diet work very well
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: can't wait to hear it! I love your current intro!
Mommy Guide Inc: Haven’t heard of that before Tim - is that 800 calories somehow?
Mommy Guide Inc: RAYM is awesome so now looking forward to the new one.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes that book indeed is awesome Ana.
Mommy Guide Inc: Next up the Alphabet game.:)
Spooling Around: I got an apple watch, it reminds me to stand up during work. it helps
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes, it's crazy how it's not only good for your physical health but your mental health improves so much when you move!
Enda Trading: I only eat 2 times a day since about 4 years, a good breakfast and dinner is all you need when your body get used to it, but not health advise, I do take a multi vit too, it works
Jeff de Boer: Good progress. Steady improvement is the best. Going 110% out of the gate leads to burning out. Slow and steady wins the race, as long as we keep moving!
Mommy Guide Inc: Nice Enda.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Jeff.:)
BostonDonMTB: It is crazy how you feel like you need more once you get started. I was doing 5 mile rides, but then I would ride 7 or 8 miles on the trainer. I moved up to 10 miles, and now I am up to 13+ miles.
BostonDonMTB: Typically locally I wouldn't do more than 15 miles on the trails, so I am building to that.
Jeff de Boer: :hand-pink-waving:
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow Don! Almost double now from your original one.:)
BostonDonMTB: @Mommy Guide Inc Oh yeah. The riding is getting easier, and find myself at a certain mileage say 10 miles, and I feel like ok, lets get to 12 miles and so on.
Mommy Guide Inc: Do you have like a go pro on your helmet Don? Can we see your rides?
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: hello big man from luzern
Ellie Calhoun: Oh I'm late!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Eric and Ellie:)
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: huhuuu @Mommy Guide Inc
Tatiana Teaches: Hello 👋🏼 hello from the dentists office
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Tatiana! Was able to watch a bit your show with Doc the other day before sleeping.:)
Jeff de Boer: With a demanding job; is your job more important than your hera
BostonDonMTB: @Mommy Guide Inc I have a ton of GoPro's The latest version that I have is the Hero Black 8. The thing I am concerned with is the footage not being smooth with that version of stabilization.
Jeff de Boer: Health*
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Hope all is well Tatiana. And that this is just dental routine check up and all is well
Mommy Guide Inc: I am sure you’ll find the best way to share the journey soon Don. Looking forward to it.:)
Ellie Calhoun: It becomes a way of life, looking for the places to get movement in.
BostonDonMTB: @Mommy Guide Inc thank you.
Mommy Guide Inc: Now that the Holidays is fast approaching - people often lose track of their healthy habits coz of the festivities and events that come along with the season.
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: happy christmas @momy
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: happy christmas @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: Looking forward to some tips to balance that - enjoy the holidays still but not lose track of our health journey
Ellie Calhoun: Regarding sugar, I need to cut it out entirely otherwise I'm constantly making that decision. If I just say "I don't eat that" it's easy to follow.
BostonDonMTB: A riding friend of mine notice on my Strava that I was doing more miles. He reached out to plan a trail ride next week.
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Don - that’s awesome.:)
Jeff de Boer: :hand-purple-blue-peace:
BostonDonMTB: I think I will be up for going to the trails to ride since I have been getting my strength and stamina by doing some road rides and my bike smart trainer.
BostonDonMTB: @good advice @Jeff de Boer
Tech Troublemaker: Bring the excitement!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Eric - indeed I’ve been doing Christmas In July
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: cool i swam through the rotsee several times :P that was fun
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy!
Tech Troublemaker: @BostonDonMTB. I bought a GoPro 12. It is a lot of fun to use.
Tech Troublemaker: Hey LaLa!
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: why not @Mommy Guide Inc creating your paper craft thingis - need time for your customers
BostonDonMTB: @Tech Troublemaker It is a nice camera. I should see if I can my older models for cheap and maybe get enough to buy the new version of the GoPro.
Eaglevp: Hi Ellie and Roy
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Eric, Tatiana, Jeff, and Ellie
Ellie Calhoun: Yes! Awesome 👏
Eaglevp: Hi Eric
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Keith
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Eric - every opportunity to create crafty stuff makes me excited and the Holidays is indeed the busiest for crafters like me.:)
Jeff de Boer: Hello!
Marielou Mandl: So proud of you Markus!!! 🎉🎉🎉
Eaglevp: Hello@Jeff de Boer
Eaglevp: Hi@Marielou Mandl
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: @Mommy Guide Inc yes, your livestreams show that you are very hard-working
Tech Troublemaker: Don, it was so big onsale. Only reason I bought it
BostonDonMTB: @Tech Troublemaker It has many uses.
Mommy Guide Inc: Excited for the pivot Markus and everything that it would bring.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: 3M - Markus Move Movement
Marielou Mandl: Yall inspired me to download Stava
Tech Troublemaker: Merry Christmas everyone 🎄🎅
Marielou Mandl: 🤩Merry Lala Christmas 🎄
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: I’m here!!!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: 🥰
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Marielou rocks! Well done
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Marielou! Saw the last few minutes of your last livestream yesterday.:)
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Hi friends 👋
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Katy!
Eaglevp: Hi@Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach
Marielou Mandl: We have fun, don’t we friends 🥰
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Hi guys x
Ellie Calhoun: Markus Moves More!!
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Thank you x
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks friends! Thanks Markus! Pls don’t forget to smash the LIKE button on your way out. See you all next week!
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: I’d love a video about the Insta 360 and invisible selfie stick at some pount
Mommy Guide Inc: Soon that list will be a scrolling one! Thanks Markus!!!!
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: You’re looking great Markus
Jeff de Boer: Gute nacht!