Eaglevp: How’s the video coming on Markus?
Eaglevp: Have you been busy editing it?
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello friends 👋🎉
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Watching from carline at 100 degrees from Houston Tx 🤪
Eaglevp: Hello Ana how are you today?
Eaglevp: Wow that’s hot Ana pleased it’s a lot cooler here in the UK
Fishstick USA: Hello Markus and all !
Eaglevp: Let’s go
Eaglevp: Hi Fishstick
Eaglevp: Quality over quantity
Adam Tinkoff: Hey Markus
Eaglevp: Hello Adam
Tim Heale 9: Not sure its for me 😏
Eaglevp: Think it could be fun to play with it
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Or trying to match tik tok
Adam Tinkoff: I think they are aiming for the younger demographic - which is their future.
Eaglevp: Been trying it this afternoon on the phone looks very good
Adam Tinkoff: Unfortunately, I do not represent their potential market. I am their legacy. (old man yelling at the clouds)
Tim Heale 9: I think I'll give it a miss 😂
Eaglevp: Same here Adam
Eaglevp: That could go viral yelling at the clouds Adam
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I’m excited I’m and old woman too but I want to try it!!!
Adam Tinkoff: Ana is a "cloud whisperer" lol &lt;3
Tim Heale 9: There is an awful lot of rubbish on YT
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I’ll yell at the sun ☀️ please stop roasting us!!!!
Tim Heale 9: @Ana Zugheri - Faith52 You can have some of our wet and cold
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Wow that’s pretty cool 😎
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: @Tim can I come get it lol
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Q is that inside the YouTube studio?
Tim Heale 9: I have enough trouble with English 😂
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Q friends, what do you think if I was to do a live in Spanish inside my YT channel?
Adam Tinkoff: Dubs will be helpful for educational content.
Adam Tinkoff: and Mexican Novellas.
Adam Tinkoff: Ana, I would watch your channel to practicar mi español.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: 😂 I can be pretty dramatic
Tim Heale 9: I can try it in Italian, just wave my arms a lot
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I can speak whale 🐳 too like dory
Tim Heale 9: Not sure I will get much from it
Fishstick USA: Ana. Haha
Adam Tinkoff: I think the insight tools look helpful. Hopefully, they will be useful for the micro-creator too.
Tim Heale 9: I have an exciting series of videos coming up over the next few months of a road trip I am doing next month
Adam Tinkoff: Unfortunately, the attention seems to be on AI and the short form and it feels like LIVE streaming is less of a priority.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I agree
Tim Heale 9: AI has its place, I use it for a few things
Adam Tinkoff: Wait, what's that? A CLOUD! AAAAAAHHHHAHHRRRGGG!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Uuuuuuh that looks fancy!
Fishstick USA: Pe MM
Fishstick USA: Markus. When I use the YT editor for a video, I will let you know
Tim Heale 9: We could be like actors and screenwriters where AI is putting them out of work 😂
Paul Burke: I read an article about someone who used chatgpt to create a meditation schedule and they found it very helpful.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: You are doing great with your videos Phillip 🎉
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: It’s been a game changer for me a goop personal assistant
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Great show Markus ♥️
Tim Heale 9: I'm away 11 to 19 Oct on a road trip
Tim Heale 9: It will be a series
Adam Tinkoff: Thanks buddy!