Pierre Kelly: you did find coach Adam?
Eaglevp: Q.Do you feel any fitter Markus?
Pierre Kelly: were you ever overweight prior to this challenge?
Cheryl Wolf: Hello
Cheryl Wolf: Are you sleeping better?
Eaglevp: Hi Cheryl
Neil Farrimond: Hey Markus! Keep up the amazing work.
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Kieth
Eaglevp: Hello Neil
Eaglevp: When's your video coming out Cheryl?
Cheryl Wolf: No date yet but soon, doing some work to prepare
Eaglevp: Looking forward to it coming out Cheryl
Cheryl Wolf: 🎉Congrats Markus
Andrea Nunn: for how long will you track your progress?
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Congrats on your walks
Eaglevp: Hello@Fishstick ~ Phillip
Pierre Kelly: ever actually tried running on a treadmill?
Cheryl Wolf: Tons fun cottage cheese recipes yummy
Cheryl Wolf: Walk with Markus 🏃‍➡️
Ellie Calhoun: Hi all! 👋
Cheryl Wolf: Hey Ellie
Eaglevp: Hi Ellie
Ellie Calhoun: Can track your food intake. I've done that and it's very eye opening!
Andrea Nunn: are you hoping to change/improve something in your bloodwork?
Fishstick ~ Phillip: You will lose weight. Do not fixate on the scales. You will feel the effects by notches on your belt, how your shirts fit, and when someone notices a change. You are doing great.
Cheryl Wolf: Phillip excellent, agree how your clothes feel, yes you will have better health soon, side effect will be weight lose
Cheryl Wolf: Truth!!
Fishstick ~ Phillip: I bought smaller plates. I fix water to drink. I do not eat after supper/dinner. This means I am not eating 12 hours a day. Keep an eye on blood sugar levels and blood pressure.
Fishstick ~ Phillip: *I say I bought smaller plates and put less on them.
Ellie Calhoun: Yes we eat on small plates
Pierre Kelly: is your blood pressure okay?
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Some people like to run. I do not. My spine is slightly curved, and running is painful. Also, all of my friends who run get obsessed and have had their knees replaced. Walk, walk, walk.
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: oh no walking today 😛 fuuli nase /lazy nose
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: hello 🖖
Ellie Calhoun: We are here to help you keep at it!!
Cheryl Wolf: isometric exercises are fantastic as well
Fishstick ~ Phillip: You should buy a blood pressure machine. Maybe test your blood sugar. Ask your doctor.
Ellie Calhoun: We are built for walking!
Fishstick ~ Phillip: I suggest stretching exercises. Arms and bending. This will benefit you as your health improves. You can stretch in your living room.
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Cheryl is right. But she is too smart and knows the big words. :)
Cheryl Wolf: Lol Phillip
Cheryl Wolf: St
Fishstick ~ Phillip: I have 10 grandchildren if you like lifting weights. It helps me. Haha.
Cheryl Wolf: Wow ten busy busy
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: @Fishstick ~ Phillip you throw your grandchildren around? so mean 😛
Cheryl Wolf: Brands ♥️
Cheryl Wolf: Bands northlands
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: 1x 1.5 liter full filled bottle of watter - is my excercise tool 🙂 thats enough for me - and then i have a 2.5kg an 5kg weight thingi..
Cheryl Wolf: Lol fatfingers
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Seriously, the grandchildren are contributing to my strength health. This is why I suggest stretching. If you hurt yourself, you will get discouraged. Be careful.
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: and i go walking for 1 hour every day - usually at midnight - through the dark forest or the city... wonderful - thats my program - thats enough for me 🙂 i will never be a supermodel
BostonDonMTB: Hey everyone, sorry I am late.
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: we have beautiful brains 😛
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Walking is great for you. I am not certain about midnight. I may be attacked by a raccoon or possum. I live in a rural area. Haha
BostonDonMTB: I am super psyched to be doing this.
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: i as well @Fishstick ~ Phillip i see many fox, and martens(marder) eagel etc - but no bear 😛
BostonDonMTB: I have yet to do filming. Soon though.
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: @Fishstick ~ Phillip although the bear is the animal in the city's emblem
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: i am not saint gallus who can talk to the bear :P
BostonDonMTB: Yes, I don't want to load myself up with thinking about footage. I'd rather get myself moving for now and be consistent with it. Then make the next step.
BostonDonMTB: Yeah, in your last video you were very creative with your shots. NIcely done.
BostonDonMTB: Do you get hot walking in your jeans? I would have to wear shorts.
BostonDonMTB: How is everyone else doing?
BostonDonMTB: Besides Eric, anyone else joining the party of walking or moving in some way?
Cheryl Wolf: I took pilates class and now this week I sneeze and my abs hurt lol
BostonDonMTB: @Cheryl Wolf That is terrible. I have done that before.
BostonDonMTB: Oops, I thought you put your back out. Read it wrong.
BostonDonMTB: I will be adding strength workout soon.
Ellie Calhoun: I try to walk daily and actually have started to watch and listen to Markus' videos while walking.
Ellie Calhoun: And listening to podcasts...
BostonDonMTB: @Ellie Calhoun That is a great idea.
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Q: Do you struggle with diet? You should share your meals & snacks. I drink water. I eat a sandwich for lunch, we eat a good supper. I eat low or no carb/sugar snacks. I eat fruit. I drink diet sodas.
BostonDonMTB: Diet will be my next thing to tackle. I had a doctor's appointment yesterday we went over my blood work from last week, and dealing with high blood pressure that I found that I had in February.
Ellie Calhoun: 😆 just my shorter walks in the yard. When I do a long walk I just walk and try to keep the pace up.
Fishstick ~ Phillip: I struggled with water. So I keep a tumbler with cool water. I now drink sodas (Dr Pepper Zero) as a treat.
BostonDonMTB: I am taking some medicine for the blood pressure, but with eating better I will hopefully be off it eventually. Sugar is my biggest problem.
Cheryl Wolf: Its never to late to start again
Fishstick ~ Phillip: *on my back
BostonDonMTB: @Fishstick ~ Phillip I agree having a good doctor helps. My doctor is new to me since February and he seems to be really good for what I want to have for a doctor.
Ellie Calhoun: To make change physically, you may have some beliefs that need changing. Much of self care has to do with your mindset
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi friends! Hi Markus!
Cheryl Wolf: can I just say Phillip love that markus just said your 46!
Mommy Guide Inc: Alarm didn’t turn on.:( sorry am late but glad to have caught you all still
Cheryl Wolf: lala
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Markus, you are an inspiring guy. I think a lot of you. Salut'
BostonDonMTB: @Mommy Guide Inc Hi Lala
Eaglevp: Hi Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Cheryl, Philip, Don, Ellie, Pierre, Andrea, and Keith!!!
Fishstick ~ Phillip: I also went to a dietician/nutritionist. Your doctor might have a recommendation.
Cheryl Wolf: 🤩
Mommy Guide Inc: You all are part of my weekly happy resource;)
Mommy Guide Inc: I will watch on replay:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Still doing my walking with my son.:)
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Lala! Just keep walking! Yay!
Fishstick ~ Phillip: This hour went fast. Bye all.
Cheryl Wolf: Don't forget to hit the like button
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks friends! Have a great rest of the week!
BostonDonMTB: Markus, now that you have started this, and see what you have inspired, do you have any lofty goals, content, or locations you want to show us?