Eaglevp: Hi Tim
Eaglevp: Hello@Eric Maechler - Online Marketing
Stannex: Dance it out, Markus!!!
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: hi @Eaglevp
Eaglevp: Hi@Stannex
Stannex: Hi @Eaglevp ... and everyone else!
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: i like this trailer - i need one too
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello 👋 friends!!! Here we go!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi everyone!!!
Eaglevp: Hey @Ana Zugheri - Faith52 is in the room
Stannex: Hi, Lala!
Eaglevp: Boom Lala his here
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Tim, Keith, Eric, Stan and Ana!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello! Hello! So glad to see y’all here ♥️
Mommy Guide Inc: Eric Markus’ opening video is super awesome right? It’s such a good feel one
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: yess @Mommy Guide Inc totaly
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: tooo hot #switzerland
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: We are 107 f here in texas
Tim Heale 9: I was second in Keith was first
Eaglevp: I am pleased I am not in Texas@Ana Zugheri - Faith52
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: It’s horrible 😣
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: no you @Markus Schaub didn't drive me away last week. your show wasn't too bad 😛
Tim Heale 9: You could try running round the lake to cool down 😂
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes first and second today - Keith and Tim!
Eaglevp: It's only in the 70's here in the UK
Tim Heale 9: Hi Lala
Daniel Chi: Hey Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: So which do you prefer Markus - hot or cold weather?
Stannex: Happy upcoming anniversary!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Let’s all go to UK 🇬🇧
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Daniel!
Daniel Chi: Just stopping by for a quick hello. I love your thumbnails. 😀
Eaglevp: Hello@Daniel Chi
Tech Troublemaker: Hey No Topic!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy!!!
Eaglevp: Hi Roy
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: the turbo train (east switzerland) has a good AC #geheimtip
Tim Heale 9: You will be complaining when it gets cold and snowing
Daniel Chi: Hey hey @Eaglevp!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Lala and @Eaglevp
Daniel Chi: Hey there Lala @Mommy Guide Inc!
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow 2 years Markus - confetti 🎊
Daniel Chi: 🤣
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Everyone! Sorry Im' late. DANIEL!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: LALA!!
Mommy Guide Inc: You’re awesome authentic self Markus! Everyone loves Markus!!! Don’t forget to smash the LIKE button friends.:
Daniel Chi: YES!!! That's awesome! Can't wait!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hi 👋 welcome
Eaglevp: Hello@Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing
Mommy Guide Inc: Janet!!! Hi my dear friend.:)
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: ecamm camp in the UK? i am in :P
Tim Heale 9: You sound like an Englishman talking about the weather
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi @Eaglevp
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes I’m much rather do cold weather. 😊
Fishstick USA: Hello Markus
Eaglevp: Hi@Fishstick USA
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello 👋 @fishtick USA
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Ana & @Fishstick USA
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Philip@FishstickUSA
Tim Heale 9: Boom I have gone over 520 subs
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Who is this? link?
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow Tim - congratulations!!! No way to go but up!
Eaglevp: Congrats Tim
Tim Heale 9: Thanks
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I want to talk live vs premiere??? How, cons, pros, do you premier all recorded videos?
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Wooo hoo Tim!!!!!! 🥳 congratulations 🎊
Fishstick USA: 8 hrs editing for 40 sec intro
Mommy Guide Inc: Ana my premiered videos lately are doing better than my livestreams.:) coz my livestreams are awfully long. He he he
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: don't want the course. just want to know who it is
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow Philip that is going to be a super awesome intro. Am so bad at editing.
Eaglevp: I prefer live to premieres@Ana Zugheri - Faith52
Eaglevp: You should stick to 45 mins Lala
Sarra Jerad: hello 👋
Mommy Guide Inc: I want to thank Markus by the way for always pushing me to go ahead and upload edited videos.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: @Lala ah! I see
Eaglevp: Hi@Sarra Jerad
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Markus we will watch that.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sarra!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Markus is such an encourager 🎉
Paul Burke: Congrats Markus...I've noticed your live attendance always going up every week
Eaglevp: Hello@Paul Burke
Sarra Jerad: hahaha I was there one time already but I take the welcome. thanks! ☺️
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello 👋 Sarra and Paul! Welcome
Mommy Guide Inc: Don’t forget to smash the like button friends and if you are not yet subscribed to consider subscribing to this awesome channel. If it’s inspiration you want? Markus can give that.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Paul!
Paul Burke: hey @Eaglevp and @Ana Zugheri - Faith52 and @Mommy Guide Inc 🙂
Stuart Video -Tech Installations: Hi @Markus Schaub
Daniel Chi: Markus, your thumbnail colour and the thermometer really caught my eye, so I had to click and watch!
Eaglevp: Hi@Stuart Video -Tech Installations
Mommy Guide Inc: Keith great advice but am too talkative and so hard to finish a craft project in 45 mins. He he he.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello 👋 @stuart video
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I agree Daniel
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes! I love your authenticity
Eaglevp: Agree Lala you will just have to get faster on your projects........lol
Stuart Video -Tech Installations: Hi @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey! That’s an awesome observation Daniel.:) indeed Markus’ thumbnails have been getting better and better
Mommy Guide Inc: After Markus livestream on doing thumbnails - I’ve changed all my latest thumbnails like 3 times til I finally settled on what I have now. It did help increase views.:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Me too! Working on doing better thumbnails after the inspiration Markus gave us.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi 👋 Ana. The videos that stopped growing suddenly had a renewed life. So now I want to change all my past thumbnails. He he he
Eaglevp: That's going to take some time Lal
Mommy Guide Inc: Keith I will try promise. That should be a future goal - crafty nights done in 45mins that would be a world record for me. He he he
Tim Heale 9: I premier my recorded podcasts
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Aaahhh! Thank you for that explanation!!! Learned something new.
Tim Heale 9: I also repurpose all my live show and podcasts as well as my recorded shows
Mommy Guide Inc: My thumbnails before were so busy! Text so small. Really bad.
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Markus and all the excellent people who are here 😀👍
Eaglevp: Hi EJNAR
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ejnar!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Q about thumbnails…if I have a guest, it’s better to use a photo about the topic or put the photo of the guest?
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hi Ejnar!
Mommy Guide Inc: Ana from my experience - having the guest on the thumbnail is better. Based on my stats:)
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Keith, Lala and Ana. 😀
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Thank you Lala, I can see that.
Fishstick USA: That was a good thumbnail about losing weight
Fishstick USA: I did not think is was real
Fishstick USA: It drew me in
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh my thanks for pushing me on video editing Markus, Roy and the others. It’s getting easier but too many things to be learned still but at least I am able to upload almost daily.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: @FishstickUSA agree. That video also is one of Markus most viewed videos I think.:) great interview as well:)
David W. Ryan: Hi Markus! sorry I'm late
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi David!
Eaglevp: hI@David W. Ryan
David W. Ryan: hi Lala and @Eaglevp !
Tim Heale 9: You could ask me back on