Eaglevp: Hi Lala
Eaglevp: Hello Horace
Mommy Guide Inc: and here we go!
Mommy Guide Inc: 🙂
Horace Podmore Political Commentator: =Hi Keith
Eaglevp: Hi@Pierre Kelly
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Keith@Eaglevp:)
Ellie Calhoun: Markus!!!
Pierre Kelly: wondered why you removed a few of my comments?
Mommy Guide Inc: Let's do the Markus wave!
Eaglevp: Hi Ellie
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ellie! Loved your photos in Boston! It must have been super fun.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Happy Thursday friends 👋
Eaglevp: Yo Ana
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana! Greetings from Friday in the future:) he he he
Mommy Guide Inc: We should put together all these awesome dance moves Markus:)
Mommy Guide Inc: This song could be a great way to inspire us to get going:)
Eaglevp: Blast off
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: It is inspiring!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Aw but the song is so good
Fishstick USA: Hello Markus
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Maybe do it in the middle 😄
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Philip @Fishstick USA:)
Ellie Calhoun: Try it! An experiment, no dancing... but never get rid of the song!
Eaglevp: Hi@Fishstick USA
Eaglevp: Hi@Paul Burke
Pierre Kelly: Paul's here!
Fishstick USA: C: When things get hard, do not be hard on yourself. I missed a Friday video date. Saturday was fine.
Paul Burke: breaking up after watching the Barbie movie? what would be the silliest movie to breakup after watching? Die Hard? Transformers. "sorry darling...I'm a autobot and you're a decepticon. it's over"
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Paul! lol:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes I agree Philip - give ourself grace. There are days that we just have to let it be. Tomorrow is another opportunity:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks everyone. If you have a question for Markus pls put a Q: so Markus can easily see it:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Also it would be awesome if you could smash that LIKE button now:) And consider subscribing if you are enjoying the show thus far:)
Stannex: Button smashed! Hi, everyone!
Eaglevp: Hi Stan
Fishstick USA: Q: When do you decide to make a change on your channel? Examples: Do you reedit or shorten your intro video, or start it earlier? Do i publish on different days due to work schedule? Change whatever?
Horace Podmore Political Commentator: If you stop enjoying it then you burn out quicker, then is the time to come to attention turn right and march away 😻
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus is top at inspiring people. That's one of the many reasons we love Markus in the community:)
Eaglevp: Agree Horace
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Stan@Stannex! Thanks for smashing that LIKE button:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yea! I’m about to experiment something new…but yes it needs to be something that you enjoy doing.
Horace Podmore Political Commentator: Try a mix of content to see what you enjoy the most
Fishstick USA: C: I did not shave today in honor of you Markus. 🧔‍♂️ My goal is to be more like you.
Fishstick USA: Seriously, you were big on my making a channel.
Eaglevp: You should always be experimenting with your channel and different niche's until you find one that works for you.
Fishstick USA: @eaglevp Good point
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yea!!! Live stream is not picking up for me so I’m going to do recordings and pop up with reels and shorts…
Horace Podmore Political Commentator: Consistance is the key
Mommy Guide Inc: awww that's so nice @Fishstick USA. Glad that you have started and continue to put out content. Cheering you on my friend:)
Adam Tinkoff: Good morning!
Stannex: It certainly matters if you're livestreaming. But if you're uploading edited videos, timing of release only really matters if a HUGE portion of your audience are watching in the first 12 hours.
Mommy Guide Inc: I agree Horace & Keith. Continuously be learning and exploring:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Coach Adam:)
Stannex: Hi, Adam!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Adam is here!!!
Horace Podmore Political Commentator: Designer stubble!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi everyone. Hi Markus. sorry I'm late. Cookies anyone?
Ejnar Riis Hansen: Hello Everyone. Hope you all have a fantastic Thursday 😀
Eaglevp: Hi@Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing
Eaglevp: Hello Ejnar
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Love fishstick content!!!
Fishstick USA: C: Markus, I see you are getting more comfortable. This helped me. I was too stiff. Some of my friends tell me that I seem more comfortable and my personality is coming out.
Ejnar Riis Hansen: Hi Keith😀
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: hi back @eaglevp
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi my sister from another mother - Janet@Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Btw Markus you have been such a trooper and supportive friend on my live streams ♥️♥️♥️♥️♥️ you are such a giver!!!
Eaglevp: Ana do you know what type of content your subscribers want,you can always ask on your stream or community post
Fishstick USA: @ana zugheri - faith52 thank you. You have great interviews.
Mommy Guide Inc: yey! What a win for you @Fishstick USA:)
Fishstick USA: My site is @NextStepOfFaith
Mommy Guide Inc: Ana - delivers the best things about basic stuff with a little bit extra:)
Ellie Calhoun: Hi everyone! I'm here but listening while walking so not chatting much! It's almost 80 degree here!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Ellie!!!
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Janet!
Ellie Calhoun: I was just going to say get an accountability partner or 2!
Eaglevp: https://www.youtube.com/@NextStepofFaith
Adam Tinkoff: I'm doing the thing... it's just not making videos right now... but I'm slinging a lot of paint.
Adam Tinkoff: but I plan to come back soon.
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for sharing the link Keith:) Pls do check it out and consider subscribing too:)
Fishstick USA: C: Look for encouragement. Look to your friends.
Mommy Guide Inc: And what awesome results those slinging of paint has created Adam:) Excited for your return:)
Adam Tinkoff: I'm subscriber 41 for FishSticks. Whoop
Mommy Guide Inc: Adam's return to content creation.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Adam:)
Horace Podmore Political Commentator: If you work colab and encourage the other to keep going that can help
Eaglevp: Adam would love to see you do a live while doing a painting from start to finish
Stannex: And people like to WATCH you making art.
Ellie Calhoun: Sometimes making a small shift in content or your audience or your intention is enough to re-inspire
Eaglevp: I have learnt a lot just watching you draw Stan
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: My mother doesn’t even watch my videos lol 😂
Stannex: Thanks, Keith! :^)
Fishstick USA: C: Markus, I have not promoted my channel yet. I told few friends and family. Iam working on technical and consistency. My plan is to start promoting at the first of the year.
Mariane Cresp: Hello Markus 👋🏼
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: That's such good advise Markus. I am trying to simplify. (I know... that would take a miracle) 😻
Adam Tinkoff: Yes, a little bit more often will always be better than a whole lot every once in a while. Say that 10x fast.
Fishstick USA: @Elle Calhoun - I like your comments 🙂
Horace Podmore Political Commentator: YT isn't good to new channels!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Mariane:)
Eaglevp: Hi@Mariane Cresp
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Mariane. You are up early
Horace Podmore Political Commentator: And LEDA
Mariane Cresp: Hello 👋🏼 Keith
Mariane Cresp: Hi 👋🏼 Janet. I was up earlier at 2am … went to bed at 5am and back up at 7:30am now
Horace Podmore Political Commentator: dit dit dit dar
Fishstick USA: C: I teach a Sunday School class of 2-4 people. Audience size does not concern me. 20 views is great for me.
Mariane Cresp: When things are too hard, I close the book on all my to-dos … grab a clean piece of paper and just do one ☝️ physical action thing.
Ellie Calhoun: @Fishstick USA thanks!☺️
StressedOutStressFre: Aloha Fam
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Vincent @StressedOutStressFree
Eaglevp: Hello@StressedOutStressFre
Stannex: Hi, Mariane!
Mariane Cresp: Hi 👋🏼 Stan
StressedOutStressFre: thank you
Eaglevp: Just supported you Vincent
StressedOutStressFre: Hi @Mommy Guide Inc @Eaglevp
Ellie Calhoun: Yes! Even if it's a failure, because it means you tried and are learning!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: That’s how we learn 🤗
Mariane Cresp: Yay, you did it! WIN!
Ellie Calhoun: Lots of great reminders Markus!!
Fishstick USA: Thank you Markus !
Ellie Calhoun: You got this Markus!!!