Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello 👋 happy Thursday
Eaglevp: Hello @Ana Zugheri - Faith52
Eaglevp: Hi Neil
Ellie Calhoun: hi everyone!
Eaglevp: Hi Ellie
Creative Amplifiers: Hello Marcus & Neil
Tim Heale 9: Evening all, YouTube has an thing that only some get to grow, it's not for all 😏
Eaglevp: Hi@Creative Amplifiers
Eaglevp: Evening Tim enjoyed your show tonight
Tim Heale 9: I'm just kicking back with a spiced rum or two 😂
Creative Amplifiers: I'll bring the eggs!
Stannex: Ears for Markus!!!
Eaglevp: Hi Stan
Creative Amplifiers: @Eaglevp Hello
Eaglevp: Neil you should have Tim on your channel he talks about mental health
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Hello Markus and all
Tim Heale 9: I love Portugal, especially Oporto
Eaglevp: Hi@Fishstick ~ Phillip
Ileane Smith: Hi Markus! Hey Neil🙋🏽‍♀️
Ileane Smith: Hello everyone
Eaglevp: Hello@Ileane Smith
Sammy Super Star: Hey Everyone!
Eaglevp: Sammy in the room how are you my friend
Tim Heale 9: Ecamm is my main platform
Sammy Super Star: I'm doing really good @Eaglevp
Eaglevp: When's the next movie Sammy
Tim Heale 9: @NeilFarrimond are you in competition with Adrian?
Ellie Calhoun: Don't forget to hit the Like Button👍
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: The world belongs to the brave! I call that faith
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: In what part of USA are you Neil?
Tim Heale 9: Are any of you guys coming to London Podcast Show in May?
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: lol people are shocked when they meet me because they don’t think I’m as short as I really am 😋☺️
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Oh! How cool is that!!! Portugal
Creative Amplifiers: @Tim Heale 9 Yes I will be going in May. I have enjoyed it for last couple of years
Tim Heale 9: @Creative Amplifiers it is a great show
Eaglevp: It certainly is Tim
Tim Heale 9: I think I will. be there again
Creative Amplifiers: Ah you are too kind Neil 😀
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes!! So much easier, and great idea for accountability
Creative Amplifiers: ......... It is Mark!
Tim Heale 9: PodMatch is a great place to find guests for shows
Tim Heale 9: @NeilFarrimond book me 😏
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Wow! I should not complain about solo producing lol 😂
Tim Heale 9: I can be very funny
Tim Heale 9: I am very happy doing both solo and with multi guests
Tim Heale 9: Live is so much fun
Tim Heale 9: @Markus Schaub You don't watch mine 😏
Tim Heale 9: I go live every Thursday liv e at 7pm GMT
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: That’s right Tim, I love going live it is just that “push the button thing that gets me. Once on it is fun 🤩
Creative Amplifiers: I love being live but I am a musician........................
Tim Heale 9: @Creative Amplifiers You really don't want to hear me sing 😂
Tim Heale 9: @HoracePodmore uses Twitter X all the time
Creative Amplifiers: @Tim Heale 9 or me I'm a percussionist
Tim Heale 9: @Creative Amplifiers I have no rthyem at all, I'm also tone deaf
Creative Amplifiers: @Tim Heale 9 🤣
Tim Heale 9: @Markus Schaub @NeilFarrimond I get more views after my lives
Creative Amplifiers: How did I know that would be the answer 🤣
Stannex: You need an American co-host ...? 😆
Eaglevp: You will have to plan that 24 hour one Markus
Creative Amplifiers: We wanted to have an easy way for people to get involved. Sharing pictures was the way to do that
Creative Amplifiers: ....also a way to help promote their channel or content
Tim Heale 9: All of the above
Eaglevp: Evmux people like me,not a Mac user myself
Creative Amplifiers: .....yes Neil live research for the show!
Tim Heale 9: I was on StreamYard before switching to Ecamm which was a mission
Tim Heale 9: LEDA is fun but it has is it day
Tech Troublemaker: Dang I am late.
Eaglevp: Yes you are Roy
Creative Amplifiers: Hey @Tech Troublemaker
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Creative Amplifiers
Tim Heale 9: With Ecamm you just need bandwith
Eaglevp: Markus you will have to master going live with the pocket 3
Tech Troublemaker: I am not sure the benefit of going live to both having to stay in the middle the whole time. 🙂 It will cut off my arms IG as I talk with my hands
Creative Amplifiers: Yes my life got much easier when I got full cable
Basic Networks and Streaming: Hola all
Eaglevp: Hi@Basic Networks and Streaming
Eaglevp: Yes you have to have the Youtube studio open with the pocket 3
Basic Networks and Streaming: If I had to do the two I’ll just use two computers
Basic Networks and Streaming: Yes 1st time with this account
Tim Heale 9: I have used both Restream and StreamYard with Ecamm live then I got questioned by LiveSTream Pros why I was doing that, because I didn't have the bandwith 😏
Eaglevp: You just have to open Youtube in your browser on your phone and not the app
Basic Networks and Streaming: You know me well. Only brought 3 network with me to the Philippines so I’m getting better
Tech Troublemaker: Victor, tell Lala we said Hey!
Basic Networks and Streaming: I will
Basic Networks and Streaming: Today. It’s 6am ish now
Basic Networks and Streaming: We will have breakfast soon.
Tim Heale 9: I'm going to be travelling this summer and uploading and maybe going live on my Riding Through History tour of Europe this summer
Tech Troublemaker: #CreatorCamp
Tech Troublemaker: I plan to make my wife go with me. Haha.
Stannex: I'd love to be able to go this time ... but it's not looking good right now.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Haha Roy!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Sorry I’m late
Eaglevp: Hi Janet
Creative Amplifiers: …. Make Roy?!…..
Tim Heale 9: More Spiced Rum 😂
Tech Troublemaker: Strongly and lovely encouraging her to go
Tech Troublemaker: She is a red head, I can't make her do anything really. Haha.
Creative Amplifiers: ….. yes Roy 🤣
Tim Heale 9: TTFN Tar Tar For Now
Creative Amplifiers: I’m married to a redhead too Roy. I understand 🤣
Eaglevp: Great stream with an excellent guest Markus
Creative Amplifiers: Wonderful eve guys thank you
Stannex: Great conversation, guys!
Tim Heale 9: Do you want me on?