@FishstickUSA: Hello Markus
@eaglevp: Hi Phillip
@eaglevp: Yes you do have to work on that
@eaglevp: I do
@collegeslammer: hey all
@collegeslammer: kind of a small crowd
@eaglevp: That’s a good start Markus film yourself cleaning up your studio
@eaglevp: Hello collegeslammer welcome to the stream
@eaglevp: Do you sleep well Markus
@eaglevp: Motivation
@FishstickUSA: I bought an Elgato prompter and an Elgato 4k Webcam. I use it when ai lead a devotion livestream. Helps we with eye contact.
@TechTroublemaker: Notion?!
@eaglevp: Ai that’s what I am trying out at present
@FishstickUSA: I wish I had your natural eye contact
@eaglevp: Hi Roy
@eaglevp: I am trying VEO 3
@eaglevp: Yes make videos
@TechTroublemaker: oooo what is AI?
@TechTroublemaker: yes, I have heard about AI in Notion but figured you needed a paid account to really use it.
@TechTroublemaker: Life already has given me a trial period fairly often.
@TechTroublemaker: Hey Keith! Hey Phillip!
@TechTroublemaker: Now I am playing with ChatGPT Atlas as I really want ChatGPT to really get up in to my private business.
@TechTroublemaker: You will find out I am watching Alive with Steve Burns from Blues Clues. 🙂
@TechTroublemaker: He is attempting to answer life's questions. Not sure I agree with his attempts but an interesting experiment.