Mommy Guide Inc: Here we go!
Kali Co: ooo this is a great convo!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Kali!
Mommy Guide Inc: What you drinking today Markus? Water? he he he
Mommy Guide Inc: oooh the Cola drink. he he he
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi everyone.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Janet@Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: LALA!!!! (little girl scream!!!)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: we talked about this topic in our SA group today.
Kali Co: hahahahahha hey janet!!
Kali Co: JANET!!!!! 🤗❤️💃
Mommy Guide Inc: he he he. Janet - in a shrieking voice too:) Here goes my favorite intro music:)
Kali Co: awe i miss stephanie i feel like i haven't spoken with her in a while
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: 🎶🎶🎶🎵🎵
Mommy Guide Inc: Agree Kali - actually I miss you all he he he.
Mommy Guide Inc: oh yes that's Markus favorite hand gesture - right?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I feel the same @Kali Co Miss her
Kali Co: @Mommy Guide Inc i wish we could all have a meet up easily
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @Kali Co & everyone. can you imagine? it would be so fun and amazing
Kali Co: kevin and his cool robots
Kali Co: @Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing right??? it'd be life changing energy
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey! Hi Markus!
Kali Co: @Mommy Guide Inc it'll definitely happen. i have no doubts. i just get impatient!
Mommy Guide Inc: absolutely - great to be back on the chat!
Kali Co: #MARKUSRULES
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I can't wait for the topic.
Kali Co: you could totally use that thumbnail for this one
Kali Co: that would be an awesome thumbnail for this stream!
Sammy Super Star: Hey Markus
Kali Co: sammy!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Sammy
Kali Co: Q: What're your thoughts on art AI stealing art from artists & then selling it without giving credit to the original artists it pulled from? Do artists have anything to worry about?
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: What trending topic can one use for 2023?
Mommy Guide Inc: What is this app again Markus?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: what is the name of this AI ???
Kali Co: chatgpt @Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: thanks Kali
Kali Co: i think ai will continue to be a trending topic, and some interesting ideas you can use for your content being a crafter! @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: thanks Kali!
Mommy Guide Inc: Great question Kali.
Kali Co: oo i can't wait to see how it answers lala's question!
Kali Co: LOL @Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing
Kali Co: i think ai is awesome for writing blog posts and emails
Kali Co: you can use chatgpt to write emails
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I can't wait to try to write a blog post using ai from my live.
Kali Co: yes!! @Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing
Sammy Super Star: Dee nimmin went live and he made videos ideas and scripts
Kali Co: Q: How to make a good youtube thumbnail
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Sammy!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh interesting Sammh
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: that would be Sammy
Kali Co: Jasper gives youtube ideas, outlines, titles, and hooks
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: □
Kali Co: (Jasper the ai)
Mommy Guide Inc: yes lala- start working on those 3-5minuter basic crafting videos. - note to self!
Mommy Guide Inc: he he he. tons of suggestions there.
Kali Co: fair enough!
Mommy Guide Inc: great suggestion for thumbnails. but its going away in 2023 right? on YouTube anyway?
Kali Co: solid advice!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: thumbnails are really goind away in 2023. wow
Cheryl Wolf: I’m late , I have cookies
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: hey cheryl. we were drinking water at the beginning!
Kali Co: just less important, but not going away
Kali Co: 😂😂😂 cookies!!! @Cheryl Wolf
Mommy Guide Inc: HI Cheryl! Cookies - is always a great idea. he he he
Cheryl Wolf: 🤪kali
Sammy Super Star: Can you do one with live streaming
Kali Co: LOL
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed - Roy is right. Die Hard is a Christmas movie indeed.
Sammy Super Star: Keep me accountable before the Interview next week I need to have 3K ahhahah
Mommy Guide Inc: Go Sammy. You got this.
Kali Co: so awesome!! @Sammy Super Star
Eaglevp: Evening Markus
Eaglevp: Hi Kali
Cheryl Wolf: Hi keith
Eaglevp: Hello Lala and Cheryl
Kali Co: hey!! @Eaglevp
Eaglevp: Hi Sammy
Sammy Super Star: Hey @Eaglevp
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Keith:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Congratulations Keith:) that's awesome:)
Sammy Super Star: that is amazing @Eaglevp
Kali Co: no that thumbnail was perfect for this video!!
Kali Co: the one you showed us first!
Kali Co: those are cute though
Kali Co: oo oo
Kali Co: Draw an alien skeleton playing poker with dogs
Kali Co: in a swamp
Sammy Super Star: do a person interviewing oersin
Kali Co: oo oooo
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh I love that. I would use it!!!
Kali Co: WOAH
Kali Co: those are so cool hahahhaha
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: They are so you Kali
Kali Co: an alligator eating a popsicle at a themepark!
Kali Co: @Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing omg that's such a cool compliment thank you 😂❤️
Sammy Super Star: Interviewing a Person I mean
Kali Co: i like the cartoon one
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: □
Sammy Super Star: I got a new keyboard and its tinier then I have been using for years
Kali Co: LOL
Cheryl Wolf: 🤣
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: good one Kali. I would like to see that
Mommy Guide Inc: ooh that's a nice one. let's see what it shows for French fries falling in love Markus:)
Kali Co: yeah one more! of the two french fries falling in love
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: □
Kali Co: omg i've never seen these emotes janet hahaha thank you for showing me them
Kali Co: OMG YES
Mommy Guide Inc: Kali they're cute!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: so fun
Kali Co: hahahahhaha
Kali Co: omg so cute
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Thanks Markus. that was fun and interesting.