Tim Heale 9: @Mommy Guide Inc thank you Lala
Eaglevp: Another amazing Leda .......Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: And here we go:)
Eaglevp: I have got my dancing shoe's on now
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed Keith. 5 minutes of cardio - let’s go:)
Eaglevp: Ok Lala that's a few pounds off the weight
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Markus and Tatiana:)
Eaglevp: Hello Tatiana
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Ana:)
Eaglevp: Hi@Ana Zugheri - Faith 52
Mommy Guide Inc: If you are not yet subscribed to our awesome guest here is her channel - https://youtube.com/@TatianaTeaches
Mommy Guide Inc: And don’t forget to smash that Like button:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for sharing your amazing journey Tatiana. How you found a way to realize and execute your plans and now you’re here.:) what an inspiring story. Congratulations!
David W. Ryan: Hi Markus and Tatiana!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi David!
Eaglevp: Hi@David W. Ryan
David W. Ryan: Hi Lala!
Tim Heale 9: LEDA Team together 😻
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi David@SpoolingAround
David W. Ryan: Hi @Eaglevp
Eaglevp: Hey@MySnoopy80
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Hi @Mysnoopy80! Great to see you back in the chat:)
MySnoopy80: Hi@eaglevp
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: So powerful
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Beauty from ashes.
MySnoopy80: Hi Lala❤️great to see you too
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi everyone
Eaglevp: Hi@Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing
Tim Heale 9: I use Ecamm Live all the time nor just for live but also for recording
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Janet my friend hello@AnimalParadise-Communication & Healing
Cheryl Wolf: Hello all
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @CherylWolf
Eaglevp: Cheryl's in the room
Cheryl Wolf: Hey lala
Cheryl Wolf: Hey Tim & Keith
Eaglevp: Hi Cheryl how are you?
Cheryl Wolf: Great ! How are you?
Tim Heale 9: I've not see any live from you lately Cheryl?
Mommy Guide Inc: Aww thanks to everybody for being here and I hope you’re being inspired by Markus and Tatiana. Pls don’t forget to Like this livestream:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: what basic steps can one take to become more confident in our story telling as content creators Tatiana?
Ileane Smith: Hi Markus! Hi Tatiana 🙋🏽‍♀️
Cheryl Wolf: Very good point Tatiana
Tim Heale 9: @TatianaTeachers The more I go live the better and more comfortable I become
Eaglevp: Ileane Smith hello
Ileane Smith: Hey everyone 😍
Mommy Guide Inc: Find an accountability partner/grp and to give us tough love if need be.:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Ouch! That’s me
Ellie Calhoun: Hi everyone!
Eaglevp: Hi@Shelly Saves the Day
Ileane Smith: Create your personal checklist
Eaglevp: Hi Ellie
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I love lists!!!!
Ileane Smith: Hi Shelly!
Shelly Saves the Day: 20% ?
David W. Ryan: 10
Ellie Calhoun: 10%
Eaglevp: 10
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I do have to get accountability
Ileane Smith: 10
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey hi @ShellySavesTheDay:)
Ellie Calhoun: I was going to say2% lol
Shelly Saves the Day: hi Ileane 👋
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Ellie:)
Shelly Saves the Day: hi
Ileane Smith: What age are these people 😂😂😂
Tim Heale 9: As long as we make mental health easy to talk about them we are getting the message across 😻
Ileane Smith: Sometimes I remember stories but I can’t …. Oops forgot what I was about to say
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow! That’s a great eye opener why story telling is more impactful
Shelly Saves the Day: 🎊
Ileane Smith: Markus I love your color scheme and layout
Tim Heale 9: I'm here for the first time 😂
Tim Heale 9: I had an awesome story teller on my show this evening
Mommy Guide Inc: A story is a narrative of things that has happened?
MySnoopy80: Beginning, middle, end?
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh indeed not just past but indeed the present and future.:)
Ellie Calhoun: @MySnoopy80 I was thinking that
Ellie Calhoun: No
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: This is soooo good!!!
Eaglevp: Yes
MySnoopy80: Yes so much!,
Tim Heale 9: Had that as a kid at Saturday morning pictures
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes!!! Curiosity
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: @Ellie I crave chocolate cake ALL THE TIME 🤪
MySnoopy80: Me too;))
Ellie Calhoun: @ana 😂
David W. Ryan: love the gaphic
Mommy Guide Inc: Personal connection via story telling with our community - keeping this in mind.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Practice telling stories to build more confidence in using them better. Thanks:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Story Structure: Hook-Vivid Language-Characters (protagonist/antagonist)-Place-Plot-Purpose
Cheryl Wolf: Thank you Tatiana
Mommy Guide Inc: I agree Ana. Thanks so much Tatiana. Again if you are not yet following Tatiana pls do so https://youtube.com/@TatianaTeaches
David W. Ryan: this is great info!
Mommy Guide Inc: What a beautiful show today Markus and Tatiana. Thanks so much.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: 👏👏👏👏👏
Mommy Guide Inc: Take note of events in our life and document them. I do so mostly via memory keeping - with photos and journaling
MySnoopy80: Bye all! Have a great week❤️
Mommy Guide Inc: Call to action - Practice! Awesome. Thanks again Tatiana:)
Eaglevp: Great guest and an excellent stream Markus I learnt a lot from this stream
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks everyone and hope to see you all back in the chat next week. You all are awesome!
Mommy Guide Inc: Vivid language. - I think I want to practice this more
Cheryl Wolf: ❤️
MySnoopy80: The human connection
Mommy Guide Inc: The hook I learned to add them from Markus during my first LEDA. He encouraged me to add a hook in my introduction
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yes Markus - make me accountable pls:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes a part 2 pls!