Mommy Guide Inc: Let the countdown begin.:)
Adam Tinkoff: Markus!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Y'all!
Mariane Cresp: Hello all!
Eaglevp: Evening Markus
Eaglevp: Hi Roy
Eaglevp: Hello@Mariane Cresp
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Lala @Mommy Guide Inc Hey @Eaglevp Hey @Adam Tinkoff
Eaglevp: Hi Lala
Eaglevp: Hey Adam
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Markus, Roy, Mariane & Keith! Missed last week’s episode. Glad to be back with you all in the chat.:) Hope everyone is doing great.:)
Tim Heale 9: Greetings one and all
Mariane Cresp: Hi Keith!
Eaglevp: Hi Tim
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello 👋
Eaglevp: Hi@Ana Zugheri - Faith52
Mommy Guide Inc: Howdy Tim and Ana!
Tech Troublemaker: 😥I missed last week too. I am sorry
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Coach Adam.:)
Tech Troublemaker: I am confident that Live streaming has given me confidence. I have spoken in front of crowds thanks to streaming.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello hello Tim, Lala, Roy, Markus!!!!! Glad to see y’all here as I sit in carline 😃
Adam Tinkoff: I'm on video conference calls all morning, so it's very much the same, but I get to talk a whole lot more most of the time.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I Just made a reel and ugh! I was so nervous 😩
Mommy Guide Inc: Doing livestream has truly built my confidence level and made me able
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: @Lala and you have gotten better and better!!!
Tim Heale 9: I love live streaming
Mommy Guide Inc: Ana in the car with a little bit of extra! ! It can be a segment Ana
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Uuuhh! I like that! Great idea. ⭐️
Mommy Guide Inc: Aww thanks Ana still a very much work in progress but truly i continue to learn so much more about myself and others via livestreaming
Tech Troublemaker: I used to keep my Live Streaming alter ego to myself and now I let anyone know. I am proud of what I am doing online so it is easier to share with others.
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Tim Heale 9
Tim Heale 9: Hi @Tech Troublemaker
Tim Heale 9: The more you do it the easer it gets
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: @Tech Troublemaker you are another example of wonderful growth. I loved your show this past Thursday! You inspired me.
Tech Troublemaker: PSA: Don't upgrade to Sonoma yet. Some streaming software platforms are freezing thanks to new Apple enhancement for video conferencing. Give it a week or two.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Start, improve, don’t stop!!! ❤️
Andy Halper: Wise man you are!
Mommy Guide Inc: And thanks for doing your show Roy - learned so much from watching your livestreams - your interviews and tutorials is bow a constant source of info and inspiration.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Andy!!!!!!! 🎉🎉🎉🎉🎉
Tech Troublemaker: Thank you @Ana Zugheri - Faith52 You guys inspire me.
Andy Halper: ANA!!! 💫
Andrea Nunn: Hi all!
Mommy Guide Inc: So true Markus. I absolutely agree.:)
Tech Troublemaker: Hey, um, this is Markus show. Say nice things about him. He is awesome and consistent and I can't wait to meet you guys at #CreatorCamp
Andrea Nunn: I am watching on the big screen versus my phone
Andy Halper: MARKUS, you make my heart sing! I have no idea what that means, but it’s true!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Andy!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Markus I think you got yourself a tagline for your show!!! Start, improve, don’t stop 🛑
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Andrea:)
Andy Halper: ROY ROCKS!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Andy Halper
Andrea Nunn: Journey still going but evolving!
Andy Halper: LALA is an angel to us all! That’s a good thing!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Andrea Nunn
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: This is the show and the space Markus has created!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Roy for the reminder.:)
Ellie Calhoun: I'm here! Good distraction!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Ellie!!!! 🎉🎉🎉
Tim Heale 9: One has to scarper TTFN Tar tar for now
Ellie Calhoun: I had my notifications off so I can be productive. 😂 but out of the corner of my eye saw Lala's announcement
Andrea Nunn: Hi @Ellie Calhoun @Mommy Guide Inc @Tech Troublemaker
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks so much everyone for being here don’t forget to smash the Like button friends. One thing Markus has taught me is that supporting other creators is a priceless thing.
Ellie Calhoun: I'm editing a video I don't want to do...
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ellie!
Andy Halper: This feels like a reunion of sorts … both familiar and new.
Ellie Calhoun: Hi everyone!!
Mommy Guide Inc: TTFN Tim! Thanks for dropping by:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey congratulations Ellie - you can do this. I can so relate about video editing.:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I’m so excited for you!
Mommy Guide Inc: Good for
Ellie Calhoun: Thanks Lala... I'm shifting a little in my content style... my topic is becoming about self care and its importance. I have an idea to do more of a podcast style and interviews.
Tech Troublemaker: I did an AirBnB for my last night.
Mommy Guide Inc: Good for you Markus for doing new things:)
Tech Troublemaker: Good for you Markus for doing new things:)
Ellie Calhoun: But it makes me more nervous! Yeah, I'm thinking Live... yikes 😬
Andy Halper: There’s a great book by Peter Block called: THE ANSWER TO HOW IS YES!
Ellie Calhoun: Nope, well I've been interviewed
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh wow! Congratulations Ellie!!! That is awesome. A pivot! Cheering you on Ellie:)
Mariane Cresp: still nerve wracking for me ... but getting better at managing my nerves
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh thanks foe the book recommendation Andy!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Glad to see y’all here! Like Ellie said you are a great distraction and forget about craziness of the day.