Angelo Allen: Hi LaLa and Animal Paradise!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Janet and Angelo!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Angelo
Angelo Allen: I LOVE these swinging dancers!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: 💃💃💃💃💃💃
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Bette!!!!
Eaglevp: Hi Lala
Eaglevp: Hello@Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing
Eaglevp: Hi Markus
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: my favorite song/video
Eaglevp: Hey@Angelo Allen
Mommy Guide Inc: So true. 💃 🕺 is a great way to exercise.:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: LET"S GO
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Keith!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Let’s Go! Creators anthem oh yeah!
Angelo Allen: I LOVE IT!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: amen Lala
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I loved when Markus did makeup
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed Janet that was truly epic!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for being here everyone pls don’t forget to smash that LIKE button:)
Cheryl Wolf: Hey All
Angelo Allen: Hey Cheryl!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Cheryl!!!!
Eaglevp: Hi again Cheryl
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Keith
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Keith
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Angelo
Mommy Guide Inc: Aww the great Raym - the awesome creator of the Let’s Go song of Markus:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Confetti!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: don't forget to LIKE
Eaglevp: Thank you Markus
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: exciting Keith. yay
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey!!!! Congratulations Keith @EagleVP
Eaglevp: Hi Bette
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Bette!!! so happy you are here.
Eaglevp: Hi@Fishstick USA
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Betty
Mommy Guide Inc: Bette @crazysexymenopause I almost fit the title Bette except for the “sexy” part. Kidding aside I know being sexy is a mindset and not just a physical thing.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: What a great collaboration husband and wife team. Love it!
Mommy Guide Inc: I am glad that Bette and Janet - that you both decided to be in front of the camera.:)
Angelo Allen: Thanks Mommy Guide LaLa!
Cheryl Wolf: 💜
Angelo Allen: About 18 months ago...
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Love you have each other. 💖
Mommy Guide Inc: Bette’s channel delivers a ton of awesome content. Pls don’t forget to Like and Subscribe too - https://youtube.com/@crazysexymenopause
Eaglevp: Evening again Tim
Angelo Allen: Hey Tim! Boom back atcha!
Tim Heale 9: Hi Angelo thanks for your comments on LEDA
Tim Heale 9: Hi Lala
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Tim
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey there Tim
Tim Heale 9: Hi Cheryl thank for joining my live earlier 😻
Eaglevp: Welcome@Paul Burke
Cheryl Wolf: Hey Paul
Tim Heale 9: Hi Animal 😻
Mommy Guide Inc: That’s such a great one - after the storm is a 🌈:)
Paul Burke: hey there 🙂
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh Bette you are young!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I'm with you. Life is just beginning. Love that becasue it really is.
Tim Heale 9: Locked up together for a couple of years ❤️
Mommy Guide Inc: It’s a beautiful and inspiring indeed. You absolutely walk your talk Bette:)
Tim Heale 9: There's brave
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: yay Angelo. you are such a beautiful couple and team
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Paul-ie
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hello friends 👋👋👋👋
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Ana
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: ANA!!!!
Eaglevp: Hello@Ana Zugheri - Faith 52
Tim Heale 9: I covered menopause from a mans perspective on my show a while ago 😻
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana!
Tim Heale 9: Hi Ana
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hello @Mommy Guide Inc
Eaglevp: I remember that show Tim
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hey Tim!!! ☀️
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Such a real topic!!!! Hot 🥵 flashes are real!!!!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Menopause is not a death sentence - it’s an awesome time to reboot / reset / reassess our body and how to move forward. Love it!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: For me is coffee 😖
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: If only Lala!!! I have had night sweats for 30 years! so fun! not! everyone is different.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Pick your poison!
Tim Heale 9: Make it an everyday conversation 👍
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Learning to age well.
Mommy Guide Inc: I went thru it very early as a result of surgery and was utterly shocked at the changes I had to go thru.
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh my. Glad that you eventually realized that it was hot flashes Janet.
David W. Ryan: Hi Markus and Bette!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi David
Eaglevp: Hi@David W. Ryan
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi David W. Ryan! Love how you say your name this way.:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: that is very humbling Bette.
Mommy Guide Inc: Live A healthier lifestyle - note to self!
Mommy Guide Inc: Great question Markus!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: that is so true Bette. I thought I was dying!!!
Paul Burke: pretty smooth on editing there Markus. Smooth transisitons
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes! Be supportive 😉
Cheryl Wolf: internal heat
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: have to get sweaters and jackets that button. tear them off and then chills so throw back on.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed a supportive community - partner, family, friends would be a great thing.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Designing programs for healthier lifestyle - that’s awesome Bette.
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow we’re at the top of the hour. Time flies when we’re having so much fun.
Eaglevp: Great show Markus & Bette
Tim Heale 9: Enjoyed the show 😻
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks everyone! Thanks Markus & Bette.:) what a great way to start my day and Friyay with you all.:) Have a great rest of the day everyone.:)