Mommy Guide Inc: And here we go!
itdair.network: Yay! Thank you very much @Mommy Guide Inc !
itdair.network: Yay!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Coach Suzan in the house!
Cheryl Wolf: 💃💃yes Dance
Cheryl Wolf: Hello All
Cheryl Wolf: Hey lala
Eaglevp: Hey again Cheryl and Hello Lala
Cheryl Wolf: Hey keith
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hi 👋
Cheryl Wolf: hey Ana
Eaglevp: Hi@Ana Zugheri - Faith 52
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Markus & Suzan.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Lala!!! Cheryl!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Everyone is here!!!
itdair.network: Hi Cheryl! Hi everyone arriving now!
Cheryl Wolf: Hey Janet
Eaglevp: Hi@Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing
itdair.network: Hi Markus and Suzan!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: 💃💃💃💃💃
Eaglevp: Hi Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Cheryl! tim!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: In the car but here listening 👂
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I so love this song and video
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: let's go
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey! Janet!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Ana
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: don't forget to LIKE
Mommy Guide Inc: Safety travels @Ana:)
Fishstick USA: Markus, I enjoy your countdown up to your show.
Eaglevp: Hi@Fishstick USA
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @Eaglevp hey back
Mommy Guide Inc: Its so much fun indeed @FishstickUSA
Cheryl Wolf: Yes truly is
itdair.network: Thank you Markus! Yes first time here! 🙂
Fishstick USA: ? Where did you get your theme song?
Horace Podmore: Haj Markus
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yay coach Suzan!
Sammy Super Star: Hey Markus
Eaglevp: Hi@Horace Podmore
Fishstick USA: Hello Suzan
itdair.network: Hi Sammy!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Sammy
itdair.network: Hi Suszan!
Horace Podmore: Hi Suzan
Eaglevp: Hi@Sammy Super Star
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Suzan!!
Cheryl Wolf: Hey Sammy
Mommy Guide Inc: @fishstick this is the link of Markus’ stream where he invited the composer of his awesome intro song
Horace Podmore: Hi Sammy
Mommy Guide Inc: https://www.youtube.com/live/Vjyr6JDrNMM?feature=share
Horace Podmore: Hi Cheryl
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Coach @SuzanCz
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @HoracePodmore
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @SammySuperStar
Mommy Guide Inc: Awesome topic pla
Horace Podmore: Hi Lala
Cheryl Wolf: Hey @Horace Podmore
Mommy Guide Inc: Pls dont forget to smash the LIKE button
Mommy Guide Inc: If you have questions pls put Q: before it so Markus can easily see it:)
Fishstick USA: ? What is the proper balance between increasing views for Shorts and focusing on your views/income for Long form videos ?
Fishstick USA: ? Can a YouTuber to have a Shorts-only site ?
Horace Podmore: It’s not all about money 😏
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: So love your kitty 🐱
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed with Janet we see Luna or Max every now and then.:)
Cheryl Wolf: I am going to go to zoo film with animals so people notice lol
Mommy Guide Inc: Agree @Horace engagement and meeting so many people and them becoming friends has been one of the biggest blessings of being a content creator:)
Fishstick USA: ? Do you have a recommendation for proper length of Long videos ? I think videos (not livecasts) are too long once they hit 25-30 minutes. By that time, I am looking for a way to stop watching.
Cheryl Wolf: @Fishstick USA I heard that it's watch time so long form content feeds the watch time.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I’ll go with you cheryl
Fishstick USA: I apologize for tossing out so many questions. You can answer as part or the conversation or later. I am not trying to dictate the flow of this conversation.
Mommy Guide Inc: @FishstickUSA questions are absolutely ok:) thanks for the awesome questions:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Great questions @Fishstick USA
Cheryl Wolf: Q What would say is Top three things to focus on in early stages
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Markus, I love the welcome confetti 🎉
Fishstick USA: I like several long form videos for history subjects. But the long videos of driving, weeding the garden, and repetitive dialogue destroy my soul.
Cheryl Wolf: lol off point yes me
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey 14 people right now - thank you and hope you’re getting so much from
Mommy Guide Inc: The topic today.:) pls dont forget to smash the LIKE button and ask away:)
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Hunter
Mommy Guide Inc: Q:
Cheryl Wolf: Ana you are doing it
Cheryl Wolf: 🤩
Enda Trading: Hi from Ireland, will TikTok be banned in the US?
Mommy Guide Inc: True. At the end of the day we still should have control over our content/biz.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @EndaTrading from Ireland:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hello Enda, welcome to the stream!
Enda Trading: Hi @MommyGuideInc
Enda Trading: Courses are a great business plan
Mommy Guide Inc: For questions pls put Q: before it so Markus can easily see it. Thanks!
Enda Trading: Passive income
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hunter 😻
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: How can you best optimize your views from
Cheryl Wolf: Yes, the right audience prefect for me
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: So true about those eggs
Mommy Guide Inc: Q:How can you best optimize your views from shorts to help your channel perform better in the long run?
Mommy Guide Inc: Love you too @SuzanCz and @Markus! Advance Happy Valentine’s Day everyone!!!
Enda Trading: Recording your long form through landscape and through a mobile is a good tip to repropose for shorts
Mommy Guide Inc: Connection!
Cheryl Wolf: I like to say what I know this far or what we know at this point
Mommy Guide Inc: @Enda repurposing another awesome topic.
Cheryl Wolf: Messy
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for the awesome answers Coach@SiuzanCz
Mommy Guide Inc: Pls dont forget to hit the LIKE button and subscribe to Markus channel and Coach @SuzanCz’s for more awesome videos on awesome topics.:)
Cheryl Wolf: I so bummed , I have to leave have a call. Thank you so much markus and Suzan
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: we have to be in it for the long haul
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed we soon find our own tribe so to speak.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yes Lala, and you have the best tribe.
Mommy Guide Inc: Have a great rest of the day @CherylWolf!
SiShong Victor: Yo Yo
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: See ya Cheryl
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Victor
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey@FishstickUSA looking forward to your YT journey:)
SiShong Victor: Hola LaLa
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @Fishstick USA go for it. we will support you.
itdair.network: Hi @SiShong Victor !
SiShong Victor: 👋🏼
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: How are you doing YT differently?
Horace Podmore: Just subscribed to your channel 👍
Brian Newcomb: Hi Markus new here to your channel
itdair.network: Hi Brian! Welcome!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey thanks for subscriving @Horace
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi and yey@BrianNewcomb welcome to Maekus’
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus’ channel and his awesome community:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Sorry about the typos everyone i cant find my reading glasses - LOL
SiShong Victor: Short or Long Form what makes sense = depends
Paul Burke: Loving the pop of color backgrounds
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: hey PAUL
Mommy Guide Inc: OMG Hi @PaulBurke! Yey
Paul Burke: hey Mommy Guide!
Paul Burke: hey Animal Paradise!
itdair.network: Hi Paul Burke!
Fishstick USA: ? I have noticed that for many YTrs they seem to be presenting different brands with Long form vs. their Short form videos. Is it important to fully understand your brand before you begin ?
Paul Burke: hey itdar!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks to everyone for being here still and hope you’re enjoying this livestream. Lets show some love to Markus by hitting the like button.:)
itdair.network: Awesome livestream!
Mommy Guide Inc: The only constant thing is - change.:)
Fishstick USA: Best guess brand. Be yourself. That is good!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: that was a great short
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes pls do check out Markus’ awesome shorts on YT and Tiiktok:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey it’s coming so best is to head on over to Coach @SuzanCz’s channel
SiShong Victor: I start many thing, don't finish much
Mommy Guide Inc: https://Susancz.com
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: great show. thanks Markus & Suzan