Markus Schaub: Welcome to the live!
David W. Ryan: Hi Markus!
David W. Ryan: music is loud
Coach Adam Runs: Hey there, Markus! How's your fitness going?
Coach Adam Runs: Music is gone. All good.
Stan!: Hi, Markus! Hi, group!
Coach Adam Runs: I'm here if you have any questions. Go get it!
Coach Adam Runs: You really need to tell us you've done it.
Coach Adam Runs: Make it a memory.
Coach Adam Runs: Good idea, high vis is always a great idea if you walk at night or early morning.
Stan!: I had one of those shows last night. My guest had to cancel so I just opened up for questions ... and somehow we still went more than an hour.
Sara S: Hey Markus!
Sara S: Yes. This is my last calendar after 45 years.
Sara S: Feels mixed. It’s like anything you track for a really long time.
Sara S: I haven’t been doing a good enough job with my steps, but I walked this morning and again this afternoon.
Sara S: Definitely more consistency
Coach Adam Runs: Sara. You made today count. Great job!
David W. Ryan: I strated to do walks but got off track. I need to move more.
Sara S: Tx Adam
Coach Adam Runs: Put a treadmill in front of your [insert device here]
Coach Adam Runs: Motion = medicine.
Coach Adam Runs: Yes, I completed the Joshua Tree Half Marathon with my two amazing daughters over the weekend.
Stan!: That was your initial goal/milestone when you started getting back into running about a year ago, right?
Coach Adam Runs: Which was especially difficult because it was entirely at night in a remote area - no street lights
Coach Adam Runs: It was the hardest race I've run so far... because the surface was entirely shifting sands due to the high winds.
Coach Adam Runs: It was like running on sand dunes
Ketia Francis-Johnson: Hello everyone! 👋🏽
Coach Adam Runs: in the inky darkness.
Coach Adam Runs: Roughly 21KM - I was ready for a tall cocktail after 15KM... but the bar was a cactus.
Ketia Francis-Johnson: Markus! 🎊👋🏽🤩
Ketia Francis-Johnson: Yes! You are my inspiration!
Coach Adam Runs: My next race is more local in 11 weeks. I restart my training this weekend.
Coach Adam Runs: Markus, we will totally complete a race together - maybe we can pull together a relay team.
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: hoi zämä
Coach Adam Runs: ... preferebaly in Ibiza or some other paradise island.
Coach Adam Runs: You will get there. One step at a time.
Coach Adam Runs: Don't let perfection be the enemy of good enough. Get it done!
Coach Adam Runs: If you have a body - you have a fitness story to share.
Ketia Francis-Johnson: Self pep talks are important… it shows that one is reflecting on their current state and make adjustments if needed