Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Markus!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey! Happy Summer Solstice!
CSLiveDK : Hi Markus and all the fantastic people here😀👋
Mommy Guide Inc: Let’s go!.:) Hi Ejnar:)
Tech Troublemaker: yes supposedly we use a minute a day
Tech Troublemaker: It's Ejnar.
Tech Troublemaker: Make that LOSE a minute a day
CSLiveDK : Hi Lala👋
austinator: hey Markus, long time no see
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Hello
Tech Troublemaker: I cried when you I didn't see your video. Okay, I didn't but I wondered hey, I hope Markus is okay.
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @austinator
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Phillip!
Mommy Guide Inc: Austin!!’ We miss you much
CSLiveDK : Hi Roy 😀
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Philip.:₱
austinator: I'm doing alright, super busy as always running myself to the ground but today is my day off because I NEED it... I've been making content when I feel like I can or want to... but yeah, that
austinator: it's also super hot here right now, 100°F+
Mommy Guide Inc: Awww big hugs Austin. College life is hard and busy.
Spooling Around: Hi Markus!
austinator: I'm trying to go back and learn CG animation as well
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh wow. Summer feels for real Austin right truly happy to see you in the chat Austin.:)
Spooling Around: It's David W. Ryan
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi david.:)
Spooling Around: Hi Lala!
Run Adam Run: Good evening, Markus. How's the heat treating you in Lucern?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Adam.:)
austinator: real feel right now is 44°C right now 🥵🥵🥵
Run Adam Run: This week I shift to running at night to avoid the heat of the sun.
Pierre Kelly: Hey all
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks indeed for being here friends.:) always glad to see you all in the chat.:)
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Good day. I hosted a livestream this morning. Used YTStudio, Dell webcam, Shure mic, KeyLight Air, small Nexigo Light, and window light. I created slides and shared 2nd screen. Went well. Very happy.
Mommy Guide Inc: Pls don’t forget to hit the LIKE button.:)
Run Adam Run: I need a better low light camera and a head lamp. LOL
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh that’s awesome:)
Mariane Cresp: Hello Markus and everybody. Just quick pop by to say Hi! 👋🏼
Pierre Kelly: hi @Mariane Cresp
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey what a win Philip.:)
Fishstick ~ Phillip: This was a devotions group of 15 people. Got a lot of compliments.
Mariane Cresp: Hello Pierre
Spooling Around: 34 C (94f) where I am
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Markus, I appreciate your encouragement. You are a great guy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Bi Pierre and Mariane:)
Mariane Cresp: I’ve been up since 3am and it’s now just past 6am. Time to do my morning routine 😊
Neil Farrimond: Hey Markus
Run Adam Run: It's International Yoga Day and I'm eating a pretzel. Ironic.
Mariane Cresp: Yes, Markus is brilliant!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Neil.
Neil Farrimond: Hi @Mommy Guide Inc 🙂
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow Mariane - youre a super early riser?
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Neil Farrimond
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @adam
Neil Farrimond: Hey @Tech Troublemaker
Run Adam Run: Hey Roy, digging your dive into the story. I think it's a great direction. Good luck!
Mommy Guide Inc: Lol Adam.:) love 🥨
Neil Farrimond: You got this Markus!
Run Adam Run: Mommy, you and me both - especially the soft ones.
Fishstick ~ Phillip: 90F (32C) today. Supposed to reach 99F (37C) by Tuesday. I will melt.
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes and one with almond and cream cheese - yummy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Stay indoors and atay safe my friends. Do t forget to rehydrate
Run Adam Run: Copa America is here on our side.
Mommy Guide Inc: Okay here goes my typo issues again sorry friends cant find my eyeglasses. Theyrr here somewhere in bed but i can tfind thrm. LOL
Run Adam Run: I have a soft spot for action cameras and have a drone - but the majority of my videos are shot on my iPhone because I always run with it.
Mommy Guide Inc: Thats awesome! Mine doesnt do the flipping.
Run Adam Run: I run with the X4 sometimes, but I'm always afraid of damaging the lens.
Mommy Guide Inc: Love your gears Friends.:)
Run Adam Run: Resell it!
Run Adam Run: I have the Go3S - I'd wait.
Tech Troublemaker: I love shooting video on my phone but the GoPro was for a second camera but then suddenly for now it has become main camera as I learn to use it.
Run Adam Run: The X4 protection lenses add too much glare for me.
Run Adam Run: The tiny camera makes sense for runners and tiny spaces, but the image quality and color is not as good.
Run Adam Run: I look forward to what GoPro will release in September.
Run Adam Run: I sometimes put the camera on a small tripod to run past it.
Run Adam Run: Afraid it will tip over.
Mommy Guide Inc: Love how you do your running videos Adam.:)
Spooling Around: I have an older Olympus as my main cam and some GoPro knock offs for overheads and side cams
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Nice to catch ya'll here.
Run Adam Run: I have a super robust tripod - it's the horse trail that's uneven, and wind, etc. Never a truly flat surface
Run Adam Run: Ana!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thats great David! How you make things do with what you have. What’s the next project?
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Doing ok friend! So happy to see you too.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana! How are you my friend?
Run Adam Run: Nice clamp.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: @Coach Adam @Mommy Guide Inc the Lord is good. Im good. Doing a lot of soul searching lately and healing.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Missing live streaming and connecting with ya'll.
Run Adam Run: It's great to see you hear Ana. We all understand how life jumps up sometimes
Pierre Kelly: How's life @Ana Zugheri - Faith52 ?
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Big 50!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: So true. Pls include us in your prayers Ana.:)
Neil Farrimond: Live begins at 50 🙂 That's what I told myself ;-)
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: lol I am looking forward to be 50 @Neil Farrimond because that is what i hear.
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yes am a golden+1 club! He he he
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: lol
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: 50/50
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: You should do a 50s party, 50 guests, 50 videos, 50 cakes! lol and you started your streaming singing so you should sing for your 50
Stan!: I'm here ... with.a new YT channel. (Ugh!)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Stan!
Stan!: Doing what I can!
Mommy Guide Inc: God bless on the nee channel Stan! You are an inspiration. You just continue to create and go live on FB while you get things fixed
Run Adam Run: On my 50th birthday I packed my car and said goodbye to Florida... and drove all the way to San Diego with my wife and 3 dogs.
Run Adam Run: Boy, that was a weird birthday.
Run Adam Run: I drove across the entire state of Texas... which is VERY large. Ask Ana.
Run Adam Run: It took 3 days just to cross Texas.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: @Run Adam Run it is! by the time you get out of tx you could have visit 4 countries in Europe lol
Tech Troublemaker: Interstate 10. such a long drive
Run Adam Run: I did visit 4 countries in Texas... at least it felt like that. Planet Houston, Dallasonia, San Antoniolandia.
Run Adam Run: and good Old El Paso.
Run Adam Run: Boston is walkable if you have FEET
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes! you need to come to TX!!!
Stan!: In Europe MOST cities are "walkable" (probably just about ALL of them)
Run Adam Run: Texas is a state of it's own. Nothing can compare to it.
Stan!: For you, flying to TX is probably 3–4 hours more than flying to Boston
Mommy Guide Inc: That would be a great thought and then you get to run together with Ana in Texas Adam:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes!!!
Run Adam Run: Yes, the Houston Marathon is on my bucket list.
Stan!: I really miss being able to travel by train
Run Adam Run: Nobody is really ready for a marathon.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: we can make a conference ourselves so we can charge people and make the cost of it possible! lol
Stan!: We'll all go to "Markus Con"
Run Adam Run: Actually, no. It's beyond what the body can be ready for. It requires going beyond what you can prepare for. Trust me on this one.
Run Adam Run: YES MARKUS CON
Run Adam Run: I love that idea
Neil Farrimond: Come to Portugal 🙂
Neil Farrimond: #MARKON
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: you'll be surprised! People pay to go to the silliest things conferences lol.
Run Adam Run: Oh yes, my daughter is an ultra runner and completes 100 miles at a clip. It's absolutely nuts.
Run Adam Run: Portugal looks so beautiful, especially the food.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I want to go to Spain one day and from there tour that side of the world.
Enda Trading: Hello all
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Markon it is!!!
Run Adam Run: Takes her 30 or so hours... still it's beyond what she can prepare for, every time it's a struggle.
Stan!: Markon is ON!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: What a powerful girl!
Run Adam Run: She had to put up with me as her Dad. Maybe that has something to do with her fortitude. She's always running away for something or other. LOL
Spooling Around: I'm happy I can climb stairs right now
Run Adam Run: "Will he ever stop talking?" Is her running mantra.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: lol
Run Adam Run: Yes, we will. We are running the Joshua Tree marathon together - with both of my daughters. There will be videos.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I can bearly put in 5000 steps in a day...
Run Adam Run: I think it
Run Adam Run: Sorry
Run Adam Run: I think it's important to get out from behind a screen.
Enda Trading: I used to work in NY skyscrapers and in stead of waiting for the lift after work I sometimes i used to run down the stairs haha
Enda Trading: Yes, it was a mix of jumping and running haha sometimes up to 40
Enda Trading: I was young and full of energy
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I like going for walks but in my neighborhood there are alot of loose dogs and Im scare of them. So better safe than sorry, I just go around my driveway like a million times lol
Spooling Around: I have an Apple watch and it reminds me to stand up during the day.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: yes, those are super helpful.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: So nice connecting with you all friends.
Stan!: Woo hoo!