Eaglevp: Hi Lala
Eaglevp: Evening Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Keith! Good morning!
Eaglevp: Hope it's a nice morning for you Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: So far so good Keith hope you all are having a great day so far:)
SuzanCz: Hi everyone!
Mariane Cresp: Hi Markus
Eaglevp: Hi@SuzanCz
SuzanCz: Markuuuuuusssss!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Susan and Marian.:)
Eaglevp: Hey @Mariane Cresp
SuzanCz: Hi @eaglevp & Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: Suzan:)
Shelly Saves the Day: hope you have a great stream!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Shelly.:)
Shelly Saves the Day: hi 👋
Eaglevp: Hi@Shelly Saves the Day
Mariane Cresp: Hello 👋🏼 all
Eaglevp: Have you got an easter egg for your girlfriend Markus?
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes since yesterday no work here in the Philippines in observance of Holy Week or Lent:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Moni!
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi. Markus. 😀
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ejnar.:)
Eaglevp: Hi Ejnar
Mommy Guide Inc: Go Markus!
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: I will be at home in the Easter with my family😀
SuzanCz: Easter = sleep
Tech Troublemaker: It's Markus!
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Lala and Keith.😀👍
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy! See you later.:)
Eaglevp: Hello Roy
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @SuzanCz Hey Keith! Hey Lala!
Mariane Cresp: In this week’s lesson Markus we talk about being kind to yourself and forgiving yourself if you’re not able to do all the things on your task list 😊
Enda Trading: Hello all
Tech Troublemaker: @Mommy Guide Inc I rescheduled it for next week. I updated the invite.
Tech Troublemaker: Holy Week has me busy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh ok. Thanks for the heads up Roy.:)
Mariane Cresp: 😅
Mommy Guide Inc: So your morning commute with Markus? Or noon time break with Markus?
Mommy Guide Inc: I tired going live directly from my pocket 2 didn’t work. He he he.
SuzanCz: It’s interesting how you’re ok with going live but not “filming yourself” when, in the end, it’s the same thing… is t it?
SuzanCz: That’s exactly how it will work! Just like it did before. Confidence comes *after* not before.
Tech Troublemaker: live is live recorded is recorded. Same person? Maybe.
Mommy Guide Inc: I am sure when you find the right content for that Vlog it’s going to easier. Just need to go for it.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: When is the Creative Amplifier show?
Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
SuzanCz: JUST DO IT! 🙌
Mariane Cresp: This week’s lesson tackles exactly how you’re feeling Markus
Eaglevp: Hi Sammy
SuzanCz: I’m starting my channel back up. Accountability buddies? 😉
Sammy Super Star: Hey Eaglevp!
Mommy Guide Inc: Ok daily short vlogs in April:)
Mommy Guide Inc: April 1 - ok it is for real right? It is April Fool’s Day hehehe
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sammy!
Sammy Super Star: Forgot it’s about to be April 1st and no LEDA 😔
Tech Troublemaker: Happy Dance for @SuzanCz
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey! Let’s go Suzan.:)
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: hello crazy livestreamer - happy easter
Eaglevp: Hello@Eric Maechler - Online Marketing
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: No LEDA. How do we manage without it? It’s a little sad I think. 😞👋
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Eric!
Stannex: Dancing Markus!
SuzanCz: I have one done and in editing. But the challenge isn’t the next video. The challenge is the new habit. The challenge is our 10th, 20th, 50th video. That’s what accountability is really all about.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Stan!
Eaglevp: Hi Stan
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: it was the perfect moment 😛 i hope you catched it for a reel 😛 #dancing
Stannex: I can only stay a moment ... but I want to know about this Markus-generated challenge!
Stannex: Hi, Lala! Hi, Keith!
Mommy Guide Inc: Stan has a show later today in case anyone is available.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: How about we do a hop?
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Ok, I think I will make my own LEDA After special Edition😀👍
Stannex: Thank you for the plug, Lala! ❤
Mommy Guide Inc: We think of a topic and we all do a video about it and we “hop” from
Mommy Guide Inc: From one channel to the other
SuzanCz: I’m starting with pre-recorded every other week until my systems are in place, then kicking up to every week.
Stannex: Three times a week (but one is on a separate sumo-related channel).
Mommy Guide Inc: We do that in the crafting community. It has been a good experience and great way to gain traction.
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: haha @Mommy Guide Inc what a interessting idea 😛 or you create a topic - how to build some creativ thing
SuzanCz: I love that idea, @mommy Guide Inc. I’d play.
SuzanCz: 1st one is next week.
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hey Suzan. Long time no see😀
Stannex: Ooops! Have to go!
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: @SuzanCz i created all my videos (2 video / week) till mai 😛 we must be prepared allways
SuzanCz: We’re talking about video, yes? Not sex? 😜
SuzanCz: @Eric cool!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey let’s do it friends. A creator “hop”
SuzanCz: Cuz we were saying 2x/ week, 3x/wk, every other week. It’s all about rhythm. 😜😂
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: no "slack" - i am planing all my next videos - recording tomorrow 😛 till july 😛 i like to have an archive. creativity cant forced
Mommy Guide Inc: Lol Suzan!
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: @SuzanCz to much for me old man #rofl
SuzanCz: That makes sense, Eric. So you can give yourself room to breathe without creating any gaps.
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow Eric - til July! Hats off to you my friend!
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: exactly @SuzanCz
Mommy Guide Inc: Normally we have a topic - then there’s a playlist in the description and people can click on that and they will be able to watch everyone’s video or livestream on the hop
Mommy Guide Inc: Say Markus first then it goes to Susan then to Eric and so on and so forth
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: creating english conten? @Mommy Guide Inc i am not as brave as markus 🤣
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: content
Mommy Guide Inc: Sorry Suzan your name keeps getting auto corrected.
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Eric you can do it. I have Taglish accent
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: yes we / swiss recognize the crazy accent
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: i should reactivate my english channel
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: i do it 😛 send me the info about your creator hub 😛 its just a little channel nobody know it
SuzanCz: @mommy guide Inc The different spelling doesn’t bother me in the least. That’s actually the official spelling!
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: @Mommy Guide Inc i am shy 😛
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: do you have a fb fanpage for your channel? @Markus Schaub
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: link
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: oh i see we are alrady connected in fb
SuzanCz: I’m out. Good to see you Markus. We should chat! ❤️
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: last post 1.feb
Mommy Guide Inc: You can do it Eric. I started the same way. LEDA back then really helped me overcome the being shy
Mommy Guide Inc: Hopefully we can walk alongside you Eric and overcome
Mommy Guide Inc: Bye Suzan. Have a great Easter:)
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: bye @SuzanCz
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: worse than a dentist appoint - it could'nt be right?
Mommy Guide Inc: Don’t
Mommy Guide Inc: Don’t forget to hit the LIKE a button friends:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Eric it’ll get better.:)
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: do i like you all? ROFL
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Markus! Thanks friends and see you next week back here.:)
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: ok boys and girls - for me its pizza time - have a nice easter and see you all soon
Mommy Guide Inc: Eric absolutely - he he he. Head on everyone to everyone’s channel and check everyone out.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Enjoy your pizza 🍕 Eric!