Tim Heale 9: Hi Markus, Lala & Keith
Mommy Guide Inc: The week has been super busy! Had friends come from Canada and Singapore.:) Hope you had a great one too Keith!
Eaglevp: Evening Tim
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Markus! Hi everyone
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Lala!!! happy Friday
Eaglevp: Yes thanks Lala been a busy week for me
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: :hand-pink-waving:
Eaglevp: Hi@Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Janet!!! Miss you friend.:) Great to see you back in the chat!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @Mommy Guide Inc I have to write you! ... surprise!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks everyone for being here don’t forget to smash the like button!
Fishstick USA: Gruezi! Bonjour! Halo! And Hello!
Eaglevp: Hey@Fishstick USA
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey hi @Fishstick USA
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: stream and feel alive!!!1
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: 💃💃💃💃💃💃💃💃
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Keith & Tim
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yay India
Tim Heale 9: Greetings on and all
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yay
Eaglevp: Hello@India Delgado
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Naps all around
Mommy Guide Inc: Yerp!!! Hi @India
Mommy Guide Inc: India you make
Tina Wan Kenobi: Good morning ☕️
Mommy Guide Inc: You make working at a bank really exciting:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh wow Hi Tina! You are up early:)
Tina Wan Kenobi: Hi Eagle, Lala! Yes i went to bed at 9 😊
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: so true. we all learn in different ways. the challenge for a teacher/coach is to learn how to present the material so everyone can grasp it... the ah ha's
Tina Wan Kenobi: Hi Janet!
Tina Wan Kenobi: Gosh Im late by 10 mins 😵‍💫
Mommy Guide Inc: No worries Tina::) The party just started:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Tina this reminds me we should start setting up your streamdeck:)
hughdemand: Hi @Mommy Guide Inc , @Eaglevp
Tina Wan Kenobi: My streamdeck is still hibernating 😆
Mommy Guide Inc: This is India’s YT channel. in case you are not part of her community - pls join us there as well:) https://youtube.com/@IndiaDelgado
Tina Wan Kenobi: I dont see her pup anywhere 🧐
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: When I was a 1st time home buyer (interest rates were 18% and going up every day) my realtor did not tell me about the programs.
Tina Wan Kenobi: Aww hehe 😆
Tina Wan Kenobi: Its amazing how u guys can Weave your RL careers with your new passion with livestreaming
Mommy Guide Inc: India is an awesome Coach:)
Mommy Guide Inc: There you go - commonality - passion for helping people.:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yes very much needed
Tina Wan Kenobi: Have u guys liked this stream yet? 👍🏻
Mommy Guide Inc: Impostor Syndrome - something we all struggle with at one point in time as content creators.
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes awesome people in the chat now - friends -‘dont forget to smash that like button. Thanks @Tina:)
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Hello everyone 😀🇩🇰
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @CSLive-Communication Social Media Livestreaming
Eaglevp: Hi@CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming
Tech Troublemaker: Hey hey! A place with my favorite people.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hey Roy@TechTroublemaker
Tech Troublemaker: Smack that "Like" button y'all
Tech Troublemaker: Q: How do you juggle your livestreaming live and your day job?
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Lala and @Eaglevp
Tina Wan Kenobi: Hi Roy!
Tech Troublemaker: Tina!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Roy
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: 100 hours is better😀😉
Mommy Guide Inc: 30 days and i onow a perfect way to start with that join us in LEDA soon!
Tina Wan Kenobi: Brain bleed to think of a Daily topic for livestream!
Mommy Guide Inc: 100 hours great suggestion Ejnar:)
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: 🥰🇩🇰
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes join us in LEDA this April https://livestreamingpros.com/leda
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yes. love the networking
Mommy Guide Inc: The best thing About being a content creator really is being able to have met all of you amazing people.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Let’s show both Markus and India some
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: :face-red-heart-shape:
Mommy Guide Inc: Show some love by smashing the Like button and subscribing to both of them.
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: 👍 ok it’s done. Just joined LEDA for the fifth time. Love to meet all the old friends here and of course new ones will ad up. See you all again♥️🙏👍😀✅
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey see you again Ejnar on LEDA in April.:) Hope to see you all there again:)
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: 👍👍👍👍
Tina Wan Kenobi: Just ask. 😎
Tina Wan Kenobi: India, has anyone ever told you that you look like Alicia Keys? 😁
Mommy Guide Inc: India’s YT channel - https://youtube.com/@IndiaDelgado
Tech Troublemaker: Q: India, how to you manage your Content Creation and your Day Job?
Tim Heale 9: I see a lot of financial advisers on PodMatch
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: This really doesn’t feels like we are competing, more that we are helping each other out. That feels good and safe to be a part of this. It’s very hard to explain this feeling but it’s so good🥰🙏
Mommy Guide Inc: Find our passion - and push forth with that in what we do.:)
Tim Heale 9: I live twice a week and if I can't do a live I have a pre-recorded episode that goes out as a premier, so I have some content going out
Mommy Guide Inc: Great plan and consistency Tim:)
Tech Troublemaker: Thank you!
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed Calendly has helped me remember my schedule coz am very notorious about forgetting stuff including my livestreams.:) LOL
Paul Burke: oh cool...you're still streamin!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thank you so much Markus, India and everyone in the chat! Time flies by so fast when youre having fun
hughdemand: Thanks India & Markus, great show.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Thank you India & Markus. Great stream. so much good food for thought.
Paul Burke: i see. i see.
Eaglevp: Great interview Markus and India
Mommy Guide Inc: Dont forget to smash the like button on your way out friends:)
Paul Burke: hey @Mommy Guide Inc and @Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing