Pierre Kelly: evening all
Eaglevp: hI@Pierre Kelly
itdair.network: Hi Markus and everyone! 👋🏻
Eaglevp: Hope you had a nice Christmas@Pierre Kelly
Eaglevp: Q.Did you get all you wanted Markus for Christmas
Pierre Kelly: only 3 amd that's it? where everybody else?
MySnoopy80: Hi everyone❤️
Pierre Kelly: Hey @MySnoopy80
Eaglevp: Hello@MySnoopy80 and welcome to the stream
Ellie Calhoun: Hey Markus!! Hi everyone!
Eaglevp: Hi Ellie
MySnoopy80: Hi@pierre Kelly and Keith
Eaglevp: Hope you all had a nice Christmas
Pierre Kelly: Christmas was okay,
MySnoopy80: And change my name
MySnoopy80: Yeah you did real good!❤️
Eaglevp: All the new skills Markus his learning@MySnoopy80
Ellie Calhoun: We had my whole family here. Lots of love and fun and great food! My Marcus does the cooking and that's a gift to me!
Ellie Calhoun: Still cleaning 😂
Tech Troublemaker: Hey!!
Eaglevp: Hi Roy
itdair.network: Hi Roy 👋🏻
Mariane Cresp: Hello Markus!
Eaglevp: Hello@Mariane Cresp
Tech Troublemaker: Action Hero Markus!
Mariane Cresp: Hello Keith
Coach Adam: Hey there everyone!
Tech Troublemaker: Keith, I agree everyone needs a bigger desk. Haha
Eaglevp: Welcome Coach Adam
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Adam
Coach Adam: I need a second desk. LOL
Eaglevp: I know I certainly do Roy would love to have a room big enough.
Ellie Calhoun: Happy New Year to you all! I've got to leave. ❤️🥳❤️🎉
itdair.network: Each one of you has been doing great on your channels and content! Congratulations!🎉
Eaglevp: It's been good watching all your vlogmas video's Roy
Motif Music Studios: Hello to all! Happy New Year!
Eaglevp: Happy new year Ellie
MySnoopy80: Happy new year to you too, Ellie
Motif Music Studios: Neat "vision" outlines! So helpful.
Eaglevp: Hi@Motif Music Studios
Tech Troublemaker: Thanks Keith. Markus posts amazing vlogs. I loved the adventures of Markus
Motif Music Studios: @Tech Troublemaker in the house!
Eaglevp: Agree Roy I really do like Markus vlogging style think he should do a lot more
Stannex: Oh good! I didn't miss it all! Hi, Markus! Hi, everyone!
Coach Adam: Markus, YOU are the product if you have nothing to sell.
Eaglevp: I follow a channel that's just grown from 755 subs to over 1700 in just 48 hours through one video about the british benefit system
Tech Troublemaker: Markus, the brand, is the product
Eaglevp: Hi Stan
Stannex: Hi, Keith!
Coach Adam: I'm going to call you "Money" from now on instead of Markus.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi everyone. sorry I'm late.
Stannex: I'd pay full market price for Markus, for sure!
Eaglevp: Hi@Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing
Coach Adam: M&M lol
Tech Troublemaker: I just hope is merch shop ships internationally
Tech Troublemaker: I hope his merch shop ships internationally
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi @Eaglevp
Motif Music Studios: @Eaglevp nice to see you here!
Motif Music Studios: @Eaglevp that's some wild growth!
Eaglevp: It certainly is@Motif Music Studios
Motif Music Studios: @Eaglevp I would be both thrilled and terrified all at once with that kind of growth!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yes Merc shop
Eaglevp: Think I would be as well@Motif Music Studios
Tech Troublemaker: “Markus in Charge” hoodies
Motif Music Studios: Marcus in charge! LOL. Awesome.
MySnoopy80: I would wear that😄😄
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh I would buy and wear a hoodie
Stannex: You have my permission to use that caricature I did for merch, if you want to.
MySnoopy80: Ooooooh you're right.....
Motif Music Studios: @Stannex that would be so fun!!! Great idea!
MySnoopy80: 😂
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: That would be perfect Stan.
Stannex: There's A LOT of "stan" in the world.
Tech Troublemaker: His merch is manifesting itself here in the chat. 🤪
Coach Adam: That's great!
Coach Adam: MONEY!
Motif Music Studios: SO FUN and personalized!!!
Motif Music Studios: I have a Spreadshop shop, but haven't uploaded any designs!
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Hello Markus. Greetings from the USA!
Motif Music Studios: Ah, that's true and insightful!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: it's a work in progress
Eaglevp: Hi Phillip
Tech Troublemaker: I am using FourthWall. I like them so far.
Motif Music Studios: LOL. Keep waiting for a full night's sleep, but may have to disregard that!
Motif Music Studios: Thanks for the kick in the behind to look at that again. My husband has an amazing eye for design so maybe I should ask for a design for my BIRTHDAY!
Stannex: 😎👍
Coach Adam: I've had a Spreadshop for over 10 years, and it is truly set it and forget it - but it does take some effort to come up with great products.
Coach Adam: but every once in while something sells and I enjoy that $5 profit all day long. LOL
Motif Music Studios: That's neat, @Coach Adam . Love the thought of enjoying that $5 profit with a smile. LOL.
MySnoopy80: A Hoodie wit Markus rules! Also works with caps
Andrea Nunn: Hi Marcus! Hi all!
Coach Adam: I try to spread it around. "Spreadshop"
MySnoopy80: Yes I really love that cap
Coach Adam: $5 goes a long was with a jar of peanut butter. LOL
Eaglevp: Hi@Andrea Nunn
Coach Adam: Typo... goes a long way with a jar of peanut butter. LOLOL
Motif Music Studios: YES! Happy New Year, all! All the best for a fabulously creative year ahead!
Coach Adam: I would be happy to help you set up your shop
Andrea Nunn: Goals: Personal training certification and health coaching certificate. Then online implementation!!
Motif Music Studios: Haha! YES! Love it and that shared aspect of encouragement.
Coach Adam: Product idea - Single word t-shirts and cups are a best seller. You just have to pick the right word and font.
Tech Troublemaker: My goal is to have goals
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: haha Royh
Motif Music Studios: I am with Roy on that! Funny!
Coach Adam: My goal for 2024 is a simple one, that is to make 30 videos and get a little better with each one so I can be more like Roy.
Andrea Nunn: Goals: continue with weekly videos!
Motif Music Studios: My goal is to keep honing how to create videos that build curiosity and build a helpful library for piano teachers!
Stannex: The most important step is always to start DOING it. Embrace the imperfection.
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: happy christmas und e guet neus denn bald :)
Coach Adam: What Stan said...
Tech Troublemaker: Adam, your skills and vision are so amazing. I have thrown a lot of paint at thewall but the picture is still unclear. I am the mistake prone jester for others to learn from
Eaglevp: Got to go Happy new year to you all.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Happy New Year and have a good weekend too
Tech Troublemaker: Bye Keith
MySnoopy80: Bye Keith have a good one
Stannex: Happy New Year, Keith!
Coach Adam: Roy, don't sell yourself short - we can see the goodness in your core and we love that.
Motif Music Studios: @Coach Adam TRUTH bomb, Roy's way. I agree!
Coach Adam: Also, Roy's conviction (to streaming not crime) is inspiring! LOL
Andrea Nunn: No shame! Yes, messy by nature
Tech Troublemaker: Plenty of room in the swimming pool. We just wear different swimsuits and tackle the diving board differently
Coach Adam: Thank God for that. I can't handle seeing you both in the same suit.
Stannex: I have the same problem with edited videos. Livestreams are soooo much easier for me!
Coach Adam: at the same time
MySnoopy80: Bye everyone and happy new year to all ❤️❤️
itdair.network: Have an awesome starting year 2024, and all the best for each one of you always! 👏🏻
Stannex: Happy New Year, all!
Stannex: See you in 2024!
Pierre Kelly: Have a great 2024 to you all!
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Bye for now