Cheryl Wolf: Hello Markus
Cheryl Wolf: I am singing along
Cheryl Wolf: Thank you , yes
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hello 👋 friends!!!!!
Cheryl Wolf: I had someone that wanted to do presentation not an intervies
Cheryl Wolf: interview
Cheryl Wolf: No they wanted to do it on my show instread of being interviewed , so that conversation is important
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I’m actually in North Carolina, so not home not in the car but here 😂
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hi Cheryl 😘👋
Cheryl Wolf: Nice lucky
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Hello Everyone👋😀
Cheryl Wolf: typed bad sorry markus fat fingers
Sammy Super Star: Hey Markus
Cheryl Wolf: Very simple way , I was thinking of using notion for that
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: That is a great tip
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yep, trust!!!
Paul Burke: impressive prep
Cheryl Wolf: Hey paul long time no see
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Omgoodnes that’s is perfect!!!! I’m time zone impeard can never get that right.
Paul Burke: hey @Cheryl Wolf ! It has been a long time
Cheryl Wolf: I missed you!!
Paul Burke: back at you!
Paul Burke: Markus! Haver you ever revealed what you're looking at during these livestreams? Have we ever got a MPOV (Markus Point of View)
Paul Burke: do you have a preshow ritual? Almost like a superstitious must-do?
Fishstick USA: I’m late
Cheryl Wolf: Are you sleeping better? Markus
Fishstick USA: BTW. I like the countdown
Cheryl Wolf: 🤣your welcome shinny object
Cheryl Wolf: Hey @Fishstick USA
Cheryl Wolf: Be a good listener
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes, sometimes I get distracted managing the tech and missed what the guest said 🫣
Cheryl Wolf: yes Ana I totally with ya
Cheryl Wolf: Chat can throw me off , and then I forget where I was going
Cheryl Wolf: Good Job Markus
Cheryl Wolf: He is soooo good