Mommy Guide Inc: Good evening Roy!
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Hellloooooooooooooo
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Katy! Hope all is well:)
Marielou Mandl: My favorite song
Marielou Mandl: 💃🏻dancing in the kitchen while I make my lunch
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Marielou it’s such a feel good and inspiring song:)
Tech Troublemaker: I would try dancing in my kitchen but I don't want to have to clean up the mess from all the things crashing to the floor.
Marielou Mandl: Start the stream and feel aliiivvveeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
Mommy Guide Inc: Lol Roy.:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello 👋
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Hello all
Mommy Guide Inc: What’s for lunch Marielou? Now I am hungry.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana and Philip:)
Eaglevp: Hi Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Keith!
Eaglevp: Hello Lala
Eaglevp: Hi Roy
Eaglevp: Hey @Fishstick ~ Phillip
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Keith Hey Katy Hey Ana Hey Marielou!
Eaglevp: Hi@Marielou Mandl
Marielou Mandl: Hi hi ! Roasted veggies and quinoa for lunch today
Eaglevp: Hi Katy
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yes it’s easy to remember coz Marielou’s livestream is after your livestream.:)
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Hi my pals!
Marielou Mandl: Ooh over and under estimate ! Interesting
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Hello @Eaglevp.
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Phillip!
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus who is creative amplifier? I know that’s the name of your camp in Creator Camp right?
Marielou Mandl: Doc also goes to extreme right away 😂
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh love quinoa as rice substitute very yummy and healthy:)
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: I have cauliflower rice
Eaglevp: https://www.youtube.com/@CreativeAmplifiers
Coach Adam: Hey Marky Markus
Eaglevp: That's the link Lala
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: My doggie is snoring: I’m so sorry. He’s so rude and sooo ungrateful for this great content!
Mommy Guide Inc: Coz Creative Amplifier was in the chat in one of my livestreams and I don’t know who it was exactly:)
Eaglevp: Hi Coach Adam
Markus Schaub: https://www.youtube.com/@CreativeAmplifiers
Tech Troublemaker: I love Neil, Mark and Lisa. Fun show. I was a guest a couple of weeks ago
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh it must be Neil then. He was in the chat that day too. Thanks Markus, Keith and Roy:)
Tech Troublemaker: I had peanut butter and grape jelly on really healthy aka really dry thin bread.
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Oooh grape jelly: sounds yummy
Eaglevp: Homemade Chicken Curry
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh Roy that actually sounds great for breakfast in a bit. You guys are making me so hungry.
Rich Vybz: Hey everybody!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Rich!
Coach Adam: I'm testing the LoseIt vs MyFitnessPal apps (for a future video) to watch my diet and get into racing form.
Eaglevp: Hi Rich
Mommy Guide Inc: Cruising
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Coach Adam. That’s very interesting.:)
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: I watch homesteading, Self Reliance (a guy who builds his own log cabins in Canada) and a girl who lives in the artic circle
Rich Vybz: I love taskmaster! the new series is just about to start soon
mommyguideinc: And of course I am here too! Hi Marielou
Coach Adam: The diet apps require you scan all the food you eat which is a bit of a pain in the donkey.
Coach Adam: Pretzels and beer are my guilty pleasure followed by pizza, and after that... more pizza.
Mommy Guide Inc: I am afraid that app would tell me - too much sugar and carbs!
Marielou Mandl: Lots of Taylor swift eras tour footage too
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh Katy that sounds fun
Mommy Guide Inc: Lol Adam. You wouldn’t guess mine are chocolates.:) I can’t have a meal without sweets after.:(
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: I love all that sort of stuff Lala. I want to have my own mini homestead with goats and donkeys
Eaglevp: If your watching to much youtube your not creating
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I’m at the grocery store right now…ya’ll making me buy more than what’s on my list lol 😂
Mommy Guide Inc: I know I should stop coz am not getting any younger. Too much sweets is bad for me I know. But why are healthy food not yummy most of the time?
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Markus and all The good people here😀
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Good point Markus!!
Marielou Mandl: Eat the sweets and feel AAALLIIVEEEEEE
Eaglevp: Hi Ejnar
Coach Adam: For YouTube I love watching travel vloggers, especially if I'm heading there.
Mommy Guide Inc: He he he Ana.:) hi Ejnar:)
Eaglevp: You should turn that round Markus and get creating or more live streams
sishongvictor: lol never stop eating it’s important
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Eaglevp😀
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Lala😀
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Victor on IG.:)
Coach Adam: It's ok to stop eating if you are driving.
Coach Adam: Does anyone have the guilty pleasure of watching "Mukbang" videos? (other people eating)
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh 2 gadgets.
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Markus. Lala on OBS? Markus that can’t happen. He he he
Mommy Guide Inc: Coach Adam mukhang is a very common content for Filipinos.:)
Motif Music Studios: Vertical looking great on my phone!
Coach Adam: Yeah, the eating videos are a weird phenomena.
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes one or more livestreams and I am done with the test on vertical livestream:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Amie.:) hope I got the spelling ok today:)
Motif Music Studios: Oh that’s interesting! I need to try this
Motif Music Studios: @mommyguide YES! you got it!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey! I am a constant work in progress. My spelling is looking great today.:) thanks Amie.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Which one do you think you prefer for content Markus?
Marielou Mandl: You’re doing great!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sammy on IG.:)
Sammy Super Star: Hey Markus
Sammy Super Star: I’m on YouTube now
Sammy Super Star: Your doing amazing
Stannex: Hello, Markus! Hello, chat room!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Amie!!!!!
Eaglevp: Hi Sammy
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes that’s true Markus slept early so up early too:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Stan!
Sammy Super Star: Markus has to go to sleep early so then he can be up early
Sammy Super Star: Oh I like your new glasses Markus
Coach Adam: Happy Spring! Monday marks the wonderful holiday of Holi - the festival of colors where everyone throws color and water balloons at each other. It's amazing.
Stannex: One of the hardest thing to learn is to let there be silence for a little bit.
Tech Troublemaker: YouTube is where all the beautiful people hang out.
Eaglevp: Hello Stan
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow Sammy didn’t realize that Markus has new set of glasses.
Sammy Super Star: They look different? Am I right
Mommy Guide Inc: Coach will that happen this Monday?
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: I’ll be zzzzzz at 8am
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh early meeting for you so I guess we have to end soon.:)
Coach Adam: Holi is celebrated in India where much of my professional team lives and works.
Motif Music Studios: Color and water balloons sounds festive indeed!
Coach Adam: Holi, also known as the Festival of Colors, is a Hindu festival that celebrates the end of winter, the triumph of good over evil, and the love between Radha and Krishna.
Sammy Super Star: I wake up at 7am or earlier, I can’t really stay up until 12 or even 1am, I go to bed like a old man, sometimes I’m in bed at 9 or 10pm lol 😆
Mommy Guide Inc: Sounds awesome. Thanks Coach Adam for sharing:)
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: You look very intelligent with the 🤓
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus sleeps?
Sammy Super Star: Markus does a sleep stream lol 😆
Mommy Guide Inc: He he he. Kidding aside yes we all need to sleep in more.:)
Andrea Nunn: my first vertical stream!!
Coach Adam: Google picture of Holi and it will delight you. It's amazing. So much fun.
Andrea Nunn: looks great!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Andrea.:)
Tech Troublemaker: Let's talk about Stream Streams
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed Markus has kinda mastered the perfect way to set up scenes vertically:)
Sammy Super Star: I feel asleep while watching Roy’s stream before
Tech Troublemaker: I will do a 24 hour stream one day. I wonder how many will comment when I fall asleep.
Sammy Super Star: I took many naps while watching LSP over the years, that is how I stay up
Sammy Super Star: Yes
Mommy Guide Inc: I learned how to take naps from Sammy:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Friends don’t forget to LIKE this livestream.:) thanks
Sammy Super Star: The last time I did a 24 hour stream it went so bad
Coach Adam: Stream about streams that stream about streams...
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Markus and everyone
Eaglevp: Hi Janet
Mommy Guide Inc: Janet!! Hi my friend how are you sis?
Tech Troublemaker: Thanks @Sammy Super Star I am glad I am so interesting. 😛
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Janet!
Sammy Super Star: Yes @Coach Adam
Coach Adam: Streams about streams seems seamy. Right, Sammy?
Sammy Super Star: Yes!! 100% Adam
Coach Adam: LOLOLOL
Sammy Super Star: Your content is amazing Roy but the mornings when I wake up at 6:30 and don’t take a nap that is when I go to sleep
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Lala & Sammy, yall are funny
Mommy Guide Inc: I cannot for the life of me understand why people would want to watch someone sleep.:)
Sammy Super Star: I need to do a very long stream so then I can get my watch hours
Sammy Super Star: If I do a vertical live stream for 72 hours then I will have watch time
Mommy Guide Inc: I think the longest livestream I did was 6 hours
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I love my hoodie
Marielou Mandl: How did you get started with streaming?
Tech Troublemaker: I love my Hoodie!
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus does have amazing merch:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I’m starting going live again in the summer so everyone come and take a nap on my channel!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Haha Ana
techtroublemaker: My streams sometimes make me sleepy too. Long days. But after the stream the Adrenaline rush prevents me from going to sleep.
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Ana goes live constantly this month. Hope you can drop by.:)
Coach Adam: I followed Lala's lead...
Andrea Nunn: LEDA!!
Mommy Guide Inc: And Ana has still an ongoing mindset challenge.:) https://youtube.com/@anazugheri-faith52?si=scM-5jJx3Rb-0aox
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: I started to follow Ian Anderson Gray as he is a fellow singer and friend with some of my singing friends. He told his audience about ECamm so I got the free trial. I then won his top prize!
Tech Troublemaker: When no one is there, talk to the camera like it is a friend. Or the voices in your head, that's an option too.
Eaglevp: That was good Katy
Andrea Nunn: And Markus was the most "ever present" moderator and supporter!!
Markus Schaub: https://markusschaub.shop/
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: What colours do you have with your merch items?
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Thanks Keith
Mommy Guide Inc: I can absolutely do a nonstop talk marathon. I got a failing grade in grade 1 I think for being so talkative. Lol!
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Lala 🤣🤣🤣
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Thanks for the link Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Andrea I absolutely agree about Markus for being such a great supporter for us all:)
Coach Adam: I met Lala in Grade 1 detention, serving for the same violation.
mommyguideinc: Here with you Roy:)
janetdobbsanimalparadise: Hi Lala
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: I’ve subbed Ana Lala. I’ve not heard of her before.
Mommy Guide Inc: Lol Coach Adam - detention mates.:) Breakfast Club group
janetdobbsanimalparadise: All you had to do was mention and we show up
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh Katy Ana has an awesome podcast too.:)
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Thank you for telling us about her Lala. BTW keep being your wonderful talkative self. We love you for it! 💖
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: So good to see everyone. Miss you all. Have the best day/night
Marielou Mandl: 🥳🥳🥳🥳🥳
Stannex: Always great to hang out with you, Markus! Get some sleep!
Mommy Guide Inc: He he he. Thanks Katy and appreciate also your support dropping by on my crafty streams too. Love you Katy.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Channel members of Markus! You can also join us in the membership:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yay LALA
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: LOVE YOU TOOOOO 😘😘