Mommy Guide Inc: And herre we go!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Dance 💃🏻
Eaglevp: Evening Markus and Lala
Eaglevp: Hi@Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing
Ellie Calhoun: Hi everyone!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Keith! Hi Ellie!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Janet!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Ok morning exercise -‘check!
Sammy Super Star: Hey Markus
Eaglevp: Hey@Sammy Super Star
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sammy!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi everyone. had to move to my computer. soiunds so much better.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Lala, Markus, Ellie, Keithy, Sammy....
Mommy Guide Inc: And Hello back to you Markus!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Lala are you getting your sleep???
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yes slept at 9pm
Mommy Guide Inc: So got 8 hours of sleep - check!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yes!! I don't have a topic for tomorrow's live!!! got behind this week
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: hahaha
Ellie Calhoun: On Saturday, I'm recording a video for my YouTube channel and then will start doing shirts and going Live
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Ellie, I can't wait to see your "shirts"
Eaglevp: To do more shorts if time allows me
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus - still do edited videos! I really must create them. Procrastination go away!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: haha
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: you go Ellie. this is exciting
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey congratulations Ellie! Will try my best to ne there live but otherwise on replay for sure.
Eaglevp: Look forward to joining your lives @Ellie Calhoun
Ellie Calhoun: Right now my YouTube channel only has old videos from 2021
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Markus you would be a great video editor but it takes time to learn. you know... just one step at a time.
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes let’s do that Markus. Tag team:)
Eaglevp: I really love editing my weakness is picking out the right music
Ellie Calhoun: I'm at @elliemcalhoun
Mommy Guide Inc: Its like when i am actually in front of the computer - i freeze!
Mommy Guide Inc: I can always make up a million and one things to do except the editing
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Don't worry Markus. You are in great company. Even seasoned on-air professionals choke when they know things are being recorded but totally flow when live.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: they don't
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I love good accountability. really helps
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: □□
Ellie Calhoun: I don't know when my first Live will be, but I will edit and publish the first video by... end of Wed the 11th... hopefully sooner!
Eaglevp: We all have a voice Markus
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: oh that is funny.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: oh great Ellie
Mommy Guide Inc: Looking forward to your live Ellie on YT.:) rhis year my word is -HEALTHY so definitely having your lives on YT talk about how to improve health by movement will be very helpful
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: word for the year: Compassion & Gratitude (ok 2 words!!!) haha
Mommy Guide Inc: He he he - love the 2 words Janet!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I like COURAGE
Eaglevp: What is important to you Markus?
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Ellie i agree wirh you. Our videos on YT stays forever - so we can always greater reach specially for your content coz its evergreen.:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I like Compassion. Compassion for self so we can be kind on our journey and compassion for others as well. always working on that.
Ellie Calhoun: my word might be "courage" as well.
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes compassion is something we all should have.:) specially in this difficult times
Ellie Calhoun: Markus, you should send out a survey to your fans and ask some questions, like why we show up to listen to you!
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yes maybe lets all start using our community tab in YT to be more engaging. Havent been using that functionality
Eaglevp: That's a good question Ellie,I like the interviews Markus does and I think he should do more
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: You've got it Markus. challenging to be compassionate to ourselves. if we are not compassionate for ourselves how can we truly be compassionate to others.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I'm here because of you Markus. because of the community. FOMO!!! I love the interviews but also the games or other new things that inspire me. So many reasons I love to show up live here.
Mommy Guide Inc: Why do i show up as often as i can? You are an amazing speaker and LISTENER. Something thats very vital for doing interviews.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: As often as i can to Markus stream that is:)
Eaglevp: You have a gift for making people relaxed when you are interviewing them
Ellie Calhoun: Why I show up to watch you? there is something compelling about you. You have a way about you, making connections with people, you have interest in us and make us feel a part of something.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Is anyone taking doc rock's interview course that starts Saturday. speaking of interviewing...
Ellie Calhoun: So, now you need to reread these and reword it to be your "why"
Mommy Guide Inc: And then these interviews can be turned into podcasts Markus.:) in the future:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh what a great idea Lala
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Markus you are such a natural as a host and interviewer
Ellie Calhoun: I agree, Janet
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Markus is never fazed - always very relaxed so if you’re a guest you’ll forget that you’re live and interact like your usual self.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: so true Lala.
Mommy Guide Inc: Please dont forget to like this stream. It helps his channel if we like it.:) and share away too:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: 5 likes and 5 watching. pretty good!
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yeah!!!
Ellie Calhoun: so good to see you and even if you just ramble, it's great!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I don't know what I'm doing tomorrow. hahaha