Ellie Calhoun: Hello 👋 hello!
Eaglevp: Hello Ellie
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Keith, yes Roy I agree! Your vlogmas videos are great!
Ellie Calhoun: It's all different!
Mommy Guide Inc: Good day everyone!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: How are you Markus? Hope youre feeling better bow:)
Eaglevp: Hi Lala
Mariane Cresp: Hello Markus and everyone 👋🏼
Eaglevp: Think you should do more vlogging Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Philip great to finally meet you.:) Hi Mariane.:)
Tech Troublemaker: @Markus Schaub , you are always welcome to make fun of me. I do it all the time.
Mariane Cresp: Hello Lala
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Lala!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Mariane Cresp
Mariane Cresp: Roy, hello! 👋🏼
Eaglevp: Hi@Mariane Cresp
Tech Troublemaker: So excited you met Kali so close to home despite the train adventures.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi keith! And Ellie.:) yes loving the vlog-type videos of both Roy and Markus:)
Sammy Super Star: Hey Markus
Eaglevp: Hi@Sammy Super Star
Sammy Super Star: Did you get new glasses?
Mariane Cresp: Hello 👋🏼 Keith
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sammy! No storm or train issue can stop Markus and Kali meet up.:)
Sammy Super Star: I love the train
Sammy Super Star: Trains are so much fun
Sammy Super Star: I think there are more train delays from New Jersey to New York City then what you experienced
Sammy Super Star: First vlog! It was really good
Sammy Super Star: My first vlog was even worse
Sammy Super Star: My first vlog I think was in 2017
Sammy Super Star: How long was the train ride?
Mommy Guide Inc: I agree Sammy! The vlogs are so much fun and editing is goof:)
SuzanCz: Hey Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Coach Suzan!
Eaglevp: Hello@SuzanCz
Sammy Super Star: Was it easier to take the train or fly or you couldn’t even fly
SuzanCz: Cool!
SuzanCz: Hi @mommy Guide Inc and @Eaglevp
Sammy Super Star: In 2 years you will react to your self reacting to your self that is reacting to your live stream of the vlog.
SuzanCz: I like the shots where you’re lookin away. Really good B Roll!
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Suzan!
Sammy Super Star: You did some great b-roll for your vlog
Tech Troublemaker: Reacting to yourself reacting to yourself is called "Inception"
Sammy Super Star: The camera that you used was really good
Sammy Super Star: The B- Roll could be great stock footage
SuzanCz: Hi Ellie!
Sammy Super Star: Super cool!
Sammy Super Star: Day 3 was great
Mommy Guide Inc: Great narratives - and every second counted.:(
Mommy Guide Inc: Oops happy face :)
Pierre Kelly: Hi all
Eaglevp: Hi@Pierre Kelly
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Pierre Kelly
Fishstick USA: Smart tips on gimbal and use of background colors
Sammy Super Star: You might need the 60?
Sammy Super Star: Also your shutter speed might be a little low
Sammy Super Star: Yes
Tech Troublemaker: Love the walking scene the best
Pierre Kelly: That looks snowy
Fishstick USA: I forget. Which camera do you use?
Tech Troublemaker: Hit that "LIKE" button friends
Stuart Video -Tech Installations: Hi Markus!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi everyone
Mommy Guide Inc: Philip Markus was using a DJI Pocket 3
Eaglevp: Hello@Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing
Eaglevp: Hi@Stuart Video -Tech Installations
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I loved the puppets that you shared with us
Tech Troublemaker: Zero Euros is like "free beer" but not like "free puppies"
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: oh wow
Pierre Kelly: Should've used royalty free music to cover it
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Janet and Stuart:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hopefully not it was just fast.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Too funny.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Roy for the reminder to smash the Like button friends.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: I only wish the video was longer.:) it was so much fun.
Tech Troublemaker: All my music is Epidemic
Mommy Guide Inc: I love the vlog stgle mix in explaining the “tech”
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Maybe you mean you are not "sales-zzzzeee"
Stannex: Hi, Markus! Hi, Lala! Hi, everyone!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Stan!!!!
Eaglevp: Hi Stan
Stannex: Yes, Markus ... never tell yourself that you "can't do" something ... you'll just find ways to prove yourself right.
Pierre Kelly: Hey @Stannex
Mommy Guide Inc: Stan’s nee coloring calendar 2024 is shoer awesome guys- pls do check it out! Perfect gift for the holidays:)
Stannex: Hi @Eaglevp
Stannex: Hi @Pierre Kelly
Stannex: Thank you, @Mommy Guide Inc
Pierre Kelly: would people distract you from filming inside?
Tech Troublemaker: Today's video I realized the camera wasn't recording and of course, the unrecorded version is always better. 😛 So hence I am not driving on the final version, just in the car.
Tech Troublemaker: I am loving your Vlogmas videos Markus. Keep hitting the record.
Mommy Guide Inc: Tech happens all the time - but we just need to keep going. Perfection not the goal.:)
Fishstick USA: Good recommendations on car videos. Look at the camera once in a while. 👍
Stannex: I've thought about trying a Vlog ... maybe in the new year.
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Roy and Markus for a different ki d of vlogmas presentations this year. More please.:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Are we going to be on the same show with lala?
Mommy Guide Inc: Can Markus do not 1 but 2 crafty challenge in one stream? You need to go watch us and see! I am sure Markus will ve able to do and will be a crafter sooner than latet!
Tech Troublemaker: Can the Internet handle both @Markus Schaub and @Mommy Guide Inc in the same live stream?
Tech Troublemaker: Lala has been rocking it as well.
Mommy Guide Inc: Bwahaha Roy! For sure there will be tons of fun!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: haha @ Roy!!!
Tech Troublemaker: She was on my Holiday special. She never sleeps
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh i sleep guys promise.:)
Coach Adam: I'm here!
Coach Adam: A little late - but I made it
Stannex: Lala is my hero!
Pierre Kelly: Hey @Coach Adam
Stannex: Hiya @Coach Adam
Tech Troublemaker: Mine too! She is so amazing!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes more vlogs please.:) Hi Coach Adam!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Coach Adam
Pierre Kelly: I think you should watch Reel rejects for inspiration
Pierre Kelly: bit*
Coach Adam: I love your vlog style. You are a natural.
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh in Salem the tour guide was insinuating that I maybe a vampire! That was hilarious!
Pierre Kelly: @Mommy Guide Inc Wait, were'nt you Buffy?
Eaglevp: Hi Adam
Stannex: I think we ALL have "on camera" versions of ourselves. Yours seems completely genuine, which is a really tough thing to do!
Tech Troublemaker: HIT LIKE Ya'll!
Stannex: Like! Thumbs up! Heart!
Mommy Guide Inc: Bwahaha! If i will be like Buffy why not? But that really woke me up after 2 hours of ghost walk.:) he he he
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Markus! Wow that went fast.