Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Markus. Happy Thanksgiving 🦃🍁🍽
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I’m thankful for you and all you do
Deep True Crime : Happy Thanksgiving!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: 💃🏻💃🏻💃🏻💃🏻💃🏻
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: And to you
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Markus happy happy
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I know the feeling.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Such a small world 🌎 now
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: There is a story in America. The settlers in Massachusetts were starving and native people saved them by sharing their harvest
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: And many places it celebrates the bounty of the harvest
Tina Wan Kenobi: Hi Markus!
Tim Heale 9: Hi Markus
Tina Wan Kenobi: Hi Janet and Tim!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Tina
Tina Wan Kenobi: Happy thanksgiving to those celebrating it
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh shipping. Really hard. I sent my rcp to lala. Oh what a shock $$$$
Tim Heale 9: They also burn witches there
Tina Wan Kenobi: Its 5am here 😁 gonna start meditation in 30 mins.
Rich Vybz: Hey Tina wan Kenobl
Tim Heale 9: Salam
Tina Wan Kenobi: Hi Rich!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Salem back then.
Rich Vybz: Hey Markus
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Nope
Tim Heale 9: Luria went live earlier before I went live, Happy Thanks giving
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Always thankful for our community
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: If we start every day saying 1 thing we are grateful for our lives will be better
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: You are so lucky to have your parents
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yes 👍🏻
Tim Heale 9: My mother is still alive and spending my inheritance 😂
Tim Heale 9: Oh Keith is away today
Tina Wan Kenobi: Yes more than ever, because of the pAndemic, we know how we need to put value in time and people in our lives more than materials things.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: But savor the moment. That’s all we have 💕
Tina Wan Kenobi: Tim hahaha 😆😆
Tim Heale 9: At his daughters for the weekend
Tim Heale 9: I just savered a spiced rum
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Love that Tina. Good cooking
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: And yummy too
Tim Heale 9: I think I have nailed my target audience and format for my live show, just before yours
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yes the live community
Tim Heale 9: Ping me the link and I will join you now!
Tina Wan Kenobi: Go live together?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Tina did you see lala and me yesterday live together? So fun
Tina Wan Kenobi: Yes Janet! I watched the replay. You two had a good lunch together. 🥰
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: She is so fun
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: We tested go live while sitting next to each other haha
Tina Wan Kenobi: Yes no dull moment with lala right? I like to Drive with her bec i dont fall asleep BEHIND the wheel for long drives 😆😆
Tim Heale 9: Just trying to find a way in
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yes
Tina Wan Kenobi: Tim you coming up in the stream
Tim Heale 9: Just connecting
Tina Wan Kenobi: Janet Thank you for meeting up with her. ❤️
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh I would not have missed it. And driving while she was live was wiw
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Wow 🤩
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: We were so happy to see you
Tim Heale 9: That link doesn’t work
Tim Heale 9: Ecamm link?