Down To Earth With Katy : Hiiii
Down To Earth With Katy : Hi my friend
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: guets neus / happy new year
Down To Earth With Katy : You’ve done so well so far
Down To Earth With Katy : I’ve felt that a lot during this Christmas and gradually getting my life back on track
Down To Earth With Katy : That song helps re not giving up. I hope you can have that song in your head, I should sing it to myself too
Budgeting Momma: Hi Marcus
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: good self-control
Stan!: Happy New Year, Markus! And everyone!
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: i'm still recovering from the new year's eve party 99/00 where i danced for 3 days straight
Stan!: "Dance like no one is watching."
CSLiveDK : Hi Markus. Happy New year😀👍🥂
Down To Earth With Katy : Wow I’m impressed by the dancing! I love dancing. I aim to start moving this year
Down To Earth With Katy : Ooh, that’s a scary thought re 20th & 21st century!!
Down To Earth With Katy : I danced with my toes for 5 mins today! That’s my first step towards moving
Daniel Chi - Creator Techlab: Markus!!! Happy New Year!
Mariane Cresp: Happy New Year 🥳 Markus!
Down To Earth With Katy : I think you’ve been really consistent this year
Stan!: Hi, Mariane! HNY!
Daniel Chi - Creator Techlab: Woohoooooo!
Down To Earth With Katy : Nice to see you all. Happy 2025
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: better to set small goals that you can achieve than to set big ones and not achieve them and then become depressed
Mommy Guide Inc: Happy Nee Year Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi friends!
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: On the road but wanted to say happy new year my friend!
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: my goals are simple. have fun with my life - only make mistakes that are not that bad - and stay alive 😛
Mommy Guide Inc: It’s ok my friend.:)
Down To Earth With Katy : I love setting NY goals, it helps me to feel strong, excited and motivated
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: you can have fun with walking - thats for your motivation - and if you have trouble one time - dance your way - like the guy here in st.gallen wo is famous for dancing trough the city
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana, Stan, Eric, Daniel, Pierre, Coach Adam, Katy and budgeting Momma
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: huhuu @Mommy Guide Inc i see your not live on your stream 😛
Mommy Guide Inc: I start with a One Word for the year and mine this year is abundance
CSLiveDK : A little funny about this about loosing weight every new year. Here in Denmark people says the problem is not what you eat between Christmas and new year but between new year and Christmas. 🤣
Down To Earth With Katy : I love that: go and set them and then go and get them!
CSLiveDK : Hi Lala😀
Mommy Guide Inc: Eric lol hi Ejnar
Mommy Guide Inc: We started the NY with walking.:)
CSLiveDK : Happy e
Mommy Guide Inc: Don’t forget to hit the LIKE button my friends:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Too much eating in December.:)
CSLiveDK : Happy new year to Ana and all the other excellent people here. Nice to meet you all again😀
Down To Earth With Katy : I think mine might be Thriving
Mommy Guide Inc: Katy that was mine 3 years ago:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Last year was faithful
Down To Earth With Katy : Yay Lala xx
Down To Earth With Katy : Abounding in life!
Mommy Guide Inc: Congratulations Markus by the way on finishing the music video!
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Mine is visualizing
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: ok friends i have to go - i have to create 2 new videos now - for my 50 reserve video archive :P
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: bye be
Mommy Guide Inc: I am doing Doc Rock’s challenge - do something daily - I plan to do a video daily for a year
Mommy Guide Inc: Bye Eric!
Mommy Guide Inc: I don’t want to do it and I don’t like edited video that’s why I will do it. Lol
Mommy Guide Inc: Facing my fear.
Mommy Guide Inc: Batch production would definitely help me with that. Let’s see if I can.