Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
Down To Earth With Katy : hiiii
Sara S: Made it!
Down To Earth With Katy : How are you Markus? The little UFO looks cute!
Down To Earth With Katy : Hi friends
Down To Earth With Katy : I've had a bit of a break from content creation as my poor mac mini needed to go to hospital twice and is still not 100%
Down To Earth With Katy : I don't need it but ......fun! I don't blame you!
Down To Earth With Katy : wow! That IS fun!!
Marielou Mandl: on its so cute!
Marielou Mandl: yea! I love that !!!!
Eaglevp: Evening Markus
Down To Earth With Katy : hands free?!
Eaglevp: Looks good the DJI Neo
Eaglevp: Hello Katy
Eaglevp: Hi@Marielou Mandl
Down To Earth With Katy : Hi Keith x
Marielou Mandl: Hi @Eaglevp and friends.
Eaglevp: So when is the next walking update coming out Markus?
Down To Earth With Katy : That look steep! Do you just put your hand out to get it back??
Marielou Mandl: I'm surprised its not closer to the osmo pocket 3 video quality
Pierre Kelly: afternoon all
Eaglevp: Hello@Pierre Kelly
SuzanCz: Hi!
Pierre Kelly: did you get the drone to work?
SuzanCz: Oh - that’s cool!
Eaglevp: Have you finished your new intro yet Markus?
Eaglevp: Hi Suzan
SuzanCz: Finally caught you live!
SuzanCz: Yes, looking forward to seeing you.
Down To Earth With Katy : I've still forgotten to send you the clip! I'm so sorry!
SuzanCz: Can you bring your new drone?! #fun
Eaglevp: Do you need any more footage from me?
SuzanCz: Yesssssss
SuzanCz: Yes, let’s plan on some walking!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Markus! Hi friends sorry I am late. Good morning:)
Mommy Guide Inc: DJI Neo. ooh another awesome gear:)
Eaglevp: Hello Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Keith, Suzan, Katy, Marielou, and Sammy:)
SuzanCz: You’d think it would give you a heads up before it got critical! 🤔
Down To Earth With Katy : These are nice bedtime drone stories
Mommy Guide Inc: do you need a license to use a drone in Switzerland?
Sara S: My phone battery is going so I have to go. What a fun toy!
Down To Earth With Katy : Take care Sara! Good to see you here
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi and bye Sara. Have a great rest of the day:)
Mommy Guide Inc: that's great!
Mommy Guide Inc: oooh live flying:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks friends for being here and see Markus test out his awesome gear - don't forget to kindly hit the LIKE button:)
SuzanCz: We don’t use “sensible” for decision-making around here! 😆
Down To Earth With Katy : does it recognise objects and avoid them?
Down To Earth With Katy : ooh, don't break it Markus!!
Mommy Guide Inc: this is it pancit!
Mommy Guide Inc: no remote needed? voice activated? good job~
SuzanCz: So fun!
Eaglevp: pLEASED THAT WENT WELL
Down To Earth With Katy : it recognises your voice and hand?
Eaglevp: Pleased that went well
Mommy Guide Inc: whew! good job Neo:)
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: hello crazy swiss friend
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Eric:)
Eaglevp: Hi@Eric Maechler - Online Marketing
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: huhuu @Mommy Guide Inc @Eaglevp
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: as long as you head is on the right place - flying drones are not dangerous
Rich Vybz: hey Markus!
Eaglevp: Hello @Rich Vybz
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Rich!
Rich Vybz: hey Eaglevp hey Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: that would be so much fun!
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: have fun with the creative crowd #usa
Mommy Guide Inc: will miss you all too - but i know you will share it with us all:)
Mommy Guide Inc: yes! you can do it. Congratulations also for inspiring us with your awesome health journey! My son and I still walk every other day:)
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: soon its time for snow walk 😛
Mommy Guide Inc: Eating habits still not good - that one i need to change soon!
Mommy Guide Inc: we do it inside the mall so whether rain or shine- we can still do it.
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: i see snow already 🙂 and 7 day ago it was 28
Eaglevp: Lala I am thinking of visiting the Philippines sometime in 2025 would love to meet up if possible.
Rich Vybz: My journey has had a major setback unfortunately, dealing with major lower back issues atm. seeing a physiotherapist next week
Mommy Guide Inc: oh I am Markus - coz i am quite small - so i am very much beyond normal limits. he he he. for heatlh reasons - i need to stop eating also junk food.
Mommy Guide Inc: oMG Keith!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes absoutey - i will not let you leave the Philippines without meeting up. Tell me your schedule and I'll be your tour guide. i'll make myself available for you.
Mommy Guide Inc: ok i will make myself accountable - first thing to go - rice and sweets!
Eaglevp: Will do Lala going to do a lot of travelling over the next 4 years
Mommy Guide Inc: I'll report next week if I will be successful.
Rich Vybz: Yes im treating it as though my starting point has been moved a few positions back. Still on the same journey, but have to add a few more steps
Mommy Guide Inc: Go Keith! If you can go Feb - Victor will be here too")
Down To Earth With Katy : I have a chocolate bar each day Lala and put on weight.
Eaglevp: May visit you as well Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: Go Rich!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes I don't want to feel "deprived" but absolutely need to lessen the carbs.
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: rice? isn't that a staple food for you? filipinos - what do you eat there? potatoes @Mommy Guide Inc
Down To Earth With Katy : I look for the smallest chocolate (they are called Freddos in the UK) but shops have stopped selling the small bars!
Mommy Guide Inc: ooh that's recorded Markus - the hesitant Crafter going live soon! Vlogmas here we come:)
Eaglevp: My weakness is fudge
Down To Earth With Katy : I have very low carbs and no sweets or sugary drinks really but I do have a choc bar
Down To Earth With Katy : ooh, I love fudge
Mommy Guide Inc: Katy - thats a great idea - go small! yes!
Mommy Guide Inc: I do dessert after each meal:(
Mommy Guide Inc: i love my sweets.:(
Mommy Guide Inc: Eric yes rice is staple food - but will have to learn to live without it coz i eat too much of it - i eat rice even for snacks. not good:(
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: i am the pasta killer 😛
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: i hope you can find an alternativ @Mommy Guide Inc - eating without joy is not fun
Mommy Guide Inc: Eric thanks for that awesome advice - a healthier alternative and smaller portions - thats the first step.
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: 👍 @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: Pasta for me even meets rice - he he he- carbs meet carbs - it's delicious though.
Mommy Guide Inc: yes Markus - one cup of rice per meal. let's start with that:)
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: kebab ziit
Mommy Guide Inc: yey! Congratulations Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: You've been able to sustain it:)
Mommy Guide Inc: I can do 3-4 cups per meal.
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: 500g pasta a small portion 😛
Mommy Guide Inc: thanks for that advice Markus. I'll update you and everyone next week!
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: i'm lucky - my weight has been stable for 20 years :) even though i do a lot of sport - that's why i'm so "relaxed" i will ned be a top model
Mommy Guide Inc: great Eric! 20 years. wow!
Mommy Guide Inc: i used to be very malnourished - coz when i was still studying i don't have time to eat.
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: @Mommy Guide Inc in my youth i was always like a toothpick - bang afterwards - but that's normal in my fam - everyone was +100
Mommy Guide Inc: at age 40 i started to gain weight and it never went down. LOL - need to go middle -
Mommy Guide Inc: i learned to enjoy my food at age 40+ before i eat coz i am hungry but never really enjoyed what i was eating. then i learned to appreciate delicous food and that's it!
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: @Mommy Guide Inc thats hard - for me eating was alwys the source of joy.... i wish all can du that
Mommy Guide Inc: true Eric - delicous food is a source of joy now - so that's why i don't cook - coz i want to eat delicious food. I am a bad cook:( he he he
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: yes i am 1,97 with 110-120cm thats ok - sometime i whish my "paukä" stomage is smaler but it is what it is
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: i always say - when i cannot climb stairs - then is should change something 😛
Mommy Guide Inc: Same Eric. SInce i've been underweight most of my life - the heavier me is bad for my knees.
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks so much Markus. Time flies by so much when you're having fun.
Mommy Guide Inc: maybe next time you can share some of your healthy meals Markus? Friends?
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: take care @Mommy Guide Inc #knee