Rich Vybz: ho ho ho, happy winter solstice!!!
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Frohe Weihnachten
Eaglevp: Evening Markus
Eaglevp: Hi Rich
Eaglevp: Hello coach Adam
Rich Vybz: hey eaglevp
Eaglevp: Yeh Phillip
Eaglevp: Hi Janet
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello 👋
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi everyone! Hi Keith and Ana!
Ellie Calhoun: Hello hello!👋
Rich Vybz: hey mommy
Eaglevp: Hi Lala and Ellie
Eaglevp: Hi Ana
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Good to see everybody 🎄🎉
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Janet, Afam and Rich! Yey Pholip and Ellie.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Merry almost CHRISTmas
Coach Adam: Lala!
Ellie Calhoun: Happy Solstice and Merry Christmas 🎄
Mommy Guide Inc: In our own words - Maligayang Pasko!
Mommy Guide Inc: You said it right Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Awwww the angel is on the gift now/:) Congratulations my friend.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Christmas is for me the birth of Jesus - the reason for the season, family, gift giving and tons and toms of food and christmas carols.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: And tons and tons of craftinng!!!
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Personal - Jesus birth and a time for family especially the children. Content creator - Time for planning for new year content.
Ellie Calhoun: Christmas for us is family, gathering eating and celebrating.
Coach Adam: I time to cook for all my Christian friends and family.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Jesus! Peace and love ❤️
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes! Gathered together and games 😋
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Lots of food 🍱
Rich Vybz: peace for all
Fishstick ~ Phillip: For me, this year means 4 days until retirement.
Mommy Guide Inc: Nice whys my friends.:) wish i could celebrate alongside all of you face to face but glad that at least i can do so virtually.:)
Ellie Calhoun: Congratulations Philip!!🎉🎉🎉
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Congratulations 🎊
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow let the last 4 days begin til the big R! Congratulations Philip!
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Lala, my first project is making a craft room for my wife.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: So fun!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I’m praying for another year of friendship ♥️
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey a craft room for Markus. He he he.:) and for you all!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I love wrapping gifts 🎁
Ellie Calhoun: I have so much still to do!
Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone
Rich Vybz: hey sammy
Eaglevp: Hi Sammy
Mommy Guide Inc: I love giving put gifts and handmade cards too.:( and created 2 advent calendars for 2 of mg most active viewers and cards for them yoo:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I look forward to start a new year with a new season of creating content and also learning a new healthy routine for myself
Sammy Super Star: I’m doing great
Sammy Super Star: Like the added music
Ellie Calhoun: It's my yearly tradition 😂 end up being awake until 3:00 am Christmas morning
Sammy Super Star: I’m excited for Christmas, I’m buying my self a new lens
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Sammy! Yes to healthier routines Ana! Love it.:)
Ellie Calhoun: Me too Ana! New year for a new start with content creating! I've been away from it for a long time.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Let’s do it Ellie!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Thank you! I do need all the cheering 📣 I can get. Yes! Accountability
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Go into a fitness center? No, I want to eat out more. Haha
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I’ve been on a new me dedicated journey for two weeks so far so good
Sammy Super Star: I’m working on some big things on the channel
Sammy Super Star: I’m going to try and get some more watch hours before 2024
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey!!! Go Ellie.:) Philip let’s eat more - but healthier options.:)
Coach Adam: Fitness vs Fatness is a noble pursuit. I joined a gym on black friday and I’m still sore from Thanksgiving
Ellie Calhoun: I started a new healthy routine and then Covid derailed me for most of Dec
Sammy Super Star: I might be making weekly short films 😉
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I had to, I received q scary diagnosis…so don’t be like Ana and start now
Sammy Super Star: I’m going to have a loop of a stream just to get some watch hours lol 😂
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Health it’s my word
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Lala. I agree on healthy eating!
Eaglevp: Growth Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Nice one Keith - Growth is nice. Mine is goign yo be - Faithful:)
Sammy Super Star: a lot of people are testing for covid again and its very sad
Ellie Calhoun: I have to test because I work with clients too closely
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes! Plan with an action
Sammy Super Star: I got to get the word out for my films
Coach Adam: My word is preservation. I want to look this good well into my 7th decade. Lol
Sammy Super Star: I got the Sony FX30 now so I can do what ever I want to do BUT I had to buy a new SD card that was $$$$
Sammy Super Star: It will be fun
Coach Adam: and 2024 will be the year I make my best videos ever. I can’t control my audience, but I can do my best.
Sammy Super Star: Action Word create
Sammy Super Star: No I get it
Sammy Super Star: 100% Markus
Mommy Guide Inc: Awesome Sammy. Create was my word about a decade ago.:)
Fishstick ~ Phillip: I had all preventative shots and was dipped for fleas.
Sammy Super Star: I have 4 of them right now
Sammy Super Star: It wasn't the space of the SD card it is the speed. Some of the recording settings can't be used with the ones I have now. I needed to get 300mb SD card and just for 1 is $170
Ellie Calhoun: I have to think about my word for 2024... there are so many options! 😂
Mommy Guide Inc: You looking great Coach Adam.:)
Coach Adam: We both look marvelous, Lala!
Sammy Super Star: Yes 100% @Coach Adam
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Coach Adam but need to eat more healthy for sure - i cant say No yo chocolates and sweets;(
Sammy Super Star: Yes! I really enjoy your show
Stannex: I made it!
Mommy Guide Inc: You ate a great story teller Markus. Lovin your vlogmas and Roy’s.
Sammy Super Star: Real People that makes real connection
Stannex: Hello, Markus ... Happy Christmas!
Sammy Super Star: I think that is everyone @Mommy Guide Inc
Eaglevp: Hi Stan
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Stan! Stan goes live late:)
Stannex: Gathering with friends for Christmas dinner. Other than that ... just general merriment.
Stannex: Hi, @Mommy Guide Inc @Eaglevp @Coach Adam @Ellie Calhoun @Sammy Super Star ... and EVERYONE!
Stannex: YEs, tonight's show is a Holiday Special!
Coach Adam: Stan! Thanks for the awesome Year of the Dragon card. I love it!
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh lay I suggest Stan’s colouring calendar for 2024 as an awesome 🎁:)
Ellie Calhoun: Good to be here! Merry Merry!!!
Coach Adam: Great to hang out with you as always. Cheers!
Stannex: Ho ho ho!
Mommy Guide Inc: Merry Christmas Markus and to all of you my awesome friends!!!
itdair.network: Best wishes for each one of you! 🍾🎉