Run Adam Run: Markus!
Run Adam Run: We are all eating and waiting for the fireworks
Stan!: Markus!!
BostonDonMTB: Howdy all
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Adam! We guessed as much! Happy 4th of July!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Stan!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello friends, Happy 4th!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana amd Don! Glad to see you back Don!
BostonDonMTB: Hi Lala
Eaglevp: Hi@Ana Zugheri - Faith52
Mommy Guide Inc: Today my som
Eaglevp: Hi@BostonDonMTB
Mommy Guide Inc: My son and I did 7651 steps.:)
Eaglevp: Hi Stan
Stan!: Hi @Mommy Guide Inc
BostonDonMTB: Hi @Eaglevp
Stan!: Hi @Eaglevp
Eaglevp: Hello Adam
Pierre Kelly: happy 4th of July!
Stan!: Bingo! 1pm here on the U.S. West Coast.
Eaglevp: Hi@Pierre Kelly
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Pierre.:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Go @Lala!!!!
Run Adam Run: Congrats to Lala!!!
BostonDonMTB: You inspired me to get on my bike after I watched your video. I did 5.9 miles on Tues on the road, yesterday I did 5.2 miles on the road again. Leaving soon for another ride.
Eaglevp: Well done Lal my average is 5000 steps per day
Mommy Guide Inc: 2 days ago it was only 5k+steps. Just doing it every other day I am doing it alongside Matkus. Now problem
Mommy Guide Inc: Now problem is after running - we eat! Yikes.
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Keith! My son is a great walking buddy.:) he really keep me
BostonDonMTB: I haven't been on my bike since October. LONG TIME. I decided after your video to take "My first pedal". To keep moving. Well done Markus. Mission accomplished.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I haven’t done my steps yet, hopefully I’ll get to it later this evening I have 8000 to go. 😜
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Don that’s awesome!
BostonDonMTB: Thank you Lala.
Run Adam Run: It was a great video
BostonDonMTB: Thank you!
Mommy Guide Inc: So true Adam. I also liked Markus’ walking path.:) beautiful Lake Lucerne in the background most of the time.:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I listen to podcasts or audiobooks while I walk and I get lots on them so I don’t think too much on how hard it is to do it in this heat 🥵
Run Adam Run: Walking is better for fat loss.
BostonDonMTB: I remember me encouraging you in LEDA after your first live. So felt like I need to do this.
Eaglevp: Hope so Adam
Mommy Guide Inc: Gosh Don LEDA - always have fond memories of it.
Run Adam Run: You could get up if getting it done before the heat is more important than sleeping in.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes, the accountability is my motor, I get encouraged when I watch Coach Adam and now you Markus!
Run Adam Run: For sure, if we can do it, ANYONE can
Run Adam Run: Yes, if it wasn’t hot I’d be sleeping
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: My issue of walking outside is…lately we have spot coyotes and straight dogs in the neighborhood…they scare me 😱
Neil Farrimond: Hey Markus!
Run Adam Run: Do you have a treadmill, Ana?
Run Adam Run: I have a desk treadmill in front of my TV
Eaglevp: Evening Niel
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Party 🎉
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Neil:)
Neil Farrimond: Hi Keith.
Run Adam Run: I have a story of being chased by a pack of stray dogs I
Run Adam Run: When I was running in Rome
Run Adam Run: and I got a personal best time out of fear of being bitten
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Exactly, I have a treadmill but definitely not the same. I go to the park on Mondays and Tuesdays. I walk while she does soccer practice. Right now I just go around my driveway lol 🤪
Run Adam Run: OMG, what a nightmare
Mommy Guide Inc: I forgot - i do have a stationary bike i can use in case the weather is bad.
Mommy Guide Inc: Yikes Adam!
Neil Farrimond: Mountain Biking is me and my wife’s go to exercise now. I was a runner for years but my knee isn’t as good as it used to be. We have e-Bikes which gives us a lot more range to explore Portugal.
Run Adam Run: I can’t wait to see your view of Lurcern
Run Adam Run: I did some laundry and discovered my rowing machine in the bedroom lol
Mommy Guide Inc: Neil that’s awesome
Mommy Guide Inc: You did Regata Adam?
BostonDonMTB: You are still exerting yourself on the e-bike.
Run Adam Run: Yes, exactly. lol
Neil Farrimond: You should do travel-exercise videos that showcase your beautiful country 👍🏻
BostonDonMTB: I just put all my riding stuff on. I am going to drive to a rail trail in the next town over. I haven't been on it yet. Probably could ride 10+ miles.
BostonDonMTB: Film.
Mommy Guide Inc: Don that is your content right? Motor Biking?
BostonDonMTB: My content was talking to people about mountain biking and their passion. I haven't put up a video in A LONG TIME. I have 5 interview already recorded, but not edited. I was in a real funk.
Neil Farrimond: Small steps.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: One thing at a time!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Go Don! Hope you can put those videos out soon.:)
Neil Farrimond: I cut out milk and sugar from my coffee about 10 years ago, was one of the best things for me. Small steps.
BostonDonMTB: That is the plan.
Mommy Guide Inc: Its not motor bike but mountain bike. Sorry about that. I remember you went live tweaking your logo
Pierre Kelly: nice Neil
Mommy Guide Inc: Friends pls don’t forget to hit the LIKE button:)
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Hello Markus
Neil Farrimond: You have so much content now!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Philip was thinking about you just now and you appeared in the chat! Yey:)
michele bussan: try low carb diet with intermittent fasting long with your walking
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Since I was diagnosed with diabetes in December, I have made lots of changes in my life, mentally, physically and spiritually. All go together, but yes micro changes…brings you to a macro one.
Stan!: When you're DOING something, you constantly get new stories to talk about.
Stan!: You have a video of DOING the thing ... and one where you can talk ABOUT doing.
michele bussan: thanks
Mommy Guide Inc: Nice intentionality Ana.:) love it. And yes ive seen Ana’s posts and videos on her walking / runs.:)
BostonDonMTB: Alright everyone, I am going off to ride. I will likely record future rides. I have my GoPro, and wireless mics. I just need to figure out mounting so you guys can see me ride.
BostonDonMTB: @Ana Zugheri - Faith52 you are right about the micro to macro.
Mommy Guide Inc: One thing i know for sure - Markus has better knee condition that me.:) Go my friend.:)
BostonDonMTB: @Stan! You got that right.
Mommy Guide Inc: Don looking forward to it pls do share your channel
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes! I did! My A1C went from 6.8 to 6.0 in six months without meds. I will be honored to share 😊
Mommy Guide Inc: Your video links Don so we can follow your journey as well:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Am so happy for that win Ana!
Mommy Guide Inc: Adam, Ana, Laura we have awesome
Mommy Guide Inc: Awesome inspiratjon in you all. Thank you!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Thank you @Mommy you are awesome 👏
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes, I’m planning my comeback to streaming and video making. 💪🎉🤗
Mommy Guide Inc: Awesome livestreams coming up! Excited much.:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: The love 💕 is mutual
michele bussan: get ub 10000 steps a day
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey go Ana! Looking forward to them.:)
michele bussan: get 10,000 steps a day
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks friends
michele bussan: doesn't have to be walking, keep moving
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Michele - i want to do 14k 2-3x a week.:)
Stan!: Happy walking, Markus!