Ellie Calhoun: Catching you live!?!?!
Ellie Calhoun: Favorite song 🎶
Ellie Calhoun: And I'm first?
Ellie Calhoun: Wow!!! We've had first rain in a long time!
Ellie Calhoun: Get those things for your shoes that grip and walk outside. I love walking in the snow as long as I have the right boots, jacket and snow pants
elle naturally: Smow!!!
elle naturally: Will maybe snow next week in new england
elle naturally: How much snow do you usually have?
Eaglevp: Hi Markus
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Keith, Hi Elle!
Ellie Calhoun: I hope we get snow here in New England!
elle naturally: Hi Ellie
Ellie Calhoun: Yay!
elle naturally: Ellie which state are you in? I think snow next Friday is possible
elle naturally: Woaa Eagle that is a lot!
Ellie Calhoun: I'm in MA. You?
elle naturally: MA
elle naturally: Western central?
Ellie Calhoun: @elle we should meet up!
elle naturally: Yes
Ellie Calhoun: I sent you bouncing on a trampoline, did you get it?
Eaglevp: I will send you more footage from Tunisia when I get back next week Markus
Eaglevp: It was a personal best Ellie
Eaglevp: Yes watching from Hammeramet, Tunisia
Ellie Calhoun: Hmmm I'll have to find it
Eaglevp: Cyprus next month for 28 days
Ellie Calhoun: Good for you! That's amazing to walk home in that snow!
elle naturally: Do you have a rule that only E names can be live?
elle naturally: 🤔😂
Ellie Calhoun: @elle 😂
Eaglevp: I watched your video so decided to book
elle naturally: I knew it!
Eaglevp: Hi Elle
elle naturally: Hi Eagle
Ellie Calhoun: That's cool!
Eaglevp: Got to go bye all
Ellie Calhoun: That's great to find the tool for you! You are doing great!!
Ellie Calhoun: Good night! 😴🌙💤😘
elle naturally: ☺️
elle naturally: 😄
elle naturally: Have a great night!