Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Markus!
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Hello Markus and Lala
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello, hello! So happy to see your pretty face my friend!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: How fun!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Philip! Hi Ana!
Eaglevp: Evening Markus and Lala
Eaglevp: Hi Phillip
Eaglevp: Hello Ana
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Keith:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi everyone. sorry I'm late to the party. LALA & Markus!!! 😻
Eaglevp: You have really done well Lala to organise this event
Eaglevp: Hi Janet
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Janet!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I can't wait for it to arrive. I want a long sleeve tShirt. I told you I would buy if you do it.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: yall are too funny
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: never change
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: that's a huge difference $$$$
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Let's see it!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: awww! I love hats, that is so cute!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: wow. love it.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: nice....
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: love it!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Wow!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: can you put the reg link in the comments?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Me too Markus.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I am sure is going to be an amazing and super fun event.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I want to order it too!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: https://mommyguideinc.com/mgi-craft-getaway-2024/
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: thanks!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: so I have to join your membership to see this page?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: never mind. I found it.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Houston Tx!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: i'm trying to do the free but it will not let me. it sends me to payupal and then back somewhere.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I have only the free one. now I have subscribed and will try again.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: i'm getting there. it kept sending me to the wrong place but I think it will work now. I'll let you know. good you have us to test
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: lol
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I did it!!!. so next to try the next step.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Talk to me!!!!!! lol
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: it says it does not ship to the USA!!! but this is just all video access. bummer!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: no problem. and I will share this with some of my crafting friends and family. yaya.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: be positive. you WILL
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: well, let's pray for that!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I think the Lord will bless your obedience and dedication. I pray that one day if not this one, you have SOLD OUT tickets
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes! I will share it too.
Adam El Gringo: I'm late, but hopefully didn't miss the best part. LOL
Adam El Gringo: and not sure why I can't switch to my alterego "Adam Tinkoff"
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Adam
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: we all love to celebrate 🎉
Adam El Gringo: Two of the most beautiful people in the world right here on this stream. We are so fortunate and blessed to have you both in our lives. Thank You.
Adam El Gringo: HAPPY BIRTHDAY!!!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: You can do it! You are a pioneer and an amazing example of a woman to follow and learn from
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I thought it was tomorrow!!! on wait!!! it is tomorrow in Lala land!!! happy happy happy birthday dear sister
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: 🎊🎊🎊🎊🎊🎊
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: '\
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: yay the year of the dragon. lots of virtual fireworks
Adam El Gringo: My mom had a wooden spoon she used to shake at us kids and say "oh you will see fireworks if you don't stop"
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh that's a good one Adam.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: You are on fire this is brilliant.
Adam El Gringo: Your event in person is on my bucket list. One of these years...
Adam El Gringo: Markus, you are coming with me.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: 🐙
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: How fun!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks friends. prayers pls.:) 🙏
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: It's your birthday! celebrate and giggle
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh I will have to support too
Adam El Gringo: Yeah - just under $20
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: It came up $18.50 I think
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: no not shipped in the uys
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: us
Adam El Gringo: I will sign up once you fix the link. Happy to support you.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: yes Paypal did
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: do a short live from the event. it would be like being there with you