Mommy Guide Inc: Here we go!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Dance 💃🏻 time
Mommy Guide Inc: Let’s do the dance emoji!:) 💃 🕺
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: 💃🏻💃🏻💃🏻💃🏻💃🏻💃🏻📫📫📫📫
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh my finger slipped
Cheryl Wolf: Hey all
Ellie Calhoun: 💃🕺💃🕺💃🕺💃🕺💃🕺💃🕺👯👯👯👯👯👯
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Markus!!!!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Cheryl
Cheryl Wolf: Markus ❤️💃💃
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Cheryl!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Here we go
Cheryl Wolf: Hey lala
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Ellie
Mommy Guide Inc: Has anyone by any chance memorized this awesome song? let’s Go!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I love this song
Mommy Guide Inc: I agree Ellie- this should be every content creators theme song.:)
Cheryl Wolf: 🎶🎶🎶
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yesssss
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL - the make up stream! Epic!
Cheryl Wolf: Agree lala
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Luna just jumped up to dance and purrs …. Treats for everyone
Cheryl Wolf: Hey luna 😻
Mommy Guide Inc: Awww Hi Luna!
Ellie Calhoun: Hello Markus!!!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hiiiii Markus
Eaglevp: Hi Lala
Cheryl Wolf: Hey Kieth
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Keith@EagleVP!
Eaglevp: Hello Ellie
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Keith!!!!!
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Keith
Cheryl Wolf: Markus story time
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: So happy you are here
Ellie Calhoun: You are here!
Eaglevp: Hi@Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Once upon a time…..
Eaglevp: Hey Cheryl
Ellie Calhoun: I need a nudge, getting close to live again.
Ellie Calhoun: Actually way behind on Leda too!
Mommy Guide Inc: Has anyone been repurposing content? How do you do it if ever?
Ellie Calhoun: Time issues! Lol
Ellie Calhoun: I'm going to reignite my group and page on FB.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh fantastic about podcasting M
Mommy Guide Inc: Ellie am a day behind in LEDA too. But nice thing is we can always catch up!:) we can do it!
Ellie Calhoun: Lala I'm a whole week behind! 😳
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Go Ellie!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yes for audio only and podcasting with descript
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hello 👋 friends! Happy Thursday ☀️🎉
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Ana!!!!
Cheryl Wolf: Hey Ana
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I’m the car 🚗
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana.:)
Cheryl Wolf: Confessions of a content creator
Ellie Calhoun: Thanks Lala, hope I can get to that soon...
Eaglevp: Hi@Ana Zugheri - Faith 52
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Oh this is the topic to talk about!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Love that Cheryl
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: 😂
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Cheryl - confessions of our struggles
Cheryl Wolf: Yes Lala the struggle is real
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Are y’all doing Leda?
Cheryl Wolf: mine is going or doing recordings. I was better when I went live I was on schedule
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Hi Markus 👍
Mommy Guide Inc: I feel I’ve information overload - it’s too much I don’t know which one to do first. Do I do a darts of which one goes first? He he he
Shelly Saves the Day: 🙂🙂🙂
Eaglevp: Hi Ejnar
Cheryl Wolf: Hey shelly
Ellie Calhoun: Was that ? for me regarding a time going live? (I'm multitasking lol) if so, no I don't have a time
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @shelly Saves the Day! Yey!
Eaglevp: Hi Shelly
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Ejnar.:)
Shelly Saves the Day: That’s definitely a reason I love live too.
Cheryl Wolf: Hey Ejnar
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Shelly!
Mommy Guide Inc: Sheryl I always find ways to not start editing.:( I will commit to you all - at least one edited video weekly! There pls make me accountable
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh yes… a poll
Cheryl Wolf: Lala I hear you
Ellie Calhoun: I'm in the middle of editing a video that I was supposed to publish yesterday 😕
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey!!! Maybe Markus you can do some streams on basic editing for beginning content creators? He he he I’ll definitely fall in that category
Ellie Calhoun: @Cheryl, keep trying to edit video! I believe in you!!!
Cheryl Wolf: You got this Ellie
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Fake it ‘til you make it!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Look at you!!!! That was cool
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yes to that Ana!
Mommy Guide Inc: Friends please don’t forget to LIKE this livestream. It truly helps Markus channel when we do so:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow instant poll! Love it!
Ellie Calhoun: Plan is to publish Wednesday but I was traveling... will do it tonight. Keep reminding myself it doesn't have to be perfect
Cheryl Wolf: no, this is confessions of creators we confess our struggles and Markus helps us work it out
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh will check out Shelly’s videos.:) binge watch them:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: To me, it’s like I know ALL the theories on how to stop the procrastination…and I just don’t do it
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh try editing live - would love to see that Markus:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Ellie! Up to now I do the exercises you taught me and it has helped a lot Ellie. So pls do continue sharing.
Cheryl Wolf: That is wonderful lala
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: My biggest problem is subtitles, directly from danish to English. I have to translate all manually. It’s time consuming. Time that could be better used doing other things. Hope AI can help with that😀
Ellie Calhoun: Thank you Lala 😊💕
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh my that sounds a bit daunting Ejnar but hopefully you find a way to do the subtitles indeed. I tried watching some of your videos but indeed can’t understand Danish.
Cheryl Wolf: Jump before we are ready
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes!!! 😂😂😂😂
Mommy Guide Inc: I loved the video about you showing some places
Eaglevp: Hi Esme
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I have it on my calendar to start going live tonight at 7…I’m already making excuses no to 😝
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Esme Bickle! Welcome to Markus’ channel:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I didn’t even announce it
Horace Podmore: Hi Esme 🍻
Ellie Calhoun: @Ana do it!!!
Cheryl Wolf: Ana 😂
Eaglevp: Hey Horace
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yay! Welcome @esme
Mommy Guide Inc: Please don’t forget to LIKE & SUBSCRIBE to Markus’ channel.
Esme Bickle: Tim told me
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Pm central time
Mommy Guide Inc: Awww so nice of Tim. Glad to see our community growing:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Oh 😖🫣
Horace Podmore: Tim also told me about you
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Welcome new friends!!!
Cheryl Wolf: 1 am your time Markus ?
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: What time is for you right now?
Kali : markus!!!
Kali : #MARKUSRULES
Cheryl Wolf: Night owl
Ellie Calhoun: Hey Kali!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: 😂 no no no oh gosh you are making me do it!!!!
Cheryl Wolf: Kali !!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh time zones - the bane of my being on time. He he he. So pls do share your links for your lives in the future so we can be there:)
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Hey Kali😀😀😀👍👋
Eaglevp: Cheryl are you still doing live's on facebook have not seen you for awhile
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Kali!!!!
Ellie Calhoun: Yes, Ana, I'll try to be there
Kali : @Ellie Calhoun @Cheryl Wolf @Mommy Guide Inc @CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming @Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing hey!!! 🤗❤️ dang! the gang is all ehre!!
Kali : CONFETTI!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Miss that #markusrules
Eaglevp: Hello Kali
Kali : @Eaglevp hey!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Here we all are
Tim Heale 9: Hi Markus I see some of my friends have jumped in
Cheryl Wolf: Hey Tim
Eaglevp: Thank Tim for recommending Markus live stream
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Hi @TimHeale9! Thanks for sharing this stream to your friends so now it’s an awesome party.:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Me and my big mouth 👄 😂
Kali : @CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming thanks ejnar!!
Kali : @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52 😂
Tim Heale 9: Hi All ❤️
Mommy Guide Inc: I missed the MasterClass:( but Luria mentioned about an encore! Will be there - pls remind me. He he he.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: All the good reasons!!!!! Markus you are awesome
Cheryl Wolf: Yep off on videos time to
Cheryl Wolf: Jump back in
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: @Kalli so awesome see you here
Ellie Calhoun: Markus, keep asking why... why do you love it?
Kali : @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52 so awesome to be here!! 🤗❤️
Mommy Guide Inc: Everyone is Awesome!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey!!! Putting it in my Calendly now.
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: It was so good yesterday in the masterclass. Enjoyed it. So powerful as as always. 😀👍
Kali : Markus I feel like you could aim your content specifically at "smaller" creators and give them a platform to talk about their passions/business. you could even make your discord about that too -
Tim Heale 9: I do both live and record
Kali : where creators come together
Kali : and meet other creators in their niche
Cheryl Wolf: Perfect Kali
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Love that kali
Kali : ❤
Kali : not blabbering!!
Cheryl Wolf: 🎉🎉🎉Party
Kali : woohoo!! ❤ ❤ yes party!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Oh that is good! Oh Kali you just nailed it for him
Kali : markus i have so many ideas for you 😭❤️
Cheryl Wolf: Kali knows her sh$t
Kali : @Cheryl Wolf 😂😂
Kali : i will!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: https://www.facebook.com/215103768906965/posts/pfbid0gEe2uZDrNuhizvYjcyTqde4x3JBMSbTBv8HxNVM3p6DeeQvpbSxi4MNALwnfda5ml/?mibextid=unz460
Kali : right?! just improv! hahaha
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: We will hole you accountable 🤣🤣🤣🤣🤣
Cheryl Wolf: Live stream party multiple guest maybe Markus
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hold not 🕳️ hole
Mommy Guide Inc: See you all there next week! Thanks for the reminder Kali!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes kali is the Markus to the Ana!!!!
Kali : @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52 LOL
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow Mac M2! New gear Markus. Yeah!
Kali : @Mommy Guide Inc ❤
Ellie Calhoun: I love that Ana
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh I vote for that
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Party 🎉
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Me😀
Cheryl Wolf: 🖐️
Kali : eys!
Kali : *yes!
Mommy Guide Inc: Sometimes we just need to unload and share our woes with others and it feels better already right?
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes
Kali : that would be so awesome!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yes my party people family
Kali : @Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing party animal!! hehehe
Ellie Calhoun: I'm in
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Haha Kali😻🦄
Adam Tinkoff: Hey Markus
Adam Tinkoff: Happy Implementation Day
Eaglevp: Hello Adam
Tim Heale 9: Hi Adam
Adam Tinkoff: Thanks for the invite
Adam Tinkoff: It's 420 - there's that.
Ellie Calhoun: Bette is awesome!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh good markus… sleep 😴 💤
Adam Tinkoff: I am 420
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: New idea. Markus Sleep stream😀👍😂
Cheryl Wolf: that’s fantastic I am so glad you’re getting sleep and getting help with that. Yay, Markud
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Love Betti
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey! See you again next week with Markus and Bette.:) it’s a party date! He he he. Yes we need sleep - Cheryl r
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh a sleep membership
Adam Tinkoff: Sleep health is a great topic
Mommy Guide Inc: Cheryl reminds us of that among other great health tips
Cheryl Wolf: Exactly markus
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Have a good day Lala or nap 😴
Mommy Guide Inc: I slept at 8pm last night:) got enough sleep today:)
Ellie Calhoun: That's great Markus!!! I'm glad you are taking charge of your sleep!
Adam Tinkoff: We all sleep, so we are all experts on some level
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Thanks Markus
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Thanks everyone
Adam Tinkoff: You did it!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yay Lala