Eaglevp: Hi@elle naturally
elle naturally: Hi Eagle
Down To Earth With Katy : Helloooooo
Down To Earth With Katy : From a very stormy south of UK 🇬🇧
elle naturally: Hi Katy
Eaglevp: Hi Katy
elle naturally: ❄️❄️❄️❄️
Coach Adam Runs: Hey there Markus, how's the fitness going?
Down To Earth With Katy : Massive apologies Marcus. I find it hard to record myself walking as I have to concentrate on my steps due to the fatigue.
Down To Earth With Katy : Hi Elle! Hi Keith! 👋
Eaglevp: Hello Adam
elle naturally: Hello coach adam
Down To Earth With Katy : Great song!
Down To Earth With Katy : Amazing!!! I’d love to see how you did it
Down To Earth With Katy : Suno?
Coach Adam Runs: Song idea: "Delete your couch and walk outside"
Coach Adam Runs: In a Power Punk Pop style.
Down To Earth With Katy : Love it. Very clever!
Coach Adam Runs: Oh it will be great!
Enda Trading: Hello from Hanoi!
Coach Adam Runs: I LOVE IT!!!
elle naturally: lol
elle naturally: Hello enda
Enda Trading: Hi @elle naturally
elle naturally: ☺️
Eaglevp: Hi@Enda Trading
Coach Adam Runs: I love them both
Down To Earth With Katy : No more crumbs between the seams 🤣
Coach Adam Runs: Great message
elle naturally: Hmmm version two??
Down To Earth With Katy : I think the first one
Down To Earth With Katy : The second one sounds a bit like the Friends theme song
elle naturally: It does sound familiar
Coach Adam Runs: That's kinda what I was after. It's full of positive energy.
Coach Adam Runs: Power Punk Pop
Coach Adam Runs: Triple P
Coach Adam Runs: I think you have a typo.
Coach Adam Runs: It's Delete your Couch not "COACH" lololol
elle naturally: Oopppsie
Coach Adam Runs: LOL!!!
Coach Adam Runs: I think I like the Suno lyrics better!
Down To Earth With Katy : Delete your coach 🤣
Coach Adam Runs: Yeah this is it
Coach Adam Runs: Live a life beyond your chair!!!
Coach Adam Runs: It's really great!
Coach Adam Runs: "Try again"
Coach Adam Runs: LMAO!!!
Coach Adam Runs: Tell it that it's for a power pop song poster
Coach Adam Runs: YES!!
Coach Adam Runs: Try again
Coach Adam Runs: Delette?
Coach Adam Runs: Yes, much closer to the spirit of the song
Coach Adam Runs: Super fun
Ellie Calhoun: Hey everyone! I'm late to the party!!🎉
elle naturally: Hi Ellie
Ellie Calhoun: What's goin on?
elle naturally: 😎
Coach Adam Runs: seams
Coach Adam Runs: no "c"
Tech Troublemaker: Hey everyone!
Coach Adam Runs: It might win a VMA
Coach Adam Runs: INSERT JEOPARDY MUSIC HERE
Coach Adam Runs: or Sponge Bob's "Three Hours Later..."
Coach Adam Runs: YAY!!
Coach Adam Runs: Super catchy! I love it.
Coach Adam Runs: You can trim in YouTube
elle naturally: Love it
Coach Adam Runs: click the pencil
Coach Adam Runs: Use ChatGPT to write your description
Tech Troublemaker: ChatGPT rocks! I use it every day for so many things. I even have it set as my default search engine now.
Coach Adam Runs: ChatGPT picked up Delete your COACH!!! lol
Kathy Hester: Hi Marcus!
Coach Adam Runs: The song rocks!