Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Janet! How are you today my sister from another mother?:)
Eaglevp: Hello@Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing
Cheryl Wolf: Hello All
Eaglevp: Hi Cheryl
Cheryl Wolf: hey keith and lala
Tim Heale 9: Hi Cheryl
Cheryl Wolf: hey Tim
Mommy Guide Inc: Excited to see Markus and Coach Shelly together on screen.:)
Shelly Saves the Day: Hello everyone! Thanks for being here! Looking forward to chatting with all of you!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey hey 👋
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey!!! Hi @ShellySavesTheDay!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I am here too but driving
Eaglevp: Hi@Shelly Saves the Day
Cheryl Wolf: 🎂Hey Ana Happy Birthday!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Birthday girl is here - Happy Birthday Ana!
Esme Bickle: Hi everyone
Eaglevp: Hello@Ana Zugheri - Faith 52
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Esme Bickle! Thanks for being here:)
Cheryl Wolf: The high and lows we ride the wave
Tech Troublemaker: Hey everyone!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy@TechTroublemaker
Cheryl Wolf: Hey Roy
Eaglevp: Hi Roy
Mommy Guide Inc: So true that’s how i got to watch @ShellySavesTheDay
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Thank you 😊 this is a wonderful way to spend my birthday 🎂 among friends!!!
anthony quate: hi.just received the mike does it have Bluetooth?
Mommy Guide Inc: For more of our awesome guest’s videos please dont forget to subscribe to her @ShellySavesTheDay
Mommy Guide Inc: And dont forget to smash the Like button for this awesome livestream.:)
Sam Coker: i like gloves
Sam Coker: what gloves do you have at home
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Q what would you say is the secret sauce for consistency?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Happy Ana birthday 🥳
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Thank you 😊 I am celebrating 🥳 with y’all!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: We celebrate 🎉 you!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Awww thanks for celebrating your awesome birthday with us Ana:)
Roger Wakefield: OMG… It is the amazing “Shelly”!!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Thank you guys! I for sure feel the love ❤️
Eaglevp: Hi@Roger Wakefield
Mommy Guide Inc: Batch production - great advice Shelly:) Hi @RogerWakefield:)
Roger Wakefield: Hello…
Cheryl Wolf: Hello Roger
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes!!!!
Roger Wakefield: I’m just a plumber….
Mommy Guide Inc: Confetti 🎉 all around:)
Roger Wakefield: YES!!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes! That is also a good idea…collaboration.
Tim Heale 9: @Cheryl Wolf Not see you live lately, are you doing LEDA?
Mommy Guide Inc: Great advice. Let our content breathe
Cheryl Wolf: I have not gone live; I am recording @Tim Heale 9
Mommy Guide Inc: Just keep moving.:) it is what it is.
Roger Wakefield: Thumbs up everyone… This is greatness!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Consider subscribing and following our awesome guest Shelly - https://youtube.com/@ShellySavesTheDay
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes!!! I’m in that moment…I have all these ideas but I don’t get in action…Im stuck I keep procrastinating
Cheryl Wolf: Q Do you think it is because we think about ourselves and not who we are doing the video for
U Do It: Hey there Markus!
U Do It: Hey Roger, Shelly, Cheryl, Ana, @Mommy Guide Inc
Roger Wakefield: Hello Big John…
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @UDoIt!
Adam's Exploits: Hello Markus and Shelly.
Cheryl Wolf: Hey @U Do It
U Do It: Mrs U Do It misses you Roger!
Adam's Exploits: Hi @U Do It and @Roger Wakefield
U Do It: Hey Adam!!!
Adam's Exploits: Hi @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow great advice - even half baked ideas 💡 can be used. Learn from it:) Be brave and bold. Let’s do it!
Tim Heale 9: Q YT Shorts how is it some fly and some stall ie 2 shorts on the same subject a few minutes apart 1 goes to the ballistic and the other bombs?
Cheryl Wolf: What? Shelly is human lol
Mommy Guide Inc: Mindset. Thanks for this reminder Shelly:)
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL @ CherylWolf.
Mommy Guide Inc: Congratulations by the way Shelly for reaching 40k subscribers yet again!!!!
Adam's Exploits: ome people think that they know everything. However, even Socrates, one of history’s greatest philosophers, doubted his omniscience and famously stated “all I know is that I know nothing”.
Mommy Guide Inc: Wisdom right there @Adam’s Exploits
Adam's Exploits: Shelly is doing really well with her Shorts cliets.
Cheryl Wolf: We like real people
Cheryl Wolf: @Mommy Guide Inc So true
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks everyone for being here - pls dont forget to Like this livestream and consider subscribing to our awesome host and guest:)
Tim Heale 9: Wow I hit 245 and 45 not growing that fast 😏
Mommy Guide Inc: @TimHeale9 your shows are awesome. You’ll get to that next milestone soon. Cheering you on friend.
Cheryl Wolf: Size or engagement
Mommy Guide Inc: I think one thing that i am learning from Shelly tonight is to just really - keep on. Do what needs to be done.:)
Sammy Super Star: Hey everyone!
Cheryl Wolf: hey sammy
Adam's Exploits: Hi @Sammy Super Star
Tim Heale 9: Thanks Lala, I don't get hung up on numbers, I do it for fun 😻
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @TraditionalMedia and @SammySuperStar
Cheryl Wolf: Shelly you take the focus off you and more on the wins you give others
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed @TimHeale9. keep going my friend.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Aww indeed sometimes a positive comment may impact the creator more than we can think of.:) so let’s try to comment and encourage.:)
Adam's Exploits: I had an old friend who did jewelry videos and her Adsense was high
Mommy Guide Inc: So many important nuggets of wisdom Shelly.:) Just keeping it real.
Mommy Guide Inc: Keep ourselves grounded. Do the work and not just dream or plan it. Guilty of this sometimes.
Cheryl Wolf: wow!! congrats
Cheryl Wolf: Markus you sing
Esme Bickle: I have two left feet we
BostonDonMTB: Is there a way to quantify those new "Shorts" acquired subscribers are actually engaging with your purposed content videos?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Don@BostonDonMTB
BostonDonMTB: @Mommy Guide Inc Hi Lala, hope all is well.
Cheryl Wolf: Thank you
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Don. Yes all is well:)