Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Markus!
Stan!: Hello, hello, hello!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Stan!
Mommy Guide Inc: oh yes!
Stan!: Hi, @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: And you are here:)
Stan!: Yeah. It's important to say it ... but it's ALSO good not to beat yourself up about it.
Stan!: Last week didn't work ... okay. That's done. Let's try something different next week.
Mommy Guide Inc: so true Stan!
Mommy Guide Inc: yes let's start with one walk. just did one walk with Biboy this week. Need to go back to the every other day schedule.
Stan!: I had students in Japan who would do interesting things because they KNEW I was going to ask "What did you do last weekend" in class next week.
Mommy Guide Inc: yes wouldn't it be nice if we were just neighbours and we could all walk alongside each other? then dinner or snack after? healthy ones of course. he he he
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Hello! coming in for a bit, glad to see eveyone here.
Mommy Guide Inc: You are here despite all things. I want able to go live the whole week last week too! Wed I got home very late and the AC wasn't working I couldnt go live coz it would be too hot with the lights on.
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Thank you! yes, 3rd week on a row, praying I can stay consistent.
Mommy Guide Inc: then Saturday I updated my OS to Sequoia finally and none of my cameras worked. eventually it worked but it was past midnight so I just went live earlier.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana!!!
Stan!: Lala is helping to inspire me to try something new, too.
Mommy Guide Inc: Stan whatever you decide my friend - we will be there:)
Stan!: My old channel got closed out about a year ago
Stan!: My new one has been up since last June and I'm still doing weekly livestreams
Mommy Guide Inc: Stan is back and he has two shows on his new channel - 50 Years in the Dungeon and of course his Random Encounters Show.
Stan!: Lala has inspired me to seriously look at doing "drawing of the week" stuff for new artists to try.
Mommy Guide Inc: oh yes its going to be really late for you Markus.
Stan!: Yeah, my timing is not good for viewers in Europe.
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: I just changed my notifications too, I wasn't getting any from Stan.
Stan!: YES! One of my main themes has always been EVERYONE can draw ... you just need to let yourself learn step by step. (Like starting to walk or other things.) The key is to have FUN along the way.
Mommy Guide Inc: its a challenge that actually speaks for someone like "me". and I know there's many out there like me.
Mommy Guide Inc: congratulations Ana!
Mommy Guide Inc: I saw a procreate book in the mall earlier Stan. I was contemplating on getting it and now I feel I should. he he he
Mommy Guide Inc: there is next week. and you got busy with work but you are still here Mrkus.
Stan!: We're all here for one another!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Stan and Ana! Ana's basic with a little bit of extra - I truly find that very inspiring.
Tech Troublemaker: Yay! I didn't completely miss you after all.
Mommy Guide Inc: ooh don't my friend. I slept early so I actually have almost 8 hours in.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Lala!
Tech Troublemaker: But you would have missed "seeing" us?
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus maybe you can also do some app reviews for health monitoring?
Tech Troublemaker: And yes, you can just hit go live and it will ask a could of questions and off you go.
Mommy Guide Inc: like what you use?
Tech Troublemaker: I just started back walking after being a slacker for months.
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Thank you @Mommy Guide Inc
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: It's in the air, I am tired too...
Mommy Guide Inc: oh yeah!!! Congratulations Roy! is it safe to go live while walking?Markus maybe you would want to bring Laura - Stuart's wife on as a guest? she is a marathon coach.
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: but I know why...I am working on launching a podcast in Spanish and I stayed up late working on potential names.
Mommy Guide Inc: ooh exciting Ana.
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: yes! that is the good thing that I can just grab the English content and translate it.
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL green on green screen.
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: I have a good number of people asking me for the content in Spanish...so give the people what they want lol
Mommy Guide Inc: oooh excited to hear more Ana. we'll look forward to it.
Tech Troublemaker: I have been fighting with YouTube Studio to try and translate my transcripts into Spanish and Klingon
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: I can do it for you Roy!
Tech Troublemaker: I have the way to translate it but it won't let me upload it to my videos. Working on it.
Mommy Guide Inc: Lol Ana on Klingon and Markus on Spanish and me on German.
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: That is what I do for a friend of mine, she uses google and they I just come bahind it to make sure it really works. It's pretty accurate so I don't spend too much time on that.
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Yes, team work!
Stan!: Love you right back, Markus!
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Yes, I was playing with chatgpt and I still need to train it to be funny in spanish lol
Tech Troublemaker: We love you!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thank you Markus! See you again next week. Indeed we love you friend!!!
Cheryl French: Hey everybody!
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Yes, Markus, you are inspiration and we love your streams.
Mommy Guide Inc: Please don't forget to hit the LIKE button friends
Stan!: Have a good week, everyone!
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Hello and goodbye Cheryl!!!
Cheryl French: So good to see you Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Cheryl!!!!
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Have a good week!
Cheryl French: Sorry to miss most of it!