Mommy Guide Inc: And the party has started!
Eaglevp: Boom Katy's on the show
Claire Sara: Woohoo!!
Claire Sara: Nice to see you all!
Tim Heale 9: Boom it happens on line
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Tim!
Tim Heale 9: Hi Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: This is such a great feel good music indeed. For livestreamers:) 💃 🕺
Eaglevp: Hi Tim
Tim Heale 9: Hi Keith
Mommy Guide Inc: I spy Tim and Claire!
Tim Heale 9: I thought that wasn't Katy
Stannex: Woo hoo! Here we go!
Ellie Calhoun: Hey Markus!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Hi Markus & Katy!
David W. Ryan: Hi Markus!
Tim Heale 9: My first time
Claire Sara: I'll take the welcome confetti as many times as I can get it haha
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Stan!!!
Eaglevp: Hi@David W. Ryan @Ellie Calhoun
Tim Heale 9: Won't be my last time
Claire Sara: Amazing!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes promise i won’t time you out today Stan! LOL
Ellie Calhoun: Who hoo!!!
Eaglevp: Hi Stan
Stannex: Exciting! Wish I could be there, too!
Cheryl Wolf: Hello All
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ellie & David!!!
Claire Sara: Hi Cheryl!
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Katy!
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Claire
Eaglevp: Hi Cheryl
Mommy Guide Inc: OMG i am waiting for my visa renewal Markus.:) bit i am on waiting list
Stannex: No worries, Lala! If you do, I'm sure I'll deserve it. LOL
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Cheryl;)
Cheryl Wolf: Hi keith , Ellie, lala 🤩
Stannex: Hi @Eaglevp!
Claire Sara: Great hat
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Cheryl, Keith, Lala, Stan, Claire, Tim, David... everyone!
Mommy Guide Inc: Love the Fedora hat Katy:)
Cheryl Wolf: I love hats!! very smart looking
Tim Heale 9: Katy had a red one on yesterday
Ellie Calhoun: Love the hat!!
Stannex: Hi @Ellie Calhoun !
Mommy Guide Inc: Saw the post about that podcast event - saw Tim with you also:)
Tim Heale 9: Not to mention we did a live stream from the show
Tech Troublemaker: Hey everyone!
Ellie Calhoun: I'm so excited to meet Markus in person!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy@TechTroublemaker
Claire Sara: Hey Roy!!
Mommy Guide Inc: You’re looking great Katy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh Ellie i pray 🙏 i can join you all in Creator Camp
Eaglevp: Hi Roy
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow Katy is so talented.
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Eaglevp and @Mommy Guide Inc and @Claire Sara and @Ellie Calhoun and @Tim Heale 9 and @Stannex and @Markus Schaub @Cheryl Wolf and @David W. Ryan , etc.
Cheryl Wolf: Please explain beauty health?
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow thank you all for being here please don’t forget to hit the LIKE button - it truly helps Markus’ channel:)
Ellie Calhoun: Quite a range of skills!
Mommy Guide Inc: What an awesome journey towards content creation
Cheryl Wolf: yes lala for sure!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Cheryl.:) ❤️
Stannex: There's power in authenticity.
Stannex: Thank you, Lala. ☺
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hi friends 👏🤗
Cheryl Wolf: Yes BE YOURSELF, thank you take the focus off us put it on who we sever
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi everyone. Sorry I'm late to the party. I brought Reiki cookies 🍪🍪🍪
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Janet!!!
Cheryl Wolf: oops Serve
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Lala. you are up early!
Cheryl Wolf: Hey Janet
Eaglevp: Hi Janet
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Cheryl!!!
Stannex: Hi, Janet!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Love Thrive with Live
Mommy Guide Inc: Slept early Janet.:)
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Janet
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi everyone. The gang is all here
MySnoopy80: Hi❤️
Eaglevp: Hi@MySnoopy80
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Moni@MySnoopy:)
MySnoopy80: Hi@eaglevp
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Podcasting is my favorite 🤩
MySnoopy80: Hi LALA❤️
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yes repurposing and podcasts. so good
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: But now that we can do it both it’s the best of both worlds!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I want to learn how to set up a podcast. I'm pretty clueless
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana! And love your podcast too Ana!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey confetti 🎉 for Markus on starting his new podcast!!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: OH that's interesting.
MySnoopy80: 🎉🎉🎉
Mommy Guide Inc: I love how Katy puts out a what do you call it - a written version of her podcast:)
David W. Ryan: DeScript is amazing
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I always load my lives into descript to get the transcript.
Mommy Guide Inc: There thanks Janet - transcript! My brain is still not functioning at 100% he he he
Fishstick USA: Q: I am sorry that I am late due to work. My question to Markus is where will you host your podcast?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: This info would make a great little masterclass or workshop. I would love all of the information step by step. wow thanks
Motif Music Studios: Nice to catch you live!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Q: what about podcasting on YouTube? did you already talk about that?
Mommy Guide Inc: This is Katy’s podcast https://thrivewithliveshow.alitu.com
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: thanks Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Katy’s other socials are in the description of this awesome livestream.:)
Motif Music Studios: Yes, I am so curious about starting a YouTube podcast series, as my "Coffee with Composers" series really suits that!
Fishstick USA: Q: Katy and Markus, will your podcast be audio plus video or audio only?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Sweet
Tim Heale 9: I repurpose all my interviews and live shows as podcasts
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @MotifMusicStudios and @FishstickUSA
Fishstick USA: Q: I have a friend has a podcast on Apple. Do you have a reason to use or not to use Apple?
Tim Heale 9: Teaser episode
Motif Music Studios: @Mommy Guide Inc hellooo!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: ah like the good old radio days
Motif Music Studios: This is a great episode for me! I really love going live and connecting with others so may consider those shorty episodes too!
Motif Music Studios: Hair in the air, don't care - that's fabulous!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I’m going to start wearing a hat lol
Mommy Guide Inc: Podcasts have shorts now? How awesome! Oh 5-minuters or so.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: This is golden info Kati!!!!!love it!!! And love the idea for Markus! Yes!!! This is great content for your podcast!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: is there a best length for a podcast?
Motif Music Studios: Yes, so authentic. I think Elyse Meyers is a good example of how people are drawn to authenticity.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes!!! Find your flow. ♥️
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: He is!!!
Fishstick USA: Q: Katy, I see you use Apple, Spotify and Google. Is one better than the other?
MySnoopy80: I second that
Motif Music Studios: Oh wow. I need to figure this out. Great tips! Thank you~
Mommy Guide Inc: Go @MotifMusicStudios
Cheryl Wolf: I will third that
Stannex: One thing that speaks volumes about what kind of person Markus is — the quality of people you find in his chat rooms! Such wonderful folks!
Motif Music Studios: @Mommy Guide Inc thank you!
Motif Music Studios: @Stannex that's so true. Really appreciate the guests here!
Motif Music Studios: I missed when you said what your preferred platform is!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes!
Stannex: Best length for a podcast: Just long as you need ... and not a minute more. ;^)
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: This has really open and expanded my vision. I’m so grateful to both of you and our friends asking really good questions ♥️
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yes @Stannex
Mommy Guide Inc: It took me awhile to figure out how to get into apple podcast but the others were instant.:)
Motif Music Studios: Love that reminder again to 'audience first' and knowing what their needs are,
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: YES!!
John Westhaver: Hi amazing people.
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Katy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @JohnWesthaver
Cheryl Wolf: Thank you Katy!!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh this is fantastic Katy
Motif Music Studios: So fabulous! Love that this is just what I've been thinking about!
Motif Music Studios: @John Westhaver Good day!
Stannex: Hi @John Westhaver
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh exciting John
John Westhaver: Katy I love your support! You are amazing!
Eaglevp: Hi John
Mommy Guide Inc: https://www.facebook.com/thrivewithlivevideo?mibextid=LQQJ4d
Motif Music Studios: Yes, Amie! Bravo Markus!
Stannex: This hour always goes so quickly!
Motif Music Studios: Thank you! Excited to follow what you do!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Thank you Katy and Markus. this has been great