Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Go Marcus and MarieLou!
Images by Gretchen: Hi Marcus
Eaglevp: Evening Katy
Eaglevp: Hi@Images by Gretchen
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Katy! Hi Marielou:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Gretchen!!!
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Hi Keith! Hi all!
ana_zrjuly: Watching on IG!!! So cool 😎
Images by Gretchen: Lala!!!!
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: When I was at middle school I was pretending to be a DJ with our vinyl records 🤪
mommyguideinc: Hi friends!!! I am also on Markus' IG awesome!
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Great
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: great layouts Marcus
Mommy Guide Inc: That's so cool Katy:)
mommyguideinc: Hi Evelyn and Neil!
evelynmyangle: Yeah
Mommy Guide Inc: The pandemic despite being one of the darkest moments in human history also paved the way for most of us to become content creator:)
evelynmyangle: Hello Taylor
mommyguideinc: Hi Amy @Creativeamplifierrs and 24hrboss:)
ana_zrjuly: Yes
Mommy Guide Inc: yes a lot of people became "plantitos" and "plantitas"
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Ooh, I like the March Madness challenge idea!
24hrboss: These eCamm Instagram Lives are next Level🔥
Mommy Guide Inc: friends don't forget to smash the LIKE button and hopefully consider following both Markus and Marielou if you are new on their IG and YT
Eaglevp: Katy you will have to do April madness
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Good idea Keith
mommyguideinc: Hi Ana:) I absolutely agree 24hrboss:)
24hrboss: So you don't acknowledge those in the chat for your short lives?
Sara S: Markus!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: HI Sara!
Cheryl French: Hej Markus!!!
24hrboss: Yes!! @mommyguideinc
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Cheryl:)
Cheryl French: Hey Lala!
Sara S: Hey All!
Pierre Kelly: H all
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Pierre:)
Eaglevp: Hi@Cheryl French and@Pierre Kelly
Eaglevp: Hi Stan
Cheryl French: Hey!
Eaglevp: Hello@Sara S
Mommy Guide Inc: Great idea - prep questions ahead of time:) Thanks Marielou:)
24hrboss: That's bold - 2hrs of a Talk 👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼
Cheryl French: Thesel are good ideas!
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Uses your time and energies well doing that: effectively batching but doing it all at once. I like that
Stannex: This is such great material that I came in and started making notes so fast I didn't even have a chance to say hi!
Stannex: Hi, everyone!
Mommy Guide Inc: Stan! Hi:)
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Wow! Find things to do for 2 1/2 hours on live!
Pierre Kelly: It's also like HSN and TJC
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Sali
Mommy Guide Inc: I could probably do HSN etc coz I can talk and talk and talk. he hehe.
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: I feel the same MarieLou.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Philip!
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed - we got everything - now just need to determine which one works for us.:)
ana_zrjuly: You are so inspiring 🎉♥️
Mommy Guide Inc: For questions pls put a Q: so Markus can easily find it:) Thank you so much friends for being here and hope you are having an awesome fun and learning so much.
ana_zrjuly: When I grow up, I want to be like you 😋
Pierre Kelly: YOu know what? I miss the old intro?
Stannex: Not ready? GO!
Cheryl French: Ana!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana!
Mommy Guide Inc: switching things around and see what works best for us. nice suggestion Marielou:) thanks:)
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Love those thoughts
Cheryl French: So true! Be more of ourselves!
ana_zrjuly: Love that creator therapy ♥️🎉
Tech Troublemaker: More vertical videos...
Cheryl French: Hey Roy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Cheryl! Hey Lala!
ana_zrjuly: Atomic habits, love it!!! 🥰
ana_zrjuly: Excuses versus reasons
Mommy Guide Inc: ouch! excuses.guilty.
Fishstick ~ Phillip: I am fine with vertical. Markus, you seem to format it well.
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: The vertical is a bit strange on YT as on my iPad I can see you both teeny weeny to see the comments at the same time
Tech Troublemaker: I love excuses! They are the lifeblood of why I don't do enough videos. :face-blue-smiling:
Mommy Guide Inc: I tried it last night - it's hard coz the scene was so small for a crafty livestream. but was so surprised how it got pushed even after the live - I ended with 55 views and now at 300+ views
Fishstick ~ Phillip: C: I am watching on ipad which is normal. I also have it running on my phone.
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: That’s great Lala!
Cheryl French: Wow, Lala!
Mommy Guide Inc: for the user experience - crafters still prefer the non-vertical for livestreams but will continue to test
Stannex: As a consumer, I don't have a strong feeling about vertical. As a creator, I'm struggling with how to work it in with my art creation content.
Tech Troublemaker: I am trying to figure out what need vertical fits.
Mommy Guide Inc: I feel you Stan.
ana_zrjuly: Reset!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Marielou has a video and editing classes if anyone is interested and of course we can subscribe to her YouTube channel @marielousmandl
24hrboss: People want a magic pill, and there isn't one. Growth takes time.
Mommy Guide Inc: Laptop died so now on my phone.:) hope i didnt miss much.
Tech Troublemaker: Be sure to HIT that LIKE Button 👍
Pierre Kelly: You ok @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Pierre.:)
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: I find it difficult to make engaging videos from my bed (I am getting into action even though chronically ill): speaking at the same time as stock videos and chapter heading and bullet points and ..
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: sometimes as a small talking head in the corner trying not to show that I’m in bed
Mommy Guide Inc: Go Markus! We want to see the imperfect video.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Your podcasts are awesome Katy. Hope today youre feeling much better. Biggie hugs.:)
24hrboss: What are some of the tutorial videos that Marie does? Or any suggestions we can do as Creators?
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Thank you Lala xxx
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Go for it Marcus
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: You’re a fab creator coach Marielou
Pierre Kelly: Yes
Stannex: I'd show up for "imperfect Markus" ANY day!
Mommy Guide Inc: Absolutely! I would watch Matkus live or on recorded video:)
Motif Music Studios: Really neat set up with the vertical live here! Way to rock an new opportunity!
Stannex: Me memory of you preparing for that video was that you got all the pieces together and then got hung up on the "how do put these together" ... like it was a jigsaw puzzle.
Motif Music Studios: Ah that's so lovely!
Pierre Kelly: oh ho @Motif Music Studios
Mommy Guide Inc: I agree Amy:)
Motif Music Studios: @Pierre Kelly helloooo!
The Honest Accomplice: Wait does this replace Marielou’s live? Do I have to superchat? So many questions
Tech Troublemaker: For just hanging out, it is probably great. But for presenting something, I hate it.
Motif Music Studios: @Tech Troublemaker in the house! Nice to see you here.
Motif Music Studios: Yes, great reminders on that clarity.
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Thank you x
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Motif Music Studios!
Motif Music Studios: Totally makes sense, @marilou
Motif Music Studios: Are you using ECamm for it to look like this in vertical!
Pierre Kelly: Didn't she put a trivia murder party voice in there?
Tech Troublemaker: Yes, Ecamm Live and LSP overlays. Great combination
Motif Music Studios: Ah, looks so good!
The Honest Accomplice: Hey Roy
24hrboss: I'm thinking tutorials for tech? For example I do a lot of Canva videos. I do livestreaming and podcasts. Do you recommend live tutorials for some of that?
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Dan! Loved your interview about linkedIn that you shared out. Good stuff.
Pierre Kelly: adding music to content creatrion as long as it's roya;ty free
The Honest Accomplice: Thank you stay tuned for part 2
Pierre Kelly: royalty*
24hrboss: Good conversation BTW. I'm anew follower of Markus..and just started following MarieLou
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Dan!
Stannex: It's like a new dish ... how do you know you don't like it if you haven't tried it?
The Honest Accomplice: Hi LaLa
Mommy Guide Inc: Not? Ready Go!
Stannex: Yay, Markus and Marielou! Thank you for a GREAT show!
The Honest Accomplice: Markus accent is throwing me off. I always thought he was Canadian