Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Philip!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed it's a great day!
Mommy Guide Inc: great cinematography!
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Yeih!!! he is back 🤩
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana! You and Markus are back. Yey!!!!
Next Step of Faith: Switching to my channel account 😜 Love you Markus!
Stan!: The Return of Markus! Now THIS is how to spend a Thursday!
Mommy Guide Inc: Stan!!! Congratulations on your 2nd Year Anniversary on YT!!!
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Yes! and it feels great to see you all here.
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus!!!!!
Stan!: Thank you, Lala! Actually, I've been on YT longer than that ... but it was 2 years ago that I got SERIOUS about it.
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Congrats Stan!
Mommy Guide Inc: yes let's celebrate the 2 years of intentionality Stan! You are awesome.
Stan!: Thank you, @Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra
Stan!: About 3 months and a bit. But now you're BACK!
Stan!: Thank you, @Mommy Guide Inc
Stan!: You're looking good, Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Life happens. And we knew you will ba back!
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: I think we can all relate. Life hits you...but look at you!!! You get up and start again.
Mommy Guide Inc: Agree let's keep moving. I'll go back to walking as it was my commitment to Markus that I will walk alongside him. I really need to exercise.
Mariane Cresp: MARKUS!!! So lovely to see you!
Mommy Guide Inc: Mariane! Have you eaten breakfast?
Budgeting Momma: Hi Markus
Stan!: So much easier to advise others than to take your own good advice
Mariane Cresp: Yes Lala … I had bistek for breakfast
Mommy Guide Inc: Agree Ana. Starting is the hardest part right. That first step. You truly are awesome Markus.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Budgeting Momma.
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: I am better at telling people what to do...lol than doing it myself 😁
Stan!: Hi @Mariane Cresp ... good to see you again!
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: In the Christian world, we say that the enemy comes to steal, destroy and rob...I very much relate it to mental health. The lies can weight you down.
Mariane Cresp: STAN! So lovely to see you too!
Mommy Guide Inc: Most important Markus - you are well and you are back!
Mariane Cresp: Hi Irene Budgeting Momma
Budgeting Momma: Hey, hi Mariane
Budgeting Momma: Hi mommy guide
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Yes!!! you own me big time...I was worried lol only because I love you.
Stan!: It's so much easier when the weather is beautiful. (That's an advantage that Coach Adam has ... San Diego ALWAYS has gorgeous weather)
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Well, today is the day my friend!!!
Stan!: One step at a time ... literally
Budgeting Momma: You did a very inspirational video a while back. Maybe use it to help motivate you moving forward.
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: btw...i haven't seen him lately either, we have to check on him.
Stan!: That Markus guy was really inspirational ... you should listen to him.
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: @Budgeting Momma I think that actually really works!
Mommy Guide Inc: Stan I can see that as one of your cartoon quips.
Budgeting Momma: Yes it helps to hear some motivation
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes you absolutely still know how. it's second nature to you. I remember I'll message you to ask about tech stuff too. maybe most people don't know but Markus is quite good at tech:)
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: He is a good friend for sure!
Mommy Guide Inc: When I was in LEDA - Markus literally was there for all of us!
Budgeting Momma: We are all here to help you keep going.
Next Step of Faith: I am so glad you have returned.
Mommy Guide Inc: Let's share Markus channel friends and don't forget to LIKE this video.
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: I love your walking videos! You could make some more of those
Mommy Guide Inc: So Markus - are we back on the weekly livestreams? Maybe doing your editing, your thought process on what you're doing to keep healthy would be a great topic. I always love to see the behind the scene
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: I supposed to make a comeback today too...so what you just said...if you are helping at least one person...that is me!
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Im not quiet ready but...I have until midnight lol
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: oh man!!! you are really helpng me ha!!! Yes, I want to do a video not a live.
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Just record it!!!
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Kind of...I need time to do a thumbnail and time to edit, but after your live, I have to go prep dinner
Mommy Guide Inc: go Ana:) a video / podcast - you're so good at that.
Budgeting Momma: Moving your body is very important. If you are not able to go for a walk maybe just small exercise like stretching for 10 minutes
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: so all has to happen after dinner...but ugh, I get so tired after that...
Stan!: Markus, I have a cartoon for you ... where should I send it? Email? FB?
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: but now I feel like I have to deliver because I just told you all lol
Tech Troublemaker: Hey! It's that @Markus Schaub guy!
Tech Troublemaker: Hit that LIKE button everyone so Markus knows how much we love and miss him when he ain't here.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy!!!
Budgeting Momma: Ana what kinda of videos do you do?
Stan!: FB Messenger ... sent!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Lala!
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: oh gosh! today. I promise.
Mommy Guide Inc: awww Stan! that's awesome:)
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: oh my, @Stan! that is golden!!!!
Stan!: Pin it over your computer ... :^)
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: @Budgeting Momma I am recreating my content, mind, soul and body. I want to share my 1 year journey that has changed my life for the better.
Budgeting Momma: @ana that sounds interesting
BostonDonMTB: Hi Markus welcome back
BostonDonMTB: Hi everyone
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Don!
BostonDonMTB: Hey Roy
BostonDonMTB: I will have to watch on replay to get the scoop.
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Ana! Hey Stan! Hey @Budgeting Momma
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: I would love to!!! I am becoming so passionate about telling others...the basics to have an extraordinary life!
Tech Troublemaker: I will start walking again too.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Don! Great to see you all. Everyone is here and happy to see you back Markus.
Budgeting Momma: Hi tech troublemaker
BostonDonMTB: I have been riding a lot. I did my longest ride of the year yesterday.
Stan!: Hi @Tech Troublemaker
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Yes!!! let's all go on a walk!!!
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: You could do a challenge of making all of us record a 30 sec or a minute walk and then put it all together with the magic you know how
Stan!: 1pm my time
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: 3pm for me CST
Budgeting Momma: 3 pm central time for me
Stan!: GREAT to see you, Markus! See you next week!
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: We are so glad to see you back and that you are pulling the community back together.
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks so much Markus. Great to see you back! Thanks friends. Don't forget to hit the LIKE button on your way out:)
Budgeting Momma: Happy to see you back
Ana Zugheri - So Basic with a little Extra: Have a great rest of your day, everyone!!!