Tatiana Teaches: 💃🏻 🕺🏽
Tatiana Teaches: Get it guys!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey everyone!
MySnoopy80: Hi everyone ❤️
Colter Reed: So what do you say, @Tatiana Teaches — did we get it?
Eaglevp: Hi@Tech Troublemaker @MySnoopy80
Tatiana Teaches: You got it and you brought it! 😉
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi everyone
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Janet, Tatiana, and @Eaglevp
MySnoopy80: Hi@eaglevp
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Markus & Colter
Eaglevp: Hi @Colter Reed
Tatiana Teaches: Hi Roy 👋🏼
Colter Reed: Hi, @Eaglevp !
Eaglevp: Hello@Tatiana Teaches
Eaglevp: Hey@Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing
Tatiana Teaches: Hi 🦅 VP!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: 💃
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi back @eaglevp
MySnoopy80: Yes please!!
Motif Music Studios: Glad to be here live!
Eaglevp: Hi @Motif Music Studios
Motif Music Studios: @Eaglevp hello.
Pierre Kelly: What is up?
Adam Tinkoff: Have you tried Obsidian app?
Eaglevp: Hello Adam
Eaglevp: Hi@Ana Zugheri - Faith 52
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Love seeing so many of you here. Don’t forget to like 👍 and share!
Motif Music Studios: I feel these worries about planning vs. spontaneity.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Welcome!!!!!
Motif Music Studios: Oh, thank you for the warm welcome! Yay!
Tatiana Teaches: When we do group projects in my college courses, I always talk with my students about different work styles: pre-planners vs procrastinators, etc. 👀
Motif Music Studios: Love that confetti! Awesome!
Pierre Kelly: The Obsidian app? What's that about?
Adam Tinkoff: Obsidian app is free, and fantastic note taking tool for creating your second brain.
Adam Tinkoff: Obsidian is like Notion, but more secure and you have far more control - and it's free.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I love productivity app as but nothing like pen and paper if you ask me.
Motif Music Studios: I am also learning lots about the way the brain creates dopamine and how some that are seeking dopamine often have different workflow that is highly appealing! [not always efficient,but appealing! 😉
Tatiana Teaches: @motif music- glad you appreciate it. 🙂
Adam Tinkoff: Obsidian is built around creating "linked notes" which help you see more deeply into topics by creating connections. It's very hard to do this with paper.
Motif Music Studios: Yes, those perfectionist vibes can be hard to overcome. A great strength too. I feel like our weaknesses are often our strengths as well.
Tatiana Teaches: @Adam T: i use notion but thanks for mentioning a free alternative!
Motif Music Studios: YES to task expansion! Great point.
Motif Music Studios: I often do practice sprints that are timed.
Adam Tinkoff: There are tons of videos on YT comparing Obsidian to Notion.
MySnoopy80: Yeah because you dont loose to much time on every little detail
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: @motif yes! I love the satisfaction of crossing out something off my list.
Motif Music Studios: @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52 right? So helpful to add that focus sprint and the motivation that comes from a checklist.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Connect with Colter at Colterreed.com
Tech Troublemaker: Colter's newsletter and his shorts have fit together so well and reiterate what focus of his newsletter. Great stuff
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: You have a great voice and look like a pro on your videos!!!
Motif Music Studios: @Tech Troublemaker great to know! Just subscribed to Colter's channel as a topic of interest to me.
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Hello Everyone👍👋
Eaglevp: Hello@CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hello Ejnar so glad you are here! 😀
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes!
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: Hi @Ana - I need to be with all the great people here😀
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: That is a great idea!!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: A pick me up folder 📁
Motif Music Studios: YES to having to just start and those small actionable improvements!
Tech Troublemaker: I love Mark's videos. Colter, you need to do an elephant toothpaste video on your channel. 😛
Motif Music Studios: So many parallels to music practice in becoming a creator!
Motif Music Studios: I definitely need to hone my workflow practices!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I’m in that boat…I feel like I need to have it all together before I press that button
Motif Music Studios: @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52 I've loved that ponder of improving by 1% with each upload.
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Love that
Motif Music Studios: Such great ponders. Sleep is one I am not great at budgeting for.
Pierre Kelly: What is sleep anyway?
Tatiana Teaches: I need to start talking to Future Tatiana more often.
Tech Troublemaker: I am so good at procrastination. And when I need to do something i can easily find a distraction to pull me away.
CSLive - Communication Social Media Livestreaming: I am trying to change from live for work to work for live to give me control over my life and how to work😀
Motif Music Studios: That's such a neat idea.
Motif Music Studios: YES to reducing friction!
Pierre Kelly: Say yes to friction!
Motif Music Studios: @Pierre Kelly I suppose there are good kinds of using friction in your favour. 😉
Tatiana Teaches: Broken Brain Syndrome 😆
Pierre Kelly: It's a NASCAR race not a drag race.
Adam Tinkoff: 26.2
Adam Tinkoff: I ran 4 of them. I remember every mile. Oye!
Tatiana Teaches: Good analogy Pierre! 🏁
Sammy Super Star: Hey Colter
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Sammy Super Star
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: That is the secret sauce!
Eaglevp: Hi@Sammy Super Star
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hi Sammy
Sammy Super Star: Hey @Tech Troublemaker @Eaglevp
Eaglevp: Great show Markus