Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Janet my sister from another mother:)
Mommy Guide Inc: And here we go!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yes Lala. sisters forever! :face-red-heart-shape:
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Janet we are. Let’s turn on the “Hype” - you can all watch that YT shorts from Markus later:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: oh boy. my favorite song
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hello friends 👋
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: ANA!!! how are you?
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Hi Ana!!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Good 👍 good, glad to see y’all here!!! Makes my day!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @Ana - everytime I put on makeup I think about your segment.... so good
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed Ana - our Livestreaming Family!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: 😂😂😂😂
Mommy Guide Inc: Love that episode too!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: have fun too!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Love how Markus is always updating this video:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Markus & Chirstian!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Love love love astronomy...
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Christian. ✈🚀🛸
Mommy Guide Inc: It just gets better Christian! Now Markus has you:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: 😆 Markus alway have wonderful guests!
Mommy Guide Inc: For Christian’s amazing YT Channel - https://youtube.com/@LaunchPadAstronomy
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I'm so happy you followed your intuition.
Kali : Christian!!! #MARKUSRULES
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: there are no coincidences 😉
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: KALI!!!
Kali : @Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing JANET!!!! 🤗❤️
Mommy Guide Inc: I think that everyone at one point in time wanted to be an astronaut right? Space and space exploration - something that’s always very interesting
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey!!! Hi @Kali
Kali : @Mommy Guide Inc hey lala!!!! 🤗❤️ happy to see you here!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Markus’ livestreams is part of my weekly schedule:) it’s like a family reunion weekly.:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @Mommy Guide Inc I feel the same Lala
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: So true!!! I’m stuck and the only way to get unstuck is do it
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52 so true
Mommy Guide Inc: Christian + Astronomy and his guests as well equals an amazing learning experience. I bring along my kids to watch as well. Continuous learning in a fun interactive way:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for watching don’t forget to smash the Like button:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Lol
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I know!!! I can’t wait to one day get an ugly comment so I ca celebrate 🎉
Mommy Guide Inc: Bring it On! Turn it into a positive - 😍
Kali : i can't tell if you're talking about my mom or outerspace (jk)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Love it!
Kali : i feel like flat earthers are just trying to rebel. little do they know, it's the truth of chaotic space that's rebellious 🔥
Kali : @Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing hahaha she's a space case 😛 just kidding
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Back in the day we were called "space cadets" or dumb blondes. ahhaha
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I knew I liked your mom. ;-)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I know that in the religious world 🌎 has been against science, but I strongly believe that is wonderful and it actually supports facts about God’s creation.
Kali : @Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing 😂😂
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @Kali :eyes-pink-heart-shape:😝
Mommy Guide Inc: Amen to that @Ana
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: the launch was so exciting
Adam Tinkoff: Good morning kids.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Adam
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Hi Adam:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: wow! very exciting
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Wow!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: 100k subs in 6-8months! Awesome:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Preparation - continuous learning by creating content. Love it!
Adam Tinkoff: I believe most people are curious about the great mystery that surrounds us. Astronomers like Christian help to shine light on what we know, and discovering, and what might actually be...
Mommy Guide Inc: Agree Adam:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yep!
Adam Tinkoff: Also I appreciate the "intellectually gentle" way he approaches these incredibly complex topics...
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Yes, a very very good teacher... able to talk and teach all levels without talking down to anyone. very challenging to do that. Teaching is not easy.
Cheryl Wolf: Hello
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Cheryl
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Cheryl @Cherylwolf:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for sharing that Christian. Most of the time - patience is also key to content creation. Just keep at it:)
Cheryl Wolf: His classes fill up quick
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Are you at Towson State? Your courses would be amazing. I took astronomy in the very early 70's. Light years ago!
Adam Tinkoff: Also there will be new ideas and topics that will happen
Adam Tinkoff: Right now it seems AI is the big thing... but that too shall pass.
Cheryl Wolf: Hey everyone Dont forget give this video a thumbs 👍
Adam Tinkoff: I'm all thumbs
Cheryl Wolf: Lol @adam
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: haha @Adam. Stuck in his thumb and pulled out a plum
Paul Burke: Smart Christian...handing it off to someone else to free yourself
Paul Burke: Q - where did you find the editor? Fiverr?
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Hi Paul!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Paul!
Paul Burke: hey @Mommy Guide Inc and @Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing ...I've been lurking 😂
Cheryl Wolf: Paul the lurker 🤣
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @Paul Burke I know your type~!!!!
Paul Burke: oh cool! I hope it helps
Mommy Guide Inc: I think that is going to be next for me us well. I dont think i can really delegate the editing of the videos to someone else.:) i can only do shorts fast. Long form editing is something else.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Big time about the edit. on so many levels...
Paul Burke: thats really cool you can use @name in the title of the show and it links over to the LaunchPad channel
Cheryl Wolf: Jupiter, the planet of energy
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: this is so exciting
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Oh wow. that would be YES
Mommy Guide Inc: That’s awesome Christian.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: https://youtube.com/@LaunchPadAstronomy
Mommy Guide Inc: Don’t forget to smash the LIKE button as well for this awesome livestream:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Thanks Christian & Markus. I love this topic.