Eaglevp: Hello Roy
Mommy Guide Inc: I do Keith.:) after awhile it became like second nature.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy!:)
Stannex: Yay! I'm here for the intro!!!
Eaglevp: So are you doing a live everyday in August...Lala
Eaglevp: Hi Stan
Mommy Guide Inc: I love how Markus has a ton of versions of "Live That Streaming Life".
Pierre Kelly: afternoon everyone
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Stan! Goshi miss Random Encounters.
Eaglevp: Hi Pierre
Mommy Guide Inc: I think I will Keith.:) And can you be there as a guest?:)
Stannex: Hi, Keith! Hi, Lala! And, of course... Hi, Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Pierre:)
Eaglevp: Yes would love that Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Congratulations Markus for the start of your Monday creator video upload:) Keep 'em coming:)
Eaglevp: Yes Markus keep up the Monday video's
Eaglevp: It's finding a topic that people are really interested in,I did one on loneliness and have had 721 views
Eaglevp: I watched a video that got over 60000 views talking about how hobbies help with your mental well being
Eaglevp: Thanks Markus
Stannex: Tough week for me ... multiple deadlines and travel next week ... so I'm mostly just listening as I do some drawing.
Mommy Guide Inc: Keith indeed when the topic resonates with people and very honest and raw
Eaglevp: Agree Lala
Stannex: "Better deadlines than death." ... I'm going to put that on the wall over my desk.
Mommy Guide Inc: Stan I think that's a great "problem" - lot of work. Safe travels my friend:)
Mommy Guide Inc: so true Markus - too much of anything - even the good thing can be a cause of stress.
Stannex: That was my first time seeing the Northern Lights ... and it was mostly through my phone's screen.
Mommy Guide Inc: I would love to see the Northern lights:) I was surprised that some parts of the US had been able to witness it as well.
Mommy Guide Inc: The "tipping point" so to speak to achieve that "viral" video is so hard.
Mommy Guide Inc: so keeping the mindset that I've done it - and I move on.
Mommy Guide Inc: indeed but I just really want to experience a "viral" video - even for once. not for anything else - just a bucket list. he he he.
CSLiveDK : Hello everyone 😀
Eaglevp: It's on my bucket list just one viral video
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ejnar:)
Run Adam Run: Good day everyone! Love from San Diego!
Eaglevp: Hi Ejnar
Eaglevp: Hi Run Adam Run
Stannex: I think you're right that it's KEY to know WHY you're doing this. That way you can hopefully avoid chasing "viral" or "view count" for no reason.
Run Adam Run: I'm running over the Coronado Bridge this weekend!
Mommy Guide Inc: I have a great feeling that it's very near Keith!
Stannex: Hi, Adam!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Coach Adam - Congratulations!!!!
CSLiveDK : Hi Keith and Lala😀
Eaglevp: I do hope so for you Lala
Run Adam Run: (I'm not in it for the money)
Run Adam Run: We can all say we knew Markus before he became the next Taylor.
Mommy Guide Inc: So true Adam:)
CSLiveDK : It’s going fine here. Try to get paying costumers in my business. Live every day in April went fine, but the view numbers varies a lot. I made it in Danish and tried to run through my first LEDA. 😀
Run Adam Run: Yes, if you are recognized by one name only, you are too famous.
Mommy Guide Inc: I would never have thought in my wildest dream that I would become a content creator. But I am enjoying the journey thus far. specially the awesome people I meet and now I can call "my friend".
Eaglevp: Your famous already Markus in this community
Run Adam Run: Is there much of a streaming community in German?
CSLiveDK : That’s the problem with the language. I need to think of getting clients here and this must be in Danish. I try to make videos and courses in Danish about zoom and Ecamm. Not much is existing in Danis
Mommy Guide Inc: the excitement of learning new things even at this age is very exciting. keeps my mind off from all the "growing old" pains.
Mommy Guide Inc: that's a great idea Ejnar. Bridging the disconnect. Good luck my friend.
Mommy Guide Inc: when I wake up with no pain is a good day:)
Stannex: It's fun to be a "rock star" on a small scale. There was a while that inside a game convention I was recognized everywhere, but once I stepped back onto the streets I was just an unknown guy.
Mommy Guide Inc: yes 50 is "golden" and is very much celebrated here as well.:)
Stannex: Adam is definitely a BIG inspiration!
Mommy Guide Inc: love that Stan!
CSLiveDK : Except for some pain in my legs I try to not let age come in the way. It’s just a number but it makes so many limits that shouldn’t be accepted. I am 60 now😀🤔
Mommy Guide Inc: Friends thanks for being here and sharing your thoughts:) Please don't forget to hit the LIKE button:)
Mommy Guide Inc: I am ok with being older it's the aches and pains that goes along with it that is kinda limiting for me. I want to do so many things but reality hits and I realise I am not 20 anymore. he he he.
Mommy Guide Inc: ooh Markus YT actually suggested one of your old shorts to me this week! I was so excited.
Stannex: A lot of people like to "lurk" and listen to the conversation ... and that is fine whether it's live or replay.
Run Adam Run: So is shower.
Mommy Guide Inc: So true Stan. Congratulations also Stan on the D&D segment. It has picked up quite a following:) often times I am there watching but driving so couldn't comment.
Run Adam Run: Douche = Shower
Mommy Guide Inc: Hello friends! Would love to hear from you in the future! And if you're liking the engagement here maybe you want more and consider subscribing as well:)
Stannex: Thank you, Lala. :^)
Run Adam Run: Stan has massive talent. I have one of his illustrations proudly on my credenza.
Pierre Kelly: Thanks @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: so true Adam. I have one of my wall in my Craft Hub of Stan's work. He created my wall canvass for the reopening of my craft hub. Thanks Stan!
Run Adam Run: It's like a bookshelf
Mommy Guide Inc: I had to google it Adam:) he he he
Run Adam Run: It means "expensive"
Stannex: Just like you encourage people to stream for fun, I encourage people to draw just for fun!
Mommy Guide Inc: I am thinking of doing a "challenge" type of segment something like - are you smarter than a 5th grader or who wore it better kinda thing but on crafts. what you think friends?
Run Adam Run: You could ask people on the street what they think obscure crafting tools are used for
Mommy Guide Inc: aww thanks Markus and Adam. Yes please help me by giving me suggestions:) sometimes I just want to mix things up a bit:)
Run Adam Run: Breakfast with Markus video
Mommy Guide Inc: Friends don't forget to give Markus a "LIKE" on this livestream on our way out:)
Stannex: Thanks for another great hour, Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: And excited for the video this Monday;)
Run Adam Run: Great show as always. Fun hanging out with you.