Mommy Guide Inc: Awww big virtual hugs my friend.
Mommy Guide Inc: Gosh the good old times. Wish we xojld have an awesome
Mommy Guide Inc: Reunion in the future:)
Craft By Jay: hi la la
Craft By Jay: happy 4 am lol
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey!!! Hi Jay! You made it! Thanks for dropping by my friend./)
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed awesome to be awake before the rooster.:) he he he
Eaglevp: Hi@Craft By Jay
Craft By Jay: hello
Mommy Guide Inc: And we have Markus!
Neil Farrimond: Hey Markus
Eaglevp: Evening Neil
Craft By Jay: hello markus
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Neil!
Craft By Jay: yes la la invited me
Neil Farrimond: Hi @Eaglevp & @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes let’s welcome Jay@CraftByJay.:) He is one of my “techiest” crafter friend.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: What editing platform are you using Markus?
CSLiveDK : Hello everyone 😀
Eaglevp: Hi Ejnar
CSLiveDK : Hi Keith👋
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ejnar congratulations for your LEDA and the milestones you achieved.:) celebrating with you:)
Ellie Calhoun: Hello every body!!
Eaglevp: Hello Ellie
Mommy Guide Inc: Ellie yey!!!
CSLiveDK : Thanks Lala. Yes I did again. 31 days in a row😀 LEDA lives on
Ellie Calhoun: What is this magic?!?! invisible selfie stick?
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: do you think its a must to put on transitions for every cut? When do you need to do so?
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed congratulations again Ejnar:)
CSLiveDK : ♥️
Ellie Calhoun: Good question Lala!
Mommy Guide Inc: Ellie i think its the Insta 350
Mommy Guide Inc: Insta 360
Ellie Calhoun: That's cool! Seems like a drone shot
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus and his awesome gear.:) love seeing the gears in action.
Ellie Calhoun: Lala, I put transitions in when it's sort of a topic change.
Craft By Jay: it's a neat camera
Mommy Guide Inc: So Ellie only when there is a topic change. Thanks. I’ll take that advice.:)
Ellie Calhoun: I also watch the final result and if it seems like too many I take some out. Too many can be annoying I think
Mommy Guide Inc: I love the DJI Osmo pocket too but mine is the older sister the Osmo Pocket 2. But love it still. That’s what i used Jay in filming my latest craft room tour
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Ellie i kinda felt the same way when i did like so many. I felt - Lala too much!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Friends don’t forget to hit the LIKE button.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: how do you do split
Mommy Guide Inc: Split screen Markus?
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: how to blur faces and backgrounds? Depends
Mommy Guide Inc: Depends on editing platform?
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh DaVinci Resolve. Q: Is it easy to use? Can a nontech savy person navigate Da Vinci Resolve?
Budgeting Momma: Hi Markus
Budgeting Momma: What do you to edit?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @BudgetingMomma:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for the answers Mwrkus:)
itdair.network: Hi Markus and everyone! This is a great live and skills on video editing! 🏆
Budgeting Momma: What program are using to edit?
Tech Troublemaker: Wait how do we join you "editing"?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy@TechTroublemaker.:)
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Lala @Mommy Guide Inc Happy Friday!
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus saying - he is enjoying editing.:) i should adopt that mindset:)
Budgeting Momma: That cool… love it.
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh Roy you are right it is indeed Friyay here already:)
Tech Troublemaker: If you force yourself to do it enough you will learn to love it. Once you learn how to do cool stuff then it gets fun.
Eaglevp: Hi Roy
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Keith!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Roy looking forward to that day. The day i say - I love editing:) he he he
Tech Troublemaker: I have been using inShot on my iPhone. I am starting to like it. It does captions and you only pay for it once. I have CapCut Pro but I hope to get rid of it after this year to save money.
Ellie Calhoun: Gotta run! Nice seeing you all!
Eaglevp: By Ellie have a nice weekend
Mommy Guide Inc: Nice plan Roy. We have way too many subscriptions right? He he he
Mommy Guide Inc: Bye Ellie:)
itdair.network: Q: Which storage you use, NAS (Network Storage Storage) or Portable SSD (Solid State Drive) for video backup after video editing?
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: do you do voiceovers or audio is always the one during filming?
itdair.network: Thank you Markus, you doing an awesome work!
Tech Troublemaker: I suggest occasional Lcuts and Jcuts
Tech Troublemaker: Just to add some change ups .. around
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes thank you Markus and friends for the suggestions.:) great to be able to just ask away and not be judged.:)
Tech Troublemaker: In a J cut, the next scene's audio plays before the image changes. With L cuts, the audio from the
Tech Troublemaker: preceding scene carries over, and then the visuals shift
Mommy Guide Inc: J cut and L cuts need to learn that Roy.
itdair.network: Hi Roy @Tech Troublemaker and Lala @Mommy Guide Inc, good to see you both. 🙂🙏🏼
Mommy Guide Inc: Video every Monday. Nice:) will rake that challenge - video every weekend for me.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Markus! Thanks friends:)