Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Keith!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello friends!
Mommy Guide Inc: And the thumbnail is now alive - he he he
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Look at that nice merch!!!
Eaglevp: Hi@Ana Zugheri - Faith52
Political Commentator Horace Podmore: Watch yah Keith
Eaglevp: Evening Horace
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ana and Horace:)
Political Commentator Horace Podmore: Hi Mommy
Ellie Calhoun: Hi everyone 👋
Mommy Guide Inc: Best dance goes to Colter for real!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ellie!
Tech Troublemaker: And one time at Creator Camp...
Eaglevp: Hi Roy
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy! Friends don't forget to smash the LIKE button:)
Pierre Kelly: Afternoon all
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Keith!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Pierre!
Mommy Guide Inc: Perfect a hoodie for winter time.
Mariane Cresp: Looks good Markus!
Ellie Calhoun: Looks great!
Tech Troublemaker: Smashed it first. Nah nah nah nah nah!
Eaglevp: Hello@Mariane Cresp
Mariane Cresp: Hello Keith and everyone!
Eaglevp: Hi@Pierre Kelly
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Mariane:)
Mariane Cresp: Hi Lala!
Mariane Cresp: Do you have to pay for the sample?
Mommy Guide Inc: oh wow that was a mousepad? cool! and It arrived in less than a week? that' fast.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I missed the stream last week but man that was fast!!! Look at you!!! Love it!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: What is the site you are using to set your store?
Tech Troublemaker: Samples are reasonably priced.
Tech Troublemaker: fourthwall for the win
Motif Music Studios: Oh fun! Can't wait to see the samples!
Eaglevp: Hello@Motif Music Studios
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Amy!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Got it!!!
Motif Music Studios: Oh that's so fun! You've got me inspired!
Motif Music Studios: Way to be taking action so fast in the new year!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: do you have to pay any fees to create your store?
Motif Music Studios: @Eaglevp glad to spot you here too!
Mommy Guide Inc: I don't think so Ana. setting up your shop is free:)
Pierre Kelly: That mousepad looks cool
Ellie Calhoun: That's great! Love the mouse pad!
Mommy Guide Inc: ooh that's a cool checklist!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: you are doing an amazing job friend!!
Tech Troublemaker: Love my fourthwall shop.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I love that!!
Ellie Calhoun: I like that you can have a membership!
Mommy Guide Inc: oooh memberships thru the shop?
Tech Troublemaker: I did memberships on buymeacoffee. I didn't know I could do them on fourthwall.
Tech Troublemaker: :goat-turquoise-white-horns:I joined!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Roy beat me to being first member! member now too!
Tech Troublemaker: I already bought a hoodie, so you can send me a checklist mousepad
Kali : MERCH?!?!?!
Tech Troublemaker: Chat ate my chat, very strange
Mommy Guide Inc: just a mousepad Markus! the Not? one
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Kali!!! Yes Markus have Merch and also a membership!
Kali : woah!!!
Eaglevp: Hi@Kali
Kali : @Mommy Guide Inc hey lala!! omg this is amazing!!!
Kali : @Eaglevp hey!!
Mommy Guide Inc: It is!
Kali : crap!
SuzanCz: hey there! Long time no see. What did I miss?
Kali : that is such a cool idea for a mousepad
Kali : hey!! @SuzanCz
Mommy Guide Inc: Roy is so fast - it took me awhile to find my bag and get my credit card. he he he.
Eaglevp: Hello@SuzanCz
Ellie Calhoun: I joined as a member!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Suzan:)
SuzanCz: Hi @Kali and @Eaglevp
SuzanCz: Hi @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: yey welcome Ellie to Markus' membership. Membership is three Markus' Merch shop - https://markusschaub.shop/
Tech Troublemaker: I am still trying to find myself.
Kali : @Tech Troublemaker isn't that what life is about 🧘‍♀️
Mommy Guide Inc: ooh there was a flickering for awhile - that was the prompter?
Kali : that seemed like a capture card thing?
SuzanCz: Alright... this is embarrasing to ask -- but can someone explain the "not?"?
SuzanCz: Oh! you have a lot more than just the 4 items on your website!
SuzanCz: Hi @Ellie Calhoun!
Ellie Calhoun: I want the mousepad
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Suzan!
SuzanCz: Beautiful sweatshirt!
Kali : Q who are you going through for your merch?
Fishstick ~ Phillip: SusanCz has a new video. Liked!
SuzanCz: Thank you, @Fishstick ~ Phillip! ❤
Eaglevp: Hi@Fishstick ~ Phillip
Mommy Guide Inc: shipping was free! but I don't remember putting in my address - toink!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: my cc got compromised two days ago but as soon as I get my new one I will get myself some merch!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Philip! Thanks for the reminder:)
SuzanCz: Maybe you can set it up so when people become members, it triggers an automation while you're live? That would be cool!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: that could be your trade mark, not a mistake but different, maybe
Mommy Guide Inc: oh my Ana. hope that didn't create a big issue and that you get the replacement soon.
Adam Tinkoff: Hey there everyone! Love the hoodie!
Eaglevp: Hello Adam
Tech Troublemaker: Yah @SuzanCz
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Coach Adam! Loving loving your videos.
Ellie Calhoun: Not Ready Go!!
SuzanCz: Hi @Tech Troublemaker !!
Mommy Guide Inc: This is Coach SuzanCz's latest video link: https://youtu.be/iwCYIXbpOQM?si=3zcjc_l1KwaIytxE
Motif Music Studios: I gotta run, but nice to hang out!
SuzanCz: @Ellie Calhoun Oooohhhh.... "Not ready? Go!" So there shouldn't be a ? after "not"?
Mommy Guide Inc: thanks Amy@Motif Music Studios. Have a great rest of the day)
SuzanCz: Thank you so much @Mommy Guide Inc for sharing it! Love how supportive this community is!
Ellie Calhoun: I didn't notice a place to put an address.
Tech Troublemaker: the slogan is a little passive aggressive, tough love. Sometimes as creators that is what we need.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I have to run but love seeing ya'll here. Let the fun continue!! Love you friends.
Tech Troublemaker: Bye Amie!
SuzanCz: I just bought it!
SuzanCz: " bought"
Pierre Kelly: @SuzanCz get back to reviving it!
Mommy Guide Inc: ooh I thought I missed it
SuzanCz: @Pierre Kelly That is the plan! This week's video is step 1. Already editing the next video. 😀
SuzanCz: @Markus Schaub : Should it be "Not ready? Go!"
SuzanCz: I'm wondeering if the "?" is in the right place...?
SuzanCz: Absolutely a member! This is exciting!
SuzanCz: Oh - whoops. Just saw the time. I'm out. See you all again soon!
Mommy Guide Inc: Coach SuzanC I think it's intentional:) to make it kinda different and more cool:)
SuzanCz: It's confusing! Sorry.
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Coach SuzanC - have a great rest of the day:)
Ellie Calhoun: No! I like the ? Being in a strange place. It's a conversation starter!
Mommy Guide Inc: yes digital products - yes!
Pierre Kelly: How did you test out the products?
Mommy Guide Inc: that's great that your merch and membership is in one link - makes it easier:)
Pierre Kelly: Also, Awesome Fun Things has a membership program too
Adam El Gringo: (you have a new member)
Mommy Guide Inc: yey!!! Welcome coach Adam to Markus' membership:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: For next episode Markus can we do Gleam.io?
Adam El Gringo: That's my second account - I'm heading to Mexico next week
Adam El Gringo: On Saturday to Mexico City
Mommy Guide Inc: I plan to use it for my upcoming event but not sure how to set it up. he he he
Mommy Guide Inc: oooh @Adam El Gringo - love that. Bring us along? he he he
Adam El Gringo: Yes, I'll be posting my Mexico videos on my second account "Adam El Gringo"
Mommy Guide Inc: thanks Markus!
Adam El Gringo: I don't want to mix Tacos and Mindset... but that's not a bad idea.
Mommy Guide Inc: so Adam El Gringo will be Coach Adam's second account for travel vlogs, etc.
Adam El Gringo: Yes, Adam El Gringo is my alterego. 🙂
Mommy Guide Inc: check out Coach Adam's 2nd channel here : https://www.youtube.com/@adamelgringo5774
Ellie Calhoun: Great show Markus! Great Merch!!! 💕🎉✨
Mommy Guide Inc: I agree. Another awesome show.