Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Keith!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi everyone!!!
Eaglevp: Hi Lala
Eaglevp: Markus certainly got the moves
Mommy Guide Inc: This is a really interesting topic
Mommy Guide Inc: Let’s Go!
Eaglevp: I'M READY
Mariane Cresp: Hello all!
Eaglevp: Hi@Mariane Cresp
Eaglevp: Welcome everyone to Markus's live stream
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Mariane!
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hello Everyone😀😀👏
Eaglevp: Hi Ejnar
Mommy Guide Inc: And we have Ejnar!
Tim Heale 9: Boom one and all
Eaglevp: Boom Tim is in the room
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hej Keith😀
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hi Lala😀
Eaglevp: Hello Anne
Mommy Guide Inc: And we have Tim!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi everyone
Eaglevp: Hey@Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing
David W. Ryan: Hi Markus and Anne
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow! What a great and inspiring story Anne.:) hi - Anne
Eaglevp: Hello@David W. Ryan
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Janet and David in the house:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: That is amazing you list so much and keeping it off
Mommy Guide Inc: Health is wealth indeed
Eaglevp: What's your secret AAnne?
Eaglevp: What's your secret Anne ?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Lala!!!
Ellie Calhoun: Hello!!!
Eaglevp: Hello Ellie
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ellie was just watching your FB post today on movement
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: how did you keep the weight at bay Anne?
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Keith, hi Janet! Thanks for watching my post!
Ellie Calhoun: Wow! 4 million
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Beautiful you serve your lovely community. You are a beautiful shining light
Mariane Cresp: Yes, the vanity metrics can get in our minds and affect our self-esteem
Ellie Calhoun: Lala! Thanks for watching my video, I appreciate you 💜
Rich Vybz: great explanation
Eaglevp: Hi@Rich Vybz
Mommy Guide Inc: What a great mission and why
Rich Vybz: hey eaglevp
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hi 👋 happy to jump in
Mommy Guide Inc: For more of Anne’s content visit her channel and consider supporting her by subscribing to her channel @YourDietAngel https://youtube.com/@Yourdietangel
Ellie Calhoun: Accidental weight loss! That's the way to go!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Rich and Ana:)
Eaglevp: Hi@Ana Zugheri - Faith52
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I wish I suffer that kind of accident
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hello @Eaglevp glad to “see” you here.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes! We need help taking care of our health
Ellie Calhoun: So what is that missing link?
Mommy Guide Inc: The photos say it all - very inspiring! Q: How long did it take to reach your ideal weight and health goals achieved Anne?
Sylvie Grohne: Hello from Germany 🙂
Eaglevp: Hello@Sylvie Grohne
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Everyone! Busy day. I missed the beginning.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Look at you Markus!!! That was a very timely overlay 👏👏👏👏👏
Eaglevp: Hi@Tech Troublemaker
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Eaglevp
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey hi @Sylvie and Roy!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hi Roy
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Lala!!!! Hey Ana!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for being here Sylvie in Markus’ channel.
Mommy Guide Inc: Pls don’t forget to smash that Like button if you’re finding value in Markus livestream today.:)
Ellie Calhoun: It's an old perspective. I have a client who says she's had to RE-learn how to walk as a thinner person.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I believe is not just a physical but also a mental thing
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: *not just
Mommy Guide Inc: There you go Ana .
Mommy Guide Inc: Absolutely agree about keeping the weight at bay as well is a mind set first and foremost
Eaglevp: Hi Stan
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hi Stan!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Stammex
Mommy Guide Inc: “Stannex
Paul Burke: 425 pounds? wow...thats amazing. Great work!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Paul!
Eaglevp: Hi Paul
Tim Heale 9: That's almost 200kg amazing
Paul Burke: 🙂
Paul Burke: hey @Mommy Guide Inc ! and @Eaglevp
Mommy Guide Inc: Recipes! That absolutely is something I want to have a hold of. Healthy satisfying recipes
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I second that
Mommy Guide Inc: Sharing is caring.:) Glad that you decided to share your journey and inspire others to take the challenge
Stannex: Everyone's metabolism is different.
Mommy Guide Inc: Q: what kept you going when the going got tough Anne? I am sure there were days you probably felt it was hard
Tim Heale 9: TTFN Tar tar for now 😻
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks 14 awesome people in the chat. Pls don’t forget to smash that LIKE button and consider subscribing to Markus’ awesome channel
Eaglevp: Great stream
Stannex: Thank you! It was a great conversation!
Eaglevp: TTFN