Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Markus!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Advance Happy Birthday my friend:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Audio Markus is very low
Stan!: Hello, hello!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Stan!
Stan!: Mic isn't working
Fishstick USA: Hello Markus
Stan!: Hi, @Mommy Guide Inc ... shouldn't you be sleeping?
Fishstick USA: Sound is very low
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Philip!
Stan!: It's "Tech Difficulties ... the Musical"
Stan!: Yes! The mic is working!
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh i thought it was just me. Yes!!! Loud and clear Markus!
Fishstick USA: Sound fine now.
Stan!: Five to Fifty! Woo hoo!
Stan!: Next week I'll have to bring a cake
Mommy Guide Inc: That’s awesome! Surprise birthday travel:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Ok Stan ill bring the balloons and ice cream.:)
Stan!: You're already DOING my tips: Don't sweat it. LOL
Fishstick USA: I like quiet events. Small and simple.
Stan!: What have you been doing for fun lately, Markus?
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed as i grow older i like things smaller and simpler indeed:)
Tech Troublemaker: Woot! Happy PreBirthday or Post Birthday which every way that goes.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy!
Stan!: Yeah! The little things! That's the stuff that makes life great.
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Lala!
Mommy Guide Inc: Its a whole month celebration!
Fishstick USA: What is your choice for a birthday meal and dessert?
Mommy Guide Inc: In the Philippines one has to have pancit or spaghetti as it signifies long life.:)
Fishstick USA: Will you buy yourself a present? Maybe something electronic?
Mommy Guide Inc: This is it Pancit!
Enda Trading: Hello from the green island
Mommy Guide Inc: Lol Philip:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Enda:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Enda i had to Google that. Ooh Australia!!!!
CSLiveDK : Hi Markus. Freulichen geburtstag in 5 tagen. Es wunderschön👍👏🥂
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ejnar;)
Mommy Guide Inc: Its 3 hours ahead of me.:)
Enda Trading: Hi @Mommy Guide Inc its Ireland, Australia is yellow haha,
Fishstick USA: Are you planning any vacations for the Summer?
Tech Troublemaker: It is 4:19pm on Thursday here
CSLiveDK : Hi Lala😀👋
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh google had it wrong then. Lol
BostonDonMTB: Howdy Markus and everyone
Tech Troublemaker: Such a global audience. I work from home. Still at work.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Don! Since its Matkus almost birthday any fun memory you have of Markus?
CSLiveDK : We are in the same time zone, Markus😀
BostonDonMTB: All well in your part of the world?
BostonDonMTB: Hey Lala @Mommy Guide Inc
Mommy Guide Inc: Markus being always present for all out livestreams! How he did it he taught me eventually. Genius!
Stan!: 1:20p Thu here
Enda Trading: Maybe next year I will visit switzerland in the summer
Mommy Guide Inc: 4:22AM here.:)
Enda Trading: 9:22 pm
Mommy Guide Inc: Thats awesome Enda and may r drop by Philippines the next time ur back in Asia Enda?:)
Enda Trading: Maybe, i should
Stan!: Lala was just streaming a couple of ours ago ... I'm not sure she's even gone to bed yet!
Enda Trading: Ill be in Hanoi soon
Mommy Guide Inc: Lol Stan! Busted.:) but truly i got to sleep a bit. Markus ive been skipping so many of my own lives. So today was my first after almost 2 weeks.
Stan!: What is your secret @Mommy Guide Inc ?
CSLiveDK : Ellie Just visited Copenhagen. Saw it on Facebook. Only one hour drive from here😀
Mommy Guide Inc: Stan ok its just a secret between us 2 - alarm clock. Lol:)
Enda Trading: You coould split up the trip fly half way get off for a day or 2 and continue, many people do for long flights, even doha and dubai have hotels in/beside airport
Tech Troublemaker: Hey, I think I should do a 24 hour stream on September 1st. Then I should ask all of you to pop in during your timezones to visit for a bit. 😛
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yes Ellie met with Cheryl. It was so much fun to see both of them together
Tech Troublemaker: I am not going to Creator Camp this year. I am going to take a 6 week improv class instead.
BostonDonMTB: @Markus Schaub have you ben doing your walking? The weather here has been weird. Lots of consecutive rainy days. So the trails have been super wet. I am struggling lately after I did my longest ride.
Mommy Guide Inc: Sure Roy! Will there be 2 of Roy? How will you sleep? He he he
Mommy Guide Inc: Thats awesome Don. Stay safe though friend.
BostonDonMTB: Doing a 5 minute open mic night back in 1986 was the hardest thing I have ever done.
Mommy Guide Inc: I did go live today with no plan. Just craft and chill.
CSLiveDK : The longest travel I have had was 12 hours and 15 minutes in the air from Madrid to Lima in Peru. 😀 Next longest was from Lisboa to Recife in Brazil. A little more than 8 hours in air. 😀
BostonDonMTB: If the trails are wet they don't want you to use them. It puts grooves in the dirt on the trails.
Mommy Guide Inc: Took heed of everyone’s advice and just went live - surprisingly i did 5 cards from scratch with no plans and no liquid glue. Lol
BostonDonMTB: So Improv would certainly help.
Stan!: It was a FUN stream, @Mommy Guide Inc ... improv crafting!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes borrowed Stan’s concept - improv cartooning to improv crafting.:)
Stan!: That's what my whole Thursday night stream is ... improv cartooning
Enda Trading: I flew from New York over Europe to Perth, Australia it took 24hr, 10+ years ago. Not recommended :)
BostonDonMTB: Well I thought you could just spontaneous with humor like I thought Robin William did. When I worked for a comedian Bob Marley I found that they practiced very hard for their bits. Like to try again
Mommy Guide Inc: Whcih reminds me of Paul Burke. I attended his improv classes online during the pandemic
Stan!: Markus, you've done "improv video making" and "improv scheduling" on your past livestreams.
Mommy Guide Inc: Since i had no prep - everything was missing. And my scenes were all a jumble. Lol
elle naturally: Hi all sorry for being late, was in another live session
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Elle.:)
elle naturally: Hello hello
elle naturally: This is THE ONE
Mommy Guide Inc: Lets sing Happy Birthday Markus! Happy Birthday Markus! happy Birthday Happy Birthday - Happy Birthday - Markus!!!! To the tune of Happy Birthday:)
Fishstick USA: What healthy drink are you drinking?
BostonDonMTB: I am still riding at least twice a week. I need to get back up to three days, but increase my miles. I did a group ride the other night, and one last week that started with a big climb.
Mommy Guide Inc: I sang it in my hope i wish i was soprano voice.:)
BostonDonMTB: My energy got blown out, and I had to drop myself from the ride.
BostonDonMTB: Could you try a different time of day to do it?
BostonDonMTB: @Mommy Guide Inc Are you still doing your walks?
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow Don. How awesome would it be to actually see you do those awesome stuff.
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Don i do with my son. I have to to keep the bulge a bit at bay. He he he and exercise:)
BostonDonMTB: Or a morning walk?
BostonDonMTB: I do my rides around this time of day, but it might be better to do it earlier since it is getting hotter.
BostonDonMTB: 4 or 5pm here.
Mommy Guide Inc: Thats a great plan Don early morning or later in the day. Stay safe.
Mommy Guide Inc: Please dont forget to hit the LIKE button friends:)
Stan!: Woo hoo!
Stan!: Whatever you do ... ENJOY it!
Fishstick USA: Enjoyed the conversation
Mommy Guide Inc: What is Moni’s awesome surprise?