Stannex: Ready for Markus to lay some truth on us!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Welcome Stanexx! Lala!!! Hello friends.
Stannex: Groooooovy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Stan!
Stannex: Hi, Ana! Hi, Lala!
Mommy Guide Inc: Never get tired of watching this video.;)
Eaglevp: Evening Markus
Mariane Cresp: Good morning all!
Eaglevp: Hi Lala
Stannex: Hi, Mariane!
Eaglevp: Hi Stan
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Keith and Mariane!
Eaglevp: Hello @Mariane Cresp
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I love this song so much!!!!!!
Eaglevp: Hello@Ana Zugheri - Faith52
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks friends for coming. Don’t forget to smash the Likr button.
Horace Podmore: Evening Markus, hi all
Stannex: Hi, Eagle!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Hi @Eaglevp
Mariane Cresp: Hello Lala and Keith!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @Horace;)
Fishstick USA: Hello
Eaglevp: Hi@Horace Podmore
Eaglevp: Hi@Fishstick USA
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Philip!
Ellie Calhoun: Hey Markus!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Ellie!
Eaglevp: Hey Ellie
Tim Heale 9: BOOM I'm in the Live 😂
Eaglevp: Boom Tim is in the room
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey Hi Tim!
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Lala and Keith and everyone!
Tim Heale 9: Brexit
Tim Heale 9: The EU?
Ellie Calhoun: Talk about your biggest revelation when you first went through Leda
Tim Heale 9: How about the equipment you use to go live?
Ellie Calhoun: Or how you made the transition from going live in Leda to going live in YouTube
Mariane Cresp: think of a struggle you have with content creation. one specific pain point
MySnoopy80: Hi everyone
Tim Heale 9: Hi Lala
Stannex: How about, "How to get out of your own way and just MAKE a video" ... it'll be very meta!
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh Descript Markus I really need to restart using that
Fishstick USA: Q: What do you like? I think you like helping elder YouTubers participate in a livecast. Maybe create a profile
Ellie Calhoun: Taking 60 minutes won't be easy! You certainly are challenging yourself
Mariane Cresp: how to find a topic to make a youtube video
Stannex: "Five things I didn't know before I started on YouTube"
Ellie Calhoun: @Mariane 😂
Mommy Guide Inc: How To Set Up a Livestream
Ellie Calhoun: 5 things you learned going live 30 days in a row.
Mariane Cresp: 3-5 benefits of doing livestream
Mary Speegle: great topic
Stannex: "accidentally"
Mommy Guide Inc: Title: The Accidental Livestreamet
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Love the title!
Spooling Around: Hi all!
Tim Heale 9: Have you tried the AI feature in Canva?
Mariane Cresp: thumbnail picture ... person who trips ... and bumps into text livestream
Spooling Around: It’s David Rya
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Look at the crowd...that is all of us. I like where this is going.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi David @SpoolingAround
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I just saw the AI feature today, can't wait to try it.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: You should be on the stage!
Cheryl Wolf: Hey All !! Sorry I am late
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Make yourself bigger
Spooling Around: …Ryan
Eaglevp: Hi Cheryl
Cheryl Wolf: Hi Keith
Eaglevp: Hey@Spooling Around
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: what about a title on the thumbnail
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Cheryl!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Oh! here...the hook is what gets me all the time.
Cheryl Wolf: Hi lala
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Cheryl!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Title- The Accidental Livestreamer
Stannex: Hook: "I never intended to be a YouTuber, but here I am ... how did THAT happen?
Cheryl Wolf: Ana! I have video to share with you
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I like that a@Stannex
Ellie Calhoun: I usually make the thumbnail and title after I record and edit... I know that's backwards but it works for me,
Mommy Guide Inc: Love that even better Stan! I can see that with a caricature!
Stannex: • LEDA
Mariane Cresp: Hook (as per Magic Write on Canva):"I never thought I'd be a livestreamer. In fact, I didn't even know what livestreaming was until I accidentally stumbled into it one day..."
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh I haven’t tried Magic Write. Thanks Mariane
Cheryl Wolf: 💎Markus is a GEM
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: on point @Mariane Cresp
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Don't forget to like, share and subscribe!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Use chatgpt ask for a script for a talking head video with a topic to include all your bullet points?
Spooling Around: “Oops, I’m a YouTuber”
Mommy Guide Inc: David that’s a very catchy title too.:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I love the hook, creating curiosity for the audience! I was making my titles just as a sentence, I need to change to questions
Stannex: 1. Pandemic boredom, looking for something to do; 2. Discovered LSP and thought, "yeah, I think I could do that"; 3. Tried LEDA, lots of positive feedback; 4. Tried it in public "just once" & had fun
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I like the other one better.
Stannex: 5. Lots of people wanted to be guests ... and suddenly it was "a thing."
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: wow this is a great tutorial Markus! Great set up!!!
Ellie Calhoun: So fun watching you do this!
MySnoopy80: The mike is still in the video
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: @Mariane Cresp is that inside Canva?
Mariane Cresp: Yes @Ana Zugheri - Faith52 - open up a Doc and hit the + button and choose magic write 😊
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Good job!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @MySnoopy80
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Mariane for the fyi:)
MySnoopy80: Hi @LALA
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Gosh Markus! You are making it look so easy!!!! You are awesome.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes! Thanks Mariane.
Ellie Calhoun: After Leda, you made a goal to do it on YouTube... right? Challenged yourself with a deadline...
Stannex: I'M inspired!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: lol
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I love it! I feel empowered.
Mommy Guide Inc: I have several Tera filled with videos that need to be edited.;( Editing is my Waterloo. And it’s coming up - bite to self - Lala take note of how to do this!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I second that Lala
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Look at him go! He is so fast!
Ellie Calhoun: I'm in the middle of editing my next video, taking a walking break to watch Markus! I'll be publishing my video tonight!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Can't wait to see it Ellie!
Ellie Calhoun: Taking me more like 6 hours than 60 minutes!!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: so now you upload it from your phone and add the thumbnail on your desktop?
Mommy Guide Inc: What time Ellie? Will it be a premiere? Hope to be there
Spooling Around: I'm trying to edit down a 9 hour project into something watchable!
Ellie Calhoun: Lala, I was hoping for now. I think it should be ready 6:30 pm est
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Right, but to show us how this is great!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: David I love your video tutorials.:) yes more of those please:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Go Ellie!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: My issue is trying to manipulate imovie from my phone....I need my magnifiying glasses lol
Ellie Calhoun: Could be multiple videos David!
Ellie Calhoun: Ana, I do iMovie on my laptop
Stannex: Yes ... You had a week and were blocking yourself ... now it's done and it's good.
Spooling Around: nice
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: @Ellie Calhoun Im a pc user :face-purple-crying:
Mommy Guide Inc: And it’s done!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: That is also interesting....you are able to upload at the same time you are going live on your channel.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes! and you were using the phone too
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes!!!! You meet the goal.
Stannex: WOO HOO!
Ellie Calhoun: But you did it!!! Yay!! Congratulations! 🎉
Spooling Around: you have time to make another!
Stannex: Now do ANOTHER! 🤣
MySnoopy80: For me it wouldn't be possible ;)
Ellie Calhoun: So. Now... when is the next prerecorded one going to happen?
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: lol do a short now!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed Markus did it and with tons of time left to spare.
Eaglevp: Just shows what you can create when you collab with your audience
Mommy Guide Inc: @MySnoopy80 looking forward to your videos in the future.:)
Stannex: That's a TERRIFIC idea!
Fishstick USA: This is really good. You showed the bare necessities to create and publish a video. Yes, polishing is nice but you did great!
MySnoopy80: Omg lala i don't think that will happen!
Mary Speegle: you can do two in an hour
Mommy Guide Inc: Ok now let’s do it! Really a note to self.:)
Ellie Calhoun: We can brainstorm more topics for you!
Stannex: We can all give it a thumbs-up ... and maybe you can be TRENDING in under an hour!
Fishstick USA: Next time you show sing and make a music video!
Mommy Guide Inc: Maybe a duo stream with Markus @MySnoopy80:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Mary;)
Fishstick USA: *should sing and…
MySnoopy80: Yeah I would like that!
Stannex: You've got a lot of topic ideas in this chat ... LOTS of grist for the mill.
Mary Speegle: :face-fuchsia-tongue-out:
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Q how far out do you plan the topic of your streams?
Ellie Calhoun: Whooo hooo!!!