Eaglevp: Happy New Year Markus
Eaglevp: Happy New year Lala
Tech Troublemaker: hey Everybody. Happy New Year!!!
Eaglevp: Same to you@Tech Troublemaker
Eaglevp: Hi@Ana Zugheri - Faith 52
Cheryl Wolf: Hello everyone
Eaglevp: hI Cheryl
Eaglevp: Hello Diana
Cheryl Wolf: hey Keith
Andrea Nunn: Cute song!🐑
Serenity Studio Art : Hi Keith 😊
Eaglevp: Did you have a nice family Christmas Cheryl
Cheryl Wolf: yes it was nice
Cheryl Wolf: what a year markus
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Keith!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Cheryl!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: So happy to see y’all here! I hope y’all had a wonderful Christmas!
Cheryl Wolf: lala hello
Serenity Studio Art : Hi Andrea and Cheryl and Lala 🙂
Cheryl Wolf: Ann
Cheryl Wolf: Ana
Cheryl Wolf: hello
Ellie Calhoun: hey Markus!!
Andrea Nunn: Hi!
Cheryl Wolf: ellie here
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: @Cheryl hello
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy & Andrea:) Ana!
Serenity Studio Art : Hi Ellie 🙂
Cheryl Wolf: Andrrea
MySnoopy80: Hi everyone
Serenity Studio Art : Hi Ana
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks for joining Markus today and pls don’t forget to smash the LIKE button:)
MySnoopy80: Hello @eaglevp
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi @MySnooy80
Serenity Studio Art : Hi Lala🙂
MySnoopy80: Hi Lala!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Ellie and Diana:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Ellie how’s the short making going?
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yes how are your shorts Ana and Ellie?:)
Ellie Calhoun: oh no!!! I didn't do it - I totally forgot 🤣
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: You have 3 days left…so get on it lol
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: We are here to remind you 😋
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hi Andrea glad you are here
Dwain Woode MD: I made it to the live!
Ellie Calhoun: ha ha! yes, I can still get it done. Ana, you did a great job!
Mommy Guide Inc: Welcome to the community Andrea:)
Ellie Calhoun: Hi Dwain!
Tech Troublemaker: Hey @Dwain Woode MD
Mommy Guide Inc: Dr Dwain!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Hello and welcome Dwain
Andrea Nunn: Hi Eaglevp!
Cheryl Wolf: hey Dwain
Dwain Woode MD: Hi Ellie
Eaglevp: Hi@Dwain Woode MD
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes Ana congratulations on the first short. Absolutely loved it:)
Cheryl Wolf: I have go see your short Ana
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Thank you guys…I hope I can get going on it
Serenity Studio Art : Is there something special going on with shorts with the accelerator group which you are referring to? @Mommy Guide Inc
Dwain Woode MD: Hello Ana
Ellie Calhoun: @Serenity, last week Markus had Sammy on the show and got aa couple of us to commit to doing shorts
Dwain Woode MD: Hi Eaglevp
Serenity Studio Art : Hello !@Dwain Woode MD
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Thank you Markus for showing us how this works! I know nothing and it seems pretty helpful.
Tech Troublemaker: @Ana Zugheri - Faith 52 you can do this. Make faith based shorts. Short prayers, short verses, inspirational thoughts.
Serenity Studio Art : Neither do I Ellie
Mommy Guide Inc: Diana it was just when Sammy was here last week as Markus’ guest everyone decided to create shorts:)
Dwain Woode MD: Hey Ellie…thanks for watching. Jane is awesome. I have not had Cheryl on … YET.😀
MySnoopy80: @markus check the word shorts
Andrea Nunn: Hi Serenity
Dwain Woode MD: Hey Serenity … love your artwork!
Dwain Woode MD: Hey Lala!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: @MySnoopy great observation:)
Serenity Studio Art : Ah ok. Thanks . My shorts finally are doing well again today after a 3 week period tgat it went down hill @Mommy Guide Inc
Dwain Woode MD: Ellie…Keely is 🤩
Mommy Guide Inc: There is a bit of a change on the algortihm. Yey congratulations Diana@SerenityArt!
Serenity Studio Art : Aaww thank you!@Dwain Woode MD I have a solo show coming up in May
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Pretty cool!
Serenity Studio Art : Ah ok I thought so….also YT did say that over holidays views go down for all videos @Mommy Guide Inc
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Q and we can do that on the free versión correct?
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Q what does VOD stand for?
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow this is awesome. An instant engagement presentation.:)
MySnoopy80: @ana vod means video on demand
Cheryl Wolf: lala so right
Ellie Calhoun: Caan we see the word one again?
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: thank you @mysnoopy80
Ellie Calhoun: cool! can you tell who participated?
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Diana.:)
Serenity Studio Art : Another way to create engagement are games. KAHOOT is similar to this @Markus Schaub
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yes Kahoot my teachers in my center use that:)
Serenity Studio Art : You have option to create your own questions and points are kept and the names show as well@Markus Schaub
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: I love kahoot! We did that for our family Christmas party and my daughter’s bday.
Tech Troublemaker: Is @Serenity Studio Art in Kahoots with Kahoot? 😛
Mommy Guide Inc: LOL@Roy!
Ellie Calhoun: oh fun! a green screen!
Mommy Guide Inc: Loving your shorts Roy!
Serenity Studio Art : The ionly thing I don’t like about KAHOOT is that the questions are asked too fast. You have to customize it to slow it down
Serenity Studio Art : Lol @Tech Troublemaker
Ellie Calhoun: LOL!
Cheryl Wolf: yeah very cool , thanks markus
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes this is a great engagement tool. Thanks for sharing Markus!
Andrea Nunn: Is this your usual time?
Mommy Guide Inc: @Andrea yes rhis is Markus usual schedule:) thanks for asking. Hope to see you again next time
Cheryl Wolf: Game show host love it
Mommy Guide Inc: I am there now Markus! Excited much. We need Tim in here.:) hr he he
Cheryl Wolf: boooooo
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Lol
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey my fuess is right. LOL
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Good job guys!
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh i missed the last question coz i was in the chat. LOL
Ellie Calhoun: I did not know that!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: That’s crazy!
Serenity Studio Art : Omg. That fact has to be wrong
Cheryl Wolf: lol
Mommy Guide Inc: Love the trivia! More more:)
Cheryl Wolf: YES !
Mommy Guide Inc: Didnt even get na answer in
Cheryl Wolf: maybe n
Tech Troublemaker: I clicked too fast. haha
Andrea Nunn: so close!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Ni would have gotten most of the answers completely wrong
Mommy Guide Inc: No Markus i didnt lnow the answer
Cheryl Wolf: oops
Ellie Calhoun: I have no idea with this one either
Andrea Nunn: who?
Cheryl Wolf: we need one more
Tech Troublemaker: But he was dead by then I thought. I guess they licensed his music.
Cheryl Wolf: Roy😍
Serenity Studio Art : Congratulations @Tech Troublemaker
Mommy Guide Inc: Woot!!! Congratulations Roy!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes one more!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: 🎉🎉👏👏👏
Tech Troublemaker: Random
Mommy Guide Inc: I might use this on my New Year’s Eve special Markus
Ellie Calhoun: random
Cheryl Wolf: General
Tech Troublemaker: Yes, Lala will know what happens in 2023 before the rest of us.
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed the future I see.
Cheryl Wolf: Roy🤣
Cheryl Wolf: I was typing
Mommy Guide Inc: I am from Asia.:) he he he
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Lol I’m on my phone so I can’t type fast 😂
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Kids
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Wooo hooo! I knew one lol
Mommy Guide Inc: Waah my phone died!
Cheryl Wolf: Frosty
Ellie Calhoun: I'm doing horribly lol
Mommy Guide Inc: Need to charge bwahaha
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: 8?
Mommy Guide Inc: At it now:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Go frosty!!!!
Cheryl Wolf: lol
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: 🐻
MySnoopy80: I prepared for the next one:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Absolutely just guessed that
Cheryl Wolf: Congrats
Cheryl Wolf: one more
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey congratulations Frosty!!!
MySnoopy80: Yes I'm ready
Tech Troublemaker: Congrats Frosty! Give folks more times to join.
Cheryl Wolf: come on in the weather is fine
Tech Troublemaker: only 3 in so far.
Tech Troublemaker: now 4
Cheryl Wolf: time is up lol
Cheryl Wolf: 6 in
Tech Troublemaker: 6 woot!
Mommy Guide Inc: Its asking me to go yo instructions on mentimeter
Mommy Guide Inc: It said i was on 2 browsers
Mommy Guide Inc: He he he
Mommy Guide Inc: Inam very consistent - wrong answers
MySnoopy80: It's me
Ellie Calhoun: I'm again doing poorly playing as frosty
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Woo hoo!!! That was fun!
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes i had so much fun!
Ellie Calhoun: it wasn't me last time! lol
Mommy Guide Inc: Will definitely try this on my New Year’s eve stream:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh there are still
Mommy Guide Inc: More questions
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Oh gosh! 😖
Ellie Calhoun: I have no shame not knowing trivia lol
Ellie Calhoun: I missed that last question
Mommy Guide Inc: I feel so dumb. He he he.
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh not yet done
Cheryl Wolf: lol
Mommy Guide Inc: That was so much fun!
Cheryl Wolf: ET !!
Mommy Guide Inc: Please don’t forget to snash the like button!!!
Serenity Studio Art : Congratulations!
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Thank you Markus, that was fun!
Ellie Calhoun: fun! thanks Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh a bit pricey though
Tech Troublemaker: That was fun. Thanks Markus!
Cheryl Wolf: Thanks markus , fun times
Ana Zugheri - Faith 52: Yes please friends don’t forget to like 👍
Mommy Guide Inc: But its an option we have right?
Serenity Studio Art : Happy new year everyone!
Ellie Calhoun: Happy New Year! to all!
Mommy Guide Inc: Congratulations Markus for another year of awesome livestreams!
MySnoopy80: Happy new year to everyone
Cheryl Wolf: Happy New Year all