Fishstick USA: Hello. Wishing you a good day!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Happy to be here 🎉
Mommy Guide Inc: And here we go! Hi Philip and Ana.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes I am leaving tomorrow already.:)
Stannex: Hi, Markus! Hi, Lala! Hi, everyone!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Y’all better document that encounter!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Stan! Other than thumbnail Mwrkus what else can it do?
Stannex: Something like an Indy Jones style travel map?
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I Wondr if you give it details as far don’t and colors???
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: *fonts
Stannex: "Indiana Jones style map, Switzerland to Boston"
Stannex: Team Markus FTW!!!!
Stannex: &lt;3
Stannex: AI doesn't get the Indy Jones vibe, I guess
CSLiveDK - Communication Social Media Livestream: Hello everyone 😀
Stannex: "Colonial boston sightseeing"
Stannex: Those first two ARE Boston sites
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: How many days are you staying?
Stannex: How about saying that you want a "thumbnail"
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: What are you most excited about?
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: What about the name of the conference? Or food?
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I like that 👍
Fishstick USA: Credit card is fine. Be certain to call and ensure they know you are travelling
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes!!! Stream cc, no laptop 💻 leave room for goodies you want to bring back
Pierre Kelly: Afternoon everyone
Stannex: Are you going next week or the week after?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi CSLIVE
Stannex: No, I'm on the OTHER side of the country. But I grew up on the east coast (which is why I know a little about Boston).
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I’m so happy for y’all!!! How I. Wish I could be there 😩
Fishstick USA: Pick up a ac outlet adapter
Fishstick USA: Tell people you name is Federer the tennis player
Fishstick USA: *your
Stannex: Temps will be lows around 10-12 C, Highs around 20 C
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Snacks for the ✈️
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: hello
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: You’ll have so much content!!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Pierre!
Stannex: Be sure you bring something that's okay in the rain ... weather is supposed to be mixed sun and rain during your visit ... and autumn rain is chilly.
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: langi unterhose :P
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes let’s do that. Let’s try everything. He he he.
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: have fun and dont let you eat by this americans 😛
Pierre Kelly: You're going to the USA?
Stannex: Make sure you try a good lobster roll while you're there!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Eric! Friends dont forget to smash the Like button.:)
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: @Mommy Guide Inc i still dont know if i like this stream 😛 are you sure this is a good one?
Mommy Guide Inc: Ooh lobster roll. You are making me hungry Stam.:)
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: I praying for an amazing experience ♥️🙏
Mommy Guide Inc: Bwahaha i do! I love it Eric. He he he
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: ok @Mommy Guide Inc then i will press it 😛
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes! Come to the great state of Texas 🎉
Mommy Guide Inc: ThNks Ana for the prayers. Indeed not too cold please.
Stannex: I'm sad I can't go to this show ... maybe next time.
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Yes! 🎉🎉🎉🎉
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey - great Eric!
Eric Maechler - Online Marketing: @Markus Schaub greet the other ecammer also from me the other swiss
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes i want to go to texas in the future and get to meet Joana Gaines. He he he
Mommy Guide Inc: Of course meet Ana!
Stannex: Bon voyage, Markus! Have fun in Boston!
Ana Zugheri - Faith52: Lala I’ll be praying for good weather…yes Eric sold!!!!
Fishstick USA: Safe Travels!