Mommy Guide Inc: Let’s go! Hi Markus!
Eaglevp: Evening Markus & Lala
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Keith! Hope all is well.
Eaglevp: Yes thanks Lala
Run Adam Run: Markus! My favorite topic.
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Coach Adam.:)
Eaglevp: Its a great topic to discuss Markus
Eaglevp: Hi Adam
Run Adam Run: I'd be happy to be your coach. Just let me know.
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes I see your videos picking up steam. Yey!
Run Adam Run: Walking is the key.
Eaglevp: Trying to walk a mile a day for the next month Adam
Mariane Cresp: Good morning Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: And that planner a
Eaglevp: Hi Mariane
Mommy Guide Inc: The 12 week planner that Marielou shared for creators is nice
Mommy Guide Inc: Good morning Mariane.:)
Run Adam Run: Markus, if you are serious I would be honored to coach you at no cost. Just let me know in private.
Run Adam Run: I've been coaching for more than 30 years.
Mariane Cresp: With the steps ... I just want to get outside ... I just want to be consistent with that first
Run Adam Run: Let's do it. Absolutely. Everyone is witnessing a great collab.
Mommy Guide Inc: That’s awesome.;)
Run Adam Run: 10K steps probably too much in the beginning and not necessary.
Run Adam Run: but we can get there.
Eaglevp: I have managed 3k steps for the last 4 days
Tech Troublemaker: Hey! It's Thursday.
Eaglevp: Hi Roy
Tech Troublemaker: hey Keith!
Run Adam Run: Great job Keith.
Run Adam Run: It's Friday Eve!
Eaglevp: Thanks Adam hope I can keep it up.
Stan!: This is what makes Thursdays great!
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Roy’ thanks so much for helping me with the IG archive thing.
Eaglevp: Hello Stan
Eaglevp: Suffering with the calf muscles stiffening up any advice?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Stan! Awesome Keith!
Run Adam Run: Rest is just as important - it's where all the fixing happens.
Stan!: Hi, Keith! Hi, Lala!
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Hiiiii
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: I’m late as I was making 2 you tube videos!!!
Eaglevp: Today done 3,509 step 2.67km
Eaglevp: Hi Katy
Mommy Guide Inc: July will be Creator Wellness and Christmas In July
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Thank youuuu
Eaglevp: That’s great Katy
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: I want to go for it - with your wonderful encouragement
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Thank you guys
Run Adam Run: For stiff calves - make sure you are properly warming up before walking with some light stretches.
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Sounds fab Lala
Run Adam Run: Also, hydrate and take magnesium
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Katy! Yey. Looking forward to these 2 videos
Eaglevp: Will do that Adam
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Magnesium is wonderful
Mommy Guide Inc: Oh yes Adam. I didn’t realize that my aches and pains were partly lie due to lack of Magnesium
Run Adam Run: I'm confident we can get you more subscribers if you share this story on YouTube.
Run Adam Run: This is a story that's relatable and everyone will be cheering for you
Run Adam Run: YES - Magnesium is my secret weapon, but you have to take the right type or else you might suffer with gastro issues.
Mommy Guide Inc: Never too late to focus on our health and wellness.
Run Adam Run: When you focus on your health and wellness, your brain gets better too as will your ideas.
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Epsom salts are lovely for safe magnesium, relaxation and helps with aches
Tech Troublemaker: One day I will be YouTube famous like Adam. 🙂
Run Adam Run: I'm not famous... just persistent like you Roy.
Neil Farrimond: Hey Markus!
Run Adam Run: Question: will you launch this as a new channel or on the same one?
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Neil.:)
Eaglevp: Evening Neil
Eaglevp: Neil how did your meet up go ?
Run Adam Run: In the beginning it's OK
Mommy Guide Inc: Being a creator - having or keeping a good health is important
Run Adam Run: but you might lose anyone who is just looking for content creation tips
Tech Troublemaker: Maybe I should start a new channel for my vlog and maybe call it "Roy had a plan"
Run Adam Run: Honestly Markus, I think you will gain far more subscribers if you are open and honest about the journey. It's so relatable.
Run Adam Run: Not everyone wants to be a creator, but everyone thinks about their health
Tech Troublemaker: Markus be you and make it continue to be fun for you and folks will find you.
Run Adam Run: You don't have to be an expert, but you already know so many people who can guide you.
Mommy Guide Inc: Attended YouTube APAC creators meetup and indeed they said be authentic and relatable.:)
Eaglevp: What type of content do you watch on YouTube?
Mommy Guide Inc: So your health journey together with your other content I think who’ll be fine.:) but I’ve always been all over the place. He he he.
Run Adam Run: So Markus, your first assignment is to "capture" your
Run Adam Run: before picture
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes I’ve grown a bit of new following in the crafting community after becoming part of a design team but I still will be doing other contents.
Run Adam Run: and reach out to me so we can set up your plan.
Mommy Guide Inc: Excited for this awesome collab with Markus and Adam.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Markus and you all for the encouragement to create more edited videos. I’ve just finished scheduling 5 videos for July. And 3 more
Run Adam Run: Oh yes... we will find a 5K in Lucern.
Mommy Guide Inc: 3 more coming up. I’ve gotten a bit more comfortable with my simple
Run Adam Run: Yes, absolutely. Do you want to bring me on?
Mommy Guide Inc: Simple editing flow for now.
Mommy Guide Inc: I was overthinking editing before. I wanted to do all those awesome stuff but it kept me
Run Adam Run: or Messenger
Mommy Guide Inc: From creating. When I just settled with simple I got a bit more confident.
Run Adam Run: I'm ready
Mommy Guide Inc: Wow a 5k marathon in Lucerne.:) that’s a great goal Adam and Markus.
Mommy Guide Inc: Adam
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi everyone. It's been a minute!
Mommy Guide Inc: Adam coming in. Yey!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hi Adam!
Katy Simpson: Live Video & Podcasting Coach: Adam! Hi 👋
Mommy Guide Inc: Janet!!’ How are you my friend?
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Lala!!! how are you little sis
Mommy Guide Inc: Miss you much Janet.:) Hope all is well
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Trying to recover. It's a very long road.
Eaglevp: Hi Janet
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: @Eaglevp how are you?
Mommy Guide Inc: You’ll get there sis. Looking forward to a face to face meet up again in the future. Let’s all get healthier moving forward.:)
Eaglevp: Fine thanks Janet
Fishstick ~ Phillip: Hello Markus and Adam. Sorry I am running late. Adam, I enjoy your videos.
Eaglevp: Hi Phillip
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I am trying to get healthy. I took 10 steps on grass (with my cane) a few hours ago. I'm so excited. so walking is something I am working on.
Mommy Guide Inc: Yey just a step at a time Janet. Take care sis.:) love you!
Eaglevp: That’s great news Janet
Tech Troublemaker: It's the Markus and Adam Show
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Hey Roy @Tech Troublemaker
Enda Trading: Hello all
Eaglevp: Hi Enda Trading
Enda Trading: Hi @Eaglevp
Mommy Guide Inc: Hi Enda.:) Are you back in Malaysia?
Tech Troublemaker: Hey Janet!
Eaglevp: Staying In zone 2 I think
Enda Trading: My brother got a place in the London Marathon this year, he is delighted, seemingly its very difficult to get a place! 🏃
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: I'm working up to zone 1! 😻🙀
Tech Troublemaker: And then after the marathon a Pub run.
Tech Troublemaker: That is so awesome @Enda Trading Tell him congrats!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Barely
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Had hip replacement but complications.
Enda Trading: I will @Tech Troublemaker Thanks
Mommy Guide Inc: Just take it slow Janet. As Adam said slow is better than rushing things up.
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: That's why I have not been here. I have missed you all
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Love that one... Be the turtle. You need to come to my animal communication workshop. haha.
Mommy Guide Inc: Glad to see you back in the chat Janet. Focus on getting better my friend and will see you soon. Our plan to go to NYC in the future will come true.
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks Coach Adam and Markus!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: oh NYC!!!
Mommy Guide Inc: Thanks friends have a great weekend.
Eaglevp: Thanks Adam
Eaglevp: Hope you all stay healthy and have a great weekend
Mommy Guide Inc: Yes that’s a great message Keith - let’s all keep healthy. See you next week!
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Markus you are always an inspiration
Mommy Guide Inc: Indeed Markus is a great inspiration and supporter.:) thanks Markus!
Mommy Guide Inc: Bye.:)
Mommy Guide Inc: Don’t forget to hit the LIKE friends on your way out:)
Animal Paradise - Communication & Healing: Bye everyone. Thanks always Markus. this was so good.
Run Adam Run: LOL!