SmallChangesTV: MARKUS!!!
SmallChangesTV: This sounds like an old school HR video
SmallChangesTV: Your office is very clean
SmallChangesTV: Yes! LEFT
SmallChangesTV: Bad things happen when you don’t follow the rules
SmallChangesTV: I’m going to narrating my life in this guys voice from now on
SmallChangesTV: There was a disappointing amount of cleaning supplies in that broom closet
SmallChangesTV: If zombies jump out… I’m out
SmallChangesTV: I gotta drop the kids at school bbs
austinator88888: MARKUS!!!
austinator88888: this game is so good
austinator88888: is this the original Stanley Parable or the New One?
austinator88888: are you doing what the narrator says or are you going against it?
therealsammysuperstar: hey markus
therealsammysuperstar: I haven't been on twitch in like 2 years wanted to say hi
mommyguide: Markus i can't make an account. he he he. I was trying but it kept on denying my password.
mommyguide: this game's narration is awesome.  yes I finally got in.
mommyguide: are you supposed to follow the narrator or not?
mommyguide: LOL he really wanted to let you go to the red door. he he he
mommyguide: you beat the game! he he he.
mommyguide: you found a shortcut. hehehe
mommyguide: so this is like the choose your own adventure book back in the 80s in video game format?
mommyguide: yey!!!!
mommyguide: Markus doesn't want to follow the Line! LOL
mommyguide: even the lines are dancing to the music. LOL
mommyguide: hmmm is this a dream? he hehe
mommyguide: Stanley and the first open door. he heh
mommyguide: wow!
mommyguide: Best. Actor Award goes to the Narrator!
mommyguide: LOL you lived!
mommyguide: is there really a right path or door Markus? he he he
techtroublemaker: Fun game
mommyguide: Hi Roy.
techtroublemaker: Sorry I am late
techtroublemaker: Hey Lala
mommyguide: Answer the phone:) he he he
techtroublemaker: It has been a while since I played this
techtroublemaker: But a least he is married to a mannequin. 😃
mommyguide: I think the narrator's plan is for us to continue on and on and on
techtroublemaker: There is an ending. It takes a lot of patience
mommyguide: ooh ok then let's wait:)  love the vintage feels of this scene
austinator88888: alright I'm back, I was doing some Grad Party prep
mommyguide: yey a party for Austin~
austinator88888: the Party is Saturday... I might stream it a little... unsure
techtroublemaker: Congratulations @austinator88888
austinator88888: I should still be streaming tomorrow as well
austinator88888: kassfrPenguinlove
KaliCoVideo: AHhH!!!
KaliCoVideo: SORRY I'M LATE
KaliCoVideo: but am. here
austinator88888: KALI!!!
KaliCoVideo: i was rushing home so fast 😭 so glad i made it
KaliCoVideo: @austinator88888 AUSTIN!!!!
KaliCoVideo: ooo check out my cute mod status 😌
KaliCoVideo: Markus ❤️❤️❤️
austinator88888: KALLLLIIIIIII!!!!!!!!!!
KaliCoVideo: @austinator88888 AUSTIIIIIIIINNNN!!!!!!!!!!!
KaliCoVideo: @austinator88888 how;d your interviews og
KaliCoVideo: *go
techtroublemaker: Hey @kalicovideo
mommyguide: Hi Kali!
KaliCoVideo: @techtroublemaker hey Roy!! 🤗
austinator88888: @kalicovideo KKKKKKAAAAAALLLLLLIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIII!!!!!!!!!!
KaliCoVideo: @mommyguide lala!! 🤗
KaliCoVideo: @austinator88888 we could do this all day 😂
KaliCoVideo: hahahaha markus was like "enough of this"
austinator88888: also they were all over me, each of them wanted me, they all hated when I said "I have other interviews so I'm unsure if I'll be chosing this place"
KaliCoVideo: @austinator88888 that's awesome!!
austinator88888: yeah, tomorrow is Applebee's and my friend works there actually so maybe I'll end up working there 🤷‍♂️
KaliCoVideo: @austinator88888 ew not applebees 😭
austinator88888: @kalicovideo it wouldn't be my first choice actually, I'm really leaning towards Texas Roadhouse or MaCalister's Deli
KaliCoVideo: you should do one of those tbh it looks better on your resume for culinary (but that's just my opinion!)
austinator88888: Applebee's doesn't look bad on a Culinary Resume, any kind of kitchen work is good, but it's true, either of them is better
KaliCoVideo: applebee's nastay
KaliCoVideo: is it a kitchen position at these places?? :o
austinator88888: @kalicovideo yes, Line Cook or Kitchen Prep
austinator88888: or working the Grill
KaliCoVideo: @austinator88888 that's so awesome 🤗
techtroublemaker: It goes on forever until it doesn’t
austinator88888: but some say I can't be working there until I'm 18... but I literally turn 18 on the 30th
techtroublemaker: Line cook would be fun.
techtroublemaker: I don’t. It has been about four years since I played
techtroublemaker: Wasted an entire day
TobeyKai: IM HEREEEEE
TobeyKai: tobeykLove tobeykLove tobeykLove tobeykLove tobeykLove tobeykLove
KaliCoVideo: line cook would be fun. stressful, but fun. restaurants were always fun to work in. you become family there
KaliCoVideo: @TobeyKai hey!! 🤗
TobeyKai: Haiii @kalicovideo !!
TobeyKai: tobeykHYPE tobeykHYPE tobeykHYPE tobeykHYPE
TobeyKai: Told you I’d be here LUL
TobeyKai: I like the pink background lights my friend. Good taste tobeyk400k hardhe2PinkHeart
KaliCoVideo: @TobeyKai that heart is so cute 😭❤️
austinator88888: HypeBLEH
TobeyKai: tobeykLove
austinator88888: kassfrPenguinlove kassfrPenguinlove kassfrPenguinlove
TobeyKai: jukereLOVE
mommyguide: oh wow 2am!
TobeyKai: eiszei2Eiszei2love
KaliCoVideo: i'm glad i got to watch some 🤗
mommyguide: how to get those stickers so cool.
KaliCoVideo: can't wait for the next one!!
austinator88888: you're amazing Markus, I'd love to see you play more games
TobeyKai: onoezHEART
TobeyKai: I like these hearts hehe
austinator88888: @mommyguide it's from following and subscribing to other channels
techtroublemaker: ScaredyCat
mommyguide: first time on twitch! that was fun Markus!
KaliCoVideo: bye!!! 🤗❤️
techtroublemaker: Night Marcus
TobeyKai: hexaceHeart seredaLove closureFlickerHeart yukina17Hearteu bravew4Love lateni31Love eiszei2Eiszei2love
KaliCoVideo: love this music video so cute
KaliCoVideo: makes me happy cry every time
mommyguide: see you tomorrow! goodnight to you all:)
KaliCoVideo: @mommyguide gnight lala ❤️❤️❤️
TobeyKai: Love it!
TobeyKai: Good night my friends!!!
TobeyKai: tobeykLove tobeykLove tobeykLove
markusschaub: This is the new version, you are in it Kali
austinator88888: @mommyguide good morning for you 🤣
techtroublemaker: Night @tobeykai
KaliCoVideo: i love it so much ❤️😭❤️
KaliCoVideo: #MARKUSRULES
TobeyKai: Night @techtroublemaker !
mommyguide: this is an updated one Markus! love it:)
austinator88888: all this music video makes me think is how I haven't been on Markus's stream yet
markusschaub: #KALIRULES
KaliCoVideo: @austinator88888 your internet has sucked that's why 😂
austinator88888: IT DOESN'T SUCK ANY MORE!!! ITS SO GOOD
austinator88888: #KALIRULES
TobeyKai: Love your face @markusschaub !!
markusschaub: Ok, you are officially invited, Austin
TobeyKai: tobeykLove tobeykLove tobeykLove tobeykLove tobeykLove
markusschaub: Thank you @TobeyKai raymmuRAYMLOVE
KaliCoVideo: love love love love love